Theven...
Heigth...
Nine...
Yeth, I thtill have
the record, thucker!
Malcolm in the Middle
7.18 - "Bomb Shelter"
Synchronisation par Max & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
I swear this mall gets more
beautiful every time we come.
They have really
made some changes.
They're used to be
a Banana Republic over there.
Now it's over there.
Can we please just get my
underwear and get out of here?
Malcolm, you know it's hard
to buy underwear for you.
You have your father's irregular crotch.
Nothing to be ashamed of, son.
If a woman really loves you,
it won't botherher a bit.
Will you look at that?
They turned a Soap Town
into a Soap And Such.
Hi. Are you here to take class?
Yes, that's why I came
in here, to take class.
It's dancing, right?
Yes. Just sign up at the counter.
So, you're the new guy.
What? Oh, yeah, hi.
It's all right.
I don't mind a little competition,
but just so you know
what you're up against.
So the person who keeps his or her
hand on the vehicle the longest
is going to drive out of here
in this brand-new truck!
Oh, Hal, look at that truck.
Can you imagine if we could
finally get rid of the van?
That piece of junk's costing us a hundred
bucks a month in duct tape alone.
All right, the contest is going
to begin in ten seconds.
If all the contestants are
ready, here we go.
In seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
And we're off!
I can't believe we never entered
one of these contests before.
It's going to be
a long ride, honey.
We got our first loser.
Ha! Idiot!
Number two.
Ha! Damn it all to hell!
Come on, pal, here
we go, here we go.
There we go.
Oh, geez.
No, no, no, Jamie!
You have to stay in your chair
until breakfast is ready, okay?
Listen, your mommy's going
to be home in a couple days,
just as soon as she wins that truck.
And then everything
will be back to normal.
Oh, eggs.
Hello!
Oh, hi, Hal, how's it going?
Oh, uh, everything is...
everything's great, honey.
Oh, good. Listen, I was thinking
this might be the perfect time for
you to get to your "To Do" board.
Well, um, you know, I am not
sure that I'm going to be able to...
Hal, I'm making this sacrifice
for the whole family.
I think the least you can do is
catch up on some housework.
Okay, okay, I'll talk to you later.
Oh, geez.
DO TO-DO LIST
What was that?
Nothing!
Oh, my God, Dad's middle
management trophy... The Middie.
We have no choice but to
confess and take the punishment.
You're a good brother.
Are you sure you've
never danced before?
No, never.
You really have a gift.
She's right.
Turns out, I'm naturally talented
at science and dancing...
two things that are
guaranteed to get you beat up.
All right, partner up.
You know, our dance
competition's coming up next week.
You can choose any girl in
the class to be your partner.
Really? Any girl?
You and Danielle would
be a dream together.
Who?
I think I need a little
time to think about it.
Say hi to Angela for me.
So who's Angela?
She's my best friend.
He's helping her move.
-Huh.
-What?
No, I am not worried
about him and Angela.
Good for you.
I actually met my husband
when he helped me move.
Boy, there's nothing sexier than
a man coming to the rescue.
The two of you lug that mattress
up the stairs, you get it laid down
on the floor in the bedroom.
You're both already sweaty.
Anyway, I think you're
making the right choice.
A truck will never
let you down.
I've got to go.
Oh, another one out !
Can't we just throw
the thing in the trash?
That is the worst possible place.
Dad accidentally throws his car
keys out three times a week,
and he always ends up
going through the barrels.
What was that?
There's a handle here.
Oh, my God, do you
know what this means?
Yes!
Rabbits have been
using our technology!
No, it's a bomb shelter. People built these
in the '50s and '60 in case of a nuclear war.
This is incredible.
What the hell... ?
Dad?
Boys, are you down there?
Dad, look, we have a bomb shelter.
Oh, good God.
I never knew this was here.
Isn't it amazing?
All right, let's get out of here.
We don't know how stable this place is.
There could be snakes
and rats and...
Is that my trophy?
Yeah.
Here!
You broke the Middie!
They only give out
200 of these a year!
Wait!
Hurry, get the trash cans!
You boys let
me out of here!
You better not burry me
in here with the rats!
You want to see what's on TV?
Okay.
Help me out!
They let me pick
Hanna as my partner.
We really got a shot at
winning this competition.
Plus, I get to touch
her body, like, a lot.
Sorry.
Dad, if you can hear me,
knock once on the hatch.
Okay, it's pretty obvious we've
all made some mistakes here.
There's no point in trying to figure
out who's right and who's wrong.
The important thing is you forgive us so
we can forgive you so we can let you out.
Now if we're all on the same
page, knock once on the lid.
He agreed. We're both witnesses.
You know Dad, I really think...
It's a trick!
I just...!
Vengeance!
Back, Dad!
Back!
I don't know if I can
trust Dad after this.
You're insane.
I'm just saying, how much food
could there be down there?
Eventually, this will
take care of itself.
Reese!
He's had a long life.
What is he, like, 70?
Forget it.
Ah, you're right.
I forgot about Mom.
She's bound to notice eventually,
no matter how busy she is.
And once she latches onto something,
you know how she never lets it go.
Well, hello.
Mr. President.
Well, looks like we're
in this Cold War together.
So, Jack...
what are you drinking?
So what if she's a klutz?
She's still beautiful, right?
I can't wait for the competition.
You and me out there
in front of everyone?
All right, she's totally hot,
but she's got no presence.
Her footwork's sloppy and her
jazz square'sall over the place.
I'm just going to have to
make my peace with this.
I chose Hanna for the contest and
now there's nothing I can do about it.
Oh, my ankle!
I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
It hurts.
I can't stand on it.
Oh, my God, what a terrible accident.
It was an accident.
I'm so sorry.
It was.
Good! Perfect.
All right now just turn and...
I'm so glad you were still
available for the competition.
I was really upset by Hanna's, um...
accidental injury, but I think
you and I might win this thing.
Well, if we can do
it with our dancing,
maybe you could stop
sleeping with the judges.
That'll free up my evenings.
Who knew she banters, too.
Salisbury steak... my old friend.
Ha-cha.
Hello, ladies.
Dad?
Dad, you alive?
The minute I get out of here,
you boys are in so much...
...trouble!
Hey, if he's not willing to
negotiate, we've got no choice.
We're going to have to split up.
Okay, I'll meet you in
Mexico in five years.
Wait a minute.
What if we do everything on his
"To Do" board and then let him out?
That's brilliant.
He couldn't be mad at us
if we did all this for him.
He's got stuff on here that he's
been meaning to do for years.
"Change Dewey's diaper."
So, for the contest, what do
you think we should wear?
I was thinking about a really
hot sequined backless number.
And for me, something classy.
Just so you know,
I was holding back in there.
You two have no idea what I'm going
to unleash tomorrow at the contest.
Well, if it's anything like what you
unleashed during stretching, we're
pulling out of the competition.
Insults are for those who can't
express themselves... in motion!
I think I'm falling in love with him.
You, too?
So, I'll see you tomorrow?
Right.
Oh, there was one more thing.
Nope, that wasn't it.
See ya.
I'm sure it's nothing, Cheryl, but
you'll probably feel better after
a doctor's taken a look at it.
There's another one. She's
down and we're here in the...
Wow, Mom, just four
left. That's great.
Yeah, and it'll be three
before you know it.
Mom, I need some advice on something.
Sure.
I started taking this
dance class, and...
Good for you.
I just signed up to meet a girl.
Of course.
I got to dance with
the girl I wanted, but...
she had an accident and I started
dancing with this other girl and...
I didn't think there'd anything
other than dancing there, and...
And now she likes you and
you're going to break her heart?
No, that's not it.
I like her, too.
You both like each other?
Yeah.
So why are you bothering me?
I'm working here.
The point is I like her, but she's
not exactly what I consider to be...
a cute girl.
Oh, this is going
to be a tricky one.
Here, hold this.
What is wrong with you?
You're attracted to her,
she's attracted to you.
The only problem is in your head.
Listen, if you're trying to
build relationships on looks,
you are in for a world hurt.
Take Janet here.
20 years ago she marries her husband
because she thinks he looks like Lee Majors.
And today he's lost all his
hair, he's gained 200 pounds,
and she is stuck with a blimp
who won't even put on his shirt
to come to the dinner table.
She is reduced to trying to win
attention by bringing home a truck.
I mean, how sad is that?
That is what I'm doing, isn't it?
There's another one.
36 down. There's only three left
here, ladies and gentlemen.
You see that ?
That took courage.
I'll tell you, Jack, they
made women in those days.
There's nothing wrong with
a little meat on the bones.
Now that is a fanny.
Ah, Jack, you died too young.
We beat 'em.
Now they're wearing blue jeans and
eating cheeseburgers in Red Square.
Oh, and we made it to the moon.
Big waste of money.
l'll tell you what
I miss the most, Jack.
All these years, we have never
had a president as cool as you.
Here's to you, buddy.
You're right to look
at me like that.
You just can't drink a
martini without an olive.
Oh, would you look at that.
We have a back door.
I'll be right back, Jack.
After you finish the fireplace,
I'll start scrubbing the shower tiles.
And I'll give Jamie a bath,
then we can both do the gutters.
All right, but first we have to shampoo
the rug to give it time to dry.
If you are 99% sure you turned your
oven off, don't drive yourself crazy.
Besides, dogs have an
instinct to run away from fire.
Well, there was number three.
And then they were two.
Don't go anywere, folks,
we're going to crown a winner.
So it's just you and me.
All the little
children have gone home.
You have any kids?
Four.
Five.
-Epidurals?
-Please.
You tear?
Like an old sock.
All right ladies, it's time for
another bathroom break.
You're not taking a break, Mabel?
I'm good.
Me, too.
Hey, Danielle. Before we go there,
there's something I need to tell you.
I like you a lot.
You do?
I mean, great.
You know, I'd never
would have expected it.
And now, Malcolm and Danielle.
Why wouldn't you have expected it?
Huh?
Why wouldn't you have
expected to like me?
It wasn't a criticism
of you. It's just that...
Sometimes I can be really
shallow about these things.
Malcolm?
So what kind of guys do you
like when you're shallow?
No, it's nothing. It's just that...
I've made mistakes in the past going
after guys just based on their looks.
So you almost didn't go out with me
because I'm not good-looking enough?
Would you let it go,
okay? I like you.
Now dip me.
-Face or body?
-What?
Face or body, which don't you like?
Or maybe you don't like any of it.
It's all fine.
It's good enough.
Now dip me.
I can't believe you'd think like that.
For God's sakes!
You know, you're no prize.
No, we can't let Dad out until
we do everything on the list.
If Dad's going to act like...
I can explain.
Wait a minute.
You've been sneaking
out the whole time?
Is that party mix?
You're damn right it's party mix.
This is the only thing that has kept me
sane while I was trapped in that hellhole.
Then why are you going back?
I am not on trial here.
I can't believe he
wasn't really trapped.
Come on, Dewey, let's
go mess up the house.
I did it! I won the truck!
Lois, you're not going to believe
what these boys have done.
-They trapped me in a hole...
I was there for three days.
-He wasn't trapped...
Did you hear what I said?
I said I won the truck!
-Oh, my God!
-You won the truck!
We won the truck!
Let's go for a ride.
Just a sec.
First I have to change my pants.
www.tvsubtitles.net