Reese, I just bought that
for you. Will you look at...
Give it to me.
Let me see what I can do with it.
I sneezed in chem lab
and spilled acid on it.
I'm not wearing these
stupid shorts anymore.
Everyone's making fun of me.
A denim tie.
How cool is that?
Malcolm in the Middle
7.16 - "Lois Strikes Back"
Synchronisation par Max & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
No way!
No way! That's awesome.
Okay. I can't wait to see you.
No, I can't wait to see you more.
Okay, you win.
All right, Cindy's only a few blocks
away, so everybody calm down.
When she gets here, just try to be cool.
I want to make a good impression.
Do I have a bat in the hanger?
You've asked me five times.
The answer's still yes.
So, this is pretty exciting, Reese.
When did you meet this girl?
I haven't actually met her.
Her cousin goes to school with me,
and Cindy saw me at the dance
last week and thought I was hot.
Oh, well, I don't blame her.
I mean, forgetting I'm
your mother for a minute,
if I saw you walking down the street,
I would think, there is one hot guy.
Yeesh.
Cindy and I talked on the phone
almost every night last week,
and we totally have the
same sense of humor.
She said she saw me put the plastic dog
poop in the punch bowl at the school dance,
and we both agreed that the real
stuff would have been funnier.
You put plastic poop in the punch bowl?!
Once again, you completely miss the point.
So, what kind of loser would
want to go out with you?
This kind of loser.
And if she kisses half as good as her
picture does, this is going to be sweet.
Okay, there she is.
Everybody, get out of here.
No, wait.
She'll probably want to meet you.
Okay, you can stay, just
don't say anything stupid.
How's my hair?
Can you smell my pits?
Why'd you let me put
on this stupid shirt?
Reese, relax. All you have
to do is just be yourself.
You're right, Mom.
Thanks.
Enjoy your date, Reese!
And the pig was actually
wearing lipstick?
Reese was devastated.
I can just imagine.
And-And I don't like it.
No, no, no, not one little bit.
Now, uh, what is it that
you want me to do?
Look, I know that Reese has
not been a model student,
and once again, I want to
apologize for your tires.
And your mailbox.
And your lawn fountain.
But what those girls did is just cruel,
and I need to see them punished.
All right, you let me see
what I can find out.
Now, these girls are
obviously quite clever.
I mean, where do you
even... find a pig?
And then we have to get it over to
your house, and put makeup on it.
Reese was completely blindsided, huh?
You know what?
I have had it.
How would you like it if I called the
Superintendent and told him all about this?
Great. I'll put him
on the speaker phone.
REESE & CINDY
For King and Queen
Unbelievable.
I've never witnessed anything
like that in my entire life.
There's no excuse for it.
How did an immature jerk like that get to
be Principal of a high school, Hal? How?
-Well, with what they...
-He actually laughed.
He couldn't care less that our
son is curled up on his bed and
completely devastated by this.
Honey, I think you actually got
chunks of cutting board in the salad.
-Well, I happen to be very upset, Hal.
-I'm upset, too. And this...
Principal sounds like a real idiot, but,
you've talked to him, and if he's
not going to do anything about it,
I don't see what else we can do.
Well, you know what, Hal?
That's just unacceptable to me.
It's just the way it is.
Kids do cruel things to each other.
But, you know, they bounce
back when you're young.
And I actually think that Reese
is coming around a little bit.
Well, I brought him soup yesterday,
and he couldn't even make a sound.
Now, I really...
I really think thing's are
going to turn out okay.
Are you trying to calm me down?
No.
I just don't think it leads anywhere
good when you get like this.
Get like what?
Well...
you know.
No, I don't know.
How is it I get?
Well...
If I have a problem,
I would love for you
to explain it to me.
You know what, honey? This seems
like a-a longer conversation,
and it just so happens that I am right
in the middle of a project in the garage.
I'm fixing that drawer
from our bathroom cabinet.
You know how you've always
had to keep your makeup brushes
in the pockets of your robe?
Well, I finally got around to
it, and wouldn't you know,
it's time for that second gluing.
But if you let it dry too much,
you might as well make
a bird's nest out of it.
But then I'd have to sand it and paint it,
and that's a whole different magilla.
But when I'm done, we will roll up our
sleeves, and we will get through this.
I mean, if you have to vent, go ahead.
I am your sounding board.
I don't care if you have
to bite my head off.
It's okay, it's what I'm here for.
I am your rock.
You've always been there for
me, and I'll be there for you,
even though physically, I may be in
the garage, and you in the kitchen.
No matter where I am, I'm there.
I want names.
How many were there?
Good. At least you can hear me now.
Just nod when you see one.
Kristin?
It's okay.
She can't hurt you now.
You just love that beautiful hair.
Don't you, sweetie?
Damn this drawer!
What do you want from me?!
And you can kiss that baby good-bye.
Another walk off home run for
Hal, and the crowd is on its feet.
Hal! Hal!
I can't take this anymore, Reese.
You have to stop this
and get on with your life.
Did I remind you of your life?
Look, Reese.
It's my ant farm. I've been
raising them for months.
I know all their names and love
each and every one of them.
Here, have fun.
Why does everything I love
always turn into a pig?
Hey, I've got it.
You'll love this.
Today at lunch,
Rick Jensen sat in beef stew.
And then spilled lemonade on his crotch.
It was a perfect storm.
Kids were coming from
other schools to laugh at him.
Was he able to get his pants clean?
Come on, Reese.
You should get back to bed.
I'll bet his mom wasn't
able to get his pants clean.
Hi, Malcolm.
How was school?
Okay, I guess.
Well, there was this
one weird thing.
This girl named Kristin, she's one
of the girls that picked on Reese.
You're not going to believe
what happened to her.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh!
My hair! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Who did this?!
They tried to get it all out, but I heard
the janitor ended up having to cut off
all her hair with a hedge trimmer.
Really?
That's terrible.
People can be so cruel.
Oh, absolutely.
Ugh! I know, exactly.
You know, Kristin could
not stop sobbing.
I'm even earing now,
she's a complete wreck.
I know. Did you see
her without her hair?
You know, I never realized
she had such a tiny head.
Oh, but you know what
the best part is?
Now Dylan's available.
Does he?
No. Get out!
Okay, rookie...
Show me what you got.
Okay...
At least we know
you're not on steroids.
Mom, what are you doing here?
I'm here to pick up
some things for Reese.
You know, so he can catch
up on his school work.
I hope you rented a truck.
You know what?
Everyone seems very amused
by your brother's pain.
Well, I think people
better start thinking twice.
Oh, my God!
Who did this?
Moppet?!
Baby?!
No!
It's you!
There you are.
You took off so fast from school,
we didn't get a chance to talk
about what happened to Diane.
I'm a very busy woman, Malcolm.
It isn't easy running this household.
I can imagine... cooking, shopping,
cutting the heads off of dolls.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Come on, Mom, it's pretty obvious
what's going on here, and I think it's sick!
Did you see Diane's reaction?
No, I didn't...
Was she crying?
She had to be wrapped in a blanket
and carried to the school nurse's office.
Terrible, just terrible.
There's a salad in the fridge
and you boys can make yourselves
sloppy Joe's whenever you're hungry.
I've got some errands to run.
Oh, "errands," right?
I know what you're up to, Mom.
Oh, yes, Malcolm, you've caught me.
I've got to return an overdue video,
go to the cleaners, and pick up
milk and cereal for the morning.
Guilty as charged.
Oh, nice try.
Now, I want you to look
me in the eye and...
Mom, I know you're behind all
this, and sooner or later you're
going to have to talk to me.
For God's sake, Malcolm,
can't I have a moment's rest?
No, you can't!
Tell me, did it feel good to
cut through Elmo's neck?
Did it?!
Mom?
Runners on second
and third, with two out.
Here's the wind-up, and the pitch.
You know, it's a shame to see some of
these veterans hang on a little too long.
Oh, sure, they were great once,
but there comes a point when you just
have to say "I'm done," and hang them up.
Dad, you've got to do something.
Mom has been stalking those
girls who humiliated Reese
like some kind of vigilante.
What? Are you sure about this?
Yes. She's nailed two of them so far,
and she just climbed out of the
bathroom window to go get the third.
This sounds like a lot
of supposition, Malcolm.
I mean, it would be a different story if
you had hard evidence or an eyewitness.
I saw her at school today.
She was there when these butchered dolls'
heads rolled out of one of the girls' lockers.
And what exactly do you mean
when you say you were "there"?
Dad, stop it--don't you care?
Of course, I care, But I think what we
need right now is caution and prudence.
A proactive wait-and-see... if you will.
So you're not going to do anything?
Listen, when your mother gets like this,
we need to vigilantly keep
abreast of all the developments
in a fully-engaged yet
cautiously-detached...
Oh, forget it... if you're
not going to help me,
then I'll just stop her myself,
and you can stay here and
play your ridiculous little game.
Good.
Sorry about the delay, folks.
There was a fan on the field.
Now let's see if this bonus baby is really
worth all the money that they paid for him.
My God, that could've killed...
You wouldn't believe the homework Mr.
Hendricks has been dumping on us lately.
Lift your arm.
I mean, okay, your wife moved out.
Don't take it out on us.
If his behavior with her is anything
like it is in math class, I totally get it.
Hey, how is he doing?
He's having a very good day.
Hello?
Hello.
This is the Edgewood Hotel.
I'm calling to verify a room with
a queen-sized bed for tonight.
I'm sorry, there must be some mistake.
Oh?
The reservation was
made by Heidi Kaczenski.
She also requested a bottle of
champagne and the romance package.
I think you'd better
cancel that reservation.
Heidi! Get in here this minute!
Dad, what is so important? I...
You and Scott got a
hotel room for tonight?!
What?!
That was the hotel calling.
How could you do this to us?!
I didn't do anything. I was in my
room getting ready for the dance.
You really don't know
anything about this?
No!
What's this?
Oh, my God!
That is not mine!
I don't know what the
hell you were thinking,
but as of right now, you
and Scott are through!
I hate you!
I hate both of you!
I saw something move.
There's somebody out there.
What's going on out here?
I'll tell you what's going on.
I saw this punk peeking in your window.
What?!
I can't believe this!
Jordan, I thought
you were a good kid!
But I was just...
You picked the wrong night to
mess with me, you little perv!
Well, let's see what the police
have to say about this.
I need to talk to you.
Not now.
Please, I need to tell you something.
I've been a terrible mother.
It's okay, Mom.
I've known that for a long time.
No, you don't understand.
When those girls humiliated you...
Instead of trying to comfort you and
help you deal with your feelings,
I just got caught up in my own
anger and went on a rampage.
What?
All I was worried about was
making them pay, and they did.
But what disturbs me is...
how much I enjoyed crushing those
three girls and watching them suffer.
I tapped into some dark,
ugly place inside of me.
I was acting like...
...you.
Oh, God, who am I kidding?
I wasn't acting like you.
I am you.
There's this horrible thing that's
part of us that makes it seem
okay to do really scary stuff.
I must have gotten it from Grandma,
and I passed it on to you, sweetie.
And all I can say is...
I'm sorry.
I'm deeply, deeply sorry.
There's one left?
No, Reese...
That doesn't matter.
Yeah, yeah, I know that, Mom.
I'm just trying to let it sink in.
You know, that girl will
be getting away with it.
She doesn't matter.
What matters is us.
I get that stuff about us, Mom.
That was amazing.
I was just thinking about what
must be going through her head.
But you're right, it's not about her.
Exactly.
What do you mean what's
going on inside of her head?
You know, how she thinks she beat you.
"I'm perfect, and I got away with it,
and that tired, frumpy housewife
just didn't have what it
took to finish the job."
If you think you're
manipulating me, you're wrong.
That girl just needs to know she
can't go around hurting people
without there being consequences.
And that way, she'll grow up
to be a very nice young lady.
Got it.
And I want to make it clear that
this is a one time thing, due to
very special circumstances.
Understood.
Now get back there and fill
up those balloons with paint.
And I'll tell you what, Joe.
The idea that man came
from an ape still rankles me.
I say prove it.
Point well taken, Skip,
but the good news here at the ballpark
is that the rain delay is finally over, and
we can get back to playing America's...
I think we have enough.
Let's move.
I knew I'd find you here!
Well, congratulations, Columbo.
Now, move, we're in a hurry.
Mom, no!
What you're doing is crazy.
It goes against everything
you've ever taught us.
You don't get it, Malcolm.
This is a one time thing, due
to very special circumstances.
Tell him, Mom.
Get out of our way!
This is not going to happen.
They're moving.
-Adjust left.
-Adjusting left.
Direct hit.
Oh, my God!
Stop it!
Make them stop!
Let go of me you coward?
Stop it!
This is nice.
Just the two of us.
I was just thinking the same thing.
Stop it!
Stop!
It's a shame it was over so quickly.
I know.
Maybe we can go bowling
together some time.
I'd like that.
Unbelievable.
So as long as you can
rationalize your behavior,
I guess you can do whatever you want.
There are no rules, huh, Mom?
Is that what you're saying?
Oh, Malcolm, for Pete's
sake. Don't be so upset.
I'll do something
with you next week.
www.tvsubtitles.net