While Betty kept the fat man occupied,
I ducked down the hallway to his office.
If I found his phone records, they would
prove that he was the one who called the
police station on the night of the murder.
All I knew was, the next person
through that door would be the
man who killed my partner.
"Hello, McKendrick,"
I heard from behind me.
I spun around,
but standing there was...
A stupid housewife who wouldn't
let her son buy nunchaks even
though they're totally safe.
Reese!
Malcolm in the Middle
7.03 - "Reese vs. Stevie"
Synchronisation par Max, Kevin & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman (Merci à Van).
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
All right, Reese,
you're busted.
Of all the stupid...
Come on, front and center.
Now, don't blame yourself.
Dewey, you were smoking?
Do you have any idea what a dangerous,
disgusting addiction that is?
It took me years to quit!
Do you want to end up breathing
through a hole in your neck?
Do you think that's cool?
You can breathe through
a hole in your neck?
What do you think your mother's
gonna say about this?
You can't tell Mom!
She'll kill me!
Well, you should've
thought of that earlier.
Where would you even
get cigarettes anyway?
There's, like, 20 cartons
hidden in your shop vac.
Oh, my God. That is my
stash from ten years ago.
Lois would kill me if...
All right, Dewey, under the
circumstances, I am giving
you your one free pass.
-Free pass?
-That's right.
I have given each of your brothers one
free pass, one time that I didn't tell
your mother about something they did.
All right, Francis,
this is your one free pass!
Okay, Reese,
but this is your one!
Okay, Malcolm,
this is your one!
Please make this
my one free pass.
All right.
We've got some
paperwork to sign.
Chair.
Book.
Window.
Mama.
Come on, Jamie,
you can talk, just one word.
Hal, has Jamie said anything
in front of you yet?
Whatever he said, he's a liar, Lois!
He hasn't seen anything.
What are you talking about?
I'm worried about Jamie. He's...
However old he is, and
he hasn't said a word yet.
I thought that's what
we liked about him.
You know,
it's probably his filthy ears.
I bet he's all plugged up with
wax and he can't hear anything.
I don't think so.
Relax, honey. Kids go at their own pace.
Heck, in sixth grade, I had
a full beard, and I still couldn't
tie my shoes properly.
Ah. There you are.
Stevie, you ran off without
your backup inhaler.
Thanks... Dad.
-Did Stevie tell you his big news?
-No. What's going on?
Stevie's been accepted as
a research subject at the
Norvet Biomedical Institute.
Dr. Norvet himself picked him
for the motor-neuropathy program.
It's... nothing.
Nothing?
Come on, Stevie. This is the most exciting
thing that's happened to us since
they put your stomach on the inside.
Who knows?
This Christmas might just
be our first ski vacation.
Dad...
Tomorrow after school we'll
go look at snowboards.
-Dad...
-I said just look.
My desk!
Reese! What's your problem?
He's my problem.
I get to come home to my own room
and put my own stuff on my own desk.
There's such a thing
as manners, Stevie.
When you're a guest
in someone's house...
Real classy, Reese.
Go ahead, hit him.
It's not fair!
He's hit me plenty of times.
He makes fun of me,
he treats me like crap,
and just because he's in that
chair he gets away with it!
I blame...
society.
Sorry, Stevie.
Good.
Malcolm, get your dirty
socks off this table or I'll
feed them to you for dinner!
Like I'd taste a difference.
I'm gonna do it anyway.
What?
I'm gonna beat you up anyway.
This Friday after school,
we're gonna go somewhere private
and I'm gonna beat you so bad your
wheelchair's gonna need a wheelchair.
I want you to think about that
for a few days. Picture it.
Dream about it, like I'm doing.
Even if you tell on me, I will
find some way to make this happen.
So you might as well have some
dignity and keep your mouth shut.
Your ass might not know
I'm kicking it, but I will.
Here you go.
All right, Jamie.
The doctor said there's no
physical reason you can't talk,
so that is exactly what
you are going to do.
Talk.
He said the best way to get you started
is for me to talk to you constantly
about everything happening around you so
that you live in a more verbal world.
That means Mommy's going to
narrate everything she's doing
like right now when she's going
over here to make you a snack.
Then it'll be time to do the laundry,
and after that she gets to make
dinner for the whole family.
Who will wolf it down in ten seconds and leave
her to do the dishes by herself before she gets to
make the boys' lunches for school the next day.
Then she'll get ready for
bed after everybody else.
And discover that the bathroom
is a swampy, hairy mess,
and Mommy gets to spend
her last waking minutes with
a sponge and a can of cleanser.
Then it'll be time to wake up in the
morning and she'll do it all over again.
Day after day, week after week,
for the next 30 years until Mommy dies.
And with Mommy's luck,
even that won't be the end of it...
Dewey! Get out here right now.
You're smoking again after we
talked about this last week?
You know what that does to you.
I'm cutting back.
Cutting back?
How many cigarettes
are you smoking?
Under two packs a day.
What?!
How is that even possible?
I got rid of the
cartons in the garage.
Well, you didn't get rid of the
ones hidden in the crawlspace.
Or the rain gutters,
or under the ivy.
There's thousands of cigarettes
hidden all over the place.
How could you spend all that
money and not even smoke them?
I could have gone
to private school.
Keep it down.
Look, Dewey, I'm sorry,
but I had such a hard time quitting.
The only way I could do it
without freaking out was
knowing they were there.
-I know it sounds crazy.
-I'll tell you what's crazy.
Being hooked on these stupid
things even though I hate the
way they taste and smell.
Well, those are really stale.
You're not getting
the fresh, rich flavor...
Never mind!
The point is,
you can beat this.
We'll do it together.
Listen, you know how much
I love coffee, right?
Yeah, I've seen you
drink it in the shower.
Exactly. I must drink
three pots a day, easy.
Well, I'm willing to give it up for you,
cold turkey, if you give up smoking.
-Really?
-Absolutely.
That way we're both suffering.
We both know what the other's going
through and we can support each other.
You and me, Dewey.
We'll be a team.
That sounds great, Dad.
Just let me have one more to get it
out of my system. We can start...
-Dewey.
-All right.
Come on, Stevie, pay attention.
You just had Hitler
invade Malibu.
Sorry.
What's up with you lately?
Hi, guys.
Hey, Reese, how'd it
go with the principal?
Fantastic.
I love when they get old and
they start just phoning it in.
He's actually willing to believe
this is from obsessive hand washing.
Reese took out Scotty
Riselli today. It was brutal.
You should have seen it.
He hit him so hard, a few times he
actually lifted him up in the air.
And the blood was, I mean,
there's always blood,
but Scotty was like one of
those big sprinklers, you know?
And once he went down,
Reese went to work on him.
Did you know he
had dental tools?
Hey, I get Africa.
Can I...
ask you something?
Sure.
Do you find...
my personality...
abrasive?
What?
Do you think...
I'm needlessly...
antagonistic?
I don't know. Probably.
What do you care?
I don't...
want anyone...
to hate me.
It's Lisa Filmore, isn't it?
Who?
I saw you checking her out.
You like the big
stuff, huh? Nice.
Little jiggly-wiggly,
little wabbal-abbal-abbal-abbal...
You're... a jerk.
I'm just being supportive.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Let's just finish the game.
Can't.
Today's our...
first meeting...
at the Norvet Institute.
Okay, wait.
There's something good
about your personality.
You completely humor your dad with all
his idiotic plans for you to walk, no matter
how pointless and stupid it is to try.
You're never, like,
"Dad, wake up."
"I'm never getting out of this
wheelchair. I'm going to be
a cripple till the day I die."
I mean, you know it,
but you don't throw it in his face.
That's a really nice quality.
There, better?
And so I spend all this time every morning
on my hair, trying to get it just so,
although I know no one else notices.
It's such a stupid
vanity thing.
I don't know why I'm so neurotic
about my hair. You know, it's just
ridiculous if you think about it.
Wish I could let it go,
but it's like I just can't help myself.
Slow down. You haven't had breakfast yet.
Well, if you got me the nicotine
gum like I asked, then...
You okay?
Oh, that? That's nothing,
Lois. That's just...
puberty.
You know,
when a boy's lungs drop.
This is how it hits all
the men in my family.
Hacking cough, dark circles under
the eyes, yellowing fingers.
So, there I am, 13 years old,
flat-chested as I can be,
everyone around me is sprouting, and
I'm feeling just horrible about myself.
And why?
No reason at all.
I'm getting straight A's,
I'm running the food drive,
I'm all-county on the gymnastics team,
and none of this means anything to me
because I'm so fixated on my bustline.
And so like an idiot, I started
stuffing my bra with toilet paper.
Even after all these years, I remember
every morning in the bathroom,
shoving these things down my
shirt and feeling like such an
awkward, ugly, little girl.
Thank you.
Of course in second-period
Spanish I had to sit next to
the snooty Janice Montgomery
with her tangerine nail polish, which I was
dying to try, but of course she wouldn't let
me because I had drugstore shoes.
Hey, Mom.
Look at these stains.
You boys are in
so much trouble.
No more pillowcases
for a month.
Okay...
Fixing something?
Dad.
Hi.
I'm so disappointed
in you, son.
We had an agreement.
What was that?
What was what?
All right,
we both have a problem.
This is so degrading.
On the way home from school,
I almost pulled a cigarette
butt out of the gutter.
I French-kissed your mother this morning
just to lick the coffee off her teeth.
But we can do this. We just need
to find a way to divert our minds
when the pangs get too bad.
Hal, what are you doing?
What's it look like I'm doing?
Can't a father have a friendly
game of catch with his son?!
We're having fun!
I had that dream
again last night.
Cheerleading tryouts.
Like it wasn't bad enough it
happened, I have to relive it
for the rest of my life.
I was so excited to think
that I might be a Cougar,
and finally feel
like I belonged.
The routine was nothing, I'd done
that stuff in gymnastics for years.
And still, I practiced that routine for
weeks making sure that it was perfect.
The day of the tryouts,
I borrowed my sister's good sweater,
spent about an hour on my hair,
stuffed my bra, even shoved
a little extra in there for luck.
And when I got down to the gym,
I found out I had to go first,
in front of the whole squad and
everyone else who was trying out.
So I just pretended to
be braver than I was.
I smiled real big, and I went out
there and I started my routine.
I did a round-off, a cartwheel,
a kip-up, it was going great,
I was so happy.
I landed my back-flip dead solid
perfect. I threw up my arms, and
instead of everybody cheering...
everybody was laughing.
And I looked down, and there
was a 30-foot-long trail of toilet
paper along the tumbling mat.
Everything I worked for,
everything I wanted so desperately...
ruined because of my vanity.
And you know what
the worst part is?
I didn't even learn anything.
Deep down, I'm still just
as shallow as I was then.
All that fussing and primping and
time I wasted to shut out laughter
that stopped 30 years ago.
It's disgusting.
If I had any guts I would just
cut off my hair right now.
You know, just face
it down, and beat it!
You gonna get that?
I can't.
Malcolm. It's Abe.
Where's your brother?
Reese? I don't know, probably
pounding the snot out of someone.
It's Stevie!
-You've got to stop it!
-What?
What are you talking about?
Stevie and I were in the middle of
our session at the Norvet Institute,
and then he said he had to go
fight Reese, and just took off!
-I'm terrified that...
-Oh, no.
Reese, what are you doing?
Something I should've
done years ago.
I've been numbing my legs
in ice for an hour now.
What?
I can't feel a
thing down there.
See? Nothing.
First three times I did
that it hurt like hell.
Nobody's gonna say this
wasn't a fair fight.
When Stevie gets here,
I'm gonna flop over to him like a fish,
yank him out of his chair, and
smash his face in, gimp-to-gimp.
Reese, you're insane!
Am I?
They thought Einstein was crazy...
until he started kicking ass.
Hey. Where's Mom?
She's locked in her room with Jamie.
She's been there for hours.
Oh. Listen, I'm sorry I snapped
at you. I was just agitated,
but I'm feeling better now.
Hey, I really think
we're over the hump.
We're still a team, okay?
Good boy.
What are you doing?!
What?
Oh, this. It's nothing.
It's keeping me calm.
But we're quitting!
No, I'm quitting coffee.
You're quitting cigarettes.
That's cheating!
You do not get to do this.
Actually, Dewey, I get to do whatever
I want, because I am a grown-up.
All right,
if that's how you want it.
Dewey!
What are you doing?
Don't you dare!
The smooth,
wonderful taste of betrayal!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm in flavor
country, baby!
This is good.
This is growth.
Just do it.
Don't be such a chicken.
It's the only way
to stop hearing it.
All those kids laughing, my mother
coming to the nurse's office
telling me to stop blubbering,
she wouldn't have to stuff my bra if
I wasn't too lazy to grow them myself.
Oh, my God.
It was my mother.
She was the one stuffing
my bra. Oh, my God.
She was the one making me feel
so horrible and inadequate. Not me.
This wasn't about
vanity, Jamie.
This is about an abusive old
bat trying to make her kid into
something that she wasn't.
Well, I am not going to
be that kind of mother.
If you don't feel like talking yet,
then you don't have to talk.
I'm going to love you
exactly the way you are.
Shut up!
Mm. Rich, roasted goodness!
Suddenly I'm at a French cafe.
Well, I'm with two girls in
a speedboat, sucking down
a smooth blend of fine tobaccos.
Hal!
Dewey's drinking coffee!
I think crippling my legs
made my arms stronger.
Like how blind guys
have bigger noses.
This is gonna be great.
Reese, you can't do this.
Stevie's our friend.
Hey, he's not my friend.
He's your friend.
He treats me like crap.
He insults me and
disrespects me...
and you let him.
What?
You always take his side. You
always do everything his way,
even though we're brothers.
Wait. Are you jealous?
No, I'm pissed.
You and Stevie are going to
be friends your whole life,
but once you go away to college
and you're not stuck with us,
we're never gonna
see you again.
But even so, you're spending the rest of
the time left with Stevie instead of...
Do I have to tell
you I love you?
No.
Good.
Dude, like you said,
we're brothers.
It doesn't matter if I don't
want to be here, I'm stuck here.
No matter where I go or what I do, we're
always going to be forced together.
Christmas, birthdays...
We're going to be forced to be around
each other for the rest of our lives.
Really?
What was that?
I don't know.
You're... mine!
Good news, Stevie. I forgive you.
Come on, Stevie!
I can't walk. This isn't fair!
Don't reduce yourself to my level!
You're better than this!
God, I'm too late!
Stevie, please stop!
Think of the lawsuit!
You know these people will do
anything to get our money!
The Norvet Institute kicked Stevie
out of their program for unauthorized
use of their equipment.
And Reese will be okay, but he's
not allowed out of bed until he
stops seeing four of everything.
Mom's making Dad find every
last one of his old cigarettes.
She's going to make him eat
any she finds tomorrow morning,
so he's pretty motivated.
The amazing thing is I'm the only
one that got off scott-free.
Malcolm, go change
Reese's bedpan.
Hey. He's my brother.
www.tvsubtitles.net