Damn it!
Malcolm in the Middle
7.13 - "Mono"
Synchronisation par Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
I have never been so angry.
If you boys are gonna act like dogs,
I'm gonna treat you like dogs.
This is so awesome.
Mom and Dad just got
back from the doctor's,
and it turns out she has mono.
She's been ordered to stay
in bed for two weeks.
After all those years
of stepping on cracks,
it finally paid off.
I mean, it's no broken
back, but I'll take it.
Honey, come on. You'll have
plenty of time to yell at the
boys once you beat this thing,
but right now you've got billions
of germs inside of you that you
need to focus your hatred on.
Besides, you're highly contagious.
Okay.
Wait, what's on your face?
I can't wait until everybody
at school finds out you got
the kissing disease from Mom.
Which will happen right about...
now.
I didn't kiss her. You saw it.
What I saw was you and Mom
making out on the couch.
Dewey?
It was disgusting.
She licked her finger
and touched my face.
Spare us the perv details.
Okay, Jamie. Here we go.
None of Mommy's monster
germs are in here.
But don't get too comfortable in the
big boys' room. It's only temporary.
He's never leaving, is he?
What?
No. This is just until it's safe
to go back into our room.
You said the same thing
when Dewey moved in.
Are you gonna take him back
now that your ringworm's better?
I told you we are still on
yellow alert with that!
Ready, Malcolm?
Yeah.
God, I hate sleeping on the couch.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
We can't have you out there
in the general population.
Well, then, where
am I gonna sleep?
Right this way.
Come on.
Oh, God.
Okay, I can get through this.
I'll read books.
I'll sleep a lot.
I'll apologize in advance.
I have gas to beat the band.
Good job, Jamie.
What the hell was that?
He's my slave.
You don't get to have
a slave. You're my slave.
Slaves can have slaves.
This is America.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'll give you your freedom
if you give me Jamie.
Really?
Your attitude's been
pretty lousy lately.
I know you've been spitting
in my sandwiches.
I mean, I still eat them,
but now the trust is gone.
Wait.
Don't you have something
you can read over there?
I'm too tired to turn the page.
Stick 'em up!
Who wants a snack?
Here we go.
All right.
A little bit closer.
Sorry, just a minor setback.
Hal, we're fine.
Thank you for your trouble.
Wait, don't eat it
without the fun.
Yeah.
Just leave.
Well, forgive me.
I thought you might appreciate
having some human interaction.
You're in here every five minutes, when
what we really need is rest. Hal, just go.
Please, find something to do.
Finally.
Malcolm, quit hogging the covers.
You're just like your father in bed.
Hey, there.
Look at you carrying that big leaf.
All right.
You'll be a hero when
you walk in with that.
The queen's not gonna
tell you  to get out.
Oh, hey, Steve.
Steve, hey.
Oh, hey, Hal.
Hey, I was just, uh...
So what's going on in
your life, huh, fun stuff?
Oh, no, no. You know me and Carol.
Just boring, boring, boring.
Just a stay-at-home couple.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, Lois has mono.
I've got her quarantined in
the bedroom for two weeks.
So she's really out
of commission, huh?
Oh, yeah.
That's rough.
And there's no chance
she'll come out of it sooner?
No, I'm afraid not.
But thanks for asking.
You know what?
Uh, Carol and I are having
a luau in about an hour.
Just a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing.
Why don't you come by?
Wow, you guys really do this up right.
Well, they had to outdo
a whole medieval feast
at John and Stacy's and
'70s Night at the Wongs.
Wait...
So...
You guys do this all the time?
Hal...
I'm such a jerk.
I never extend myself.
I just get in my car. I go to work.
I live in my own little world.
I never think to knock on a neighbor's
door and say, "Hey, let's have a luau."
In fact, in fact, when Lois gets
better, we'll do this at our house.
Yeah, we should really talk
about that at some point.
You're right. I'm being pushy.
Friendships develop over time.
Yeah. Okay.
No.
God, no.
We're staying.
You said we both have to agree
on something or we won't watch it.
When you own your own house,
you can make a rule and break it.
That's not fair.
Look at this boring leather jacket.
Now look at the same leather
jacket covered in brilliant
scratch-resistant rhinestones.
Oh, God. Get the remote.
It's on your side.
Fine, you want to watch the
shopping channel all night,
that's what we'll watch.
Before now, this many rhinestones would
have taken hours, even days to apply.
But now there's the Pizzazzler!
It'll change your life.
See?
That's what we need.
Amen, we've been screwing around
with medicine and bed rest when all
we needed were some shiny beads.
Quick, easy, fun
and so simple to use.
Do you think we could pizzazzle
this thick wool peacoat?
I don't think they can.
Impossible.
Pizzazz-yes!
I didn't see that coming.
Works on denim, satin,
leather, pleather...
Look at that oven mitt.
Oh, come on, it's got
nothing on that wallet.
Vinyl, suede, ultrasuede, even carpet.
Pizzazzler,
it'll change your life.
You know, it actually has.
He's broken. I'm taking
you back as my slave.
-What? We had a deal.
-You gave me damaged goods.
Look.
Jamie, get me a soda
and it'd better be cold,
or I'm gonna brain you.
See?
It's not my fault you don't
know how to work him.
Jamie, get him a soda.
All right, but you're doing
that because I want you to,
not because he wants you to.
Make him think that, Dewey.
Malcolm, this is coming out great.
Do you think it's gonna
be uncomfortable?
Maybe, but you're gonna have to make
sacrifices if you're gonna be pizzazzulous.
Oh, well, I didn't think
of it pizz-at way.
Okay, I'm going over
to Dave and Tina's.
Everything okay in here?
We're fine.
Fizzazzine.
Feeling mizzazzuch bizzetter.
Are you taking your pills?
Gizzo awazzay.
Yeah, lizzeave us alazzone.
Okay, well...
Gizzazzood bizzazzye.
What?
Hal, you're not making any sense.
That's really weird, Dad.
Sorry.
Feel better.
Oh, I'll tell ya.
I get no respect.
No respect at all.
This is the guy from the
luau I was telling you about.
He's hysterical.
Ever notice that stop sign on Maple?
Evidently, Mary Keller thinks it's
a slow-down-and-check-for-cops sign.
That Hal is so great.
Too bad he's stuck with that woman.
That is right, Jay.
She never stops there.
I will terminate her.
You know who'd be
perfect for him? Ellie.
- She's just coming
out of that bad divorce.
- Stop. That is terrible.
Hey, ask me for a burger with cheese.
I'll have a burger with cheese.
You can't handle the cheese.
I'll introduce them.
Ellie, this is Hal.
Hi.
So, Carol tells me
you're here on your own?
Yeah, yeah. My wife kicked me out.
Oh, that's terrible.
So, are... are  you
out of the house?
No, no, no. I'm sleeping on the couch.
But we're being smart about it.
I mean, no contact at all.
I think it's for the best,
given our situation.
Believe me, I know.
Well, would you like
to join me in a drink?
My, oh, my. Do you
think we'll both fit?
It's so good to get out and
meet all you great people.
I have a confession to make. This
is my first night out in a long time.
I've been kind of a hermit lately.
That was me, too, but now
I wish I hadn't waited this long.
I had no idea there was something
so amazing right here on my block.
Oh, Hal.
Well, maybe we can
do this again sometime.
Well, Phil and Jenny are having
a Mexican fiesta tomorrow.
Are you asking me?
Yeah, are you going?
Sure.
I'm sorry. I don't know how to do this.
Just say good night.
Good night, Hal.
Good night.
Russell makes a mean Singapore Sling.
Oh, and you know that probate
lawyer, Mrs. Chaffley?
The one who's always on
my ass about the lawn?
Well, she can stand on her head and
drink a pitcher of beer in seven seconds.
Glad you had a good time, Hal.
We're doing fine here, too.
So, what do you wanna do now?
You wanna Pizzazzle some more?
No, I'm kinda Pizzazzled out.
How about if I do your hair?
Only if I get to do yours, too.
Dizzeal!
Thanks, little man.
Aha! I see how you're doing it.
You have a tack in your hand.
Nope.
That was just a pat on the head.
So you're pushing the soft spot?
No, Reese. I'm just being nice.
So he doesn't know when
the hit's gonna come.
Reese, there's no trick.
I'm just showing him respect.
You're not making any sense.
Don't overthink it.
Oh, I got it.
No, wait. I don't.
He's my little brother.
I'm just treating him the
way I want to be treated.
Show me the hand thing again.
*Wishing and hoping and
thinking and praying*
*Praying and dreaming
each night of his charms*
*That won't get you into his arms*
*So if you're looking to
find love you can share*
*All you gotta do is
hold him and kiss him*
*And love him and show him...*
Oh, Hal, the last few nights
have been so magical.
The barbecue, the... disco party.
Don't forget fondue night.
I think I've gone up
a whole pant size.
I think I'm falling in
love with someone.
Wow, you know, you're pretty great.
It wouldn't surprise me if he was
falling in love with you, too.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Good for her.
I can do your nails again.
I don't know what you could
possibly do to improve them.
Well, we have to do something.
Truth or Dare.
Truth.
What's the worse thing
you've ever done?
Total immunity?
Pinky swear.
All right, well, I'm not
sure if this counts,
but when the Harrises were on
vacation I drove their car for a week.
Malcolm!
It's not as bad as it sounds.
They left their window unlocked.
And a lot of people leave a spare
car key in the kitchen drawer.
Except the Goldmans.
They left theirs in a fake
soup can in the cabinet.
Well, I'm off to Steve
and Carol's... again.
Fine, Hal.
Hey, you know that Ellie
Johnson down the street?
She is a lot more fun than you think.
I think she found a fella.
Good for her.
Should be a great party
tonight. Steve's doing kabobs.
Hal, I thought about it and it's just...
too soon.
Well, they did say 7:30.
I mean, I'm not...
ready.
I hope you understand.
Well, if you're not ready,
you're not ready.
You have such an amazing attitude, Hal.
Don't ever lose that.
So I guess I should just go.
Good-bye, Hal.
Good...
Good-bye, Ellie.
Okay, now say something nice to him.
Like how you feel about him,
but only good stuff.
I don't know. He's...
...not that bad.
Good. Now tell him that.
You're not horrible like the
rest of those buttmunches.
There you go. Now pat
him on the shoulder.
It's like a slap, but slower.
Good.
Now see if he'll get you a soda.
-Get me a soda!
-No, no.
Do it with me.
Would you mind...
...getting me...
...a...
...soda?
-You stupid...
-Nothing else.
I just realized I totally lost
sight of what's really important.
There you go.
It's not that I like having
a slave getting me things.
It's that I like to have a slave so I can
watch him suffer while he gets me things.
What?
The fact that I had to ask for
this makes it taste like bile.
Thank you for helping
me figure that out.
What was that for?
Sorry, man. I had to get
the taste out of my mouth.
I still can't believe
you ate that dead fly.
Hey, I play for keeps.
All right, truth or dare?
Truth.
Remember when I was in fifth
grade and I set the couch on fire?
How'd you know it was me?
I planted all that evidence,
I had Stevie as an alibi. Even
Dad thought it was Reese.
Honestly?
I had no idea.
You were the first person I saw when
I started yelling, and you just crumbled.
You were bluffing,
but you seemed so sure.
Of course, I seemed sure.
With you boys, if I showed the
slightest weakness or hesitation
the whole thing falls apart.
Half the time, I'm just
going on blind instinct.
After all these years, five
kids, keeping up that act.
That's gotta be exhausting.
Tell me about it.
Plenty of days I come
home tired from work.
The last thing I wanna do is be Lois.
I guess I do the same thing.
Sometimes when
I come home from school,
I don't feel like arguing with you.
But it's like that's my job.
It's funny, isn't it?
I bet half the time if we knew what
the other one was really thinking,
we'd just burst out laughing.
We probably would.
Where's Ellie?
Oh, she said she just wasn't ready.
Oh, yeah.
Well, what a shame.
But you know sometimes people just
cling to these relationships that don't
make sense to anybody else, right, Hal?
What?
Nothing.
No, you clearly said something.
What are you, what are you driving at?
Well, it's just that, you know,
you're so fun and Lois is so...
Mojitos?
No, no, mojitos. You were
saying something about my
wife, so let's just hear it.
Well, um, this is nothing
against you, Hal,
it's just that your
wife is kind of a...
pill.
What?
Well, maybe that's your opinion,
buddy, but that's not the opinion
of everyone else here, is it?
So that's how it is, huh?
Well, let me tell you something.
I think all of you
people are just jealous!
My wife happens to be
the most wonderful,
amazing, beautiful woman in the
world, and I don't care to eat with
anyone who thinks otherwise.
See me cowering?
This is how a slave acts.
You'll get it. We'll both
just have to be patient.
Now, let's start at the beginning.
"No, I won't get you a soda."
Come on. Put some wrist into it.
Wait, you're missing
my eye. Get my eye.
Oh, don't worry Hal,
I'll take down the rhinestones.
No, leave them. Last night was
like making love inside of a star.
You know, Hal, now that I'm
feeling better you can take me
to one of those great parties.
Oh, I don't think so, honey.
I never really fit in
with those people.
Well, if they don't appreciate you,
I don't want anything to do with them.
Oh, for the...!
Who left the refrigerator open?
Malcolm?!
Sorry, Mom, I didn't...
Mom, remember the...?
What the hell are you laughing at?
You think wasting electricity is funny?
Not as funny as your
pathetic parenting skills.
-Isn't it interesting that you treat your
kids like criminals... -Oh, well, why
don't you just live on the street...
- ...and they end up turning into criminals?
You must be so proud. -...and see if a bunch
of strangers will give you free, cold food?
-You have all your kids afraid
of you. Is that what you want?
-That's all you want, free stuff, right?
-You want me to be afraid of you?
-You think everybody's just gonna give you...
www.tvsubtitles.net