You're the one who
invited your friend over.
Now that he's here, you can't
just suddenly change your mind.
Now get up and
be nice to Ryan.
Fine.
Hi, Ryan.
You want a beer?
Malcolm in the Middle
7.17 - "Hal's Dentist"
Synchronisation par Max & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
You look pretty dumb
in those glasses.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I read a book
about poker tells,
and my eyes have been
giving away my cards.
We'll see who looks dumb when I am
dancing on a mountain of poker chips.
-I'm out.
-Me, too.
-Fold.
-Damn!
Gentlemen.
Fiddle Faddle!
Now it's a poker game.
Easy there.
I can't help it.
Kitty's got me on an extreme diet.
-Hey, this isn't Fiddle Faddle.
-I make it at home.
I pop some corn, brush some
melted caramel on it, let it cure,
blanch and double
roast the nuts.
You lose a weekend, but
you save 73 cents a batch.
I'll bet a buck.
-I'm out.
-Fold.
Me, too.
Damn, you could see through
these glasses, can't you?
Oh! Oh, my tooth!
Please, let the dentist take a look.
It's this one.
Uh-oh, #31 is cracked.
-Is that important?
-Only for eating and talking.
It's one of the glory boys.
You better get that fixed.
Great.
My company doesn't have
a dental plan anymore.
They got us a foosball table instead.
So where you been going?
The dental college. It's not too bad,
but they do make you
sign a death waiver.
Forget about that.
Come by my office on Monday,
and I'll take care of it.
-Really?
-Absolutely.
Wow, it's been so many years
since I've been to a real dentist.
Do you supply the ether rag,
or should I bring my own?
God, I'm so bored.
Everything's boring.
It makes ditching school almost
seem like a bad choice.
Even talking about
boring is getting boring.
Yeah, boring.
Bored, bored, bored, bored...
-Wait! You see that?
-What?
It's a dead squirrel!
Gentlemen, our week just filled up.
Sorry, not interested.
Sure, it looks good to you now,
but it's just going to wind up
in the closet with all the others.
Pass.
Your loss.
See you, suckers.
Mom?
Why aren't you in school?!
You're in trouble, young man!
Oh, I don't think so.
You're in the middle of an
alley trying to get on a bike.
You are ashamed of something.
I can always smell shame.
It's kind of like rotten coconut.
Okay.
There's this stupid
bike-a-thon at work.
Some idiot made a big stink about how
the store's not doing enough for charity.
-Then don't do it.
-I have to.
I'm the idiot.
And I... I...
I can't ride a bike...
And it's very embarrassing.
So you really can't ride a bike?
No.
Hey, everybody! My mom can't...
You don't understand!
My father didn't believe
in training wheels!
Mom!
He just tied me to the bike
and pushed me down the hill.
Mom, there's glass down here!
I came back with three teeth in my hand,
and he just pushed me down all over again.
After that, I just told people
I knew how to ride.
And I've been living
with this lie ever since!
Mom!
If you tell anybody, I will kill you!
-Do you hear me?
-I won't tell a soul!
-Let me up, and I can help!
-What?!
I know how to ride
a bike! I'll teach you!
You'd really do that?
Absolutely. And you don't
have to be embarrassed.
No one will ever find
out your horrible secret.
No, lady, I don't want your drugs!
Wow, and I thought Reese
was the one dragging us down.
Maybe we should see how
he's doing with his squirrel.
If I know Reese, all the good
parts are gone by now.
Nothing exciting ever
happens around here.
Wow...
we even have boring miracles.
It must have fallen from
a plane or something.
Wow, this is brand-new.
At least what I think a
mattress would look like new.
-It's got no lumps.
-No weird stains.
No springs sticking out of it.
-It's got tags!
It's like sitting on a cloud...
with two clouds under it.
This is amazing.
I'm in ass heaven.
Maybe it's worth some money.
Sell it or keep it?
Let's think about this for a second.
Oh, my God, we totally fell asleep.
That wasn't sleep.
Sleep makes you feel like
you've been beaten up.
We got to keep this thing.
Enjoying Lord of the Rings in high-def?
Oh, it's unbelievable.
No lines, no commercials...
I'm bringing Lois here
for our anniversary.
I still can't get over all this.
A real sink to spit in.
I really don't have to swallow it.
Hal, are you crying?
They're good tears.
How much longer will it take?
I'm done.
You can't be.
I didn't bite down on the pain stick.
No, it's done; I finally got
the temporary crown on.
I got to tell you, Hal, it
was in pretty bad shape,
but I think you're going
to be happy with the results.
Wow, you really are a friend.
Two thousand dollars?!
Excuse me, but this can't be right.
Trey said he would take care of it.
The doctor handed me the bill himself.
You don't understand.
I'm a friend of Trey's.
And he gave you the friend
discount: ten percent.
You mean he was going
to charge me more?!
Can I have the key to the bathroom?
Careful, it'll cost you
$200 in a bathroom fee!
You know what?
You can tell Trey that this
is what I think of his bill.
-That was your parking validation.
-I know.
Could I have another one?
Morning.
-Last night was...
-Fantastic.
I'm glad we got these
600-thread-count sheets.
Anything else would have been
an insult to this beautiful mattress.
We really have been living like beasts.
A good night's sleep.
Just think what we can do
with all this new energy.
Yeah.
-Five more minutes?
-I'm right behind you, buddy.
-See? Just do that.
-I can't.
-You want me to show you again?
-No, Reese.
I'm afraid.
So you're chicken, huh?
Yes!
Oh.
Mom, you might not know this, but
I used to be afraid of a lot of things.
Thunder, frogs, mailboxes...
You were afraid of mailboxes?
I used to imagine that if I stuck
my hand in a mailbox, it would
slam shut and rip my hand off,
but I simply conquered my fear
by ripping the lid off of every
mailbox in the neighborhood.
I turned that fear into hate.
And you have to hate
that bike just as much.
-I don't have hate.
-You've got hate in there.
You just have to find it.
Do you hate work?
Surprisingly, no.
What about your life?
Your best years are gone,
and they weren't so good.
I don't hate my life, Reese.
What about the stuff I've done to you,
like when I baked your shoes,
or broke your wedding china,
or when I sold those tickets to those
fifth graders to watch you shower?
You did what?!
Perfect! Now direct
that anger to the bike!
Don't let me fall!
Okay, I think we've
made a lot of progress!
That's enough for today!
So, lately, I've been going
to the library with Mom.
That's all. I don't want
anyone following us.
Like I said, it's just the
library, where we do...
library things.
Has anyone seen our bicycle pump?
Hal's in. Your bet.
Five dollars?
-I'll call.
-Hi, guys.
-Where should I put this?
-I'll take care of it.
-Thanks.
-Uh-huh.
This is about the
dental visit, isn't it?
You know, I don't
recall a dental visit.
I recall a mugging!
I'm surprised you'd bring it up,
considering you ran out on the bill.
-Con artist!
-Welsher!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What's this about?
I went to Trey to get my tooth
fixed for free like he promised,
and then this pirate
hands me a bill for $2,000!
Free?! I never said
I'd fix it for free!
-You said you'd take care of it!
-And I took care of it!
I fixed it!
Now Hal is walking around here
pain-free with a stolen smile!
How dare you?!
We were all here. Now, who's right?
I think the answer is pretty clear.
-Hal!
-Trey!
What are you talking about?
The man said he'd take care of it.
Everyone knows what that means.
Yeah, it means he'd fix it for free.
Thank you!
You're just saying that because it
was your cheap-ass caramel corn
that broke his tooth in the first place.
It had nothing to do
with the caramel corn!
Guys, guys, guys,
this is ruining the game.
Malik, you do mediation
at your law firm.
-Can't you help out?
-Fine.
Fellas, I want you both to just sit
down and listen to each other.
Trey, can't you see where "I'll take
care of it" could be misinterpreted?
-Well, I suppose it could.
-Yeah!
And, Hal, can't you see
that Trey is a professional?
He went to years of medical school.
And then he gave up
and became a dentist.
Trey deserves to be
compensated for his work.
It's natural and it's fair.
I guess it is.
I'm sorry, Trey.
No offense taken.
So, Malik, how much do we owe you?
Ah, nothing. We're friends.
A-ha! You see?
It's not the same!
You came to me as a professional.
You get a salary for your work.
Imagine going to somebody's house,
playing Tetris, shuffling papers
and making long- distance
calls, and nobody paid you?!
That's it!
I don't want your repo thugs
coming after me, so here!
So, Peterson puts the report
on my desk and says, uh...
Hal, if your tooth hurts, don't eat.
I'm fine.
-Hal, just stop it.
-Stop what?
We're all afraid you're
going to choke to death.
-You can't eat if you don't chew.
-I don't need to chew.
I am fine.
The key is relaxing
the esophagus.
Jamie, I hope you're
paying attention.
So, Mom, how's the
bike-a-thon going?
Just great.
-I'm really excited about it.
-You are, huh?
How long have you been riding?
Long enough.
Fascinating!
Hey, you know what I could go for?
Another piece of cake.
There is no more.
-What about that piece?
-My piece?
That's okay. I don't need
another piece of cake.
I can just continue talking.
So, what was I talking about?
Oh, yeah, your bike riding.
These chairs are so uncomfortable.
They have no idea how
to conform to our bodies.
Hal, you have an infection.
You have to see a dentist.
I made an appointment with
Dr. Voorhees tomorrow.
Isn't that the guy we
took Dewey's hamster to?
He's a doctor.
If he isn't in the society pages, then
you're not impressed, huh, Lois?
Go back to Trey!
-We'll find the money somehow.
-No way!
Well, you are going to have to
find some way to deal with this.
I know and I have.
I'm not an idiot, Lois.
Now, please, will you
hand me my scream box?
Hey, what's all the noise?
You know the rule.
The only sound allowed
in this room is snoring.
I've been waiting ten years to
see Conrad Horner perform,
and I overslept and
completely missed it.
Oh, he'll come back in a few years.
He's 98.
I got there in time to get a program off the
floor and see his ambulance drive away.
Oh, well.
You know what would help?
Sleep.
I actually dreamed
I was in this bed sleeping.
Sleep is all we ever do anymore.
Do you even know what day it is?
I don't even know what year it is.
Get up!
Don't you have a test tomorrow?
It could affect college, your future!
I'm pursuing my dreams right
here in a much more direct way.
Well, I'm done with it.
Fine! More room for me.
So that's your plan?
You're going to sleep
for the rest of your life?
That's pretty pathetic.
I'll leave my mark.
Long after I'm gone, the memory
coils in this bed will still remember
the contours of my body.
Listen to yourself. That's insane.
This bed is evil.
It's draining your soul, Malcolm!
Malcolm?
Okay, Mom, I think today we might break
the 12-inch distance record we set yesterday.
It's white-knuckle time.
I'm not doing this anymore.
-What?!
-You know I can't do it.
I just cannot get on that
bike again. It's just too hard.
Oh, it's too hard?
Well, why didn't you say so?
When things get tough, you got to just
give up and run away from your dreams.
Lower your expectations.
That's fine. I've had my fun.
If you want to quit, go ahead and quit.
All right, Reese, you made
your point. Let's give it a try.
No, I was really saying quit.
I want to thank Hal for inviting us
all over for a special afternoon game.
I don't want to be the one
to break up the game here.
-I have nothing to be ashamed of.
-If you're implying...
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
no one is implying anything.
All I'm saying is it's hard
keeping the game together.
And despite our differences, I think
we can all agree this is nothing like
the hidden jack incident of '91.
-Here we go.
-You are damn right. Here we go.
Don't throw around accusations.
I will not be accused of cheating.
I never said you were cheating.
I said it looked like you were
cheating. That's totally different.
I don't need to cheat.
You're not that good a poker player.
So the card I needed to make my straight
just decided on its own to leave the table?
Guys, guys, come on.
I'm just saying we made it through that,
we can make it through this.
I have a feeling by
the end of this game,
the problem will be solved.
Show 'em.
Pair of twos.
Beats me.
Me, too.
Pair of two's the winner.
Wow, I win again?
Oh, I must be on a real lucky streak.
I must have a thousand dollars here.
Wait a minute.
Dead hand. Cards over.
You had a flush! Look!
You're letting me win!
You are?!
We're just trying to
get this thing settled.
I don't want your
money if I didn't win it.
I have no need for your pity!
I can't stand it anymore!
I'll give you the dental
work for free. Happy?
Let's go right down to my office
right now and put back that crown.
-It's settled.
-No!
I am not some charity case,
and I am not going to relieve
you of your conscience, either.
-Hal!
-No!
You will be the one to have
to live with the pain, not me!
Give me that glass of ice water!
-No!
I hope you're happy!
Hal, Stop! Think about it.
-Hal! Hal!
-Hal! Come on, Hal!
My back's killing me.
What happened?
Malcolm, you're awake.
We were worried
about you for a while.
What happened to
the new mattress?
-What are you talking about?
-The mattress!
I know there was a mattress.
Maybe it was a dream.
It wasn't a dream!
The mattress was perfect and
white, and it felt like a cloud!
It fell out of the sky,
and it made me happy!
Was it just a bed, or was
there a beanstalk, too?
Maybe it was a dream.
You were happy, Malcolm.
Of course it was a dream.
Okay, Mom, this is it.
Once you're up, don't look down.
-But...
-Trust me.
Just start pedaling.
I'm going to make sure
you get through this.
You are not alone.
-Thank you, Reese.
-Now go!
Oh, my God!
I'm doing it!
I'm riding!
Don't worry, Mom!
It's for your own good.
Reese?!
Try to go slow, Mom!
I'm going to crash into you!
I'm going to prove to you
that falling isn't so bad!
No, Reese, I'm doing fine, see?
Mom, it's the only way!
Reese, it worked!
I'm not afraid.
I can ride.
Thank you.
Mommy...
Help me! Help me!
So...
Want to tell me what's going on here?
It's cool, Officer.
You see, we tied him up because
he's got a painful, busted tooth,
and he refused to let us fix it.
Help! Help me!
I need help!
Okay. Drive safe.
Thank you, sir.
Help! Help me!
Help me!
www.tvsubtitles.net