Jamie, time to get going.
Let's put your shoes on.
Wonder what's gotten into him.
I have no idea.
Now pay attention. I'm only going
to show this to you one more time.
The rabbit comes out of his hole,
and runs around the tree.
But he won't stop
laughing at you.
So you grab him
by the tail
and it rips off in your hand.
You follow the trail of
blood back to his hole.
And then you reach in, pull the
rabbit out and then you strangle him!
And then you're
ready to walk around.
Malcolm in the Middle
7.19 - "Stevie in the Hospital"
Synchronisation par Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
What do you say, Reese?
You want to take the new
boat out this afternoon?
Maiden voyage.
Just you and me.
Father and son slicing through
the waves, wind in our hair.
And look.
I re-did the aft bathroom.
Sorry, Dad, I start
my new job today.
Oh, come on!
You don't actually do
any work the first day.
You're just filling out forms
and deciding on a nemesis.
Did you know how hard
it was to get this job?
Everywhere else I applied
called my references.
Thank God telemarketing
has no standards.
Basically, I get to harass old
people and shut-ins all day.
I'm getting paid to do what I love.
-Picture this, Dewey...
-Not gonna happen.
Give me one good reason.
You're forcing me to say exactly
why I don't want to do this
and it's not going to make you happy
and it's not going to make me happy.
So why don't we just leave it alone?
How 'bout it, Malcolm?
You're gonna be out
of the house soon.
This could be our last chance to
spend some quality together time.
I can't, Dad.
You know it was Stevie's
big surgery yesterday.
They just moved him out of intensive
care and I really want to go visit him.
Damn!
See you tonight.
Mom, did you remember to buy
the baking soda for my class project?
Ah, I forgot.
What? I asked you like five times.
That I remember.
My science partner's
going to hate me.
I was supposed to bring in
the baking soda for a volcano.
Now it's just going to be
a mountain full of vinegar.
Just do what your brother did.
Take the baby powder and blame
the guy who brought the vinegar.
I'm glad you changed your
mind and decided to join me.
It's nice to know that at least one
of my sons isn't too busy to spend
a little time with the old man.
Oh, here, look.
The deck is real teak.
There's even a working foghorn. Listen.
Easy, it's not a toy.
You're sitting on my bench.
What?
That's my bench.
I don't think anybody owns
the benches, young man.
I'm sure you can...
find another one.
I don't want to find another one.
I always sit here.
Jamie, I'll handle this.
Kid, I didn't see you wiping off the
pigeon poop with your son's blankie.
I've earned this
bench so take a hike.
Okay, let's set her out there
and aim for the horizon.
She's in God's hands now.
Well... in mine.
Steady.
Steady as she goes.
Look at her.
She is yar.
Are you crazy?!
What do you think you're doing?!
I'm think I'm sinking your boat!
Ma'am, anyone who enjoys breathing
will benefit from the new Ionator 5150.
This amazing all natural purifier
has been proven to remove 63%...
...of all airborne pathogens
including asbestos,
cigarette smoke and
Taiwanese dust mites.
If you order now, we guarantee...
...you'll probably be dead by morning.
But you're right, buddy,
your life's not worth 50 bucks,
so please let me off the phone so I can
start saving people who want to live.
All right, fine, I'll put you down for two,
but next time, don't jerk me around.
How's everything going over here?
People are so stupid
they'll believe anything.
I threw the fact sheet out the window
and just started making stuff up.
Ah, no problem.
I made up the fact sheet.
Six sales in 20 minutes.
You're a natural.
Keep this up and you got a good
shot at winning the sales contest.
What contest?
We're tallying total sales
over on the big board.
First prize is a flat-screen TV.
Second prize is a barbecue grill.
Third prize is one of our air purifiers.
But believe me, you don't want that.
Keep up the good work.
Hello, I'm calling from
Air Scrub Air Filters.
No, no, no, don't
put Mommy on the phone.
Just get her credit card.
How was Stevie?
I didn't get to see him.
You left for the hospital
over three hours ago.
I tried taking the express bus,
but somehow I ended up
on a shuttle to the airport.
Seriously, they need to
label those things better.
They're bright red and say
"airport shuttle" on the side.
We drove right past the hospital, but
the stupid driver wouldn't let me out.
When did people stop caring?
Calm down, Malcolm. It's no
big deal. You can go tomorrow.
Yeah, if the buses will let me.
Hey, sweetie, how was your day?
I love this new job.
If you claim to be a doctor on the phone,
no one questions it, not even other doctors.
All right, would someone care
to explain something to me?
What?
Why is this sleeve slightly
shorter than this sleeve?
Maybe one of your
arms is getting longer.
They're not. I measured them.
That's crazy.
Oh, you'd like me to think so,
but I know someone has
been messing with my stuff.
The mirrors on my car are
askew, my toothbrush is wet,
and the lint trap in the dryer,
which I emptied this morning,
is now magically full of lint.
Should you even be doing
laundry in this condition?
I want to know who's responsible
and I want to know now.
Mom, why would we
do any of that to you?
Yeah, Mom, why would we?
Excuse me, what room
is Stevie Kenarban in?
Let me check.
He's in room 220
right up the elevator.
Thank you.
I was going to come
visit yesterday morning,
but I had this giant hole in my lunch
bag and everything just spilled out.
My tuna sandwich was fine,
but my orange started rolling down this
hill, and by the time I caught up with it,
I was late for school.
It's still room 220.
Where would it be
possible to find a gift?
I would try the gift shop.
Good idea. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Can I help you find something?
Yeah, do you have any cards
that don't say "Get well"?
This is a hospital. Usually,
we're rooting for the patient.
I get it, it's just that all these
cards are really generic.
And this is for my best friend,
so I need something special.
How about flowers?
I'm not asking him to marry me.
This bear's pretty popular.
Let's see.
He's allergic to the fur,
the stuffing plastic eyes.
And what's this tag made out of?
Okay...
Let's go with the hula guy.
You're sure?
Definitely.
So we've narrowed it
down to ten possibilities.
Let's go over the pros
and cons one more time.
Attention: It is now 9:00.
Visiting hours are over.
What?
I can't believe you
let this happen!
Reese is sales machine.
If he keeps up this pace, he's
going to win the whole thing.
Don't worry.
I gave him the list of people
that told us to go to hell.
Listen, we wouldn't be calling
again if it wasn't an emergency.
The utility company's informed
us that there's an alarming
amount of graydon in your home.
Now, your family's been
chosen to survive,
but your neighbors aren't
going to be so lucky.
Look, don't buy it from Air Scrub.
Buy it from one of our competitors.
I gave you the number, but
for the love of God hurry!
Happy Air, how may I help you?
And there isn't any kind of
construction or quarantines,
and you're not planning on moving
the hospital before I can get there?
Fine. Go take care of
your precious bus crash.
I want to make sure
I cover all my bases.
I got the directions,
I got a gift, his favorite cookies.
This time there's nothing that
can stop me from visiting Stevie.
There are very few things in this
world as valuable as friendship.
Damn.
What's wrong, Dad?
Nothing, I just put the
battery in backwards.
Oh, God. Why now?
I can't leave him like this.
I'm here for you, Dad.
I think I can handle it, Malcolm.
I just need to get a little
water out of the hull.
How'd that happen?
It's nothing.
Some punk kid swamped me.
And you're just gonna let
him get away with that?
It's no big deal. I'll just go
to another part of the lake.
Why? So he can sink you there, too?
You've to fight back.
What did you always teach me
about standing up for myself?
I can't beat up a ten-year-old.
I suppose I could hold him
down while you hit him.
No, Dad. Let's beat him on the water.
With just a few modifications,
we can make this boat unstoppable.
We can reinforce the rudder
for better steering and put
a titanium tip on the prow.
We'll slice his boat in half!
We can really do all that?
Absolutely.
Could we put a little
skipper on the deck?
I don't see why not.
Malcolm, it's times like these I'm
certain you weren't switched at birth.
Thanks, Dad.
Now come on. We got
a lot of work to do.
Cookie?
Oh, thank you.
Gotcha!
Sorry, Hal, I thought you
were someone else.
What are you doing?
How long have you been in there?
Just a few hours.
A few hours?!
What's going on?
I don't know, Hal.
I think one of the boys
is screwing with me.
My bookmark was on the wrong page.
I found a loose thread on my smock.
The car radio was tuned to a station
next to the one that I always listen to.
Oh, my God, I sound insane, don't I?
Honey, what you need is to take
a step back and clear your head.
You know what helps me?
Working with Malcolm
to weaponize my boat.
I understand you're very upset,
but if you'd just let me get a word in.
I know I'm the new guy, but you've
been on the phone for a half hour
and you haven't close this deal?
Remember your ABCs.
Always Be Selling.
I can't interrupt him when
he's in the middle of...
Hey, this isn't tele-listening.
Give me the phone.
I'll show you how to churn butter.
All right, gabby, we have better
things to do than talk to you all day.
Now, give me one reason why
you don't need an air purifier.
I'm going to kill myself.
Nice try.
I use that excuse all the time.
No, I'm serious.
I just feel like I can't go on.
I'm clinically depressed.
And my cat dies because
he was allergic to me!
Oh, and my wife rans off
with my brother Ted,
and then my family just touched
the inside that I'm not allowed to...
Get the manual!
All right, Dewey, I know what's
going on. I know it's you.
If it were Reese, he'd be
bragging to everyone about it.
Malcolm doesn't have the patience.
So, that leaves you, Dewey.
If I had any proof, we'd be having this
conversation while I was walling you
up inside your bedroom closet.
This is about the volcano, isn't it?
All right, I acknowledge that perhaps
I was a little inconsiderate of your needs,
but that in no way justifies
these petty attacks.
Still, we have to move on.
So, here's the deal:
In the future, I promise to be more
attentive and aware of your feelings,
not that being the loving mother I am,
I wouldn't be doing that anyway.
And in return,
you will promise to stop this
stupid campaign to drive me crazy.
Just give me a little sign that
we understand each other.
Good.
Now, just be cool, Malcolm.
As far as anyone knows, we're just a normal
father and son who love each other.
Stay calm.
There's a woman with a stroller.
Wave with me so it looks natural.
Good, she's buying it.
Arms down.
No one suspects a thing.
Steer clear of those ducks.
We'll deal with them later.
I hope this kid shows up soon.
I was planning on
visiting Stevie today.
You just saw him yesterday, didn't you?
Not exactly.
But you did see him
over the weekend, right?
No.
Wait.
How many times have
you seen Stevie?
If you add them all up...
none.
None?
Malcolm, I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Your best friend is in the hospital, and
you're here helping me stalk a ten-year-old.
I'm trying, but visiting someone in the
hospital isn't as easy as you might think.
Malcolm, don't you see
what you're doing?
You're just avoiding
an unpleasant situation.
I know.
It's just that Stevie and I have never
really talked seriously about his illnesses.
We've kind of had this
unspoken agreement that
he was just a regular kid.
If I had to see him lying
in his hospital bed,
hooked up to God knows what, it's kind
of hard to pretend like nothing's wrong.
I just don't know what to say.
Son, don't think about it.
Sometimes all you
have to say is hello.
That's a great way to put it.
So simple.
I got it off that
bus bench over there.
It's an ad for a
long-distance company.
You get yourself down to that hospital
and show Stevie that you give a damn.
-Thanks, Dad.
-All right.
It's high noon somewhere.
Not this time.
Oh, no! What am I
ever going to do?
What about this?
Say hello to my little friend!
Hey, you broke my boat!
It's that kind of
party, little man.
That was my grandad's boat.
He gave it to me
before he died.
He started it.
There just doesn't seem like
there's any reason to go on living.
I'm overweight, I don't
have any friends. I just...
Look, look, this is pointless.
I'm just gonna hang up now.
No one cares about me.
Listen, Lyle.
I'm as lost as you are.
I mean... I may not even
graduate high school.
I'm completely broke.
If I disappeared,
who would notice?
But now I've got a purpose.
Maybe you and I were
meant to talk today.
You mean like... like fate?
Exactly.
Maybe life is like
a roller coaster,
and you only go down so
you can fun coming back up.
Maybe.
Well, I... I actually
feel a little better.
Now, this is what I want you to do.
I want you to walk to the bathroom,
and I want to hear you flush
those pills down the toilet.
They're gone.
I-I did it.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you, Reese.
Thank you.
Don't thank me, Lyle.
This is all you.
You should feel good about
yourself for what you did today.
You should treat yourself
to something really nice.
Why don't you take out your credit
card and buy a dozen air purifiers.
Well, that... That sounds
a little expensive.
I just saved your life and
now you're questioning me?!
Look, I'm, I'm sorry.
I was just saying...
Every minute I'm talking to
you, the price is going up!
I want those numbers
now, do you hear me?
Let me find my wallet...
Just give him the damn TV.
Look who's in the hospital.
Stevie Kenarban.
What a surprise.
Well, if you think I came down
here to feel sorry for you,
you've got another think coming.
'Cause I didn't feel sorry for you
when they bolted your spine or
you got that mold on your brain,
and I'm not going to
feel sorry for you now.
Glad you didn't die.
See you when you get out.
Oh, and here's your cookie.
I told you... he'd come.
www.tvsubtitles.net