Yeah... what are those
kids complaining about?
Малкълм
7.10 - Парите на Малкълм
Synchronisation par Max & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
Четири, три, две...
кафяво...
ясно...
кафяво отново...
добре.
What about this watch, Dad?
Само за $12.99.
That's where they get you, son.
See, it says $12.99, but that
doesn't include the hidden costs.
Shipping, handling, box tops...
By the time you're through you're
paying on the high side of $15.
I've never owned a $15 watch.
Но на мен ми трябва едно, Татко!
Son, a cork and a piece of string
make a perfectly fine sundial
and a great conversation
piece with the ladies.
Malcolm, aren't you having your
yearbook picture taken today?
Да.
Well, don't you think it would be
nice to get a little dressed up for it?
Защо? Аз никога няма да отида
да видя тези хора отново.
They're just a bunch of shallow jerks
who don't care about anything but
who's instant-messaging who, and who's
going to the stupid Moonlight Dance.
A bunch of kids in formal clothes,
barefoot on the beach...
It's just pathetic.
And I wouldn't have gone
even if they told me about it.
Ето я твоята униформа, Рийс.
You're really lucky you got
your old job back again.
Lucky? They have me on the delivery
route, hauling stuff around all day.
At least when I worked in the slaughter
house, there were breaks every couple
of hours to find guys' fingers.
Hey, man, is my tie straight?
Yeah...
Wow, everyone's taking these
yearbook pictures pretty seriously, huh?
Are you kidding?
This is how everyone's going to
remember us for the rest of our lives.
Yeah, it's like a time capsule.
I mean, our children are going to
look at these pictures years from
now to see what we used to be like.
Isn't that right, sweetie?
Yes... yes, it is.
Чудесно.
Next!
Oh, another rebel, huh?
Какво?
I get it, kid. The T-shirt, the
scowl... you're a tough guy.
Ти си опасен.
I see that a lot with
you scrawny ones.
No, that's not...
Come on, Chachi,
let's get it over with.
I made a mistake.
I'd like to re-sched...
Take that, society.
Next!
Здрасти, Дюй. Как беше в училище?
Ужасно!
Аз изтървах автобуса за училище ,защото
I didn't know what time it was,
and then I was late for a spelling test
because I didn't know what time it was,
and then David Klausner beat me up
because I didn't know what time it was!
You want to know what
time it is, Dewey?
It's half past a roof over your head,
clean clothes, and three meals a day.
That's what time it is!
Let me tell you something, Mom.
The roof leaks, the clothes are
hand-me-downs, and the food stinks!
-Room!
-Dirty.
Това е интересно.
Our credit card company sent
us a collection notice and an
application for a new card.
Оооо, Боже мой!
Какво е това?
Това е чек за
Малкълм за $10,000!
Какво?!
You're joking!
No, no, no! It says it's from a
McClellan Fellowship Genius
Grant to further his education...
No strings attached!
I can't believe it!
This is fantastic!
Това е невероятно!
I've never seen so many zeroes on
that side of the decimal point!
Can you imagine what
he could do with that?
Imagine what anyone
could do with that!
Imagine what we
could do with that.
What are you talking about?
Нищо.
All I'm saying is that we can do
a lot with this kind of money.
-But it's not ours, Hal; it's Malcolm's.
-Of course, it's Malcolm's.
But we have to take a moment
to think about what a teenager
is going to do with $10,000.
Well, you know he's just going to
blow it all on Legos and penny candy.
Besides, it's not like Dr. Braniac. He
isn't gonna get a free ride to whatever
college he wants to go to, right?
I don't think I like
where this is going, Hal.
Lois, all I'm thinking
about is protecting Malcolm.
I mean, sure, he's got that brilliant mind,
but right now it is being held hostage
by gallons of crazy teenage hormones.
All I'm saying is maybe we should
hold onto this for a little while,
before we decide what to do with it.
Да, но Хел...
Thanks, Mom, for letting me go
to picture day dressed like this.
You made me look
like a total jackass!
It's not your picture;
you don't care what I look like.
Някакви съобщения за мен?
Не.
Geez, my feet are killing me.
I told you, you gotta let the
blood drip into your shoes.
Once it coagulates, then it's
like walking on puffy clouds.
Look at all these people, sitting
here, just waiting for death.
Yeah, I'd like to show those
animal rights whackos this place.
This is exactly what would
happen to cows if it wasn't for us.
Wait here. I'm gonna get
someone to sign for the delivery.
Thanks for beating Hitler.
Now we're gonna
watch something else.
Благодаря ти.
This is pretty sweet.
Man, it's true what they say
old age is wasted on the old.
Hal, there's nobody home.
We can't be too careful.
Meet me at the clothesline!
Виждаш ли, Хел?
Ти знаеш , че това е грешно.
You're acting like you
have something to hide!
What are you talking about?
Това е много хубав ден.
Since when is it a crime
to get some fresh air?
No, I thought about it,
and it is just wrong.
Ние трябва да върнем тези
пари обратно на Малкълм.
Besides, the check is made out to him.
The bank probably wouldn't even...
Put that away!
Не, изчакай, погледни ме отново!
Оооо, Боже господи.
No, we're not going to do this.
Honey, you are looking
at this all wrong.
We will pay him back.
We are like a bank.
And banks don't give you back the
same exact money that you gave them.
They use it, and then pay you back
with different money later on.
It's what makes our economy
the envy of the world.
I don't know.
It just seems wrong.
Look at it as a
forced savings plan.
We're actually
doing him a favor.
Lois, I can honestly say that I was
not a good father to Malcolm until
I forged his signature on that check.
And we're going to
pay him back, right?
Absolutely every cent we spend.
Plus interest.
With no hidden handling fees.
Окей.
Добре.
Honey, we have absolutely
nothing to be ashamed of here.
Окей, върне се
в къщи.
I'll follow in 30 seconds.
Go on!
Добре. Следващия!
Sorry, pal,
you had your chance.
Не! You have to take
my picture again!
Моля!
I thought I didn't care what
people think of me, but I do.
I really do!
Look, kid, I'm making 20 cents a head,
and re-shoots come out of my pocket.
That adds up to "I
don't give a crap."
Don't blame me that you're a no-talent
clown who couldn't even cut it at Sears!
I'm not going anywhere
until you take my picture!
Fine.
Да тръгваме.
Let's just get rid of
some of that shine.
What did you do?!
I look terrible!
It looks pretty good to me.
But that's just one
clown's opinion. Next!
Aren't you the
meat delivery guy?
What the hell are
you doing here?
I, um...
He's my grandson.
He's here visiting me.
Hi, Grandma.
It's great to see you.
You can drop the act, kid.
I haven't lost my marbles.
I just like seeing someone
have some fun around here.
Clothesline.
I got an estimate
for the new pipes!
Think of it, Hal clean
water, on demand,
the decision of hot or cold
water entirely up to us!
Yes, well, we could spend the
money on new pipes, or we
could put a down payment on her.
-Where did you get this?
-At the boat show.
Boat show?
Lois, I was on my way to work, when all
of a sudden I see this giant billboard
for the boat show, only 60 miles away!
Now I'm not saying there's
an invisible hand guiding our
lives, but what are the odds?
We're not wasting
the money on a boat.
It's not wasting,
it's investing!
A boat is a money-maker, Lois.
Do you know how many opportunities
we have missed out on because we
weren't traveling in the right circles?
Where are all the
connections being made,
the elbows being rubbed,
the deals going down?
-The yacht club!
-Forget it!
We're not spending
Malcolm's money on a boat.
That's final!
Lois...
You're looking at
this the wrong way.
It's not Malcolm's
money anymore.
Until we pay him
back, it's ours.
All right, maybe I was reaching
too far with the big one, but
just take a look at these...
Huh?
You can choose the Wave
Skimmer or the Weekender.
What do you think?
I like this one.
Unbelievable!
You know what's going on, Mom?
How could he do this to me?!
Malcolm, I know it looks bad,
but let me explain!
Don't try and stick
up for him, Mom.
Oh, Malcolm, I know he's
not perfect, but I love him.
You love my yearbook
photographer?
Да.
Well... maybe love is too strong a
word for it, but he does great work.
The guy's hired to take
good yearbook pictures!
Now my grandchildren are gonna
look at my photo in 50 years and
think that their grandfather was a dork!
Well, then I'm going to have to
rethink my feelings for him.
Здрасти?
Uh, yes.
'Ello, Guv'nor.
Майка ти в къщи ли си е?
Това е татко.
Хел?
Clothesline.
Какво прави той тук?
Той е вътре.
Какво?!
-How did...
-He just is!
Look, it's isn't important
how it happened. Let's just
move on with this, okay?
Look, Dewey, you understand
we're not stealing this money.
Every cent is going back
to Malcolm. We're a bank.
Yeah, well, this bank is
getting a Rolex. A big one.
That money is going towards
new pipes for the house!
She can spend her share
any way she wants.
And I'm spending my
share on a Rolex.
I think I've earned it.
There are no shares!
Listen to me!
We are not splitting
up that money!
Who put you in charge?
Yeah, who put you
in charge? Let's vote.
There will be no voting!
I vote there's voting.
Me, too.
-I'm going to get the money.
-It's not there anymore.
Аз ги преместих.
Аз знам.
Аз ги преместих
от където ти ги беше преместила.
И аз ги преместих отново.
Какво?
I was the one who came
up with this idea...
-The money is safe.
Give it!
And that...
is the French Tuck!
I don't know. It sounds to me like
he was asking to be beaten up.
That's what I said!
Just because you're a crossing
guard, you're suddenly off limits?
"Walk, don't walk..."
Who the hell is he
to boss me around?
It's nice to see someone
with a little spirit.
So many young people just
lie about the house,
just watching their
Miami Vice and MTV's.
Pie?
Това е чудесно.
I never knew old
people could be nice.
I thought you were all wrinkled
bags of skin babbling about
how stuff used to cost less.
No, some are like that, but there's a
few of us who still have some life left.
Who's the geezer?
Това е Теди.
Handsome, isn't he?
You want me to push
you over to him?
No, I don't think that
would be a good idea.
See, we're not allowed to
have romances around here.
It's as if they don't think we're
capable of having feelings anymore.
That is totally unfair!
I mean, as long as the two of
you can see each other naked
and still keep your lunches down,
you should be able to do
whatever it is you want to do.
Благодаря ти.
Okay, I alphabetized
all the seniors' names,
helped lug your equipment for
three days from here to your shop
and I held the lights for
those creepy photo shoots.
You have to take
another picture of me.
You held up your part of the bargain,
I'll hold up mine. Sit down.
Благодаря ти!
Chin to the left...
Square your shoulders...
Усмивка!
What did you do to me?!
I look like a freak!
Kid, that's you.
That's what you look like.
Аз не искам моите внуци
да ме виждат така!
Трябва да я оправите!
Put on a special filter,
or-or brighter lights...
Моля ,направете нещо!
Съжалявам , хлапе.
Това е най-доброто,което мога да направя.
Аз съм просто фотограф,
не магьосник.
Where have you been?
Училище.
That story better
hold up, Mister.
Your father wants to
count the money again.
I just think we all get along
better when we know it's all here.
By the way, I'm going
to need some of this.
I got an estimate to
fix my transmission.
This receipt is from 1986, Hal!
I can see where you erased the date!
Аматьор.
Oh, yeah? Well, how do I know
this plumber's for real, and not
just some actor that you hired?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I held auditions
while you were at work, Hal!
I knew it!
Listen to yourself!
You've gone insane!
That would be pretty convenient
for you, wouldn't it?
Well, you are not
locking me away!
I haven't trusted either
of you since I was six!
All right, all right,
let's just split it.
Three ways,
and we'll all be happy.
I wouldn't say happy,
but it's a start.
Аз имам по-добра идея.
We just stop this nonsense and
give the money back to Malcolm.
Okay, you can have your pipes.
No, Hal, this isn't
a bargaining tool.
This money has turned
us into animals.
I'm going down to the bank
tomorrow morning and getting
a cashier's check in Malcolm's name.
Then the three of us can
slink away and forget that this
whole thing ever happened.
Can't you control that woman?
Watch your tone, young man!
Or else what?
You'll just cave,
like you did with Mom.
All right, that's it!
Go to your room!
I think maybe we should
both go to our rooms.
Fine!
Code blue! Code blue!
I think some of these
are Viagra. Go for it.
What can we do to repay you?
Give me a five-minute head start.
Honey, we want to apologize.
Yeah.
You were right.
We were turning into monsters.
The bad kind.
You're just so much
stronger than we are.
Thank God for
your levelheadedness.
Thank God there was someone in this
house who was able to keep their sanity.
And you taught us a lot of
important lessons about...
honesty and trust.
Е...
if you'll just tell us
where you hid the money...
I've done something very bad.
Какво?
There was this antique store
across the street from the bank.
And I saw this
dollhouse in the window.
And the next thing I knew,
I was walking out with it.
It was like that money in my
pocket killed the old Lois
and replaced her with
a crazy person...
It's okay, honey. I mean...
So what if you spent a couple
hundred dollars on a dollhouse?
It's no big deal.
Now where's the
rest of the money?
There isn't any.
Какво?!
You-You spent ten thousand
dollars on a stupid dollhouse?!
They wanted 12.
Но виж, Хел...
it has a tiny little dumbwaiter,
and the lights really work.
Здрасти, Джудит.
Оооо, здравей, Рийс.
Аз искам да ти благодаря много
за всичко,което направи за мен.
It felt good to do something
nice for a change.
I'm seriously thinking about
peppering that into my repertoire.
Are you the one who helped Judith
and Teddy get together yesterday?
Yes, I am, and
I would do it again.
Твоите правила са глупави.
I mean, who does it hurt to
let two old people be happy?
You whore!
You stole my husband!
No, I just used him without your
permission and gave him back to you...
Just like someone did
with my sewing machine.
Look at her.
I couldn't say no!
How can you say no to that?
Oh, shut up, you old fool!
Wait! I can fix this!
Just get back at him by
sleeping with someone else!
How about him?
When he has his teeth in,
he's quite the looker!
Okay, I sold my car.
Well, we'll add that to what
I got for my engagement ring
and my grandmother's pearls.
No one wanted to buy my bike,
but a bunch of kids did pay
to watch me eat a centipede.
We're doing the right thing.
We should all remember that.
Quit sermonizing.
I'll get enough of that from
the nut-jobs on the bus.
You guys aren't
gonna believe it!
Аз съм полочил от Маклийн
$3,857!
Това е чудесно, Малкълм!
Поздравления, сине.
Да, поздравления.
This couldn't have
come at a better time!
I know exactly what
I'm gonna do with it!
*Beverly Hills*
*That's where I want to play*
*Living in Beverly Hills*
Let's see them call
me a dork now.
www.tvsubtitles.net