Ch the boys, you see what I have?
It's a movie that we had
zwróciæ three weeks ago.
And what if we would
obejrzeæ it again?
I have found it in the dishwasher.
Twenty one days
2.99 times per day is ...
- 62.79.
- What?
How much time do you take
They will learn responsibility?
Not so przeœlizgiwaæ
for the entire e force.
Sooner or later
You will learn ...
/ Today is already tenth you?
/ Malcolm in the Middle 4x14
/ Hal's Friend
/ T of the interpreter of hearing: Harry_man
/ Correction: polishchaser1
My mother lives with her sister of the month,
c the rest because you ¹ ¿y
In the meantime, there is a house were chaos
but we have learned the nieŸle the radziæ.
- Can I Insert from glass?
- Do not. Anything that needs washing.
All right, clean up the tajmy the table.
I talked with have the Zesz of the former evening,
I miss you very much for the bear and has a long return to the house.
- How long the bear?
- A couple of weeks.
Oh, and Reese - wanted to and, after returning ¿ebyœ
the schools were of the list will sweep the garage u
What? But today is the only day,
Alison when parents are not at home, ..
¿Eby us not Disturb
with homework.
- Reese, your mother ...
- It's not all right.
Mom can not we kontrolowaæ,
when she's not here.
Your mother does not control anyone.
For example, I invite
old friend tonight
and it also will not be the wspominaæ
your mother does not mean I'm also controlled.
I repeat - your mother
never know about it.
And you boys the boys downright
'll love Larry.
In high school we were inseparable of the swelling.
And on the whole quite seriously not - your mother
can not fail for dowiedzieæ, also it was to this house.
- Dad, it hurts.
- I'm sorry.
Malcolm, Stevie.
Good morning, Mrs. Hooper.
To see if any of you hooligans,
know where is my son, Dabney?
No, the release of up to W-F'u.
What a properly on his release?
This allergic reaction
gluten, whey, b are each air.
I suppose zjawicie up
Dabney at a birthday today?
Sure.
I just want to remind ...
¿I do not want to come out of jakimiœ ebyœcie punk
hairstyles, or in sloppy clothes.
/ What do you do on the pavement?
He says the I, also have a walk perfectly well
the lawn.
But there is a second guest of,
who does not want it ¿ebym of the lawn.
- Well, so much like sidewalks?
- The entire shot him!
My God!
Dabney! Come on, hurry!
Do you make are for the EOE eye contact
with the big boy of Caucasian teenage boy?
When you are in Danger
you ¹ æ crouched up and skuliæ up.
Kuca of em, but he did not
I will let the skuliæ.
/ "The Teapot Song"
/ I have the white pot, low i ..
/ This is my hand nipple, my ...
/ When I start parowaæ, will hear ...
/ Slope me and fill ...
Answer.
Hello?
/ Hello! It is recorded The message
/ Finance from the fund ...
Part of Mom.
/ - Congratulations ...
/ - You all right.
OK, I'll ask him.
Mom wants Know-or will sweep the EOE the list of garages in?
In precisely does this.
Piama to ring a
As he reached precisely were the Tuscon entire email and healthy.
Tucson, a city that never
not asleep.
They feel sure that the bed had were the
so the œwietn the fun, but we were so ¿e
Sami guys.
- Where are your things Otto Daae?
- Zanieœ it to the room of Francis.
What?
Gretchen left a note and t are for you.
Wait, why he carries
your stuff to my room?
Because staying with you for the weekend.
I do not sleep the same in of bed to the jakiœ 35 years.
Do you want to break loose in my of bed for?
With me?
It would be the bezczelnoœci
prosiæ of the guests.
Do not forget to zmieœæ of leaves from the roof,
I'm upset because the women c ¹ ¹.
Who cares that the œlisko is wet,
roof must be clean, because I'm g of silly.
You get it.
Hello?
- Part Mom.
- I do not say the about her.
What does "Mom"? It's me Francis.
Sends the EOE me a text message?
Yes, Reese is here.
I'll tell him mom, but do you really
can not break loose AEOI through the whole night?
And can Repair the morrow my bike?
In a properly you're right. Saturday morning
it is best to ride in ¿d tablespoon.
/ Okay,
Now I get it.
/ B-governments to him the gracious,
're from the large o m the wiser.
I must koñczyæ.
This is the floor is so cold.
Already we jump into the heat that blankets.
It is a little strange.
I do not sleep with a colleague of the three classes of primary school.
That was the home of Jeffrey Feldman
and his mom ...
Otto, what the hell are you doing?
I know, I know. I'm notorious
kocowym hamster.
- Otto!
- Excuse me, cold feet.
/ Urgent!
/ Read Immediately!
Look, It can, my already Continuous ówkê.
/ Lift the terrible Rot t the
/ For me!
- Can we open presents now?
- Yes, I can?
Yes, but slowly - you do not want
æ incurring of paper, right?
Oh, but œwietna event.
This is twice as much Guests' than the last.
I can open the first
a gift from his grandfather, mother?
At least you'll have
is behind the.
- XJ ... 7000
- Super.
- What is it?
- This paintball gun.
The best I can to Buy.
- I'll take that.
- But, Mom!
When your grandfather bezmyœlny
will learn
These gifts also are not doing anything
outside stimulation you.
And when the so-called fun ends
You're a whole were red and were cheerful and until 21 o'clock.
Not this time.
Give it to mommy.
Never mind.
I just did not know how it would have the malowaæ.
Can open one
of my gifts?
New brush of hair.
Thanks, Mom.
Can'll try?
Sure.
Count down from 100
You can store help cool the boys.
Sto ...
Dziewiêædziesi the dziewiêæ t ...
Dziewiêædziesi the-eight ...
Dziewiêædziesi-seven ...
Already is.
Part, big asshole!
It's just you Haggerty
of recycled and our podjeŸdzie.
Why a properly mom does not want
¿We meet the ebyœ this Larry?
Thoughts also he has with the s influence.
You know my mother likes wyolbrzymiaæ things.
As with our œlubem.
Well, opuœci the ceremony,
but by the time the two of the hot ...
In a properly it were example.
One time on the moor,
where we ...
No, this is ¿is poor.
Oh, I got one!
Our families were far
to the same churches of a ..
You know the mother. Just zmyœla
Debt different things.
Already is, Dewey!
Test included!
Larry!
Hal, man.
Appearance You look terrible.
You are ¿buddy, wchodŸ.
Ch of boys, meet Larry Ross.
These are my sons.
This Reese and Dewey.
Malcolm's birthday party.
So goes the supervision of EOE - good yours.
By the way - are heard the I, also should be
to speak well of the above, even if it was to a ..
No, no, no.
Continuous ¿'m still married to Lois.
Ah, seriously is not it?
This œwietnie old, it œwietnie.
- You know, there is a bar were a piece of st the d ..
- Easy, is out of town for some time.
Bosco, the first beer 19:04.
One of the boys should save it.
Is the camera is not œwietny?
/ This night is for me something new.
/ The first psychological trauma,
/ Not caused by my the mother.
/ But can I zrobiæ of many
/ For what you do to me the.
/ I mean, he and Gretchen were just amazing.
/ Gretchen ...
/ I wonder what was to on this note?
They had the tractor rozebraæ a piece of the slice to,
¿Eby wydostaæ it staffroom.
But you never let me release the EOE.
What happened on?
Look at me.
Mean age, poor work, is of a hovel.
Barely cope with the children,
that I have, and the next one is on the way.
Not the shot, man.
The only reason
screwing up is
Also society at large does not tolerate
freelancers like us.
This is the price and the avoided the semi-
for being avant-garde.
Do you remember how Dawkins
nabi of us in the bottle?
- Who?
- Dawkins.
Our chef of the restaurant Carmello.
Do you remember the high school classes,
Public holidays Labor day?
Spêdziliœmy whole day on the equipment Tania
flooded the kitchen, and we will do it for the $ 200.
Wait! Yes!
- Unbelievable.
- 200 bucks.
If we were counted per cent
for all these years ...
tarzalibyœmy in forsie.
If I had the now is the money,
Such use would the pozwoliæ in a small room for a child.
Thanks a lot, Dawkins!
Want a small room, Hal?
Sami can we go zrobiæ.
I have a license of a construction worker.
We can add it to the bedroom
¿without any problem.
- What?
- Wywalisz t the wall, the rest of you extend ...
and all of the lowest-est cost.
- No, the men chose to manage this.
- Not fair from the baby, Hal.
- I know ...
- Come on, "eye of the tiger".
We create your own risk the future of.
Well, you know ... we are doing as we can.
Everything will be all right as long as ...
Oh, my God also?
Now I can see involvement,
Let's get to work.
Larry, I can not believe it!
³ I will invite you for a few beers,
and you're going to fire the EOE hole in my wall?
It's precisely because we saw no up
with each other for so many ...
This is were the stick will do something like this?
It is œwietne.
Wait until Lois sees it.
Dad?
I do not know what he will do the above Zesz the night,
but there is no hot water,
and the toilet is not full of dust.
Dewey, the father wakes up before dinner,
Tell him I'm also in Dabney.
/ Good evening ...
Yes, Mom, my Insert the church will be under the window,
and Reese's wardrobe - just as he would Did you come.
This is ridiculous.
Never sentence ¹ ¿we aim for the movie.
He's moving fast
as I can.
Œwietnie the robot doing his mom,
may he rest Daae powinnaœ the æ?
Thanks to Dewey.
You're a good brother.
And he said that the no.
Do not you find it strange
Also your mom is continuously calling
¿Ebyœ performed the task Dewey,
repair of his bike,
or transfer of the furniture?
- What are you trying to tell?
- I think it's obvious?
¿I want to do the things ebyœ for Dewey.
- If she want with her are the porozmawiaæ ...
- Honestly says the c - yes.
Hello?
Good morning lady also.
Thank you, but I must Know-,
time it is.
Wait, please listen to me the statue.
Please listen to me!
- Forget it, with her can not be the rozmawiaæ.
- Good-bye .... Good morning.
Wow, she is me and the
and naughty at the same time.
Caution!
Do not move, Mom,
This is a difficult place.
Dabney, you open,
I'm going to shower.
If the Thompson tell them
Also get the cat out of the back,
when will switch the car.
Part of Malcolm.
- Where is your mother?
- In the shower.
It's good. I'll be so there must have had to
laksygenu add to her tea.
They met with Stevie
paintball for the hour.
Malcolm, I can not AEOI.
We test the machines have to deal with the
movie night in pi ¿amach.
Dabney, the grandfather will give you the
amazing gun and have it to use.
Listen to Malcolm. I know that carefully ck
my dude ...
No! Maminsynkowie œmiej the up
You're with their mothers.
Come on. ³ I saw your eyes,
when you open the EOE.
Admit it - you can not up doczekaæ,
It can try the ¿Eby.
You just need to relieve
from his mother
Malcolm, you do not understand.
Exactly 17 minutes
my mom comes out of the shower,
expect the c me with a warm,
fluffy towels.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, my God also?
Damn it, Larry!
Suggest, Suggest ...
How can you blame the boy zwaliæ the packaging.
Good morning ¿Niczko accounting.
Larry!
What myœmy done!?
Succeeded in zrobiæ me out of my hovel,
Bigger even ruder.
- Yeah, we have a lot to do here.
- ¯ ebyœ knew he was also there!
We have more important matters.
With the deposit we aim visit from an old
Friend Dawkins.
- What?
- I'll do the have the e œledztwo than Zesz the night.
It turns out that they lived in a place
Carlson'a called settlement.
Housing part of the Young man!
Can you believe it?
He lives in a luxurious place,
and you ... do not even have walls.
- We'll get this guy.
- Larry, we need to Repair the!
It? This is nothing.
Two days made up
Pour the foundation here
a little electrical ...
Insert the front window, over.
And now let's get Dawkins.
Right.
Somebody get up early on today of the of bed.
This, Gretchen and I left a note
and I can not it anywhere znaleŸæ.
S I think that the concerns and that your
nocturnal attacks of violence.
What are you talking about?
I do not speak German horror ¿salty,
but had to have jakieœ EOE terrible nightmares.
This is bullshit, I've never œniê.
- What?
- I do not œniê.
IDE break loose and eight hours later I wake up
with a slight sore throat and, like everyone else.
Shouted; EOE hours.
I I think that was you had the EOE of the bad dream,
but do not worry, because I know exactly what Initial æ.
I'll give you massages with oil
before pójœciem to bed every ...
and the spa will be like a baby.
- We will œwietnie!
When you jump the fence,
I'll take care of the dogs, and you're on camera.
He lives in a residential camper.
This rich residential camper.
Look at this one bedroom.
You do not have the trailer.
Okay, commando mode.
Of steal trailer
and try to inputs at the point where the grease, paint is.
What's going on?
- Larry, Hal?
- Mr. Dawkins, is that you?
What of a surprise to me.
Œmia of the wchodŸcie in precisely insert the em for tea.
Stevie, shielding aniaj less.
I am glad to be attracted by tugging the Dabney of em here.
This is precisely what he needs.
- Is now I'm dead already?
- In the game, you are.
Dabney, just shoot him.
Do not shoot and do not move.
We're going for more ammunition.
Come on!
You strzelaæ.
Need to do this.
Mama mia ³ a're right.
I should now siedzieæ at home
and viewing the Daae "Dark Victory".
You fighting |.
Just pull the the trigger!
But can arise æ ¹
adverse consequences.
This talk your mother,
just shoot!
If you want to uchodziæ a guy
Shoot now!
Walk!
She brush your damn hair in the!
Sam Wey wearing their g of stupid towel!
100 .. 99 .. 98 .. 97 ..
I choose ... ¿second YnE Dubney'a.
The tea is delicious.
I would like you zaoferowaæ is more,
but mobile store with food
jeŸdzi now only twice a week.
That is enough.
He was such a gentleman ... I ³ y
Did I can about something you spytaæ?
We talked to Larry about the old days
in the restaurant and wspomnieliœmy about Labor Day ...
Oh, you mean day
where zalaliœcie kitchen.
Undercut the Galio up
the tube from the water.
Well, yes! We zawaliliœmy.
- Larry, also thinking he's right.
- Mr. Slocumb Daae did not want to pay out to you.
But I pass the checks to your fathers.
O is for me the release of for it, but ...
Post the pi of a properly em.
That was a instructive hands.
We now know that the our
incarnation of the shortcomings and is ê ¿³ ny old man,
have lived on the estate camper months,
which will give us the bird feeder.
I hope that both
czegoœ themselves have learned
Oh, yes.
What is wrong with you are wrong,
dammit!
"Eye of the Tiger", Hal.
/ Larry? Hal?
/ Is there nothing you will not fixed at, ch the boys?
Yes, Mom. In the end precisely kopaæ
This underground fort, who wanted Did you come.
I think that it will be
bawiæ well.
Give it to me.
Do not tell me darling, just Listen to.
Did you come to Mia're right.
You're always right.
From now on, I will always do the
whatever you say,
I am szczêœliwszy
bezmyœlnie succumbing to the c ones
than taking any something, but it seems to me that he wanted ¿
with my so-called friends of me.
I love you, I miss you are.
I give Dewey.
In truth, Mom?
¿Do you want the burden of ebym Rees in the hair?
But he loves her in the hair.
No good.
This is not fair!
- Let's get it already with g halfway.
- Mohawks look-up were already out of fashion, mom. And can e ..
Is hearing a strange call, Mom?
You're already dead!
The last thing I remember
he shoot the bullets months in my nose.
All right. So let's say,
Also of it at that.
Where is my baby the baby boy!
What zrobiliœcie of my poor, gentle boy of Caucasian teenage boy?
Oh, my God also?
It's your fault,
You devil's droppings.
He knew am also not supposed pozwalaæ
Dabney'owi have the friends.
- Dabney ...
- PrzyprowadŸ car!
We're going home.
Dabney ... Never so
I do not refer to the EOE.
Better get used, because I'm already
you have the white boys of opczykiem, Mom.
I'm your husband is the white of men are.
Ooops.
Dear Francis. To powstrzymaæ nightmares Otta,
just massage the semi-petal its Ohrläppchen. Gretchen.
His Ohrläppchen?
Please, please, please ...
Thank you.
www.tvsubtitles.net