Give Reese'owi a piece of the grubby hand,
I will not say a word.
For the facilitated.
/ Crazy world of Malcolm 4x05
/ Forwards Backwards
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
You have a fat notebook.
I do not believe that the already buying a new one.
Are you sure that the your dad
sell it to me for 300 bucks?
Minus 10 percent ... for me.
The six months of ¿Erania up with the children,
you do not even want the image of g æ ¹ ³ s football helmets.
As soon as I get the money
birthday, will be mine.
You got ... the money ... in the book ¿ce?
Yes. This is the only place
that no one in the family will not work.
I saw the EOE brother somewhere?
He was ...
You ... g of silly .. dung.
EOE Podbi of my eye, you moron.
Ignition acisz me for it.
There's nothing pays ignition.
You have the skoñczyæ.
I have a fairly your fights,
especially you become the more sense.
- Close hose extensions up your birthday.
- I want only money.
If you want to dostaæ anything
you he did not rip the ACAA.
I do not care who he ¹ ³.
Ends with you.
- But he ... -For you!
Let him be the last,
who inflicted the blow?
Yes, let.
And now both zejdŸcie my eyes.
Well ... for the facilitated.
Fighting | as if nothing had happened
before my eyes.
What a man possessed of these two the boys?
Help!
It will help me.
I'll help.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Today's the birthday of my son
and I wanted to him to Buy comic.
He asks the same of the money, but he loves comic books,
¿And what kind of birthday party, when there is nothing to unpacking.
Do you work here?
I Checks the fleet.
It œwietnie.
So, have you suggest something?
Something cool for max $ 20?
If you are looking for comics for 20 bucks
you should to Buy Mr. Incredible.
- I do not think would be the ready.
- And for only 20 bucks!
Reason've lost the EOE?
Shut up.
Tell me about it.
No. Well, it is unbelievable.
By day, the stars of the rock,
and a superhero by night.
Can strzelaæ p sight of the flames
and topiæ brains of the enemy forces of mind u
Yes. I think I read of it.
Mr. Incredible does not exist.
If so, why ...
Œródziemiañstwo is for customers
sufficiently advanced to what doceniæ
cinema the dash and the non-linear story.
I consider the appearance of the day
Mr. typical shirt office
Also you are not A serious
collector of literature drawn.
- There is already a new Metamorpho?
- Yes, Ricky, already serve. Wait a minute.
- I was to em ...
- Excuse me ...
Helping the client.
- It's my costume?
- What costume?
The school play.
I play in the school!
That's right.
You play ... tree?
I play Abraham Lincoln!
Recites a speech from Gettysburg.
Why is it always happens to me?
Calm down.
I always manage to
Insert the sentence at the time, right?
Do you remember this costume Frankenstein
which as we all like the?
- Yes.
- We can u Insert it again?
Otto, I think we have around
jakichœ vandals, or something like that.
MORE overturned semi-hammers
and for this a few chickens did not is alive.
-Looking as if someone
locatio of them to death.
/ Devil Cow
/ ... Return of a
It's just doing the wind.
But hen-looking,
explode as if the y
Probably with the broken semi-ot przefrun ¹ ³
to the other side ranch
hitting the c in chickens with a vengeance and trawl the c them on the ground
in a manner very similar to mine.
You see, for all
perfectly logical explanation.
/ Devil cow, and it was to her doing!
Perfectly logical.
- Did he say the "devil's cow?"
- It's just a silly g of legend.
They say the that the number of years ago, a cow
try the meat and a human constant and up to the a
And always when accounting underperformance
becomes red,
comes with a den in the mountains,
The five that the blood of the innocent.
- You're talking about a cow.
- Yes, I know. Germans are dre, right?
- River in Obuda up.
- What do you want?
I just want to tell that the final blow
will not be and must be of you.
I have a fairly that they always have an advantage
because you're the idiot, and I was the wise and understand the consequences.
I can be just as fierce
and short-sighted as you.
Sure.
Already scared.
You can also just ...
- What will the EOE?
- Discount ¿y ³ em up to your level.
And I must tell,
Also like it.
- How about purchasing has gone through the comics?
- You wrong.
Lose ground at their feet.
S ³ Look, we both hope we had,
Also it does not happen,
- But we have of doing this.
- Hal obiecaliœmy myself also do not do.
And we have another choice?
Interesting to, not it?
Again, I am the only person ¹ ¹,
who is able to help you.
I'm your best friend,
your answer when you need the post office,
or siedzieæ the case, but when you do the grill
if I can I just looking at the Daae out of the car.
I have to tell you, Hal,
Also that beer tastes better.
I'll take another one.
- It will help me can or not?
- I'll help.
But one day,
and that day may never nadejœæ,
I can poprosiæ you
byœ us is used of me somehow something.
So really it will be tomorrow.
I'll be here approximately a tenth of this, and if you answer,
Put on the costume angle swimsuit.
What? What happened on?
- This is terrible.
- What rug?
This is not a rug.
It ... antelope.
Oh, my God also?
- It was a completely solv of the flattened.
- Look at this. The slices are on the tree.
- What can the zrobiæ about something like that?
- That was I myself.
- You?
- Yes.
My moped.
Scary accident.
He was the dark.
The pop and straight in front of me.
³ I probably enjoy a much
Cajun Martini.
This should be lesson
for all of us, huh?
Bring the abbot and a little sawdust.
Do not move now.
I guess I do not want to play in the play.
I read a little bit and the Lincoln was not the
too good a part of the human being.
Did you know that the declaration of the abolition of slavery
that of a purely political movement?
It makes me nervous, because I had never previously
says nothing of EoE in the show.
Nor do they move up the EOE.
For me the continuity's sake!
Suspend the right of habeas corpus in Maryland.
You should be the widzieæ Reese.
Wpad the hysterical.
Are you sure .. Also want to ...
zadrzeæ with him?
This is the only way to dotrzeæ
to its primitive is the Piego Brain.
Know-It must, fail for not Ugne.
What is it?
/ MALCOLM WORKS OF IDEAS £ EM
Oh, my God also?
If you can be fierce,
I may be m the dry.
- How much does a copy of EoE?
- I do not know.
How many copies of a 500-sheet pack?
This is not the end, Reese.
I do not know why
so nervous.
Look how he bravely doing the EOE.
Okay, two spit book, with undulating toffee.
Do you now go to a comic book store?
Patience, Luke.
Lekkomyœlny are.
We were at the movies, we were on the beach ¿y
Lay the stuffed animal em for you
the koœcielnym bazaar.
Zrobiliœmy coffee break, lunch,
Sheikh fruit cake.
Really, I negocjowaæ until all cylinders
do not operate at maximum capacity remaining.
And if you have a cylinder?
- ZjedŸ aside.
- No, you're right. Sorry.
- That was the unfair attention.
- Stop.
- Do not Stop, Craig.
- Wypuœæ me out of the car.
Craig, do not stop.
All right. Calm down.
You will need to nauczyæ up
Proceed as with Craig Feldspar.
Duck please.
Get out hence the d I'm busy.
I will summarize the.
You know, when I breaks of all the leaflets
³ em, meditating on how you rip the ACIA.
I started ¹ ³ em up zastanawiaæ.
What's this?
Choæbym do not know how old the
Nothing will stop them.
Can're better at it than I am.
That's right.
Can that we should zapytaæ your
friends of what do the judging.
- What?
- Of your friends.
They're your friends, right?
I always happen to them shooting,
and although the in the vicinity of u
To see if any of you
knows the name of this kid?
This here.
Któryœ know her name?
But it is always behind you.
Never previously did not notice We have paid close?
So cami month of hanging out near you
go the c your friend?
This is just sad.
Well, the first name is Reese.
And guess what?
I'm better at it.
He won em. It's over.
Gretchen?
Gretchen, I'm ...
- Otto, huh?
- I've seen of the I j, Francis.
The devil's cow.
I saw of her eyes,
tl fumes unmatched as the Company.
A breath of czeluœci as hell.
- This is terrible.
- Heinous than that?
We exit the place.
Spaliæ on the ash.
¹ æ start from the beginning
No. Scoop out the disguise of a
There will be uciekaæ before the cows.
- No?
- No, it will not.
From now on ... We do not tolerate lactose.
Here's your costume Dewey.
Dad and I watch you today
on the south in the show.
I'll be the vomit.
What if I forget
jakiejœ matter?
What if something fall out of my nose,
as if the "will show and tell"?
Dewey, I'll tell you a secret.
When you're on stage, you just have to
patrzeæ the first row of the d
Your dad and I will be there siedzieæ,
And you look at me and understand,
Also all will be well.
All right?
And if are still being collected will of the
You like vomiting scroll with hat.
/ Reese making the most of this veil is used the.
I will not ... the steamed up.
Not serious, humiliation is the only thing
which speaks to the Pacana.
- All right.
- Why did you take his side?!
Birthday card.
Piea Canadian dollars.
NieŸle as the grandmother.
Rest of the money they got for my birthday on Saturday,
So I can Daae you 300 bucks for a computer when ...
"Dear Malcolm, ha ha.
"Now I've won the.
Your friend, Reese. "
Os judging you ... as grown-ego!
And yes, I'm looking of a serious literature drawn,
the cartoon of the cinema and the linear story.
- There was the gentleman already here someday?
- No, I ...
Well, Listen to FIG.
I just want to Buy a present for his son, you know?
That's not a crime.
Because my only crime
is not so large as to know how yours.
I think we all have parents, right?
I appeal to you as the decent of a man,
byœ helped me uszczêœliwiæ the son on his birthday.
I'm sorry, man.
I think that we started poorly.
All men chose zaczynaliœmy.
This one is called "Dead Man's Shoes".
It costs 50 bucks.
He talks about alienation.
I think that will appeal to your son.
Thank you.
Not so fast.
This transaction does not concern you, Feldspar.
This is Craig Feldspar.
It has a 45 level dungeon master.
Which box of each semi-flakes
sn is the shaking of the EOE, Dean?
It is however the first ad.
Has the value of collectible.
Can that we should check in "Overstreet"?
Wait, we do not.
In 1997, the first and only imposing the ad.
50,000 phrases, all of which he appears y
He holds the'd go in the bathroom,
but not for reading.
This is not a comic book store.
This shop novelties!
Really?
I would like to view the store with the latest,
May where the original 14th issue of Spider-Man-and
with the first appearance of the Green Goblin.
¯ kidding.
If you were to change the tone to a more attentive
I will allow you the ...
What are you doing!
Do not be afraid.
This reprint of 1993.
If it were to the originals,
the shielding they would go in the body I own.
Dude, You said to me,
Also it was to the original.
And now ... Let's talk about business.
Craig, I am so very grateful to you.
That was a fantastic!
He was a heroic EOE.
I Like myœleæ, ¿¿that each one of us
has some of Aquaman.
I must admit that the the truth
You know about that.
I am impressed by inserting.
Well, you know ... if you're interested
On Saturday, the reunion ...
I have my own force, Craig.
/ Car number 15, without bumping please.
/ Powróæ to refuel zone.
- What are you doing?
- He had no right of EOE!
The EoE I stole it!
That was my s the money!
No good. Let's see.
I test drove the 63 lap.
Keep the change.
/ Eighth car, so uprzejmoœci.
It's over here, Reese!
Do not care about the me the money!
I do not care about the birthday!
Do not care about me,
or your safety!
I do not care nothing
the task except for those suffering!
These ¿I do not care!
Good! Let's see who
cares the least!
/ We lost two weeks
/ Right prosecuting themselves.
This cockfights Reese did not win!
I'm too furious to odpuœciæ were!
When you see my face you'll know the ³
Also use and no chance!
/ They started and already the momentum the car on the track
(Song from "Speed ??Racer'a")
/ Pushes pedal to the metal like crazy
/ Adventure awaits him ...
Stop.
I know you will.
This may not be of such a good ...
Should tell your doctor,
Eby ¿³ przyszy you fur and tails,
because we are animals!
Except that the deposit was to would find it easier,
because we would be castrated.
Everything boils down to this,
Also have a back gate.
Thanks for making easier for me
barrier on my birthday.
- I've got the gate on my birthday.
- Weapons of em just my point.
You know, there is something like this,
as sprawiedliwoœæ.
- It is something like "mug in the pail."
- Stop it.
Malcolm, I remember what he was doing the EOE
in the round of last your birthday?
- Nothing. These ¿³ I had detention.
- And you, on your birthday?
Did you come to give me detention, after
as the General ¹ ³ ¹ I face Malcolm in the cake.
- A previous birthday yet?
- Roughly the same thing.
Wait a minute.
When you are pushed me hello yet with pony?
Do you realize that the none of you
did not have the whole force that birthday party!
There are brings them, also it's sad!
Each striving for a bit of a chance szczêœcia,
something a little bit remove the Switch On - squandered.
And at this point it must skoñczyæ.
Revenge is not worth it?
Now do you think so?
We are happy?
There is no reason to mutual rivalry.
We love you just the same.
In this family no pets.
Where's Dewey?
He told the am "Here Mr. Lincoln".
I love you, Dewey.
You can do it, son.
We are proud of you.
/ A few years ago, and eighty-seven
/ Our fathers on the continent
/ Dali beginning of the nation,
/ Unborn of freedom
I believe ...
/ ... For the nation and for the nation
/ There will disappear with us
/ From the earth's surface.
You know, Daniel is ¿³ and give to the Council
so if your romance is not scared of her.
Way to go. Can ykniesz of the
another one?
Francis, this is no time
to study animal husbandry are t
- We have to kill the cow.
- There must be something here, what you will help e
You know you will help us?
Kula.
The sphere is the answer to everything.
Oh my God, is here!
That's it!
I know what we zrobiæ!
Francis!
No, please, no!
No!
All right, Bessie.
Narobi Did you come to us a lot of troubles k,
And it has just skoñczyæ.
You will be milked.
There you go.
Did you come to these mountains as long, saturated.
It is not surprising that the nervous Did you come.
No, you're not out of the a
You're just in excess of the cow milk.
Well, this new game is good,
but it is too small for that udobruchaæ me.
Still ¹ ¿¿s not close up the EOE
to my expectations.
And what he said byœ the comic Malcolm?
Zapominaæ start of the case.
- Happy birthday, Malcolm.
- Thanks.
Do not eat the berries.
He left the j I afford then.
What can fail become?
www.tvsubtitles.net