Yes!
He won em!
He won em, finally
I beat you in the video game!
In your face, Malcolm!
In your face!
Dad, Dad!
In this game you zdobyæ,
the least points.
Fine of the game.
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x12 "Kicked out of the house"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.6 MB
/ - Come on!
/ - Never!
Now, loads a colorful,
and later the White e
How do you jakieœ clothes ...
Craig comes every day and helps us
fault ever since leaving for the mother and her sister.
After two weeks of oriented to
Also no one asks the.
Tata now the government today.
Wariowaæ stop and eat supper.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Stop!
From now on, there is zero tolerance!
S ³ yszeliœcie, zero tolerance!
You nauczyæ up zachowywaæ!
From now on ...
Who wants to dock the bookmark macaroni and cheese?
Fairly it!
Sit down!
/ The fact that we are not here does not mean
/ Also You can store up poorly zachowywaæ!
When I'm talking zero tolerance,
I mean is zero tolerance!
Tolerance decreases to zero!
I mean emptiness, nothing,
no ... tolerance!
- The receipt.
- Malcolm!
- Hello?
- We are now a call!
This Stevie needs
help with the math.
The Ides!
/ Say something about mathematics,
/ But unfortunately I do not understand :)
You can not continuously at me dzwoniæ!
It has the am, you also receive first.
If the parents domyœl in
Also are still being meet,
I get a gate and already
never met.
I know it is difficult,
but we need to be more carefully than.
I'm bored. And my
Dad will not be a while.
For a while to come.
/ Okay, fairly it!
/ Vicki Lawrence - "The Night the Lights Went Out in Georgia"
/ This is the night, in which
/ Hanged innocent of human
/ Do not trust the coming Cemu
/ Of the South after the lawyer
/ Because the judge in the city,
/ Your hands are stained with blood
/ Bloody,
/ Bloody hands
Fantastic!
Again, the sensitivity assumptions dropped my hat.
Francis, my nephew Willy.
He does not speak English.
Welcome.
Willy will be with us until
does not explain the issue of the visa.
Until that time, daily
we will rejoice of the city are wonderful.
Otto, let's go get our scores.
We can zaœpiewaæ duet
"Do not Go Breaking My Heart".
It's more of a conversation
lovers than the song.
So ... How do you like America?
Well ¿... ³ I was to about to become familiar.
/ In my house is weird.
No one answers phone.
My brothers read off that
d stand for much longer without changing clothes.
Never thinking of I,
Also I miss her for the.
Yet I do not miss,
but I'm close.
You wrong as it sounds, but at least
You end up with a month of the or two.
By the way, says the am you also my
Trish invite the dad for my birthday?
Who is Trish?
Trish with her the four months since we meet
my dad, and she hates me.
Malcolm says the pm you about it.
He says the em you that the father took the the
all my the disc?
It is said that the s ³ I'm listening them loudly,
but I am sure that the s I heard the,
listens to them in the garage in!
Malcolm, are not you think that the time we could
porozmawiaæ about my problems?
Ok, sure.
- What are they?
- What are they? I'm sitting here ...
/ Nikki!
Did you come to talking with someone?
Yes, with my secret guys,
hiding under the Put quite.
/ You can also check?
Why are you still talking,
Such g of silly comments?
According to Trish, a normal
reaction to a girl
which ceases to be
are the only one in the life of daddy.
Odpuœæ Nikki
It is trying to be me of a
My feelings are not her business!
It is not my ¹ I ¹!
Nobody said anything of
about it replaces ¶ mama!
This can seriously time n the conversation.
Ok, what you want to speak?
How much Trish hates me?
No payment of the comb out of this angle of the canvas.
Wyjaœnimy, even,
siedzieæ if we have the whole night.
/ The Boys Ch ...
ch the boys, b are reasonable dŸcie the day,
not be treated as the father.
What kind of a father? You're
s misunderstanding and you are the order!
Ignition acisz for it when you come back your mother!
Are still being you think that the mother will come back?
After the collapse of EOE few things?
Dewey?
What do you wyprawisz?
I flamed dad.
Even you!
I'll do it!
We'll do it together!
Honey, I had the worst night's sleep!
The Boys Ch ...
I lose the control over them, and you
'll never go back, it was to horrible!
Already well, honey.
Go back to sleep.
Approx.
Why she can ¿le nude EAE
on the kitchen table, and I do not?
Dewey, if every cop you also
zrobiæ something, you do it.
What are you doing? Long ago
the sermons I AEOI you break loose!
In a properly Dad, You said:
"IdŸcie break loose."
And not:
"IdŸcie break loose now."
If you leave us so the gap
it is not our fault.
The last time there
okazaliœcie my respect!
There is zero tolerance!
You are still I think that someday I'll be Such use
zaufaæ you, but this is not happening!
Next, the fifth much here that changes very
much that changes! Now idŸcie break loose!
Wait a minute. He could repeat the byœ?
The suspension of em at the end.
Do not push Reese
you know what ...
Part, Dad.
He was the EOE entire night away from home?
Believe me, I've planned the wróciæ this late stage.
I suppose also that the EOE
imprisoned somewhere, huh?
I will come back to the house,
as quickly as possible of the!
Besides, why
Reese and Dewey are asleep?
Do not change the subject!
EOE exceeded the boundaries, buster!
And until the appeal will not be ania
television, computer games,
I already can not tolerate your crimes!
Roger that!
Zero Tolerance!
You can not just odejœæ!
As long as you live,
I expect respect from you!
Why?
This house is a pigsty!
¯ Arcie in the refrigerator is overdue!
- I have found of a piece of track in the shower!
/ - He was mine.
And now yelling at me,
because you can not kontrolowaæ them.
But you know what?
I've had fairly!
If so carefully ck,
do you know where's the door!
I know where the doors are
and I know how they u Insert!
It's three in the morning.
I want someone ...
Œmia of about, use them.
See if I depends on?
Przekrêæ branch of the tablespoon and pull it.
Turn branches and chopped tablespoon of the GNE.
Look at me!
Turn and cut the scales!
I look, but do not do anything.
I was doing. Turn, continuous GNE.
And now I'm on the outside!
Congrats!
Let me close the door?
Yes.
Close the damn door!
Thank you!
For a while I apologize.
Three, two, one ...
So what exactly
prepared is your dad?
These are the stocks on his Armageddon
the UN will take over the banks.
Thanks for the hideout.
I do not know where they can pójœæ of me,
without the knowledge of other parents.
I am going to break loose in the morning will bring
you something to eat.
You know, the whole will be quite fanie
ukrywaæ you be here in my room.
You're my secret is the white.
Eat what you want, just taking care
the cord is connected the P. ..
just taking care on a string.
- The EOE dug it out of the house?
- The dig itself out of the house, Craig.
Move the I is already in Reese
and Francis, it never lasts for the long.
Reese sat on the roof until
not lost the fight with a bunch of the cats.
So you do not mind,
Malcolm also spend the night
on the CYM alcohol stink mattress
To some dark alley?
- Craig ...
- Oh God, he already can not Insert!
- Malcolm knows about himself zadbaæ.
- Right, right, is a genius.
But it is attractive to governmental,
secret military programs.
How much time is needed ¿Eby
kidnapped him to the government scientists
And I try to surgically
reunite him with jakimœ animal?
Stop playing!
The end of the piano!
Just stop playing!
I do not understand.
Let me know how you czegoœ know.
He is not already almost whole day,
where it can be?
Keep it down! These are the sitting do not have to
all will hear a s.
Why are you happy?
Because of something I myself uœwiadomi.
We have a free pass.
- What do you mean?
- Can not you see what should be my dad?
No one will punish the nearest time.
- We are untouchable.
- What do you do?
I'm not sure.
This gets a chance once in life.
Must be perfect and great.
I want, ¿Eby is shown by all the
principles that guide us in life.
Well, look at that.
- Okay, I do not know what happened the o
- I know that.
Too much of EOE pretend horse riding.
We are good maœæ, Francis.
Lubricates than the groin
and will be as good as new.
It's good stuff, Francis.
I feel a tingling sensation after it.
/ Please call
/ I've seen the EOE Milton?
/ High reward!
- I'm sorry.
- What?
Your posters are distracting people from
my posters, and that were my first.
So what?
It's not your tree.
I am sure that the your dog Milton
s the very sweet and very go
love, but I'm looking for her son.
True of a man,
that is missing are the two days ago.
Not carefully ck that the exploration of human
are more important than exploration dog?
I do not know your kid,
but my parents said,
Also your family is
worth less than my dog.
- What's your first name?
- Patrick.
Patrick, let me tell you something about your dog.
Fled.
Jakaœ it took in another family of a
Now the family spoiled him so
much as you will not œni the Father
So, your dog already loves
them more than you,
and even how to recover
it will be on you with the s,
until they run away again.
So, can you take off your posters, OK?
Pulling you pull on your posters.
Your kid probably now æpa.
Hey, I'll get the am a little food.
I do not believe that the mieszkaæ I must attic.
¯ c feeds are to remain the oœciami
of czyjegoœ dinner!
Pos you listen to me a minute?
Dad he said, also takes me
and Trish 's Camp.
Do not spend a weekend in one
tent with the women ¹ t!
He provoked it all.
³ He could stop me at the door,
if it wanted to.
Malcolm, it seems to me that
I also now you should listen to the statue.
Do you understand?
If I send you listen,
it can come up with the idea jakiœ.
And then gossiped about,
that can help men chose me.
Then can I do the same for you.
We can finally serious n Perform the conversation.
No. Behaves as an important mildew,
who wants zaimponowaæ?
- It's over.
- What?
D can not take it for much longer.
You're the most selfish
and bezmyœln the people are, as the meeting of Am.
From now on, I'm not
already the girls are yours.
You're breaking up with me?
The EOE Dhabi everything you ever
you feel the am. That's it!
Wait ...
Now what do I do?
I do not want you anymore widzieæ!
/ Just Return to the home, Malcolm.
If you want to apologize ebym ¿³
This apology.
The Pope than I b of the error, and you
EOE had the right about everything.
Gee, Dad, Wey to stop.
Who cares who he ¹ ³?
It does not matter.
I want, ¿ebyœ the back,
because you are my son!
Only you in this family
you have a chance something has achieved the æ.
What?
That's not true, my son, I just wanted to ...
I'm trying Pulling off the æ Malcolm pulled up to the house.
Ignore the last sentence, you're the only the
hoping that please Return to the house, I love you.
Dad dug me out of the house,
and Nikki broke up with me of a
I do not know if I'm already here.
I do not remember,
whether it's the hours or days.
/ This bean.
This is Nikki.
S ³ yszeliœcie it?
Talking with someone.
What are you œmieje?
There may slightly œmiaæ.
Not œmieje up.
P ³ crying. Just like my dad.
Both are now suffering.
Well Willy says:
I know that we are trying to
be friendly, but ...
your seat causes
Also poorly they feel.
Beksalala.
No, ... I will not give you satisfaction.
Do not squint the SAVE up.
Well, Willy, you want it, you get it.
Next Willy, play something on it!
Where is your music!
He ... the game ...
when I ... ³ I do something.
Approx. Nikki can flow at least
zostawiæ here jakiœ cup.
I would like, ¿Eby future and przywitaæ up.
I miss the conversations with her are.
I would like to be it is some foreign secret.
It's incredible. I do not believe,
I also like the ever a
I had the Nikki and family.
What happened on?
Why do I behave the?
Oh, my God also?
I'm terrible!
Not surprisingly,
Dad also dug me out of the house.
I'm annoying the months and selfish.
Nikki and my family May Fortunately, the.
At least they got rid of me.
Sam u ¿eram up with each other.
Wait a minute.
I must not be so.
I can not change.
I can definitely change.
From now on, I will listens the
what the people have to say.
I'll be friendly.
I'll be polite.
Yes. Yes! Like
my new Malcolm.
That's it!
What is she saying?
It's the male g os!
In her room is a guy!
The guy in the room!
I'm talking to you, also he's not here.
Waiting for t ³ ¹ I briefly a long time.
This fruit of more than two
hours of planning and work.
/ Thank you.
You can succeed, because I do not
I can znaleŸæ of an error in the plan.
Here we go!
/ Shutting unite!
/ Zakrêæcie!
/ Dewey!
/ Guys, the zakrêæcie j!
/ For me the continuity's sake!
/ It will help me a photo!
/ Zakrêæcie!
Reese, what are you doing?
/ Help!
/ Mommy ...
- Welcome home, son.
- Thanks, Dad.
It will help me close.
If it will help also, if it was to a
Here Mom, these ¿would be fixed o
Helped to o
/ I must to the bathroom ...
www.tvsubtitles.net