/ WeŸcie umbrellas,
/ Will padaæ s entire weekend.
Man, I wanted to somewhere
exit this weekend.
Can weather will
better on channel seven.
Part, Alison.
Ok, it's your summary of the book ¿book.
This guaranteed the fifth stamp.
Thank you.
The completely forgot am not zrobiæ yours!
I can not dostaæ the next pa y
No problem.
Now we get a Trojan.
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x13 "Stereo Store"
T the interpreter:
Charles MoszeUsz and polishchaser1
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.1 MB
Malcolm!
Briefcase!
Dewey!
Trousers.
Reese!
Vest.
Doctor we have not allowed the her
wracaæ home for several weeks.
Unless you work,
father of another when he found a job.
It's really crazy.
But the mainly g is simply fun.
Employ the background for you
now the nanny, the baby boys.
It should be here for a while.
What!
Why do we need a babysitter?
Because I ¿Eby house has been
where it will leave the em!
Already is.
/ - Jessica.
- Hello.
- Part Reese, Malcolm part.
- You know each other?
- It's in my class, Dad.
- It m³ years younger than me!
But the eggs.
Not possible that it will be us
niañczyæ! It m³ younger than me!
- But older than me.
- Shut up, Dewey!
S ³ Hear,
sorry for the confusion.
Today is my first
day and I can not spóŸniæ.
/ We have to accumulate
/ And robiæ as we can.
The go ahead there will be some what,
This ensures that
but for 10 years, it will remember
I will be œmiaæ!
/ In college I had a professor of ...
Wow!
That's weird.
So, you have to Cover the one of u,
and the two of you wash your hands are.
- Approx.
This is so at exciting.
Look of light!
- And what a wonderful thing?
- Terminals.
Clips!
Otto, it's like a dream!
Francis, that would be wonderful were the idea was.
Opening our doors
to industry film.
It's no big deal.
When Patrick he said,
Also wants to re ¿yserowaæ movie here,
I said the only "clear".
It's not jakiœ wysokobud ¿TERM movie.
Do not be so modest Dy, Francis.
Tell your friends are the om in "The
Brown Derby "and you will see the bigger movies.
And one day I'll be pushing the
pillow for Mr. Rutger Houer.
/ "The Brown Derby"
/ - Are the celebrity restaurant in Hollywood.
/ Closed in 1985.
- Excuse me, are you the actress?
- Yes.
He knew I was! You've seen the
in somehow something. What was that about?
- "Naughty girls from the Antipodes".
- Yes!
No.
I've always been the associate are.
Get the am awards Bootie for the best
scene with the participation of the same girls.
No.
No. No.
No. No. No!
/ Okay, are the Hear.
I want, ¿ebyœcie met Hall.
- Part.
- Part of guys.
- These are the idiots.
These are the completely useless ¿yteczni.
I'm talking seriously not. Anything
are doing, you do the opposite!
I do not know what he was talking about the
I want you dogadaæ, guys.
For sure I will learn a lot.
- Can you help me?
- Of course.
Is it a clock radio,
the same radio?
This clock radio
and also a CD player.
- Thank you.
- Please.
We saw! To see if any
of you idiots that saw the?
This guy is working on two-óch minutes
and do more than the idiots you put together!
Just I read the caption.
To see if any of you someday
tried to read the caption!
In contrast to you,
sluggish suckers,
this guy you will help me out of this wyrwaæ Straw
Assistant jobs Menada ¿era night shift.
Thank you.
So here you have the softball team?
I do not understand what it
Relative density is?
This way of comparing
objects to the constant amount of water.
Reese, you're NEXT
the angle bath after Dewey'u!
- Dewey, was were you two minutes!
/ - Good!
You can not kazaæ my brothers angle bath.
Exit to the outside, Dip
in b the gold and po-fail for so break loose!
Come on, b are each large white boy of Caucasian teenage boy.
I will take the ship,
and you, you can take the æ duck.
- Do you think that the it is œmieszne?
- A little, yes.
Reese, let's make the ad layout.
It will help me with the dishes
This forces you to angle the bath.
You can not zmusiæ me for anything!
Alison and had the right,
You're a explosive.
What are you talking about?
He says of a, you're a ...
you know what, invalid AD.
- It is for me and the furious?
- No he said I "and the furious".
- What he said and?
- I should not have.
No, no, you have to.
Give it to me.
It is not a properly about it
and what he said, but how.
This zasch of a, we need more fluid.
Ok, ... go on.
Ok, Reese is the easy,
but it is good.
Otto.
- Francis.
- There is a problem with this film.
S ³ yszeliœmy that the some of the actors
did not appear, but do not worry.
Dave employ of Gretchen.
- What? No!
- It is quite low and the role of ¿.
Just come in and say, "I think
potrzebowaæ we'll be more towels. "
I'm leaving.
- You have no idea what kind of movie?
- This is supposedly independent cinema AD.
If the "Sundance Film Festival"
does not mean anything.
This would mean the that the niskobud ¿budgets videos
can not rywalizowaæ of superprodukcjami.
- But ...
- Not important what kind of movie.
This makes it also feels
so well, you know.
As is the girl had dreams of am.
But they said that the no
to the am sufficiently at the pretty.
I also was not of sufficient am as smart.
Your mother and that of the cows are jealous.
Thank you Francis,
I am very grateful to you.
Dad had no time, search for a
new babysitter, so I have been and Jessica.
What does not bother me.
And so we do not spend much time here.
- Dewey, what are you eating?
- Sticks of carrots.
Jessica says,
Also we need more from ¿ywiaæ.
I do not know what a company
it does, but I hate them.
- Reese?
- Do not wchodŸ on the floor of!
Jessica and he said,
Also how to scrub the floor of,
This will tell you how far
Alison wants to have gone with me the æ.
Part of Malcolm, you can take the
are the atkê and nakryæ to one of u
I wonder, can you do
it myself, because I go to the movies.
The school day?
Do you think that the Hal that it wanted to?
He is not here, so if
I want AEOI to the movies, I go.
Malcolm, thinking,
Hal also looking at you ...
Hal nazywaæ discontinue it!
No I think that you can kontrolowaæ
I like these two.
What are you talking about?
I'm not saying that the do not have the ability.
I just wasting my time,
I ¹ m smarter than you.
- In what way?
- My brain operates differently, okay?
I can see what you are doing and planning
at the same time.
So if you have two brains?
Of course, also do not!
No one has two brains.
You know what operates
wielozdaniowoœæ on my computer?
Draw you a diagram?
Obtain a we, also the round connector, then your
œwiadomy of mind at the time than ordinary conversation.
Crossing the months go of round
Another represents the toolpath.
Not opposite to the first ...
Wait a minute.
Release.
¯ Eby was to understand the you find it easier,
t call the toolpath "side quests".
So in my brain are like
4 of the path that run the same time.
One whole wall supervising ¿ka
All keeps the stomach. I think that the terms o ..
Part of guys.
What are you doing outside of work for fun?
- Nothing.
- I am the ¿. The word!
The hand-held two tickets to "Oss Fest".
For the best seller of the month.
- Hal!
- What?
Damn!
We are the posi-tion hose!
Pobi of you in one day.
Fortunately I had the.
You know, I do not get to use.
You want AEOI.
No, you give them the em
Do not divert them.
We can not those idiots nagradzaæ
for chipping and doing nothing!
Randy. Do not try to speak to you as
pracowaæ you, but sometimes a little ...
Are they are doing this for me?
You know what kind of sound.
That sound of success.
Sometimes I feel as if that were the three dimensions,
I can almost reach it ¹ æ ¹ æ touch.
These could not be purely logical, and ...
- Malcolm. It's getting late stage.
- Really?
Man, the movie that more than hour ago.
Anyway, I'm glad you also know
already if you're away from me m the wiser.
Ok, Jessica takes over the house
and we need to recover.
It will not get away with it.
As soon as he finishes sent in a for
Tomorrow our clothes, making them easier for the j.
End of early walking break loose.
No more being
Nic purity for fire plates.
I agree.
It ends with now.
You know, I'm really tired.
It is ¿.
And it is already fairly late stage.
The large the better I will be sensitive,
hit the c someone after a long œnie.
- But tomorrow.
- Will go to the bottom.
Without a doubt.
Do I wash the teeth?
Sorry, Patrick.
We can porozmawiaæ about Gretchen?
I love Gretchen.
It's like my mom.
Not only is the 60-year-old stripper are.
When the dating myself with the business your are, it
I did not know of, also deals with the ... porn.
My problem is Gretchen.
Very much like the Napali and,
And I will not request the assistance of the police.
I understand. That's what you want?
Debbie and Lance?
No.
That's not what I mean.
I have an amendment to the script.
Amendments?
Let me also wyjaœniê you something.
These people are not actors.
You can not they change the
dialogues in the last minute.
Simply browse.
Just a little different differs.
- An active volcano, four letters.
- Mount Etna.
- A T. ..
- E T N A.
We do not know
how to get rid of up Jessica.
But the whole quite strongly
give her life a misery.
It's only a matter of time.
- Your tea!
- Thank you, Malcolm.
It is s the sweet.
Good boy the boys, to bed books!
- No way!
- No! I want zrobiæ more ...
Oh, my God also?
The Boys Ch ... are overworked.
I'm sorry.
I'm taking back of the book to bed books, instantly.
Or tell everyone,
Also we are walking in your shoes.
But it's a secret!
And I'll tell Alison, also spend the EOE
hour on the phone with Cindy Read.
It's a good crime be the listener?
And what a brilliant
the boy boy taking steroids?
Not at all.
"Przypakuj a little bit,
a girl fall for you are. "
- No one will believe you!
- Can not.
Leave it to strict, but always
honest person dowi the public school.
By God, it is 19:30!
We should be stronger from it!
Malcolm should be from the meters are smarter!
I'm from the meters are smarter!
But with the catch of a me a few times.
Invent something.
Something cruel, something violent.
Dewey, dress œmieszn the pid ¿AME.
Not for the deposit ê her!
Want the rest of life spêdziæ try the c
remind yourself what it tastes like chocolate?
And Wey professor Curtains.
Dewey, why not œpisz?
I'm trying to be large white boy of Caucasian teenage boy,
but ... I miss the mom.
Come here, baby.
Ok, sleep ¹ ³.
- Whose that of a turn?
- Your. Truth or dare?
Right.
What is your deepest of êbszy,
darkest secret?
So ...
/ Note, customers.
/ Store is closed.
/ Please przynieœæ your ...
Do not you think you were me?
No make up, right?
For the entire conversation is used not the em
¿Any unnecessary compliments.
I just want a toaster.
Not busy kn ¹ ³ ¹ I was sure that the you
squares of the jaw, or beautiful g of the person.
Even if this way of thinking,
I did not he said that!
Wait a minute.
Hey! Hey!
Guys! Guys!
AEOI Want a beer?
I'm buying.
- We have already plans.
- Where are you going?
The event.
I mean ... anywhere.
Insert a pretty interesting place trades.
Only a few guys.
With work.
I'm a guy from work.
Can I go with you. Sounds interesting.
- Yes ... good.
- We AEOI.
Randy, I know that the requests of help EOE
the seal, but I feel a little sick.
- Want AEOI to this party?
- No, no, I ...
Hal Listen to. I do not know why
worry about what they are Suggest,
but I'm going ochroniæ
you just before you are.
- Did not really feel good.
- Hal, you dokonaæ choice.
You really want to naraziæ Jobs
for friendship with the band of idiots?
Guys!
Wait a minute!
Will not let you zrobiæ, Hal!
/ John Williams
/ - "Indiana Jones Theme"
I do not believe that the allowed
We watch the filming as the Daae.
Well, i ..
shares.
- Service Operation.
- Need jakiejœ manual.
Where do I postawiæ.
Wherever you want ... postawiæ.
I want to postawiæ here.
Oh, yes, yes.
I. .. there.
Yeah.
This is even better.
Is someone can fail at the disconnect?
Yeah.
That's it.
You're the best.
I think we need more towels!
Cut!
We can already wracaæ to work?
- Twirling œlub sister for 6 hours.
- Yeah, thank you.
Cinema is now the star of the Brightness.
And her name is Gretchen Mannkusser.
Otto!
- Did you come œwietna.
- Really? I do not know.
I think that the whole scene was to a
g of a little silly and pointless.
You know what this may cause you?
A little sex.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know the Americans,
are very prudish.
- Good night!
/ - Good night.
PREVIOUS tomorrow
ch of the boys prepare Stroganoff.
Dewey, the am thinking that the œpisz.
Did you come to thinking about many things.
What do you do in clothes?
- You want to take care of this the æ?
- Oh, yes.
Where are you going? Come back!
I'm calling to Alison!
You tell her only friends of trades which
and g was to the silly, that after the ¿borrowed and those clothes?
You have the y ..
Or can you say to parents,
Also that you stole Did you come to the holder ring rot grandmother?
Ok, will be as follows:
Reese and I are going out,
tell your dad
Also we were here all the time.
You will be in Dewey
and he will be us was designed for use.
I want ice cream dessert and œ as the pizza.
Another Later, the pizza
and even pizza with ice cream.
Admit it, it also had to become of himself.
If I were you taught me
czegoœ up with it.
You must understand the,
Also when you're exaggerating ...
- What are you doing?
- Just Exit.
Hey, you ...
Discontinue semi-AkAA!
I can robiæ what I'm trying.
I'm terrible.
- All the hate me.
- Not at all.
They should. I do not know why
I'm so, I'm ...
Already well, well.
/ Hot Action Cop
/ - "Fever For The Flava"
Part of guys!
There is nothing like wyrwaæ up
work, well I'm talking?
Do not have a family?
Who is ready for
"Tijuañsk the car washes are"?
- Here.
- I is ¿I ¿these!
I'm ready for
Tijuañsk the car washes are.
Do someday do the EOE
Tijuañsk the car washes are?
"Can I someday do the
Tijuañsk the car washes are? "
Ok, first of Ida.
/ American Hi-Fi
/ - "The Art Of Losing"
/ Hey ho, come on!
/ I'm going to start from the start æ
/ Do not you want the fighting |
/ One, two, fuck you!
/ Do not tell me what I robiæ
/ No I want to be just like you
/ Can not you see that the it kills me?
/ I am my own in the
/ Worst enemy
/ Hit me, I will continue to ruszaæ
/ This is the art of losing
I can not uwierzyæ, also will do the EOE.
You know, I'm a party animal.
- Przynieœæ you a beer?
- No, I have enough.
Everybody run!
My parents are in precisely returned from Maui.
/ Hey ho, come on!
/ I'm going to start from the start æ
/ Do not you want the fighting |
/ One, two, fuck you!
/ Do not tell me what I robiæ
/ No I want to be just like you
- See you?
- Probably not.
What am I doing?
What am I the hell am I doing here?!
¿There is no reason,
¿Ebym here to the.
You're the idiot.
Your friends are idiots!
Each one who sits
this cottage is the idiot!
Name of the idiot himself.
I feel sick.
I know you guys. I was to the
like you before for the deposit of I s family.
Thanks to him, I know,
what is really important.
And it is important that what you are about me
thinkers, important as they are Suggest me.
I am grateful for my the
The wife, for my children.
/ Not at all.
- Reese?
- Can I jechaæ with you at home?
Always thinking of am,
Also I'm so m the Dr!
- But I'm just being selfish.
- Please.
- Drink this.
- Thank you.
Let me tell you something. It really
I helped to a Reference in g of the tooth itself.
I do not like it,
he sees the am.
You're not with the person of the.
I did not want to,
¿Ebyœ through that of a
- I used to try just ...
/ - Wróciliœmy!
Dad, Reese?
What do you ... What time is it?!
Jessica really helped Did you come to, but it
last night, I do the job already.
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
We had a lot of fun.
It's good kids.
Part of.
Okay, you two, to bed books.
EOE miss the œwietn the event.
Wait, she's not ...
I know better than m ...
She ...
Well, the name is a draw
and po-fail for break loose.
www.tvsubtitles.net