Crazy world of Malcolm
4x08 "Ch the boys at the ranch"
T the interpreter:
Charles MoszeUsz and polishchaser1
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.3 MB
Dad, hurry up!
What are you're lagging!
Dad takes us to the ranch,
to Francis for the weekend. Only guys.
I will brakowaæ
my girlfriend, Nikki.
But it's three days without mom.
I'm in the car by 6:00.
Come on, Dad,
You'll see her in the Sunday!
I had to take the æ coffee.
Well, gentlemen.
Ready to go?
- JedŸmy already!
/ - Go!
Belts.
These are the.
Map.
It is.
Glasses.
These are the.
Back cushion.
Mirrors.
Done.
Can not hear,
if the case of a loosening of?
- Dad!
All right. There is nothing
of the ego in being cautious NYM.
Welcome to the Grotto.
I'll be there for you for a while.
No hurry, just looking for Francis.
Francis?
We are the related?
Yes, we are ...
Welcome to Family of Francis!
Otto I, and this is Gretchen.
Marzyliœmy, ¿Eby you to become familiar.
And in the end we are here.
Your son is a genius!
Completely government today this place.
Not completely, of course.
Are still being responsible
in front of the royal family are.
But przetrwalibyœmy
without his pracowitoœci,
intelligence, leadership ability.
Really?
You have only one Francis?
As long as we are here,
everything is on the house.
That you wanted to Perform
overview of the staff?
- I ...
- It will be an honor for them.
All right.
Is ¿are not great the e-
This dolls of the Hopi Indians.
According to legend, situated
naughty children and the s are the bones,
Eby ¿the one already
do not mind the.
These are the so funny, are not you think?
No, no. These are the very valuable.
You can not touch them.
- Can I trust you?
- Do not see why not.
³ Very nice.
I like the shoes.
Give him the boots!
No, no, I was not able to.
All great appearance date.
Thank you.
S ³ heard Did you come to this?
He likes us.
Wracaæ to work!
Welcome.
Sorry, future am
as soon as may the am.
Keep clear ajcie up.
I have a terrible cold.
Better Golf ¿ê
Put on the whole were for the weekend.
Mom did not arrive of a
So we can bawiæ up
without her. ChodŸcie.
Where is Francis?
- Really is the boss?
- There we saw him months.
Forgive them. Always treat
Jakiegoœ Francis as a hero.
What's up, guys?
God, Francis!
As taught EOE so jeŸdziæ horses?
I had to fast for all Grip the.
We breed horses, cattle o Closest slower
Wild Wild West which can be found.
Where can I find the incidents
aerobics with jazz?
Right behind the bar with a smoothie.
The chicken was to œwietny!
Where are taught EOE so gotowaæ chili?
He spends the ¿much time in the kitchen.
The secret to good chili,
how long you prepare beans.
Let us summarize our competition is were.
Dewey sang najczyœciej.
Francis for the volume.
I was to em insidious.
Malcolm the most nervous months.
Reese has been disqualified.
Sink or swim, it happens.
It's fun. Why not
we do this in Each weekend?
Not that I would be of the Father
I almost forgot.
Francis, I save the us
On tour in the morning,
watch a sunrise of the sun
Devil's rock.
I do not want woken up so early on,
¿Eby Daae as viewed by the stupid œ g of the rocks ê.
This could silly g of the rocks and the
most of the year, but this week,
the angle of the slope S of the sun makes
Fire also comes with a devil's eyes
I can not tomorrow.
How so? That you call the EOE
and You said to me about it.
I know, but I must
lead hike at 7 am
and preparing horses
it will take me two hours.
We can AEOI for the ride in t ¿d tablespoon?
- Yes, we can?
- Sure.
- Yeah!
- Super!
What are you doing? I'll get the em
a couple of things to burn.
You're now a cowboy.
You must be early on the Insert the break loose,
you want a ride tomorrow AEOI ¿d tablespoon.
Sorry for the Devil rocks ê, Dad.
Do not worry, I'll go alone.
Will œwietnie.
Here it comes.
Wow!
Awesome, Dad.
I szczêœliwy that the
that we can watch the Daae time, son.
We sat in front of the hills;
keep horses in line.
From where they themselves know that the horse are still being is alive?
Do not jechaæ soon
before you are not familiar with horses.
Keep both hands on the
Attentive ¿s helmets and buckled.
What happened at the Francis?
I do not know. We're going hour,
and is continuously ê I can see the barn.
It looks as good.
- When can we pojeŸdziæ them?
- To them even comes close force.
- Why?
- Because you know.
I do not want a day off brothers,
¿Eby Collect remnants of the fence.
Try and zrelaksowaæ
and cieszyæ landscapes.
We are the only ones on the
manifestations ¿d ¿ce, who in May the problems.
/ Jewey a large white cowboy.
/ Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
Right now.
Why do not you want to
play with me in ping-pong?
The table is free, and I
form to be signed by Tate.
Because you're g of stupid!
Do not we come here,
Eby ¿play with you.
Wait a minute!
In precisely why we come here,
¿Eby spêdzaæ time together.
Your brother asks ¿ebyœcie
played with it and it's going to do precisely.
Our dad signed the
permission for ATVs.
No appearance you give to me for 16 years.
It is a difficult subject. It is very
sensitization in happy when he hears that the is low.
Can're retarded
in some respects.
I lost his milk teeth,
when I had the 14 years.
I'll get the keys.
Each area. Interesting
what does it mean Each area.
Would not be talking like this,
if it would not have been true.
Ok, so the tree is not the area.
Now we know.
He says the em you ¿ebyœcie
Stay away from the quads!
- What are you wearing We thought?
- They are Suggest Francis. Never!
Their heads halfway material out of the
Only plugging necks!
It is the oldest wine.
Other naœladuj the go like sheep.
I was thinking of, I can also zaufaæ you to
a few minutes, but of course I was wrong.
We are continuously at the same,
bezmyœlnymi idiots as always!
Francis, you do not need
so for them krzyczeæ.
I can krzyczeæ on whom He
Even if I did not want this
tell, it's already too late!
From now on, stay away from
horses, vehicles, swimming pool and other Guests'!
You have a non-exiting
the room until the appeal of ania
- Are sending the letter to the room?
- At precisely that.
I do not believe.
You're turning into my mother.
- Yes? Sometimes my mother is right.
- Appeal of aj it!
Oh, my God also?
Spoil of the EOE my doll?
How can the EOE be so cruel?
EOE promised me that you do not touch it,
but it was to just a lie.
IdŸcie the room, now!
We'll give her a new leg
and will be healthy again.
As Henrich cousin.
Well post the five of EOE, Francis.
I do not know when will I learn the.
They.
What about with you?
How can the EOE podpisaæ form
and did not read it sooner!
My God, my job
there is enough hard!
"Sometimes the mother's right"?
Why not just pour out the
We acid on their faces? I would have preferred to it!
I do not believe that the shouted;
for us at the Frenchman.
Do not get away with it semi-otal.
'll Get it.
Damn right.
You're with us Dewey?
Dewey?
I know that I should not have it
brothers, but the looks as well as fun.
On the tree I forgot,
I also j are in the pocket.
Bankruptcy em and off after the break of a
I know, I know, honey.
You know, I should not be on you
krzyczeæ, awful you feel about it.
- Really?
- Of course, also like that.
Both feel poorly
with what zrobiliœmy.
You know what Aunt Gretchen does,
How do you feel poorly?
Works. He works so you ¿ko,
until her body starts krzyczeæ of pain,
b and soul begged for litoœæ.
- Why?
- This is the best form of penance.
When they lose feeling in my fingers,
and back frightening at the pain.
It feels large for better.
- But I do not ...
- Let's do it!
Will be wonderful.
Two older guys a ride ¿d ¿ce.
The beauty of the desert,
the communion with nature.
I do not want you zabieraæ for much time.
He said I already horses
Also go without zawiedŸ them.
What's wrong with this horse?
Nothing, Garnuszek is very s the sweet.
Are you sure you're not
continuously at were for the boys?
Pot very well recognized
unresolved emotional issues are related.
No, I said of you,
Historically, for me, is good.
Pot is never wrong.
Once Gretchen and I will make the omelet,
with mushrooms. Do not suffer from fungus.
But he says nothing of em.
On the deposit of s and my two portions.
I forced the pot
to return and confrontation.
Such sex we had not for years.
Thank you, Garnuszek!
You should also jechaæ on your horse.
Good idea was.
Scout is afraid of nothing.
Unless you're a secretly gay.
Thank you very much.
Guys what I can for you to do?
We are looking for jakichœ fireworks.
- And you have these windmills called?
- Of course.
I have these ladies Put some sticks?
Let's start with 18 Genies,
20 grenades from here ¿gel blink CYM
and a pack of demonic dragons.
I'm not 99
You want 44 for half-price?
44 are hopeless!
Give us szeœciopak red
dogs-delayed ignition one to provide.
With dust or phosphorus?
Who we carefully ck?
And one more thing. We plan to
surprise for a friend.
Do you have something special?
It depends how much you want to spend it all.
Please pozwoliæ my
Dad this martwiæ.
Ch of boys, I want to portray ...
Komodo 3000.
Oh yes, it will restore it.
How's it going?
My fingers are sore, but it is the e
feeling in my stomach is improving.
It's good.
It means also gets rid of the guilt.
What happened on?
Am reminded of myself,
Also when you had the am 9 years
the uncle give me Fenning,
Ebym throw ¿³ ¿and the fountain be seen.
But throw the pebble am,
and stop the am coins!
I am pure from the em!
Once in the deposit y ³ em worm
the sandwiches Reese.
- I ate of it.
- Feel so poorly?
Then scrub.
Look at the blood.
We are in the middle of the road.
I can see why
przychodziæ like here.
Yes, it's come to relaksowaæ here.
Or when he had disputed with Gretchen.
Can I be of Caucasian teenage boy nieznoœnym ch.
I am in such situations, the IDE to the garage u
I think we should wracaæ.
Yes, we can just zrobiæ,
or we can be slightly better to become familiar.
Schnapps?
From experience I know
Also a lot of interesting things smokers
can zostaæ discovered
the appropriate dose.
Look at this.
Good arrow,
EOE t Przytuly of the rocks on the half-ê.
- The Hall!
- The Otto!
- Cheers!
I've never seen the em
so many stars in the sky.
- Look, there's Orion.
- Where?
There.
The three stars of his belt.
There?
There, there.
And there, is it in the spear.
Super!
Something scared of the horses.
Bite me something about the
God, Otto, you're hurt!
Finally something I hit the.
In precisely to the em at the door
the boys and nothing can not hear.
I do not like them krzyczeæ,
but this is the only way to the statue listened.
Absolutely.
He was em raw, but fair.
Byœ He could not be more just.
S smile, so for two
second looks as I'll be the idiot.
- You can speak on it if you want.
- Tell me.
The boys not in the room of three hours.
What!
I want the, spotkaæ up
at the southern gate.
That should be all explained by.
I'm afraid I also started to speak a little hostile.
Latest word is
"Pokonaæ" and "exterminate"?
I think that you're safe.
How long are you gniesz me?
Rate the c on the basis of that
rock formation, jakieœ 4 meters.
If only Francis knew he was
Also here we are, the savings to us.
Of course, the Super-Francis!
He will do a jetpack with cactus
and when we arrive!
Why are you on the one with the s?
I'm not were for Francis.
You should not be.
It's smart meters are capable of.
It's working. I will never meet the em
someone more trustworthy.
So, now!
But I know him 18 years!
The penalty of em it threatens the em him
aka the semi-em with it, b I begged him,
I shouted; him.
And he perpetrated the b ing the error for b of edema.
Two months with you
and is now a model citizen.
- So you're one with the s?
- I think it's fairly obvious.
Potrzebowo the only
Eby ¿³ ¹ father disappeared from his sight.
I know of someone who knows
as odmieniæ force.
Strange, since I'm such a genius,
that's why I'm drunk
the desert with bullets in the back of the bed of
Listen to me.
Francis has not won the all the
of small features great one day.
Do you think that the raises it out of the way?
"Hello, I'd like to Buy the large
gum, candy bar and now the osobowoœæ. "
No, Hal, Listen to me.
Jab ³ ko apple falls far from the hand.
So I'm not so
a terrible father?
Absolutely not!
If you already finished the semi-AkAA EOE, my
the books you need massages in order to return to normal.
Well, Dewey.
We can not exit the ¿any place.
Right corner.
I have.
Unless already enough.
Finally.
Skoñczyliœmy.
Wow!
I feel great.
Beautiful, is not it?
This moment is worth it,
your soul is free.
You're clean as before.
- I feel like the swims.
- It's probably ammonia.
But, odwaliliœmy slice of good works.
Clean room leads
with a clear conscience, you know?
I szczêœliwszy than ever.
It is ¿.
I want you something Daae.
Think about me,
When will it be that to use.
Thank you Gretchen.
I do not know what you want here have reached the æ,
Know-but you, also I'm on you with the y
- What is it?
- Looks like a fuse.
- What exactly are you planning?
- We plan you recover!
We back brother
How this was to.
We know how you like fire, explosions.
- Unrealised of the trial, it was to long ago.
- Really?
So where it leads?
You can dowiedzieæ to pass the c
under the fence and d c for the fuse.
Or you can dowiedzieæ
in the manner of Francis.
Definitely make your decisions are good.
I'm telling you, everything
changed the o I am the wife, to become the beam.
I'm already sixteen
geek who ...
Interesting.
Is something looks as familiar to you, Otto?
We follow in the direction of the mountains.
Behind us is certain in death.
That's right, now there is a certain in death.
I wonder what it is.
I'll tell you that Francis
shows us the way home!
- I said of you also save us.
- Yes!
Let's go there.
It's better than returning home in 1998.
I do not know, the smoke of a raft for a week.
When will Komodo 3000?
I think it was to that.
They told us when he gets away?
Bob he said that the two days.
He was worth it.
T the umaczyli:
Charles MoszeUsz and polishchaser1
www.tvsubtitles.net