What?
Well, I've ate the biscuits,
Did you come to prepare for lessons Dewey.
And I took the driver's license of, ¿Eby wyrobiæ
fa is fake proof of the identity.
And I can not zwróciæ this necklace,
because it is already sold.
Am just wanted to tell,
Also your shirt does not fit into pants.
/ Malcolm in the Middle 4x04
/ Stupid Girl
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Want more orange juice, Stevie?
Thank you ... Lois.
Stevie is staying with us for a week,
while his parents are in Hawaii.
Sip the juices cover at the beach while he
must patrzeæ, like my dad sweat dries.
Are all noticeably lived, as Steve
cut into the part of the grapefruit?
Nice to have the baby at home boy, lying will not be the
is the white, surly monster.
To me pi Did you come?
Yes, you.
Hal has no more bread
Dewey sandwiches.
You wpaœæ to store
on the way to school y
No problem.
You can simply
Daae me the money for lunch.
Do not be Dy tion are dry.
This is not the ¿are nutritious things.
Why are pre Pilio
to store the spirits?
After the bread. We all know the that the the liquor store
May the best bread in town.
Dziesiêæ lottery tickets, please.
¿I do not see any bread.
What are you talking about?
There are Melba toast.
If you can not zrobiæ of these sandwiches,
it's just too small for trying.
About Bo ¿e What?
Dewey, in precisely the win em
a thousand dollars!
A thousand dollars!
What we buy it?
I do not buy, son.
Effect of the avoided is the money
to fund your education.
The secret fund, which your mom
I never can fail dowiedzieæ.
Jams are sometimes when it rains.
Do you mind.
Thanks.
Malcolm agrees to
Yes, I know, you're also Alison.
I am glad that the We met up at the end of
after month of being szafkowymi neighbors.
"Szafkowymi neighbors"?
Yes, we ...
Aaaah ... szafkowi,
We have lockers next to each other.
Yes, it's funny, you get it.
Well, see, are siadko. And keep your
damn mutt off my lawn!
I do not have a dog.
No, no. ¯ ³ em joking, because we are neighbors,
and sometimes are sitting in the May issue of the dogs ...
You see, I always plant the adam,
Also when people know the ¿Are you kidding,
but sometimes they do not understand the
and have a moron.
There also do not understand.
Zabrzmieæ I do not want to patronize.
Just thinking about large
about such matters.
The crap I should speak
30 seconds ago, right?
I must AEOI the W-F.
What is with me do not you?
How old are you ... time?
I always spoil everything.
Even with just the girls are perfect as Alison.
Alison is ... blunt.
Not the point.
The problem is me.
Too much thinking over everything.
Really, I podtrzymaæ
than ordinary conversation without collapsing it.
Why is my brain will not let me
szczêœliwym be?
I must AEOI baby.
Going to art galleries?
This is not art!
Sorry.
Going to space
which ones sell overstatement of cost-ch am
impaled tourists without a hint of taste?
Remember the EOE.
/ Thank you very much.
Nice to me was to robiæ
business with you, Mr. Dodson.
Come on, Francis.
Meet Mr. Dodson.
It's great were part of man.
From certainly be more than once
slaughtered in the market.
In my time already.
I have to œpieszyæ to another client,
I'll see you gentlemen.
Soon, I'll check.
But with me szczêœciarz.
When I leave the homelands all friends
warned me, "Otto, b are each carefully ny".
"People want to bed the wykorzystywaæ you."
But none of these things.
As for example, Mr. Dodson.
He knows much more than I ation about managing the ranch.
But whether behaves
of the O ¿szoœci, and cocking his nose?
No. Instead, it teaches me.
For today for example, I did not know of that the cows
in need of protection against ultraviolet.
What? What is this stuff?
UV filter. For cows.
Otto, how much for it will give the EOE?
$ 200 per bucket,
plus, of course, maœæ Zinc-coated on the nose.
Do not worry.
Already he pays the ignition em.
How long they got for a thousand dollars?
Oh, Mom!
For years, the dream of em.
What? The reflections of you? We can not zrobiæ
this at home. There is my family.
But we can up spotkaæ
in the parking lot near my office.
It prêdkoœciomierz, and is a measure of vibration.
It has been reported. That's it!
I can not doczekaæ,
ways to align a pair of the little one.
Appearance Looks like you're a willing.
Yes. Let me also ask
about something, hypothetically.
If I chance for something
and pass the zloty, ie changes ¿d ¿s of the dust,
so that no one will recognize the ...
Had to byœ Approach to
Fixed cylinder.
That is, if the following are five of
such a tragic accident.
¯ s what please?
S ³ Look, a lot of "road builders" is
your way these fragile obstacles to bypass.
What if I encounter such a fragile object of ...?
He could only speed up the byœ
until when this object is not already
threat to the roadworks.
Sign here and you can
zabraæ to work.
STAA me for more.
The angel of you, Stevie.
You will be happy to goœciæ always
when I go somewhere your parents are.
Sure, Hawaii are œwietne,
but we are well ¿Se having fun, right?
Clear that, yes.
I did not bought the am.
Cheapening were about 49 cents.
These are the of oil.
You do not have uczyæ on exams?
Tomorrow I have, like, three.
Are not you afraid that if the up
no you will not learn it?
No.
- How do you do?
- What?
How do you AEOI by force not
the c dead sure that the something happens to you from the ego?
I do not know.
I think when you start just martwiæ
Sing the song myœlach Minty-mint.
"Refresh hose extensions, the orzeŸwiaj,
Restore the world ¿s breath.
"Minty-Mints a friend
your breath. "
So when I ask you for the exams
the EOE thinking about this song?
Yes.
/ Ch of boys, I'm telling you for the last time,
/ ChodŸcie here and you will help me with the bags photo!
"Minty-Mints a friend
your breath. "
Reese! You're a genius.
What?
This girl, Alison, and I ask of you
everyone in the world speaks with an accent, except for us.
And instead of her laboriously explained by t,
Think of a song I minty-mint.
And the answer I "because leeks are the suck"
and that she'd like the o
- Cool.
- I almost feel of how my brain unlocks.
And he said that the'm cute,
And he touched my arm and the.
Let it be
in our family, right?
Here she is.
Oh, boy.
I succeeded in only once.
- What if it was to just fart?
- Oh do not worry.
- I'm still learning.
- Calm down.
- Just repeat after me the.
- Part Malcolm.
Did you forget pm you about something zapytaæ.
Well do you feel?
Want inputs to the class?
No, just killing time
before the break the œniadaniow.
I know what you mean.
These mornings by tugging the in infinity.
The School are for suckers.
This shit wymyœlony
by parents as
they could siedzieæ at home
the whole day and imprezowaæ.
O my God e
Think of am the same.
It would be cool if exchanged coins
jednodolarowe on miliondolarowe.
In this way, no one was to be poor
and all we would be millionaires.
This idea was œwietny.
I ¿I want pomagaæ the poor.
And wanted to am zapytaæ you if you do not choose the byœ
up with me on Friday at dances?
Sure. He wanted to you alone I zapytaæ,
but I was waiting for the right moment i ..
- Grazing.
- Go To Class
- I am the ¿.
"Educational Fund"!
Dewey! Part of.
What brings you
this lovely day?
³ em tracks the Parents
his secret roll.
This will not only roll, son.
It's the culmination of everything he worked em
for the entire e my life.
And I will give the Council since Insert the the ¿
some money for your studies.
Which, if the burn interest ... All right!
If you do not tell Mom
Let rozjechaæ you something.
- Can I rozjechaæ bike Reese?
- Sure.
It's luggage Niku.
Want to Know-What is the best?
Nieprzesadzanie of thinking.
It's fun.
Normally, I'd be stressed out like Stevie.
But I am carefully that the force should be ...
how to tell?
Funnier.
What do you look-up for the task of ... seventeenth?
-'ve Drawn the frontal g
- What's up with you ... is not it?
For two ... Days behave ...
like an idiot.
No. From two days behave
as someone szczêœliwy and laid back.
- Turn into Reese.
- So what?
I'm not worried about schools ê,
girls and in general.
It does not make me an idiot.
That makes me the opposite of idiot.
The brain is ... muscle.
¿Recycle used ... disappears.
But if you are using it too much,
can you uciskaæ.
I had not Think of EOE, huh?
Malcolm?
Bankruptcy em.
How are you think who were the invention of a safe place?
- Paleo ...
- £ £ s ¿s ¿ek tional.
£ y £ y ¿¿ek tional.
That was about œwietne.
You should be ³ ¹ æ take me
today on the tablespoon you. Where would the EOE?
Sorry, Dewey.
¹ ³ em stuck in the office.
Rang pm today in the office, Hal and they told me
Also take the EOE are free for whole day.
That's right.
I spend the whole day on the tablespoon of Dewey'im matters.
Powinnaœ and it was to widzieæ, Lois.
Rotation of the grating and jump are lying on the ice.
He'll do the double Axel, who,
the c honestly say that the wyœmienity
Hal, we have today in the night opracowaæ
The budget of the home for the next month c
Today at night I can not, honey.
I must jechaæ to the office,
by odpracowaæ time spent with Dewey'im.
Yes, office.
Good old office never have too many.
- S ³ I'm listening?
- Malcolm, well, you're a home.
Listen to S if there jakaœ scientific method,
to convince themselves that something is pudding
without trying it?
- It is chocolate?
- No, it does not like the œ find the difference?
- I like chocolate.
It is more bronze ding,
than nieczekoladowe things.
Da of the Council byœ znaleŸæ
coffee tin garage in?
You're going to roll, right?
And if so, what? Equipped ¿³ em it wishes.
Why I had of him do not use?
It's a free country.
Dad, brighten ¿d ¿ck what you can from five days.
Spa of EOE in general?
That's the thing, Dewey.
Since I do not have to break loose roll.
It is as if the laws of nature
I'm not concerned the y
- What is it?
- Nothing.
This leaflet about the ball of the omiarzy.
It is not even mine.
J stores are for a friend.
- Dad, I think that's your problem.
- Why do not you leave me alone!
Check it out.
Mia ³ em ¿yczyæ the shirt texudo Reese,
but then I saw in the store another with the words:
"FBI - Federal bunch of Idiots."
Federal bunch of Idiots!
Combed.
No ... talk to.
Malcolm, I know that the you've had the
¿yczyæ the shirt texudo,
but I see the background are in stock
and the I Think, also is large for better.
Oh, my God also?
I had the j are after school to Buy!
Shitting me!
Zajebioza!
Stevie, you spróbowaæ
Dynka the impact of Reese.
It's as if you'd got the
somehow something hard in your head.
No ... including ... ¿Life.
As you wish.
You also will be a chance to dance.
I AEOI ... with you?
Come on, Stevie.
You must be with us zabraæ.
We are like the three musketeers.
There will be three musketeers without ...
- What's his name ...
- Nougat.
Well in precisely.
I'll be the soundtrack of awl.
Fabrizzi a champion.
¿The desert is like flying.
Dolphin and tiger appear to tañczyæ.
Can I dostaæ of the picture, but the face of the
my husband hose in place of a dolphin?
Like all great artists
will do anything for money.
Oh, my God also?
Francis, what's happened?
You will be proud of me.
I refueling of petrol in the van,
when this guy came out of the restroom.
The guy from the UV filter!
And when I saw him the feel of em up
like a wild animal.
As if to voting rights
and the nature of the doshas.
³ He walked over to him and I oœlepi of it I
the wiper wiper,
the bucket of the col on the fly away upwards,
and on the I boo-hoo.
Would you like to view the the front of the tooth?
You know what? I go to przemyœleæ
and can they will fall later.
- Why do you œwiszcze?
- Listen to, honey.
We are happy about the statue I'm listening,
but I am told the boss, I'm also
œ like the scum are, and you're ruining my image.
These scratches and bruises?
This symbol of my triumph.
I mean, dude to the fairly convincing months,
but in the end I regained the money.
- Is that blood in your pocket Qty normal?
- You AEOI the dressing room.
Want some punch?
/ (The ¿- przywaliæ s)
If I say yes, it hit me.
And so you General, but will be more fun
First if you say "yes" ..
So what do you like more,
dances slow or fast?
- Wolniaki.
- I am the ¿.
I think that the fast a piece of
is really otherworldly.
No.
I can not uwierzyæ in fajnoœæ of
Also it's so cool.
/ In Cheswick Grounds, the largest public
/ Lawn in the UK
/ Every time you ŸdŸb of the grass
/ Centimeter is growing day.
/ Let's see.
What are you doing, Steve?
³ am thinking that the boy go with the opakami the dances.
I did not want to ... AEOI.
Stevie, Listen to me.
That you're a in a wheelchair does not mean that the you can not
to enjoy your dancing, like any other.
It is believed that am also creative you All the boys of boy
endowed with qualities,
that will be appreciated that each of ¿da girl
if only there byœ selected the.
But ...
You can take a lot of things.
You can pstrykaæ fingers to the beat.
You can Turning to in a circle on the box.
It was to be the sweet hands.
Please ...
Each girl was to give to
szczêœciar the c can walk perfectly well with you.
You're kind, caring
and take care of czystoœæ.
Girls are crazy for it.
Lois ...
Stevie, you know what?
We go to these dances.
- Francis, what happened to you happened?
- I must tell you something, Otto.
There is no such czegoœ
as a UV filter for the cows.
- What are you talking about?
- That guy fool of you.
But do not worry,
I take care of the it.
- I regained the money.
- I'm such an idiot.
It's my fault had to EOE up bla.
I'm sorry and thank you.
- No problem.
- You know what?
There is one guy in my office
and I have a suspicion about him.
Come on, you will know it.
Very well. Will show my
Friend what you sell.
This magical rose ¿d ¿ka.
There is water supply.
And so.
I saw already the same.
It can, the good robot Swenson.
So, are œwietne.
I do not know.
I think I like more curly fries.
He knew I was.
You owe me a buck, Malcolm.
- A Cajun curly fries?
- Oh, my God also?
Of not completely forgot about them am.
It's my favorite.
Watch the ¿.
Why does ¹
twined eat?
We are the bistymi braæmi truss.
£ easily you talking.
¯ and any stress at all.
Yes, Reese and I get along well.
Because we are so much alike.
We should check that
if you're not accidentally bliŸniakami.
- I'll ask my mom when I get home.
- At precisely the wpad am a brilliant idea was.
I know one of the older class
of zabunkrowanym beer.
No way.
We can take the æ szeœciopak, blanket
and pójœæ a football field.
Check out.
I can not uwierzyæ,
Also soon will.
Illegal drinking, quickie with the girls
in a risky place.
High School government today!
I'm Hal!
Can only one government d
Hence the OdejdŸ, son!
I do not want, byœ me that he knew of!
- Dad, you have the crap!
- Really, I am!
/ I love you so.
I'm proud of you, Dad.
Where do you want to sit off the œæ?
Because I am thinking about the 50-yard line.
But for long would have to be there AEOI.
You have nothing to denerwowaæ, Stevie.
I'll dance with you the first few dances.
Stop yourself winiæ!
That dude is a complete donkey of.
Throw out the beer,
find someone who will drive you home,
and then break up with this Pacan.
That's precisely the'd do if I did not have
you of the enclosed brain for the entire week for s.
Here's what we've really done the.
"Minty-Mints a friend
your breath. "
Mom and he said,
Also asks the EOE j are about it.
- How's my gal?
- I do not know. No longer krzyczeæ.
Not yet seen of a
even my report.
I think I'll be had to have
the average 8.0 to exit on a clean.
What can zrobiæ,
as that the already znormalnia of em.
Alison and broke the with me as soon as
is used in the sentence I of the word "paradox".
Welcome back.
I'm sorry for Allison.
It's no big deal.
Are still being I'll be j of the award-sighted.
You know what I do not understand football?
Why visiting second ¿yna
has so many various different uniforms?
I do not know.
Stuffed kids.
Were probably win the lottery.
Breaks?
And do you want? Sure.
www.tvsubtitles.net