Finally!
G of stupid, useless ¿useful old man!
Next, the fifth large that changes in this house!
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x17 "Clip Show 2"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.0 MB
Hal River in Obuda up.
As early as the time.
So fast!
The term is only for the month of the!
He says the I, also has not been a
Conceived in the elevator!
But the scout in Dewey!
- I'll take the t, let's go!
- No, Hal, are not born yet.
Today we had skoñczyæ
our will.
Today?
³ I do not agree on it!
Besides, from where they know that the not
you born? You're not a doctor!
- I'll meet you there.
- Hal.
I have all the keys to the car.
And the wall of the GNE am saddle of a bicycle wheel.
Why do we need it
robiæ in the middle of the night?
Ch of boys should not widzieæ,
how to write a will!
If you begin to myœleæ about the future without
us, we lose control of them.
Lois, we are not prepared
for resolving such issues.
Always very ócimy k ³,
as we are working on will.
Hal, the last time
we tried 10 years ago!
I was to a large k the quarrel!
Name Did you come to me przeczulonym
and hypersensitivity ¿happy!
Hal, you can empty the NIAAA the whole night,
but we do it anyway.
All right. I'll take about the pencil.
- About the pencil is too short.
- Hal!
As early as well!
Understand that the do not do it
for themselves, but for the children.
And how terrible accident happen
and will have no plan?
Our little ones, the bed
lonely and helpless!
S I think that that is not caused to the dziliœcie
greater damage,
So I decided the wypu ...
/ (1x10 "Stock Car Races")
/ (1x03 "Shame")
/ (211 "Old Mrs. Old")
Okay constant e
As we have something znaleŸæ,
nothing is as clean up the Fishing.
See, I have found the cookie with a back ¿fault.
Wait, already something zrobiliœmy,
This will save time.
Malcolm Zapisaliœmy coin collection.
Super.
As the collection of coins?
Do you remember this pud of the hidden in the closet?
Later he found the Dewey them and the ¹ ³ ³ kn ...
That was about $ 500,
drained to sewage!
Even one coin has not been as a sieve!
- And what about the pledge the silvery one of the head?
- Ch the boys did with the armor.
Chinese porcelain.
Antique glass.
Hand-blown glass butterflies.
Why would you even be kupowaliœmy?
Hal, we have less wealth than 10 years ago.
We can not be so until
sp cycle, we can not!
- Where are the exhaust g of the bank?
- Here.
Cheques and rest,
but did not find it.
I remind you also that I wanted to
avoid ¹ æ ³ because I knew what would happen.
May in the future you will trust my person the Executives.
EOE issued a $ 300 sequins?
/ (1x13 "Rollerskates")
/ A b the BUGS ...
/ Pope of them than the few I
/ A few times in my face napluto
/ But I survived
/ Queen - "We Are the Champions"
/ We are the winners
/ My friends
/ And we'll be fighting | until the end of
/ We are the winners
Get in the car.
And what is to be?
$ 520 for the hospital
Toys for mining?
¯ dead, is alive, dying.
¯ dead, is alive, is alive, is alive, dying.
Son, you spend too much time ...
Silence!
Zwi the zaæ it!
/ (2x09 "High School Play")
Son, you probably already k time of aœæ up break loose.
Dad, you're embarrassing me
with my people!
Hal!
What are still being doing here?!
Oh my God, the idea ¿ck if
wydaliœmy at military schools ê ¹ Francis?
That was a necessary
Potrzebowo of discipline!
No, no, no!
We will to repeat,
until zaœpiewacie correctly!
One more time. With a feeling.
/ (2x13 "New Neighbors")
/ Confectioner
/ Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley
/ "Candyman"
/ Who we take sunrise of the sun
/ Sprinkle it the ros
/ Pour the chocolate
/ And throw in jakiœ miracle
/ Confectioner
/ Confectioner can do
/ Confectioner can do it,
/ Because I add a pinch of continuity
/ Then the world tastes delicious
/ All I confectioner wypiecze
/ £ lure were sensual and delicious
/ Remember the dream
/ Of childhood
/ You can even schrupaæ plates
Why did the authorities do not help the
We, the ba the mess?
Income for sequins.
See this is for next year.
- And these two are glued together.
- What a difference the difference, Lois?
You know best,
That we are in the ass!
- You sound as if you blamed me of!
- And you blame me?
Uzgodniliœmy that the you
are responsible for the finances!
- This may be the reason.
- Approx. Forget about finance.
Transfer of ownership for the rest of the former
¿life with their spouse. We'll be fine.
I think that whoever dies first,
the second will be at home with the children until ...
- What?
- Nothing.
- Why are you looking at me?
- Do you know ...
I always knew the ...
Also die first.
What?
A few days later, not committing suicide.
- He could not I Insert without you, Lois.
- What?
Do not act surprised.
We both know what I mean.
No ... ¿Yczysz my death?
Why did You said?
And there is no response to my suicide!
That explains a lot!
- Why do you think that the die first!
- Honey, you are so osobowoœæ.
¯'re alive at a very high level of stress.
We are savages?
/ (1x16 "Water Park")
I've had fairly!
/ (3x07 "Christmas")
A fire? A fire!
/ (1x02 "Red Dress")
Whose the hell dog?
/ (2x01 "Traffic Jam")
He told the am, whose dog the hell?
It operates border stock!
/ (2x13 "New Neighbors")
Border activities of the Company,
border activities of the Company!
Limit activity of the Company is inviolable!
Exit here and przeproœ me how grown-a!
It is indeed an adult of behavior!
I do not believe that the ¿I yczysz
death and personal injury ck are my osobowoœæ!
Calm down, Lois!
I just wanted to Highlight,
I'm also more peaceful the people are.
/ (3x02 "Emancipation")
/ (2x02 "Halloween Approximately")
/ (3x03 "Book Club")
Get in the car and the only.
Shut up!
I do not let the stress go Eby ¿³ ¹ control.
I do not teach themselves of this,
just as I have.
- Ignition acisz for it.
- These comments are helping no one.
I'm sorry, but I found out precisely in the am to
I'm also walking the c are the bomb!
Even though you are not interested,
How does he want to do?
Do not kill yourself!
Even though you can not oderwaæ his band ¿s!
I am very head of hairy.
But this is different!
Exactly the industry of em.
Will be a beautiful and romantic
and make everyone forget also the
about your g UPIM the funeral!
Ch the boys!
This can not handle
how would you kill?
Did you come to be amazed me!
Stop it!
And what do you say?!
We both have what przepraszaæ.
I'm sorry for you in the crease for the hair.
I'm not proud of pressing the robe stretching.
Neither of removing ear.
See?
We return to a path adults occur.
- Let's get back to work.
- I agree.
Leave it to break loose and let's go.
Hal, sit down.
Moved on through the worst.
Approx. In case of death
both parents.
Who will appoint a guardian?
- My family is out.
- I will not go to my family are.
/ (2x15 "The Grandparents")
/ (3x07 "Christmas")
Grandma!
Jesus ...
We should not have more options?
There should be more people who
after our death, take care of the Child Lock up?
/ (1x16 "Water Park")
Want to view a strike?
/ (2x20 "Bowling")
Malcolm, what are you doing?
Look at me, I'm
the best player in the world!
Terribly depends on my bowling!
Super Bowls are important!
Malcolm, come back here!
He wanted to strike Did you come?
I'll give you Strike!
Here's your damn strike!
/ (3x13 "Reese Drives")
Where's he going?
/ Sum 41 - "In Too Deep"
/ The sooner spadaliœmy
/ Zrywaliœmy and drag the Gallo
/ The back wheel of zataczaliœmy
/ As soon as things were better trimmed rotation
/ Did you come to say that the it is not
/ Was to sufficiently good things
/ But you are still we tried again
/ You can email too much, we tried
/ ¯ Eby everything was to the best,
/ Meanwhile, was to get worse
Wow! NieŸle!
Really.
/ Because I Tone occur.
/ I'm trying to utrzymaæ your head on the surface
/ Although all the time I go to the bottom
Reese, it was to awesome!
S ³ Look, when people
at school to ask about the ...
Tell them also that the em
under your bra.
Provoke them!
/ Suspect resists.
/ Appearance Looks like
/ May are also pepper spray.
/ (1x16 "Water Park")
/ ABBA - "Fernando"
/ I remember a long time ago
/ GwiaŸdzist the inn the night like this
/ In the light of the fire Fernando
/ EOE Nucl of themselves and each of the toddler EOE
/ On his guitar
/ Can the am will hear that distant drums
/ And the music sounded the horn and the distance
/ Something was to the air that the night
/ Celebrities that were clear,
/ Fernando
/ The shiny were for you and for me
/ For freedom, Fernando
/ Although also never thinking of am,
/ Also we can przegraæ
/ Not to the deposit aluminum
/ If I had the zrobiæ
/ The same again
/ He'll do the I, my friend,
There is one plus of this,
Finally, in a somehow something we agree.
There is no one who
take care of the would be our Child Lock.
He did not even mention about Francis?
- Let's go to bed each.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
Why not even consider you insert?
Hal is sufficient that
difficult without your of ideas!
This is not about Francis
but for our children!
- You know what I mean.
- Why Francis is the idea of ??the s?
Has a job, is the wife,
shows responsibility.
I admit that the Francis was not the
The easiest child, but the change accordingly!
What's the big change!
He threw ê ³ schools, conduct of about 5000 km
and the take was a wedding after 20 minutes of familiarity!
You can not podejmowaæ ¿vital decisions
without thinking and be a good parent!
A good parent knows,
Also acts causing consequences!
Lois, we are the parents because
Also not pamiêtaliœmy the rules!
Do not pay attention Did you come
the good things that make the!
- Good things? Your example?
- For example ...
I'm not tresowan the seals are, Lois.
I can not wyszczekaæ
list of good deeds,
as soon as you arch the onisz
and throw me Mackerel!
- I'm not going to chat as hysterical.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You can not escape from this
by hysterical husband hose!
Do not tripped by the protection of the
airport and will not work now!
I'm surprised!
Thus, also the EOE Think of the transfer
his care for the boy opcami.
He is the worst of them.
/ (2x02 "Halloween Approximately")
I love you so!
Why do not you admit it, Lois?
I've never liked Did you come to Francis.
Is it a surprise,
The also had a miserable childhood?
You can not winiæ me,
for what is Francis!
You really do not see
including its share of!
Weekend with his parents in school
Military: walczyliœcie sword!
Pulling off the GNE Did you come off it
during a baseball game,
Did you come because I am thinking that the crooked
of looked at you!
His first with the words was to:
"Shut up!"
Lois skakaliœcie itself to
garde of the day of his birth.
- He began ¹ ³!
- What?
Nothing.
No, I said, Did you come to that the start of the.
What does that mean?
Leave me alone.
- As a baby can ¹ æ start something?
- I do not know, Hal.
All poorly made up of the layout of
after his birth.
It is a staph infection up ¿?
What does this have to do with it?
The am are stuck in the hospital.
Without my baby!
Completely insulated.
For six weeks.
Le ¿and the am there and am worried about the
about him.
Am thinking of how much I
needs, needs my care.
When I am wypuœcili momentum of the
home as soon as can the am,
Eby ¿³ opiekowaæ up is a white,
poor Francis,
and when he reached the am,
he was to szczêœliwy!
I can not of him zajmowaæ am less
than at this time.
You be cared for the EOE
and to the szczêœliwy, like a clown!
- He was am an intruder.
- Honey, I had no idea!
I know that this is from the email and scary!
But I can not help it!
I am the worst mother in the world!
It's also my fault.
Never robiliœmy anything right!
Our parenting is a failure of the!
Take a look at this pigsty!
Look at how we live!
Why write a will, and so
we leave our children in poverty!
We are walking the c ¹ ¹ ad
forced sterilization!
What idiots in Washington
let us multiplication ¿AAE!
This family is a complete failure of the!
/ (1x05 "Malcolm babysits")
/ (2x21 "Malcolm vs. Reese")
/ (1x04 "Shame")
/ (1x08 "Krelboyne Picnic")
/ (1x06 "Sleepover")
/ (2x01 "Traffic Jam")
/ (2x04 "Dinner Out)
/ (2x02 "Halloween Approximately")
/ (2x05 "Casino")
/ (2x10 "The Bully")
/ (3x07 "Christmas")
/ (3x10 "Lois' Makeover")
/ (3x14 "Cynthia's Back")
/ (3x16 "Hal Coaches")
Eat calcium, the wipe!
I hit the in your head!
Baby, baby calm down.
I will show her the.
Does it hurt! Blood, right?
I know it's bleeding!
- Dewey. How much is 90 times 5?
- I do not ... what?
90 times 5, Think about it.
Call St. John.
Dewey, everything will be fine.
Yes, the doctor Flannerie?
Please tell him,
Also my son Dewey has a tumor on his head half.
My husband ¹ ¿met him
in the hospital. The bed for 10 minutes.
We will move.
Can I take the apple juice carton æ ³ tional?
We have only the apple-tionally wiœniowy.
Of course, that only the mother.
We are the worst parents in the world.
/ (2x03 "Lois's Birthday")
Is ¿byœ the name of the wife my chick are?
I understand, will play show ...
Now get up and apologize ...
- Dowal him, Dad!
- Will show who is in government today!
Hold this.
/ Kenny Rogers - "You Decorated My Life"
/ My force was to the sheet of paper
/ G of the smooth, with clean and white of the
/ As much as the will of all of Your Tongue
/ Did you come to changing mood in the background and in that the
/ A ¿became the balance right
/ Did you come and decorate my life
/ C your paint are the continuity me
/ The whole with all my heart
/ Decorates Did you come to my life
T ³ ³ explains: MoszeUsz
www.tvsubtitles.net