I can not uwierzyæ, it also shuts.
My mother will not come back before the 18th
Wait, I know how inputs.
Here it is.
I'll do it.
Thanks, the trick with the credit cards are
takes hours.
/ Malcolm in the Middle
/ 4x11 - Long Drive
/ T of the interpreter of hearing: Harry_man
/ Dot the translator and proofreading: polishchaser1
Why do you need zabieraæ
with each other are your pillow?
Hal, I do not know how long I'll be there,
I want to Eby ¿³ of comfort.
So what am I supposed to in the Chaa,
when will you be?
Your doctor will prescribe the mother, ¿Eby and hold the up
my sister for some time.
Dad back starting przyzwyczajaæ.
Now at least semi-AkAA walk perfectly well to the garage u
No washers.
Take a look at the trace.
In precisely why I have to
wyprowadziæ of this house.
For each time when destroying furniture
do not use the c washers, what causes it?
Killing a child.
You kill a child.
For each time as running the house,
whenever they are destroying furniture,
for each time when
roll fights with each other,
killing a child.
Lois, the doctor he said.
Powinnaœ also not up denerwowaæ.
What is a simple proof
Also for every time when they behave poorly,
as if we were to pull out the gnêli feet in
and drove it in a little child's heart.
You can the crap is to repeat?
I hope that you have
healthy enough conscience,
Also commute guilt,
that we should feel,
in better behavior,
when I will not.
Sorry.
Oh, I do not know how long
still stand.
Just a few days and leave.
We can have what we want,
when it starts to podjeŸdzie cofaæ.
In fact
do not hurt the child, right?
Week before you were born
attaches zaliœmy tableware performing a half
to her car when howling ¿d ¿and of the work.
I just want to retain the face.
Do not admit sure that the will of the
We are wykurzyæ her home.
Now we'll TODAY government.
Helga ...
The cheese is wonderful ³ y
Do you want you wanted to spróbowaæ slice sticks?
No?
How can you not lubiæ cheese?
It's made of czegoœ that comes from you.
Part, Otto.
I did not see the EOE can
squeak toys are more Helga?
It's the one that looks as
as it were fire hydrant.
No, but I facilitated the
przypalacz new marking.
Want wystraszyæ
poor thing to death?
Otto, I know how much you love Helga,
but we have of doing this.
All cows must
zostaæ marked and dewormed.
I promise that the I would be very careful ny.
But she's not talk about it.
You know, it is not
so be brave, for the appearance as possible.
Once I spoke in her
one of the terrible the History of the fire,
and had to break loose between me and the
and Gretchen for a week.
I like the the
movements in the elbows, which will add the EOE.
Where it podpatrzy of EoE?
You got me there.
I'm just a wave.
Okay, okay, we can already
return to work?
After ¿was to sensational.
Is that enough of a sensational,
¿Eby is likely to occur on the scene,
Daae show and dinner
for the founders club "Elks"?
You said what?
I can not of themselves doczekaæ,
to tell you.
We've screwed the game!
It is no longer possible.
Not taking anyone
new years.
£ easier dostaæ new heart,
zagraæ than this club.
I know, but this morning at a gas station
I met Eddie the Eigen,
³ walked up to me, ¿Eby up przywitaæ
and poœlizgn are on the oil patch.
There may exist.
¯ kidding.
I'm talking to you, as if God wanted to,
Eby ¿³ test drove the van on his hands.
Eddie is used of my cell phone,
¿Eby AAE cancels his performance.
Two minutes later,
I will do the "choose again"
and I screwed us on the show.
/ I can not uwierzyæ,
/ Also do not trust me, Dad.
/ You do not see Malcolm.
/ Even though it does not like,
/ I am not talked to him over the month.
Nickie is able to hack the right angle.
And that's good, right?
But with him a jerk, I can not uwierzyæ,
Also forces us to meetings in the dressing room.
As soon as my mom leaves,
spotykaæ we could get in my house.
Thanks to God,
Here there is no peace.
- To the EOE with t the girls are!
- No! I taught in the library.
Mia EOE answer the brother of schools y
They had stones and there to the bee hive,
and you where are the EOE?
You ¿ban yet
Getting together with the girls ¹ t.
Her name is Nicki
and you do not see with her are.
For each time,
when I'm about the collapses,
so as if you kick the tiny grave.
Not about the refracting you.
Part mom, part dad.
You know, Mom, charming appearance today give.
People do not appreciate the how delightfully
you can look the Daae in the correct light of.
I always tell the kids at school,
You're a mother are the most wonderful.
- Add the water supply for coffee.
- It Henson, the soluble do.
/ Day of the wiêŸniami?
We have no choice. In this situation
will not leave you alone with Reese.
- This is just plain awful.
- And that's it.
Take him to jail,
some criminals yell at him,
and come home spokornia the y
Hey, in the package is the rock gear.
Well, the angle of opocie, Helga.
Almost skoñczyliœmy.
- How are you doing?
- End already deworming.
God, what a stench.
- Okay, let's get this already with g halfway.
- Wait a minute, is not it EoE marking the first?
No, and why?
This may be the prime reason g.
Dinner for the founders.
For equal to 3 hours
We will sing on the stage.
The dessert section.
Better can not be the Father
Clear that not.
It's a great moment.
Dewey, I have to skupiæ,
So I want ebyœ ¿³ sat here
and watch the da of the peace.
Why I must be here,
Why can not I jechaæ on a snowboard with Reese?
Reese jeŸdzi
snowboarding.
It's just a lie,
which wymyœli the daddy of the mother.
Reese is in prison.
- For how long?
- A few hours.
If not, and you found the declines all contraband,
You can store probably already to become familiar some prisoners.
This is Samuel
He said what I sitting here,
but it is against the law,
speak of those persons not properly ¿nionym.
Wait a minute.
There was to zapinaæ needs so tight.
No good.
We must be explained by a couple of things.
It should be life for me.
We are mine are the property of their.
We should Know-,
I also do not care about your stuff.
Stand up.
He said I get up!
Rotate up!
Do not stop!
Come on!
How has the s fault check.
Sit down!
See how does it work?
Because in prison have
wymyœlaæ themselves entertained.
And when the toss here
BANDA szczylów like you ...
For us it is
Because I also like Christmas!
If urazicie me, I'll
Grip the with you for the beautiful, the tiny neck,
œcisn ¹ æ eyes until the Exit
you on top of the g words,
and lengthens ubaæ them with a fork.
- Do you think that the this is funny?
- I was thinking of that the had of the be.
So we have a new Wimpy Kid?
Let me also tell you chrupeczku, as will
looks as the first day of your stay here!
I do not expect to also get flowers,
as already will be done.
Malcolm!
We have already jechaæ.
Sorry Nicki.
I must have jechaæ of the
zawieŸæ her aunt's household items.
We should wróciæ in continuous over three hours.
As soon as I get
I'll try to sneak the æ.
- What are you doing the EOE so long?
- Ends of the homework em.
- And what are you think Dewey?
- Great, I like the your movements.
- Why are you always in the back of the?
- I'm not always ...
Well even if it is overloaded
it's not about who is where.
The question is, what is
best for the team u
Why do the best for the team in
is to put you out of the back of the?
So ... three hours,
I will be the Father
Have not we had the opportunity
pobyæ with each alone,
and I wanted to, ¿ebyœmy talk.
What mielibyœmy rozmawiaæ
for three hours?
About sex.
Mom, do not do it!
Malcolm, in a few days
d disappeared for an extended time,
and I must have Security of,
Also everything will be all right.
We przejœæ through t the conversation.
I know about your meetings with Nicki.
I do not meet with Nick,
not having sex,
I know about securing
and all other things.
Malcolm, you Know-a lot more,
than what they learn you
on education to life in the family.
It is whole quite differently when they experience
this on one's own skin.
Mom, come on.
I'll do anything you ask,
but let's skip this conversation.
Honey, she has to odbyæ.
You think I'm also happy with it?
Do you think that the plant I like the puzzlement,
which will be felt over the next six ¿a few hours?
Malcolm, I have no choice.
I will not and can be on the spot,
When will the grown of sex,
so we try to forward the message to you
my experience.
Familiarize you with each
happiness except the information that I have.
I do not know, that may be useful
and which are not, so I just tell you everything.
The sooner we start,
the sooner we're done.
At the beginning, it is
Intrauterine contribution to cover.
Listen to Otto is continuously asks me
Where is Helga,
I finished and were already up excuses.
- You have to tell him what happened the o
- I know, I work on it.
- It's just a cow.
- A cow that is in his will.
Francis, I must thank you
for what you will do with the EOE are Helg.
My bud-et is a very modest
and several pieces of beef kow the truth about me helped to
And like, it was possible you have reached the æ
the smoked flavor?
It œwietnie, Arnold.
Ray fathers has been week for life.
Can this poœwiêcisz your dziesiêæ minutes.
- Otto, I have something wyznaæ.
- Francis, and saw the EOE Helga?
No, I've seen the.
That's not her style,
¿So that on the óczyæ up somewhere alone.
Martwiæ begins.
This is delicious.
Do you think there are, also fled and,
because for this to disappoint me of a?
I do not think.
I should be with her,
when the character of her EOE.
Can I Hold the j of the for the last
for sedation.
These tender and juicy.
You have a piece of spróbowaæ.
Look at me.
Ob ¿eram up while my Helga
is there somewhere alone and scared.
Enough of that, I'll go her search for a,
And I'll be looking for the so long, until I'll find.
Choæbym had the spêdziæ
the whole night trying to find.
Otto, if you do not say it now,
I think I never will.
Talk about œmia the
Please give me a béarnaise sauce.
Helga, my beloved.
This whole fucking ripped that tough,
leads precisely to that!
It ...
Are you are listening to what I'm saying?
No.
In precisely the uœwiadomi of em ...
In jail,
will be closed until the end of life.
What I would have had the
obawiaæ of you?
Because taking any continuously at such antics
likely to have finished at this point.
And when that happens ...
You know Sammy ...
Such use by someone you przemyciæ
jakiœ the liquid to rinse the mouth flans made.
I'll tell you what happened with the last of the guest of,
which makes the fun of me.
Which found their sufficiently large y
a piece of his body and, ¿Eby skazaæ me.
As I am afraid of the convict.
And what will you do?
Stretching the gniesz his hand on the 70 miles
behind bars, until my house?
And then the absence of sperm
nab a member of the uterus starts off with the uszczaæ,
which results in a month meal.
The woman is very sensitive longer possible
emotionally at this time,
but God help you weapons
przypominaæ her about it,
because then you will be
had the two problems ...
I hope you do not
will stress too much.
Kitty and I will buy the new anti-perspirant,
and I do not trust him.
There would not even have noticed that the,
I also sweat,
if I'm still banned
on the back of the all the time.
I am so
At any song, you know?
Honestly said the c, not carefully am,
¿Eby it was to fair.
¿After all przystaliœmy
on the layout of the ad, Hal.
From where they now these claims?
From the back of the, this is the d sk
You were such a wonderful g ³ os
you never sang as a leader?
I do not know.
They told me that a little
Screech on high tones.
That you're a leader?
There is no leader, we take
All decisions as a group.
¿I do not remember any voting
of these sweaters.
¿After all zgodziliœmy up
these sweaters.
You are like those sweaters, right?
Of course.
What does he have tell?
"As a brother, I'll be first in the group,
to draw attention to the ugly sweaters "?
Dewey, what are you think of these sweaters?
Like the to me that are œmieszne.
See? We will now
appearance gave absurd.
But it does not matter
I like the appearance of the dam,
and so no one will
Such use my notes to use.
For me the continuity Bosk ...
Can if we were more
worried g of hair and less sweaters.
Now there is something wrong with my œpiewaniem?
Placed at least tell
Your first name without changing the pitch.
I am carefully that the Malik sings beautifully.
Of course, after all ¿and so
¿niasz not distinguish tones.
But at least when I'm dancing,
I do not look like I will stick the the
its rear roller tinting.
Enough, You can store today
perform show without me.
So also without me.
Me also.
And me, the ¿.
I do not know why the busiest for me
so long, ¿Eby view the eye,
and see what kind of
in truth you are.
And believe me, it is more sensitive longer possible,
than it seems czyznom husband ¿.
Apparently very little, and many can be e
You will never find
and it's all my fault.
Otto No, it's my fault.
I must tell you this.
Mia the accident occurred
the labeling of a tragic accident.
I killed the Helga and I will feed you than the the
and I'm very sorry.
- What?
- There's dead, is dead.
S I think that that does not suffer of a
I'm sorry, I should have you
tell right away, but I can not be the.
I want something knew ebyœ ¿³.
You're the only boss in my life ¿,
which I really like the I,
What's interesting - the only one
that about the break of em.
I just can not I znieœæ the thoughts,
Also hurt you.
Thank you, also You said to me the truth.
If you want to release me, I understand.
Oh, no, no, no.
That was an accident, I think that
we should inform the zapomnieæ.
There deserves such a boss like you.
Let's go home.
Francis is one sentence
which is used the EOE and you do not understand.
What he had in mind the EOE
says the c "feed of you than I are."
In the night, when am lost his virginity, taught himself am
czegoœ very important Nego for the related zkach and trust.
The body can you podpowiadaæ,
¿³ ebyœ do something ...
I hope you appreciate,
what these guys are doing for you.
Perhaps that you will enjoy this The message,
Also the constructions
for their participation in the program ...
Samuel will be next week
Overlooking the conditional.
I do not care,
Also go out on FREEDOM.
And so I never find it.
Asshole.
And people are jumping
from one person to another when
try the c znaleŸæ confirmation.
It does this through the entire e studies,
an entire year of college,
Use the c from each,
happens to the more opportunity.
Sometimes even convincing
themselves,
Also related the relationship is not serious,
because sex is such a wonderful ³ y ..
Wait ...
What do you mean by confirmation?
Proof of what?
Sometimes people are part of the Union of,
to prove they themselves are also nice,
and if this is the reason
for which I enjoy sex with someone,
you may cause
many nieprzyjemnoœci.
But is that the playing sex with someone,
there is also the truth like him?
No, honey, it is precisely the trap access,
in which the people entering through.
You see, a lot of people ...
That was a great.
Why he can not
for you are on the Insert?
Sorry.
I'm sorry that the whatever he said I was.
This is our chance, we can not this
zepsuæ in such a stupid way of g.
Entire operation of the sense of team in D ¿entelmeni
that of a good time,
and help Malik
in the angle of opotach drinking.
We are friends of me.
I do not know
Why are the ócimy k.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like something zapowiedzieæ,
what else we saw no dinner for the founders.
Relax ...
Hot-hail the team of D ¿entelmeni.
At least I should be the D ¿ê entelmenów.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Six of us are very honored,
Also can be here.
Zaœpiewamy short the song
the brotherhood ..
and forgiveness ..
and friendship.
Like the of them.
We had larger applause
the assembly of gwizdaczy.
We're all going to me a pizza!
Why do you always walk
to his house?
Sometimes you have to board the OCIA, ¿Eby move up
to each other and be on good terms.
I can zapytaæ about something else?
Sure.
Sometimes when I'm with Nicki ...
I have impression that also wants robiæ
something else, but I do not know what ...
/ Then I try to guess the æ.
/ It never does not work
/ I was thinking of, I would do the something wrong, and I've only tried to help.
/ What kind of had the zrobiæ I just siedzieæ ...
T the interpreter of hearing protection: Harry_man
www.tvsubtitles.net