/ Malcolm! Malcolm!
The school uczyliœmy up
the coolest thing.
He was about the people who gave a Show
and convinced everyone
Also the aliens landed dowali.
So when Reese uœnie,
pob the yskamy s light outside the window.
Later in the the the TV,
but we will record wind the tape ...
Dewey, too complicate it.
Reese dowali the aliens landed on the street.
Run for your life who can!
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x15 "The sale ¿garage this"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.2 MB
Mom returns WEEK earlier
from Aunt Susan.
Well zachowywaliœmy,
but we have some issues that we
We have to take care of the æ before returning.
Move, move!
Remember, when you see the lynx,
do not be a hero.
Stand on krzeœle and use the yjcie whistle.
Run for fluff!
The Ides of home.
Thinkers, also noticed that burned the grass?
Remember: ever since the d remember this Dewey
did not have the tip of one finger.
/ Ch of boys, we are!
Ch of boys, so I miss ...
- Tata smash the wall in the bedroom!
- What?
Honey, I know that the poorly it looks as,
but it is the beginning of great expansion.
I have a sketch. See how
I'm running on for the hand?
It will be something much of any for you
and the child, the seat by the window.
Promise me you will not be also in the a
and so do not go!
Hal, I'm so glad that the return of am.
My sister is the most hideous,
œwiêtoszkowat are everything
know the c the people are, as the know!
Each d the time of my visit and to spend the
pointing out to me what to do poorly the am
in life. That was awful.
Do not have to speak. Walking with her the
the five worst years of my life ¿.
EOE He knew that the this is, right?
And my parents?
Susan was to them, and for the most important.
Susan to the ¹ m and p are the dr.
It's a Susan had the talent.
But I do all the am poorly.
- Hal, thinking of am therefore on Rees.
- As if you had the and too little about the worries.
No, Hal. We do not
it sufficient that trust.
If we give him more responsibility,
he would take up the challenge.
I'm not talking about giving him the keys
home, or something like that.
I think that jakaœ incentives would do him good.
Approx.
Honey, come here!
The chicks were hatched up!
Good.
- Dewey? Mom is in the house.
- What?
Oh, right.
Repair walls will kosztowaæ $ 800.
I think I can flow return to work at the pharmacy.
Really?
It seems to me that
I can also become eight hours a day.
And when they fall, the liquid is
amniotic provides cushioning.
Something wymyœlimy.
The garage is full of unused not already been used junk.
Can we issue them on the lawn
and we'll see if we can be sprzedaæ?
- You think the sell-off garage ¿s this?
- This idea was œwietny, Reese.
- Do not carefully ved that the idea of ??a œwietny, Hal?
- That I will tell you ...
And you know what?
You'll be the boss.
You can posegregowaæ lumber,
Establish the price, select the date.
- Why? Nothing I do the.
- Reese, this is not a punishment.
It turns out you our confidence, because I know
Œwietnie also can handle.
We believe in you!
Truth Hal?
For me the continuity's sake, he's my son.
I love it.
Answer the question, Hal.
- Who wants some juice?
- Me!
/ You can not sprzedaæ
/ All my stuff!
Things in the garage with a ¹
precious memories of childhood.
This pile of old magazines
broken yo-yo
Rubik's cube and painted
in one color.
- You tried Did you come to the set j!
- I will not be with you angle the OCIA.
You have 10 seconds to give a good
reason, or the garbage dump.
That's why you're a horrible mother ¹ ¹,
because everything is the rivalry for you!
- Not true!
- Roz of the Cham up!
- Roz the connector first.
- No, I spread the connector ... Damn!
You can not just rozmawiaæ
of the family, Francis.
There is nothing more important than the present ...
Take a look! This is a letter from
our son, Rutger!
- We have to immediately retract.
- Why do you hide a letter from his son?
- Otto, no!
- What are you doing?
Nothing, because nothing is fixed about
Nothing is constant o
Besides me, the said the CYM that the nothing is fixed about
It's a constant, but only that.
Things begin to operate normally again ... Now!
Look, a post office future
As soon as I come down edema of the ankles,
is back to work with you.
Thank you, darling.
Not important what happens to the child.
Reese, if at first you insert you to heavy
and the pud and then give a light ...
Shoot The concept is that the government here I money, right?
/ (The world of Christmas decorations)
- Wow!
- What is it?
It's pirate radio station transmitter,
as the results of the studies em!
It is of the power, but I say the truth to people
within 3 blocks from campus.
As long as the FCC (American National Broadcasting Council)
and the silence of me for it.
And for lack of a license.
- You see, it operates a ..
- I wanted to just be polite.
I was not thinking of,
Also punish me for it.
Hello, Sparky.
After half of the campus must maszerowaæ fireplace,
Eby ¿³ s can Cheerlederki
zrobiæ brainwash them!
They want to forget the ebyœmy ¿why we
we are, but not Kid Charlemagne!
It exists to search for a truth.
Let's go, Hal.
And do not forget your g halfway!
For us the yszenia!
T I remember the toy.
B I begged her for the month cami.
Should speak and walk perfectly well
and wymawiaæ my first name.
But this g the silly thing ever does not work of a
Robot! Robot! Robot!
- Now I need a 12 centimeter.
- Already done!
Hey, look!
My glove for baseball.
- Dad, this is yours?
- No, it's my roommate.
- I think it is ...
- Get rid of it. It œmieæ.
Reese, may we should dowiedzieæ up ...
Mom! Malcolm does not
recognizes my DIRECTOR!
/ Malcolm, you szanowaæ
/ Rees, as the boss!
Yes!
He said that the return
and also you can not go uciszyæ!
Kid Charlemagne gives again!
Otto the planning,
Rutger also runs the college,
it will come here
and will live on the ranch.
But instead,
went to the medical school were.
When the conduct of the first
operations of the Otto to the devastated.
- Strange also had never said the.
- That the Germanic pride.
Do not show anyone your uczuæ.
Welcome to the Grotto.
Are you sure you enjoy the site.
And do not forget
odwiedziæ store the memory tkami.
Tomorrow may want pojeŸdziæ on a pony?
/ Malcolm dinner!
/ Hal, I will water the AAE for the second time!
There are so many things
that the government hides from us.
And that's why I do not want the Kid
Charlemagne at the microphone!
Do you love your country?
Yes.
Is each gave?
Voice of I,
Divert until my
the polling station to the house at a high dog.
/ Hal, he said am dinner!
/ Kid Charlemagne gives again!
We should start the sell-æ ¿approximately 7,
I seriously than traders
like the zaczynaæ early on.
Unless you also have another idea was,
which certainly is œwietny.
I was thinking of about 11:30, as previously
I'll be watching the cartoons are possible.
So you'll be refreshed
and better focused.
Good idea was.
Where would the EOE entire afternoon that the south?
Mia EOE posegregowaæ the wires according
in length. Are you still act like that.
I was doing the homework.
¯ there is no task
more than 20 minutes.
Hal, what's doing the EOE?
There was to me six weeks,
and the return of thee am barely see each other.
These ¿³ I miss em.
Can uchamy statue of music?
Really you are still you
przeciwstawiaæ of my of power?
Drive up!
Just as I began ¹ ³
trust your zdolnoœciom!
Malcolm, I'm fairly that
as referring to a brother!
This project Rees and have been supporting it!
Reese manages sell-¹
and you must listen to him.
Not important at any robiæ you also,
you have of doing this!
But he ...
Malcolm, you can pozwoliæ
He ¹ point the sell-off,
or he will be the heart
you are to the end of your life!
This guy says this,
what we all myœlimy!
Hal switched cleaning pierdo were these?
Approx. No one can expect that the hostess
Home of przedmieœæ will understand.
Dewey, what are you doing?
Five of tennis ball is not ¿le of EAE with beautiful hands,
but with ceramic bananas.
This g of stupidity. Why sort
everything according colors?
Because so he said I was!
And so that the drop in the All
Index of slowing us down.
Us?
I hope it was to good. I'll be the laughing
the bane sts as Jellybean (cat)
wake up after massages at
and did not see me side by side.
- Oh, my God also? Is it Nortare?
- It Nortare 680B.
This is the first personal computer.
- Interest in such things, right?
- There has been a lot of them.
- I'll give you five bucks for it.
- Even you! I check the network.
It is œwietnym condition.
It is worth at least $ 1,300.
It stands! No turning back, pretending
Also nothing You said, without appeal in the calculation.
You understand that the gain
money it will take me a few days?
Exactly what I want.
I want ebyœ ¿³ buy it
On Saturday, the sell-¿y
In front of everyone.
The cash.
¿Will be frightened wife, and let me tell you,
Reese also wanted to go disposed immediately.
And then tell all
Also they should listen to me only.
Now you sound like black
character in the film of James Bond.
Me!
Nothing is with me poorly!
I feel good.
And it is good. Good!
And on Saturday, we all are aware the.
Ok, but such plans revenge
May often the opposite effect.
So between us, as
thinking about something to someone zrobiæ course of the former,
do not do it on an empty ¿³ of the stomach.
/ Someone watching you through Satellite
/ And hold your finger on the beam spuœcie death.
/ And somewhere, someone watching him.
/ But who's watching them ...?
Oh no!
Do you know why you stopped the em?
Certainly not for keeping
pirate radio station.
Even if I had the right
Equipment in college,
do not hold me to it for the day.
Why so many questions!
Do you have a warrant?!
Not noticed that the stop sign you previously km.
What?
There is no stop sign.
It is next to the driveway to the golf club.
I recently put it.
The stop sign is a declaration of war!
It is for the background uœciochów
Play the smokers themselves there in golf.
When we, the ordinary people
œpieszymy to other work,
or to a church,
or for dinner with the family.
I'm sorry, also I do not see the
Bobby's first steps,
but I had to stop himself,
only because
Also you do not aristocrats
patrzeæ the skill on both sides.
Gretchen, what are you doing?
I watch the things Rutger
from the time of his childhood.
I do not remember, also that of the fat.
- Shlupi!
- Who is Shlupi?
Rutger Otto loved Shlupiego.
Otto assumes the Shlupiego,
and Rutger up and œmia œmia of the.
He was almost his m³ little brother.
Shlupi He could tell all the
things that Otto was not able to.
For example, "The Ides break loose"
or "b-governments polite"
"Take that finger, that's disgusting!"
It would were beautiful times.
And now, ... he is not.
Gretchen, I can not patrzeæ you suffer.
You porozmawiaæ with Otto.
It will not work, he never
pleaded not of an error.
You got the money, right?
Yes, the cost of me are three figures
of a small bowl of Captain Lou and placard!
I'll get on the computer.
You REMARK scenario.
Reese is œwietny idea was that the
probably trying to help this old lady.
But what the hell.
- I can help somehow something?
- How much is a vacuum cleaner?
This is set.
You can go to Buy only from the lamps.
- But you do not need a lamp.
- So you do not need a vacuum cleaner!
He'll come back here. A lamp
we take even a blender.
I can see that the large over this way of thinking about the EOE.
Where again been solved your father?
And then the army will move the stop sign to fight,
and will be their support of the company
reinforcing the golf club.
But it's not over yet.
Ok, that's the Hear.
How many characters before the stop sign?
Eight!
That's almost as many judges
S sits in the Supreme Court a slower day.
Wait, America.
Thank you very much.
This is my œwinka!
He was a in my room!
- Relax, mato the bed. I got behind her of the $ 2.
- In the middle was to $ 16!
Already on ptokach.
Mom, g the stupid Reese
will make the deepest of the upsz thing!
You're like Malcolm!
I do not want s For more complaints will hear a
to the end of the day, you understand?
The Ides!
It will help his brother.
Sorry, you microwave on sale?
No, we ...
Indeed we have.
Yes, we do. Please follow me are.
Sorry Malcolm, I, Craig.
What are you holding in your hands?
You mean this,
as the old em up ochroniæ,
Reese and all the time the claim,
Also it normally by œmieæ?
Ordinary œmieæ!
Your brother was not able to be more
be confused, and you have more wrong.
Let to Buy It
for the sum of the royal ...
/ Come with me!
Dad, what are you doing?
Craig back here! Mom ...
What are you doing with that?
Kaza of you that I wywaliæ!
Let go, you idiot!
/ - Come on!
/ - No!
- You're welcome. $ 16.
- Thank you.
- Hey, I know this and they ¿¿is on sale?
- Give suggestions.
/ That's why we believe in the Constitution.
Carefully not believe that the Constitution
the promises are without coverage.
We believe in the Bill of Rights, is not it?
I have never understood that the em
confusion about kwaterowaniu soldiers.
That is, until he
They need to get in front of them przebieraæ.
This spirit of freedom of speech!
It is a fundamental right for which
Force has devoted thousands of ce s Men Everywhere!
Skrêæ left ...
/ Note.
/ Give the c broadcasts, directly
/ Infringing article 27 of the FCC Rules.
/ Stops.
I will not give up without a fight!
I g of the angelic voice of ordinary people!
People in the gutters!
/ People on the streets!
People who are struggling for other people!
Oh, my God also?
You, the Kid Charlemagne!
- Come on!
- No!
Get off!
Reese, stop it, you moron.
You do not know what you're doing.
Enough is enough!
You're so insecure that the you can not znieœæ,
as someone else is the center of attention?
Your brother you ¿ko worked
the success of the sell-¿y
I do not need, ¿ebyœ on
each time step, it detracts from the!
/ Mom, I need to send a listen!
We Nortare 680B.
It's a computer in 1976.
Have been only a few of them,
and Craig was giving the $ 1300 for it!
$ 1,300?
Oh, my God also?
- What did you do the EOE!
- I have a large of things to sell
and do not have time to
k of the canvas is the southern.
Jet ski await at the store,
and yet I lack a bit of money.
What are you talking about?
Buys jet
for cash from the sell-¿y
It's not your the money.
For not rebuild the wall in the bedroom.
But Did you come to say that the I command.
And that means that they got the money.
No, I do not mean!
So why, I've had the dowodziæ?
Reese, it had the help of
become a better part of the human being.
Lift the sense of one's own values.
What you apparently need
because you're so stupid g ³, ¿Eby wywaliæ $ 1,300,
that the family desperately needs!
Co-operate!
I've never met the guy of em!
I hate the Constitution?
I hate freedom of speech!
- I'm a snitch! I do not know!
- What the hell!
Stop!
Federal agents!
We have a warrant! Escape
will kosztowaæ additional $ 800!
Otto, Wychody, I know you are also here.
This is ridiculous, you're sitting here for three days.
I know you do not want to speak about it.
But you can not do these continuously ukrywaæ.
- Like this?
- Appearance give the szczêœliwego?
Gretchen up worries,
Visitors are run are,
and Muffy wants to recover his stall.
You need the crap.
I do not know what przestawaæ because
Nothing is constant o Hence the OdejdŸ!
If there is something that I'm an expert,
that are nonsensical family disputes.
And if Rutger is similar to me,
it will have the zrobiæ first move.
You will need to reconcile themselves
with your feelings.
I can not!
So I want ebyœ ¿something for me to do the.
Look at the rim of the holder ring.
- Shlupi?
- Yes, Shlupi.
Time, ¿Eby on this busy ¹ ³.
He was a little disappointed I was,
Rutger has not arrived when the.
Then comes the s list.
That was a very painful.
I can not of itself poradziæ.
I love him very much, Francis.
I swear that the never
³ I will do so son.
And now, look.
Rutger is an amazing boy the boy.
He's so happy sensitization in such light.
I'll get Schlupiemu phone.
I'll tell you one thing, twenty years ago
I jumped the fence and I opened the hatch on.
Bo ¿e How can the am so
be confused as to Rees?
Hal, tell it again,
I want to hear a.
Approx.
Reese ... is hopeless.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Mom?
Francis?
S ³ Listen, I was thinking of a little
And I want to ¿ebyœ knew of,
despite the fact that the we do not bow made of the Father
I think that makes Did you come to
me all the best.
I appreciate that.
Wow, Francis.
From where they are up for the Feel invited?
I do not know.
I think I had the breakthrough.
/ I wanted to tell you yet,
/ What happened at the school ...
www.tvsubtitles.net