Apparently there is a risk of additional
blood loss by caesarean section.
But Dr. Howard is convinced
I can also urodziæ naturally.
He says he also got the pretty,
thick the bearing.
- What is the bearing?
- Do not tell him! Bo also!
Why we are such gentle?
Come on, Mom,
This is horrible!
What are you talking about,
you should be grateful.
When was to the EOE in my hands, it
The bearing of the feeds you through nine months.
Okay, that's it.
He says the am that the average is enough for us.
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x10 "If the boys were cool girls"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro for HDTV version. XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.1 MB
/ This episode won the Emmy Award:
/ For mounting a Comedy Series.
/ Lois, it's not fair.
Every year you tell me
dostaæ what you want for Valentine's Day.
Each year.
And this year, I have to Buy a gift
without the slightest hint?
- We can porozmawiaæ later?
- When?
After I bring you a gift that
you do not like and come to a jerk!
I do not ever forgive me?
You have of each herb.
I do not recall so
of long morning nausea.
You're a lot older.
You know, like everybody else.
That happens, we all
the older, until the UMR, i ..
We can return to the present?
We will laugh at least four hours of
in the gallery, as I kupowaæ of the opcami ch.
- Something you are.
- It's not fair.
Want to zamieniæ?
Want zabraæ three teenagers
¿to sell out clothes?
I zmuszaæ them to try on
decent clothes?
No, it's fine.
Bo ¿e
My feet are so swollen.
Potrzebowo and I'll be the clown shoes.
I do not believe that the back
through that.
So,
the boy boy or a girl?
- What?
- Come on, just between us.
- The will of the boys want you boy or a girl?
- Hal?
I know, I know. Anything to that of a healthy ...
T know the saying.
But the EIB g heart
preferowaæ need one more.
Well ¿...
/ - Give it to me!
/ - G ³ silly toy!
I'll get the vacuum cleaner.
Destroy the EOE myœliwiec my space!
- Give!
- You give!
What the hell is going on!
Stole the mine or pen!
My favorite or pen!
See what keeps!
Why do you always have a long-pens?
Never I did not have a pen!
I want only or pen!
What is wrong with you!
You have a drawer full here n the long-pens!
Why does he always have what I want!
I never have what you need!
Even though I do not have the own of bed!
Why does everything in my
¿Life sucks!
You owe me a new space myœliwiec!
Shut up and hoses himself another or pen!
/ Give it to me!
Renee, please do not touch.
Mal, you're tion are smart.
It only or pen,
am it wanted to have to write a job.
I think that the reason is,
for which it is important for you ny.
This g of stupidity.
Not true, Mallory.
You can tell her.
Daisy is right.
You can tell me.
Why do not you say,
what do you mean?
/ Yes, you're always so quiet.
A boy of the pack upuœci it on biology.
Earlier it a bit of Death.
I'm sorry, I should have
domyœliæ. Do not be suffering g of the pin.
If it was not beautiful in the hair,
This is my g to the words that useless ¿useful.
Do not have to be a genius.
You're's the sweet and attentive.
It consists mainly of g.
Wow. This is the worst angle of the canvas,
as the had the yœmy of months.
Why do not you just die!
Give me or pen!
I'm warning you!
Terribly afraid.
What are you gonna do?
What child wants to do?
Malcolm!
Malcolm?
Rees beat the EOE!
Nobody can beat the!
I do not believe in it!
Oh, my God also?
Look at you!
I hope they did not need the seams!
About it as if you do not ask the.
Hurry, before us that large purchases.
Hello?
Mom, great.
S ³ Listen, I need a service aperture.
You AEOI the garage u
under canvas,
next rat poison, is
my collection of Mad magazine.
No. I'm looking for
is œrodkowym stack.
Francis, what are you talking about?
In the following order of I s about $ 20, about whether on the cover of
is "Stagnum p.i." or "Magnum P.U."?
Francis, I do not have time for this.
Of course, also do not!
/ Whenever to me
/ Nego something important, you ...
Poœpieszycie it? Because we'll be
parkowaæ km from input!
- Why do we jechaæ shopping?
- Because destroying everything.
New clothes no operation appears
magically in your drawers.
My so.
Hal!
Poœpiesz up!
Why do not you go without us?
I have average size, I like blue.
You can zaszaleæ.
Serious does not, Mom.
This industry.
/ Incurring suppressing us to a place,
/ You do not like,
/ ¿Eby to Buy Clothes
/ For which we do not depends,
for the money do not want to spend it all,
/ ¿Eby appearance Daae nicely for the
/ People who are not like us.
If you go to a shoe store,
front of the store with the pants,
is the break we can zjeœæ yogurt.
- Mom, can you will help me to choose earrings?
- No, you will help me choose the shirt.
You know what powinnyœmy do?
You two will go first,
and we two second floor.
Spotykaæ will be every 45 minutes
with pretzels and sprawdzaæ who what to buy the.
- And then ...
- Girls, Girls, quietly.
We do this five times a week.
Should you do this znudziæ.
I know why Mallory
wants spotykaæ up a circle of pretzels.
- Jason McNeal working there.
- Daisy!
In it zadurzy Did you come!
In Jason!
- You can e
- Mallory, he has the mustache.
Do not you want to make anything
in common with the guys.
We always care about me.
Come on, Daddy, poœpiesz up!
/ Damn, fairly it!
We're going to go shopping, that's that!
Want large s?
Do you want to have the s?
Do you want for yourself?
Would you like for your home?
- Want a hearty ...
- Hal ¿yet know what I like!
Yes, because he always tells me Did you come!
Over the past five Valentine's Day Did you come to ask about:
mower, the bath salt bath, earrings,
Hibachi, porcelain cat.
¿There is any formula, Lois.
It's madness, I tell you like it is!
Ok, I'll let you alone to dojœæ.
My feet are killing me.
Introduction Pimy on the food before shopping.
Well, so be it!
Just do not to cry, and you get
a pair of kitchen gloves!
Want kitchen gloves?
One are the salad with the mild sauce i ..
three large e Chili Burgers.
One of the bulbs are additional,
one of the extra beans and onions are the
and one of the beans are additional
and the onions are a triple.
Turn off the EOE star in my hatch
the last time, the Sultan!
What are you gonna do?
What child wants to do?
My limbs!
It hurts!
I do not want a hat, Hal.
Damn!
Ok, if you want napkins,
that we can start the æ ...
Keep an eye on your plates,
I'm going to ¿reæ possible!
/ I've got a hole in your sweater.
Look into the emitter,
I think about something snag the am.
Do not suffer niszczyæ their stuff.
Do you remember how had the am 2 years
and upuœci am the cake on a sweater?
Do not worry,
¿someday so they had the am.
Then my mother taught me and sew.
Why does not daddy
the return back to the pharmacy?
In the following order ê sure that the cigarette smoke.
Odpuœcie him.
Sometimes it needs a break.
It is not easy be the only
Men Everywhere the family. Look.
/ Part, honey.
/ Here we are.
- Part, Daddy!
Part of the girls.
I'm sorry, so it also takes the o
Nobody worried about the right?
I bought all the cookies.
Runs were up.
Daddy, I know you like me uszczêœliwiaæ?
Yes?
There is a set of œliczny
¿to make in the one store.
Baby, do not!
No, absolutely not.
I do not like wearing make-up ¿.
And these things are so expensive.
After what's œpieszyæ?
Hal already good. Mallory
discontinue manipulate father.
You know also that there are jobs.
- I want the appearance nicely Daae for Jason.
- What Jason?
Daddy, quieter!
He was standing there.
God, I do not believe it!
I do not know what you see in him.
Daddy, do not carefully ck,
Mallory also should be with someone else?
£ easily you speak.
Behind you are 50 years jakieœ the boys.
50!
Girls, enough already.
Renee, I know that the love sisters.
But you can not Insert ¿her life.
Mallory, I know you also want the appearance of the mature Daae
and more elaborately, but believe me.
Lipgloss for just $ 3.
You're right, Mom.
You're always right.
/ - Hey, I wanted to zjeœæ it!
/ - Too bad!
/ What you are wrong,
/ Wey your hands off my plate!
No.
Damn.
Somehow something I can help you?
- Do not do it.
- Thank you.
Okay, entering!
You will find something your size,
to take and you keep,
regardless of what the others do unto you.
It is believed that the g ajcie halfway.
Do not trust anyone.
- Trying to wystraszyæ us?
- Yes, fear is good.
That's 80% sell-¿.
Fear keep you at ¿life.
Do not be afraid.
We are with Malcolm.
Er massages the feet!
Good, is not it?
So, are amazing.
I have already two. This is
to my second of the bathroom.
Have a good time.
I ask er massages the foot with remote control
Eby and that was to the nicely wrapped.
I'm sorry, but that's the last one.
No!
And this on the show?
It's only a model.
Not for sale.
But ... you have to ... Need ...
perfect ... ¿for my wife ...
Sir!
Sorry. Part of. I'm Hal.
Do you remember? We met in the store?
- Yes, part.
- Part.
I wanted to to Buy One
weight ¿¿er for my wife.
Really?
Yes, you ¿¿pregnant wife.
For Valentine's Day.
It turned out that the latter will buy the EOE.
I wondered sure that the if the have
already two, is selling the byœ me this.
No, I do not think so.
I'm sorry.
I guess you do not understand.
I'm looking and looking for the ³ em.
Zap wages are double the price.
No, the tri!
I'm sorry, but no.
He is mine. ³ I bought it.
I'm sure you also find something else.
Ok, ok
And what about this?
This old man has przeœwituj the months bra.
We hence the outputs,
before they die of fear. Come on.
Mom, we tried ...
Not yet przymierzyliœcie these clothes.
No przypomnieliœcie
about the homework,
or you have sudden pain on the ¿the stomach.
How do you know ...
What do you take me for?
Now idŸcie przymierzyæ them.
Reese, Wey and Ida them with braæmi.
Mom, what are you doing?
Why Did you come to give me a different ¿o the blouse?
I do not wear rose-flow!
Never clad pink-flow!
It's red.
How do you have something to say,
it does not go ahead and say it!
For me the continuity's sake,
I'll find the inn.
Sorry.
Wow, what you became the face of the?
- You wrong spa ³ em.
- What do you mean?
Spa of the knee and I was so
touched the elbow of my ³
and the okieæ raise the long-ON
and long-ON and hit the face.
Nobody told me the hit, OK?
I do not want s will hear a lament.
T try on the once.
Roger that!
Why do you stand here?
You're wasting time.
I will not be at all the dresses!
You know what?
Do not need new clothes.
/ I'll be paso ¿parasites of the things found
/ At school. These are the best of the trash.
/ Mom! Mom!
/ Here you are.
Look at this dress for $ 200,
overestimated for $ 30.
O God, it's like a dream.
Mom, I do not believe this.
Together with Daisy will search the yœmy
cabinet under one of the amino
and found the yœmy clothes
they prepared for tomorrow.
Yes, we have clothes for the whole year round!
Well done, girls.
Look who's there?
Do not be offended in low to
as if you look-and with him the ice cream.
May later. Today is
our special day, Mom.
So rather than the doshas yœmy
to the best parts.
I did not find the yœmy anything for you.
Really, I opisaæ it.
Mia the common look,
but had the crazy eyes.
This will help also?
I beg your pardon.
I do not know what earlier in me
the ribbon of about five, I'm so are the people.
I think it's the pressure
white hose extensions up Valentine's Day.
He was upset and I was irrational,
but the fact is that the committing of I b than the error i ..
I stole the from of the bag!
Look at him.
Yeah, the plant adam also want the
The chip itself, which I had of him.
What are you talking about?
Reese is dead.
At least from the center.
You take command. I'll give you a half of
s of my sweets, control over remote control
and as also I will not be making up for the
lessons for you,
what do you say to heat s
towel after each shower?
Will you shut up?
He'll be fine.
Whatever you say ... boss.
Come on.
- Hey!
- I'm sorry to the am first.
Not true, it's our turn.
You only need just a moment.
I have only two things.
Lady, czekaliœmy in line
half hour. We need to have the AEOI.
I'm sorry, but it's our turn.
Move over, brat! It can your
¿sell out first, but not mine!
- Puœæ it!
- It's our turn!
Someone must nauczyæ you myœleæ,
such as older people.
Looking for a partner to dance?
Do you think that the you can take
What would you like, what?
¯ that people do not tell the,
nor the will, because you are "cherlawa".
End Pact.
Great, Reese return of!
Pulling off gniesz teeth before we start, Grandma?
Oh no, Reese return of!
Part, I'm Karen Tracy.
³ am talking with one of your sons.
Oh my God, I'll kill him ...
In precisely with such
explosions we can help you.
I'm with Oœrodka Social Welfare.
What?
What are you talking about?
There are yet podjêliœmy any decision,
but treats the security of Centre of
children very seriously there.
I wanted to, ¿Eby and future
you to evaluate.
What is the last known address of the children's father?
It's a mistake jakaœ each!
My boys the boys are good!
It's not me,
someone my the substrate of the teeth s.
This is your child?
Wanted to am to Buy slippers, and they
pounced on me like vultures!
She k ³ amie! We wanted to
just cut off by tugging the æ of the Rees!
Lois!
Thanks to God, you are also here.
We hence the exit before ...
Move!
Mom, seriously, not faster!
You must be so szczêœliwa.
You will not believe what the want you to
families have to deal with.
Girls, Hurry up!
It's our turn to finish.
I do not know which color you choose:
peach, melon and the ososiowy.
I must take the æ all.
No, honey, you dokonaæ choice.
Not fairly, I must also kupowaæ waste,
although I can not also choose what I want!
Please, honey. This set of
to make ¿u, o who asks Did you come.
Thank you very much, Daddy!
Hal, what are you to do the EOE?
Uzgodniliœmy, also will not get it.
And He asked me again and he said and,
Later also agrees Did you come.
Well, you know ..
and they will do the ignition akane eyes.
I ... I just ... I ...
Mallory!
How can I Did you come to do?
Do not worry, Mom.
I will not malowaæ home.
I know how desperately
you want to be the most prettier.
Mallory, unless all
we are a bit confused.
Can we talk about this at home,
How will the przymierzaæ new clothes?
Œwietny the idea, Mom.
By that time runs out
Operation of her books diet pills.
- Pill of diet books?
- I have a spare metabolism, OK?
I have not slept calories Engage the c at night sex,
the other guys on the lake!
³ am thinking that the evening
have u try assembly
There is no any assembly ¿u!
Shut up, fancy-pants,
You do not know anything.
I know that you're in the ¿y
K ³ amie, it's ridiculous!
I'm not pregnant strives, because I know that the sex
Pricing is, immoral, funny. Do not wait ...
All right, Renee.
Well, also already know the.
I'm ready for teenage ¿is the eñstwo.
Will zajebiœcie.
He is the father! Did you come to have slept with him,
just because also I like!
It was necessary to poprosiæ for the request!
my brush of hair!
Girls, please! You can store not ...
Girls do not do the!
- We should be within easier!
- No, Mom! You're the easy.
/ You are still deceiving you.
We are girls,
we know how you think!
I will not hesitate to use the red expertise!
/ Mom, Dad, the part!
Frances, what are you doing here?
Powinnaœ be in college.
He threw the am it.
But do not worry, I have a job.
The new Hooters, a mill wheel.
The tipping enough for rent
for trailers, maintenance husband and beer hose.
We lecieæ. Fighting cocks
the start up for half an hour,
you have a large frame to move.
You should speak to my
daughter a little more ...
Leave him alone!
He does not like the EOE ¿any of my husband ¿s!
I always try to us separable
and that is why I hate you!
Ever since d up odchudzi the EOE,
It's does not fit!
That's not true.
Girls do not do the.
Girls are nicer.
Girls are better.
Odpuœæ yourself!
What do you think, after what we have?
Honey, come on!
You can do it.
Been yet less than a 300m ³ s!
Believe me, Hal.
There is no escape!
There is no escape,
regardless of anything.
Szczêœliwych Valentine's Day, baby.
I wpad of it than Zesz the night.
This is the perfect gift.
I know that you like it,
because it is not for you.
Thank you, Hal,
is ideal.
- Come on, Dad, let's go.
- I play with Malcolm.
Wait, almost zapomnieliœmy ...
Szczêœliwych Valentine's Day.
Zostawiliœmy coconut,
because we know that the it's your favorite.
Thank you boys the boys, I like very much.
See you later.
OBYO to a girl of the ...
T ³ ³ explains: MoszeUsz
www.tvsubtitles.net