Hal!
I leave you a sandwich.
Thanks, honey.
Wow. Fast gone through the a
EOE had to be really hungry.
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x18 "Reese's Party"
T the interpreter:
Charles MoszeUsz and polishchaser1
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.0 MB
Ch ChodŸcie the boys, œniadanie!
SpóŸnicie up.
- Hal, what are you doing?
- For me the continuity's sake!
- My last good tie.
- ¿After you buy the am twelve.
- Zu ¿s were up.
/ - Mom!
For God's sake!
Reese wysmarka of the at my shirt!
For Dewey once to the s ³ dirty
are my panties under a cushion.
One of them is used of my calculator
graphic, ¿Eby open the juice!
Everyone quiet down! Your
mother is a nine month of you strives,
there is adequate stressed
and does not need screaming!
You know what?
I know how to solve the.
There will be only us two days.
We will have a weekend of silence
and quiet, before the baby is born.
- Without us?
- You know the plan?
How to go to put my Reese
bus that met with the grandmother of Canada.
After school, I'll take
Malcolm to Stevie.
And Dewey is with me.
You're the winner szczêœliwym.
Why us apart?
Because it's the only way that the judge
let us wyjechaæ of the city.
Nice to have fun at school, suckers.
Sends the post card to you from Whitehorse.
Reese, this industry.
The journey takes 26 hours
and also return 26 hours.
Your backpack is full en food.
And no one to call the grandmother.
Wait a minute. We spend a whole were
Weekend on the bus?
Enjoy, and also in the end we are.
I do not believe that the had to am by
you AEOI additional 130 meters.
I will not be the semi-pays for parking,
when the valley is free.
Welcome to "Love birds and couples resort".
- Wow!
- Hello, we have a reservation.
We can quickly make it easier for?
I must skorzystaæ the toilet.
Again.
I'm sorry, but the room
ordered state is not already in stock.
Oddaliœcie our room?
Sorry, spóŸnili State
4 hours and did not even called.
It's the wife.
We had to up zatrzymywaæ
at 15 km, because you still have the sikaæ.
You do not have to continuously sikaæ.
Do not martwiæ,
for sure I'll find something.
I do not know whether the state read the booklet,
but it is a romantic hotel for couples.
- We know that the so.
- See what can I do.
I must sit the œæ.
- Angela.
- Yes, Ron. Yes.
Sorry, had to sit the œæ am.
Do not disturb me.
We could switch off the fireplace?
I'm sweating like pigs.
You and I have sat in front of the
very entertaining weekend.
Tomorrow morning there is jazz in the Farmer's Market.
Then Lifetime presents
an intimate portrait of Sandra Bullock.
Tomorrow night is happening
in the park of a political nature.
Sounds fun?
- I think I want to just pobawiæ.
- Pobawiæ?
Yeah, I think we can at something pograæ.
So feel free to start itself?
No, let's play together.
- What do you mean?
- Let's play fort.
I do not have the Fort.
I have a Clue, but this edition
Collector not open.
If you want,
I can you show this picture.
No you must have game Fort.
Just do it.
Do not play the EOE at Fort
with his friends, playing to the EOE child?
Of course, also like that.
I had the friends of,
a lot of friends.
And you're low!
Come on, will show you ê.
Good morning, says
Mel Jenkins with a trucking company.
I do not know how to tell.
I guarded of your son, as you ask of a,
But when we stopped
the went to the bathroom i ..
Had to wyskoczyæ the window,
when he departs ¿d ¿Alio.
I test drove the 100 km,
before he noticed that the em.
What! How can the master of doing this
my son's favorite?
The only one she loves the am,
le ¿s now jakimœ ditch.
Well, I'd better call
Shop with coffins. Goodbye.
/ United event, today!
/ Par-Tay - an event for the whole
/ With alcohol, with sex and use the ywkami.
He knew I was! He knew I was,
Also finds you at home.
Can not you zaufaæ for 5 seconds,
let alone for the whole weekend s!
Ok, Listen to.
Do not tell me ...
Wait a minute.
What are you doing here?
I? I came to guard the home front
those of the young things that you do.
What's in the bag?
Spark?
Strawberries in chocolate?
"Bezsennoœæ in Seattle"?
- Oh God, you're gay.
- Not at all.
I do not know how to do the I, but
I invite Kathy McCulskey of the evening.
Kathy McCulskey?
I am impressed by inserting.
She does not go out of the house on
less than the minimum macanko.
In precisely because
We need a house for himself.
Sorry Malcolm,
but already I planned the party.
Reese, saw the EOE sufficient at
movies for teens,
¿Eby Know-how poorly it's over!
I not only saw the em
But he teaches them the em.
I have found the key b ³ I ¹ d
In each of these films
the event is on Saturday night.
My, the fifth special.
It gives me an extra day,
¿Eby Fill the pool, replace the crystal to,
æ undo the counter in the car
and wsadziæ plant was torn.
Please do not do this to me!
Let me tell you something, I'll try to utrzymaæ
closed room, the longest for much longer.
³ am thinking that the zarezerwowaliœmy apartment?
No Ma'am, this room has the ¿female connector.
Thank you very much.
Why bother the confirmation of your head,
as well as Take the room.
Do not be with each of them and, it's not their fault.
- Oh, so that's my fault.
- I did not tell of it.
At least we
A nice view of the parking lot.
At home I must wykrêcaæ neck,
¿TO SEE car.
You know what?
Peace is what it is.
So we have the cieszyæ.
We are here, we have time for yourself.
Let's try this cieszyæ.
I must to the bathroom.
Of course.
/ Œwietnie! They promised us
/ Bathtub in the shape of a heart.
/ We have a bathtub in the shape of a bathtub.
For me the continuity's sake, come on!
I know that you are
pregnant strives and you uncomfortable.
I know that you are swollen, and the swelling, enlarged and inflated!
But you narzekaæ the crap!
/ I'm sorry, I'm also such a fire you.
/ For three weeks we will not have
/ Already been through this never przechodziæ.
We do not know.
/ You said what?
He said I was, also I will switch the car.
No, You said,
Also we do not know, but Hal
we know it,
I had the vasectomy EOE.
- Yes, I had the.
- O God, do not do the EOE this!
- Ok the break of me hello!
- Just a little.
Hal, holding the bag EOE
ice on the crotch for 3 days!
That should be something znaczyæ.
Hal, we talked about it,
zgodziliœmy up.
You will agree Did you come to,
I've never wanted to I had a vasectomy!
- There are plenty of other ways!
- Yes, acting as hell.
We had a child
the diary is the ¿eñskiego,
the insert contraceptive
child with a condom.
Oh yes, and two children of abstinence.
Lois, I do not understand what
These things are important to me!
Valuable?
Hal, come on!
You're not that guy.
Do not be one of EOE.
When this happens,
Each guy he is.
- C4.
- Made.
E4.
Hit.
Hey, you want me przyjœæ to the party?
Will œwietnie.
The parents are away for the whole weekend s.
S entire weekend?
S you've heard.
¿48 hours without any supervision.
Whatever you want.
Practical FREEDOM.
Interesting.
Let's do it.
What is this junk?
What's going on?
Ok, will be so
We have a private interest.
It is now our garage
For the next 48 hours.
Do not come here,
do not ask for it.
Wash off the back before your parents.
Never know the,
Also we invite you to the EOE.
What are the hell are you doing?
The explanation is very clear,
s but I can hear the beating of your own heart.
Reese, these things ...
In precisely say, and it does not suit me.
I can you zaufaæ
and will not speak?
Should I delete something the æ,
¿Eby it was to physically impossible.
And that's not the worst part of the operation.
When are your dissects the purse,
the grove cut the vas deferens,
k the ad are on the table.
Snip! I do not always
hit the first time.
I can postawiæ you
the next drink? Please give us.
Mine were three hours
ever since fault these guys took over the house.
As of now, was to some
the ¿acres, a bottle thrown at me.
And even the threat of death.
On the other hand, do not cease the
Reese bredziæ the sauce.
So the evening He could Daae appearance otherwise.
Pasta flavor of how the AFA?
Œ For as the hour I will Potrzebowo the
to throw 70-liter drum ... czegoœ.
Fault dŸcie fast, no catches
attention and not taking any breathe it.
S ³ Look, I must of something spytaæ,
Although I try not to interfere the caæ.
When you try to us it still by tugging the æ ...
Approx.
Donnie, soufflé is almost ready.
- Who is it?
- I do not know, it's ... for them.
- Who ordered the girl?
/ - Not me.
- Kathy, part.
- Part.
No You said to me,
Also bed the other guys here.
Well ¿...
It also read something on the wall
in the toilet, does not mean that the true.
No. Listen to.
These are my cousins.
You know, distant cousins.
They came up unexpectedly.
So you see,
This is not the best time.
Of course not, is continuously we can
zjeœæ supper and porozmawiaæ. Bo also!
- Yes part of Young man, will show a little class.
- Thank you.
Kathy Listen to.
You've got to zaufaæ.
Hey, zaproœ girl to the center.
/ The Friends Of Distinction
/ "Grazing in the Grass"
/ Sure it's really mellow Grazin 'in the Grass
/ Grazin 'in the grass is a gas,
/ Baby, can you dig it
/ What a trip
/ Just watchin 'as the world goes past
/ Grazin 'in the grass is a gas,
/ Baby, can you dig it
/ There are so many good things to see
/ While Grazin 'in the Grass
/ Grazin 'in the grass is a gas,
/ Baby, can you dig it
98, 99, 100!
Ready or not, here I come.
Here you are.
What is it?
Nobody I never have found the.
- So that the hide so well.
- Yeah, that's probably why.
Please postawiæ it anywhere.
It is not easy it was to znaleŸæ, girl.
Can the lady wyobraziæ that the people
do not use the. At the end of a hotel for couples.
- I do not know how to operate the unit.
- For sure you'll figure this out.
Bo ¿e I have worked here for over 30 years
and never does the em.
¿We see different kinds of couples, but ...
Thank you, I'll finish it.
All right. I must zejœæ room
318 and Fill the bathtub p ¿variety of flakes.
Arm.
5 points for Chuck.
Again crotch. 50 points.
Fine of an impact, Randy.
Chuck, Randy Insert time of the catalyst.
Ok, we can dokoñczyæ later.
Do not give up Chuck,
are still being you can wygraæ.
I think once again we have a party.
¯ Are you kidding me?
We are here adnikami the plant.
No.
Reese, do not you've heard ever
of the "Stockholm Syndrome"?
You start kolegowaæ up with the kidnappers.
What are the kidnappers?
They saved my force.
- Because you decided not zabijaæ!
- Same.
They made us byœmy
took part in jakimœ crime.
Spacing of the shower
sweet an extension piece in front of the garage em!
Poor Kathy has
be completely terrified installed.
Where in general has gone through the a?
I'll never forgive,
J are also still in the ¹ ³ ¹ I gn.
We need something zrobiæ.
/ Take it easy, some
/ Of them are really nice.
This large y foretold the future of these?
S ³ Look, themselves
this can not be helped.
We do not know how to
radziæ with such criminals.
We need help.
Well zrobiliœcie,
That after me zadzwoniliœcie.
I'm sorry that the gnêliœmy Pulling off the ranch you here.
This should not last for long.
All are in the middle?
Yes, one is in the bedroom with Kathy.
- Who is Kathy?
- I have with her the date.
The ope Ch.
What do you do?
As the exhaust gniemy!
Not so fast.
You have to przemyœleæ.
We'll deal with it very gently.
When you're dealing with
of the deposit on the situation are the psychological,
you have to remember that there are many
subtle machinations that are part of the game.
- Donnie?
- Francis?
What are you doing here, I was thinking of,
Also you are in Alaska.
No, now I work on a ranch.
How are you?
You are still working at Kelsey's?
- No, I have adapted them for karaoke.
- This is the city.
So, Listen to. This house
my parents. These are my brothers.
I know that we knew not, but together
with my friends some of them wystraszyliscie.
So, may be carrying
elsewhere?
Yeah, you know, looks as it
Also will keep you ¿ko,
So do not.
S ³ Look, I do not want to ¿ebym
rang the police, right?
Are you sure you do not mind,
if I tell them who topples the tower also pressure.
- That was EOE you, Francis.
- Really?
So can I tell them
at the crossing of the highway.
It is to the EOE ¿you.
Car Wash?
Sinkhole?
All of you.
SiedŸcie politely, and we
we'll be at home. Never mind.
I think they Dalio
sufficient for thinking.
Hal.
It seemed for me,
Also I saw the spider and the meadow.
Can we save
and checking out in the morning?
I think so.
We should zostaæ
œniadaniu in the morning?
Well, we jeœæ.
You're sure that the no
I'm too old for winky dinks?
The box of arms forever
you can yourself odpuœciæ.
Well, I could of przywaliæ
in itself a means of that window.
What the hell is that!
Let them are asleep.
We should not even be here,
and devices are co-ed dzacie the party?
What's the fat chick?
Ok, fairly.
May all the exit!
Nobody does not tell us what we robiæ!
Craig ...
¯ no excuses. You and your
Friends have great being inconvenienced.
Let's go to the apartment Craig
and wait until Sunday.
We can not go there zostawiæ!
Dewey, are the principles which
I taught in a military school.
The needs of a group of mostly hose extensions on the needs
a guy who does not know how quickly biegaæ.
No! Malowaliœmy their faces.
Do not leave it here.
Dewey, we can not do zrobiæ.
I know what to do.
Seven minutes to check out.
Do you have a soap, towel and salt for bath angle?
I have.
¿I have the shampoo and slippers.
I can not znaleŸæ the shower caps.
- I have them.
- Good.
Shall we?
No.
It œmieszne.
Here we come to one spêdziæ
cy are relaxing, romantic weekend.
And we are more
nervous than before I left.
Now already nothing we can zrobiæ.
We can.
We have seven minutes.
Ignition aciliœmy, it's use.
How?
Taking any one ¹ ³ ¹ I to
each other before leaving.
Better to do it right, because I do not
We will have another chance for 18 years.
I guess I can sk guarded for practical reasons up
to perform the gesture.
Rub my feet?
With the pleasure.
What can I do for you?
Please leave me the nucleus alone.
Consent.
/ Madam?
/ Check that the two hours
/ Ago. We need to prepare the room.
/ Hello?
What the hell are you doing?
I think that would be the best
as if you left. Now!
You think so?
- Yes, just thinking.
- I think we have to refuse.
Ok, Donnie, but I remember.
It will force me hello yet to do so.
Really?
And what exactly?
He said I was.
Oh, You said.
Your mom.
The inline em for you.
You said my mom?
/ - Donnie!
- Mom?
What are you doing here?
I'm trying to hide the how to
ashamed of your behavior.
And I wonder,
where perpetrated than the am b ³ ¹ d
Come on.
Your father and I we tried
Daae you the best force,
and you just rip up the acasz?
Mom, not the me you solve the,
now take decisions on our own.
Such decisions are making?
Such a force selected the EOE!
Who you hiding in the store
with cheap suits?
Ch of ope, you have the bane sts.
Do not be so m each are dry
David Alan Ferguson!
Believe me, Each of your
stepfathers is discovered.
After ¿Goodbye up with friends of me
and get in the car. Immediately!
I have forgotten what it
kablowaæ cool feeling.
/ Yes, everything was to all right.
You know, boredom, silence,
boredom. Fun, but boring.
Look who I answer to stop the
after the've never seen it,
ever since the d it there I will escort the.
Canada was to a œwietna.
I'll bring all the bananas.
Know-You really want to?
No.
www.tvsubtitles.net