Not again!
This child to kill us.
/ Jamie continuity for me ...!
/ This is on the wall!
Ch of boys, the third level!
Yard, now!
Bo also!
How can the outputs of the diapers!
If I knew he was
it is used the'd adhesive tape!
Reese, Wey respirator,
Clean the bucket and the wall.
Find the star Malcolm the diaper
and bury at least a meter below the ground.
Dewey, prepare ¿in the garden.
/ We have already diapers!
How mogliœmy zu Insert
double the donut in one day!
Jamie gets dirty the towel already.
- Dewey, come upwards from pid ¿amy!
- Here we go again! This is my last!
We go into the shower.
/ No, no, no!
/ Wait, wait!
/ God, I have it on in the hair!
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x22 "childcare"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.3 MB
So, am wanted to check our
place on the list for the nursery ¿.
What?
Why spadliœmy on the reserve list?
These are the offenses of minors and
should be known to the general public!
Hal, what do we do?
End of my maternity leave,
Tomorrow I go back to work
and are still being we do not have
day care for Jamie!
You also will be d for much longer in the house.
The budget we have tight but
always more we can conserve.
This is crazy.
There is already in the juice.
Thinners water supply with water!
Good!
We are desperate!
Must be jakiœ care program
the Child Lock on who we become.
Where the hell did not We were looking for?
Include the czamy to a church!
We know nothing about these people!
May the best are a group of health
the Child Lock in town.
I take care of the Jamie for free.
So in May are up dowiedzieæ,
That we are practicing cymi
Calvinists years! Do you understand?
Why Malcolm does not have to be here?
Wanted to byœ zamieniæ up
Role of him now?
Puœæ. Puœæ.
And as each also pomodliæ me?
Do not know how to modliæ!
He wants us just to become familiar. So by
¿next six half hour, but you know,
That God is the best for the
in the universe and the end!
Hello everyone.
I am a pastor Roy.
I understand that the want przenieœæ
its membership of the brotherhood in Denville?
Yes. Very long
we were part of the onkami in Denville.
I did not know of,
Also we have the churches in Denville.
Already it is not. Exchanged
go to a strip bar.
Really?
Not quite naked whole. Only topless
with tassels, but are still being ...
We want The remaining
onkami part of the fraternity.
Community.
I love that word!
We are very active.
I am sure that the boys the boys
to the connecting group Bible.
I'm sure!
¿We organize these trips,
retreats, prayer breakfast included in the ...
- Caring for children?
- Caring for children.
Really? Lois, are the heard Did you come?
Take care of the Child Lock up!
I did not know that the am!
Thanks to the service that always ugom
we were related the disappearance of the churches of em!
That's wonderful!
You know the 10 commandments?
Yes, of course.
We love commandments! Third
I helped to survive for you to heavy moments.
But it all goes back to God!
So ... God ... the whole quite fine of y
Yes, it is my favorite of them all!
I promise that the you again
employment, as business moves from hooves.
³ I did not see such a slowdown, Otto.
Loosen the EOE six employees in a week.
It's the festival in Roswell.
All turyœci view the venom of the
place where he landed the planter of the UFO.
Our people lose their job,
because a bunch of tourists thoughts,
Also ship with green ludzikami
the crashed there? This is ridiculous!
Yeah, I see there are!
The government take away the Each piece of evidence
the secret vault 50 years ago.
This newspaper editors?
I'm at the ranch Grotto i ..
Oh my God, is back!
Something strange is happening in the sky!
I can see the light and jakiœ ship!
Arriving ¿d ¿ajcie here soon!
It seems to me that
Also will be here in 20 minutes.
But you'd better Hurry up!
- Part Donna, we are!
- Part, Lois.
It must be your angel of sticks.
I do not know if take away the am good
Jamie. Never so it will not.
Easy, easy.
Why are you so nervous?
Sometimes it is the small children
so keep the first day.
That must be it.
Unloaded the GNE am a little milk.
Oh, boy.
I have a large gland that were lactic acid.
Once you have begin to, it's their stop.
It's so unusual the e! At home
sometimes we forget that the child we have.
¯ Goodbye, skarbeczku.
Quickly the Arrangement skarbeczku.
I know you want the mother zostaæ
briefly on the first day.
I think that it ...
And the rest.
/ What you are wrong!
He says the EOE, also want to lecieæ
South Africa, you g of stupid old man!
I will not speak at
I robiæ! You're on my ¹ ¿¹!
Always been so quiet on here?
Best Game of God is
Also always be your turn.
/ - And that's why ...
- What does the "T" on the wall?
/ - Excuse me for a moment.
- We'll talk about that later.
Hal I have an urgent meeting in the office.
Catechesis will finish for me?
Me!
Do not be afraid. This is a story
about Daniel and the lions.
Surely you know it over the memory in.
Okay, class ...
This is a story about the man in his quest name
Daniel i .. apparently the lions.
"You'll ³ on Aug ustanowiæ Dariusz
over your 120 satraps,
who had przebywaæ
in the whole kingdom,
zaœ over them three supervisors
One of them was to Daniel. "
- When will the lions?
- Soon, Dewey, patience.
I Dariusz he said to Daniel:
Surely you every ¿ê
wrzuciæ the cave.
Where Daniel soon a fire were lions.
Am thinking of, that God savings of Daniel.
Well, of course.
³ I had to dojœæ.
As it is written, ...
lion ... wyplu of it.
Together with the lamb.
Tell me the CYM lamb.
Truly, it turned out that the
big lump in the middle of a boa constrictor
That was missing for fire Score leœny.
Gathered they will hear,
he says to them by walkie-talkie:
"Commander, are you hear me?"
/ Do not you walk perfectly well into the socket
/ Me the continuity and wracaæ Full A shame.
/ Z 's smile zaœpiewajmy chorus:
/ Powœci the gliwoœæ,
/ Powœci the gliwoœæ, powœci the gliwoœæ.
Œwietnie bawiliœmy up, right?
Pastor Roy can wezwaæ police on us.
Yes, Reese?
I can podpisaæ œ as the list,
¿Eby hence the exit?
Reese, you're not forced to become.
Since the output prevents you
silent g in g of the person to repeat half of the months:
that they all are
szczêœliwsi me?
As you know already, Mrs. Pitzer,
church services secretary,
and has been paralyzed after being bitten ¿ed
footed the ball on Zesz-season retreat.
Thanks to this tragedy were formed of wonderful e,
ce inspiring scenes
that I painted of a mouth.
Elijah flying the months to heaven
in a fiery chariot.
Jonah and the whale in the Red Sea.
/ The heat is being done to the heart,
/ When it is seen
pob as God bless the
mouth and teeth of the woman.
Oh boy!
Wow!
- Mom, I do not want AEOI this class!
- You see this check?
He'll make the am it
I have custody of the child.
Those who earn the,
I can wyraziæ are your opinions.
Those who do not, id classes with the Bible.
Hal, former three serious
incident on the way home.
We spaliæ seat in the car.
Dad, talk to her are,
I do not want AEOI for these classes.
Malcolm, you Daae
ago of these churches a chance.
I understand also that something else
than what you are accustomed to the EOE.
I opened the em for it
experience and make you feel the spiritual variety.
- How looks as Hal?
- Super. I can see that the already insert a window.
We are all at your own risk toolpath.
Do not like to walk perfectly well in the bag for garbage,
but I have already clean shirts.
For the sake litoœæ, discontinue semi-AkAA.
Part of Donna. Do not say,
Jamie also again the poorly behaved.
- It has a terribly large for energy.
- Yes, it's true.
- Thank you for everything.
- No problem.
And the same answer Seth
and in May the podrzuciæ it to you?
- Seth? What Seth?
- Take care of Seth Richards.
Information is
in the schedule of two weeks.
See?
Saturday - Lois is Seth.
You do not understand.
I only leave their
child outside the Co-op.
Do not care for others - it works.
All up exchange.
This is cooperation.
³ am thinking that the one
of the churches of this, where ... you know ...
the people feel good when
the selfless do something for other people.
Tomorrow I must pracowaæ! I'm sorry,
but you wymyœliæ something else!
- Seth, hence the need to exit!
- This is my fortress!
I'll be there in a minute ...
/ UFOs are noticeably over a local ranch.
/ Foreman says: "The Flies of the above
/ Earth and the changing of the color green. "
I must admit that I was skeptical of,
but poszczêœci of the we
the visits are genuine UFOs.
Yes, yes, yes, but look at me.
Are still being shaking, after
I see of this ship at your own eyes.
I tell you,
spoke to me telepathically.
/ He was the subsequent observation!
Move the alien on the ranch Songbird!
May the real part of l the downika!
What! Not true! K ³ ¹ s!
Otto, we can not pozwoliæ people ...
For your own safety
Do not wave to them!
The thinking that the hands are our bodies are semi-income securities.
/ You can store ¹ æ start something that you
/ Do not want to skoñczyæ!
- What?!
- I love you!
Discontinue so speak!
Ever since the error to the czyliœmy to a church,
behaves very strangely!
Because I am now another Reese.
I sat on the lessons of the Bible
dead, when suddenly I wake the.
I want to now committed ¿owaæ
in something beyond the Sun.
In something of great ego.
Come over here.
You can not just me
uderzyæ as it used to?
I'm too szczêœliwy.
It is beautiful!
Wymalowaliœcie and everything!
Welcome home, Hal.
I feel so Trim the oczony!
This time it pour!
You're the best!
May you all God b bless!
Unless you delete my own in the drink.
Sorry.
This kid killing me of ...
Where is he?!
Lois, for the sake litoœæ,
the kids are watching or not!
Where it has found the EOE?
Under your car.
Splits up the candy bar with the squirrel!
Not the venom and, unless it is sick.
Lois, I try to be
the most helpful,
but I can not goniæ
the entire operation store!
Why not close it
in the car, like the other mothers of the email.
Ms. Monson wants to ¿Eby
release of a lady of my brother!
What?
Ever since d Reese comes to your lessons,
became the me I really were!
Trust me, it's awful.
I do not like a church!
Ever since there przyszliœmy d,
it is continuously thinking about things.
What kind of God makes
Suggest children also are outside the schools!
This is not the torture.
I'm sure you also have their reasons.
As Roy says the pastor that God
is large for larger and m are smarter than us.
A trial domyœlenia about the thoughts,
it's like the old ant and
rozgryŸæ up my thoughts.
Yes, exactly.
But we can zaufaæ his m³ droœci
and wierzyæ, also cares about us.
Like me with the anthill in the backyard.
The entire bottom of the email I watch the ants
try the c domyœliæ in
which are good and which of the e
But all-looking like ants,
So here we all uderzaæ.
There is ...
I struck them in the ¿I garden,
I poured the gasoline are, running over ¿d ¿³ em and the mower.
Bed ¹ c honest, it seems to me that
Also reflected on me with the cost of the.
These ants can were up
modliæ me a whole day,
and still I have not heard of the service.
- I can not were the zrobiæ.
- But, no ...
So it is with us.
¿This we can not do anything about zrobiæ,
So why przejmowaæ?
Better get a feel for the em.
That's good, but ...
The only thing we can zrobiæ it be
most ¿yczliwymi and decent.
I staraæ up Do not stop,
if God is with great ¹ ³ ¹ charged.
Part!
Make me ¿cost of $ 50!
- I'm the cute?
- No, you're not the pretty!
Mia the am because of you lot
k the hassle and I'm fairly, are you've heard?
- Seth?
- Part, Mom! Part, Dad!
- Is it ...
- You're in a church?
Yes, I am. I know that it can oddly
Daae appearance, but are his dribbling say:
did not know the am, do I also
today opiekowaæ brat ...
child ... is of the people are.
- Dot pleasure?
- For God's sake!
Seth! OdejdŸ from the
women, now!
I painted a picture of the pretty.
/ My ¿can the reeds
/ Ranch Songbird - left
/ Ranch Grotto - right
- What the hell are you doing here?
- What does it look like the impossible?
What kind of alien.
Œwiecisz not even in darkness!
- Hence the Beat!
- You hence the falling!
You get out ...
Hal had the terrible am
As of the child.
I'm sorry that the ³ I can not help you.
Barely back of em
the whole day trips parish council.
Did you come I knew that the there are 6 types
May Hay and all the patrons?
Hal Listen to me. Beyond
resist was to work with the child.
But you are still thinking of am, I have also
choice and I have to robiæ for Jamie.
His parents came to the a terrible
situation, and then ... the am to see.
- Hey, it's the pretty picture.
- This is the Genesis ¿s can in the bulrushes.
I began to am myœleæ about this story.
When a mother and had to exit the your little one
and entrust them of a river,
Foster Eby ¿³ be someone else.
I want to be as the mother of the!
Hal ...
I do not like the child.
You say not serious?
I know it's awful,
does not deserve to be a mother are,
should be full at the ideal
the continuity of maternal love, but she's not!
There is simply no!
- I do not believe that the are talking about!
- I know, it's awful.
- Really do not remember, do you?
- What you do not remember?
Honey, Did you come to hate
all of our children.
Did you come I can not withstand
¿under any of the jakieœ two months.
What!
With Reese six months, but
It biting the nipples, so I do not blame him.
Did you come zostawiæ wanted Francis to
rural market, ¿Eby Foster were his cows.
Oh, my God also?
You're tired. Everything seems to
Trim up the words including the sun, but trust me.
In a few weeks
you will love this child as
no sooner does not love the child.
- Really?
- Yes.
Hey, do not I hear.
Where's the baby?
Asleep in silence.
Already an hour.
What is are the sweet.
Who Such use would it not kochaæ?
We need to stop the paintings of?
No ... we just znaleŸæ painter atheist.
Come on!
As early as the time!
All I understood the
the first day in the Church.
When everything is ready,
This will be the best day of my life ¿!
What are you doing?
I'll be the anniversary above the clouds and experience
joy, which are only having to know the birds.
Fry is static on the cables
high voltage.
I am not afraid.
I believe in the vision of his.
I love you, Dewey.
It's amazing!
I can see hence the roof of the car my dad!
At the beginning of the longs I'll be!
No, I'm surprised as you are.
/ No, I'm surprised as you are.
/ Amazing wyœcig!
/ What it's the sweet taste!
/ Savings the key for me!
/ By the've lost in life.
/ He was em œlepy,
/ But I have found of his keys.
The government of the United States
not happy
the level of interest,
What we have created in this sector!
Why even a whole that confusion?
All about abductions
and experiments aliens
is zmyœlone, right?
Yes. There are no aliens.
But are experiments.
But of the czyliœcie two weeks ago?
Believe me. You do not want ¿ebyœmy
were part of a your churches of a
Do not fit into
to civilized people.
Come on, I'm sure, ¿e ..
You see, in precisely
about such things we want.
www.tvsubtitles.net