It's not fair.
The move up.
It's a shame.
In case you have k-o-n-i.
/ Malcolm in the Middle
/ 4x16 - Academic Octathalon
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Was this crisp
Do you feel any different?
No. It's all right.
Took the last of the EOE.
You need to fill with a bowl from scratch.
Let it.
No more beautiful.
This ant.
I know that.
Already j ³ ¹ I saw.
No, Dewey.
You do not understand.
It scout.
If you find something appetizing,
soon they will be here an entire lot.
And therefore I will take care that the scout
not of the deposit s check in at the headquarters of the motherboard g.
/ - Dewey, time to bed each!
- Ready, Dad?
- £ Put tional coffee.
- Oh, yes. Just give me a while to ...
Rowing! Forward!
Poœpiesz, Dad.
Forward, horsey!
I have the most beautiful dress
in winter ball.
It is satin, long service, i ..
What color is the difference between pink and purple ¿?
Tional of Fio.
/ English sounds like "let's get moving."
Sorry.
Is not she lovely,
when excited?
Her cheeks are red in
and her eyes the shiny.
I must tell,
Also szczêœciarz me.
So really you're going to wykosztowaæ up
the limousine, tuxedo and the whole rest of it?
In life.
We're not going to the prom.
That would kill the oh my
fund skurzanej jacket.
- What are you talking about?
- All obmyœli of em.
Let her myœleæ that the go, and then,
just before prom, wdam out during the dn the fight.
I will be in a very bad,
will not be wanted to the AEOI,
and the next day apology,
It will take me back,
and is already on clearance,
and until her birthday.
/ Malcolm!
Where would the EOE?
- Management of today I urgent meeting.
- What? Just as we had one of last the night above.
This academic Oœmiobój.
Face the cheapest ¿s minds szymi
with the schools in the entire country.
Since then, the æwiczymy
each second breakfast included.
- I was thinking of that the it is to be fun.
- Fun ... is for losers.
Everyone sanctification, Malcolm.
I had to interrupt cello lessons.
I've not gone the
the funeral of an uncle.
I have for the last three months
I opuœci in the study,
Such use would be our obligatory the zkowym
trójkowym student.
This food is not
to eat.
It is here that I did not have the hassle k by forcing you
to work during the second breakfast included.
And now buying up!
Why can not I cancel?
This g of silly!
Extracurricular Classes
are very important.
Do you think that the same Fridays sufficient,
by dostaæ to carols ¿u?
Not sufficient.
Besides, it's a good opportunity,
to become familiar to the other m dre children.
It is never se per cubic young baby,
to make the zaæ new contacts.
Sure. Wrap the friendships zaæ
the whole force that the festival geeks.
Spend a weekend in winning the trophy
show the lying like m³ dry're not make you a nerd.
Either way you go.
Oh boy. Just not in the cabins.
Honey, where the deposit s I spray the ants?
Part of Dad.
Time of bed tional coffee.
And so.
Listen to Dewey.
We porozmawiaæ.
You do bigger, and there are many
cool things about being a large white boy of Caucasian teenage boy.
A big boy the boys do not get in the
to bed tional machine, because it hurts daddy.
So despite the fact that the it's funny
You will not be already in bawiæ of bed tional coffee.
- All right.
- That's good.
- So already you do not love.
- What?
Already I do not love.
You can not speak czegoœ such
just because you're a nervous.
I'm sorry, but nothing
can not help the way I feel.
Good night, Dad.
Reese, buy the EOE already a tuxedo?
Ball is in two days.
Of course, also I will buy the.
It's good.
Hey, look at this.
This is my dress.
The truth that the incredible?
You're sure that it will be
pasowaæ for you because ...
You're so fat.
Sometimes terrible g of slate with you.
Anyway
I like the the bows.
You also ought to Buy
which fit the shoes to them.
Part of honey.
You Will not Believe
I've had the day.
My day is ¿to the interesting months.
Am had to carry the work is dirty clothes,
I again forgot to answer EOE clothes from the laundry.
For me the continuity's sake.
In precisely I finished the 12-hour of the shift.
The last thing they are
We need from you ...
You know what?
Let's not do that.
- What?
- K the canvas.
- Too often argue.
- You're right.
Why though again we can not be silent
Daae and the time for the mutual continuity me?
Just ...
let's not talk about it.
Œwietnie me today
the uk are made from Piam.
As if each moment ¿can be of a perfect,
and the and the and the perfectly with the next are the ideal moments are.
I am so with Gretchen
twenty-five years.
S heard the am This
Szminkowy Gatku.
Keep it for later.
See? There is nothing better
of compliance is the ¿Notes This.
Let me also ask you about something.
You and Gretchen never
spieraliœcie about Home Responsibilities?
If for example, is something to be done,
you're doing it, it is ¿, not marudzicie?
I never gave it
I wondered not.
I have already dosyæ that the entire struggle!
- We work for you ¿ko whole day.
- Works like the ox, and you do not appreciate.
Spend the money
for all of your cravings!
It seems!
Spend the money,
if we were to have a machine they do.
/ The square root of 8,649 bottles
/ Non-alcoholic beer on the wall
/ Non-alcoholic beer
... beer.
/ Dep one ¹ æ ¹, puœciæ in circulation
/ The square root of 8,464 bottles
/ Non-alcoholic beer on the wall
If you were were curious,
until they reached the 92 bottles.
Oœmioboiœci, The message I have for you.
One of my informants momentous me
Also the scientific side of these professions
will be based on organic chemistry
So open your textbooks.
We start with a chapter 22,23,24,25 ...
Sir?
¹ æ I should take a nap for two hours
on the bus, not annoyed ¿wpaœæ in pressure.
Of course.
Wanted to byœ, ¿ebyœmy
zaœpiewali you ysankê wheel?
Or can I collapse the æ ¹ his jacket
and zrobiæ you with the pillow?
Thank you, I have his the pillow.
We only need her help to inflate.
I'm fairly the lamentations.
If któreœ of you are willing to
poœwiêceñ for the second day ¿...
at any time can
œæ the efforts of the bus.
Mr. Driver,
please open the door.
I do not sermons of up zatrzymywaæ.
Kaza I open the door.
Do not place óæmy already up any more.
I do not know what in me the beautiful ribbons of about
And in me.
- Already this never return.
- For what?
You see, already forgot about em.
Please.
- Here they are.
- Thank you.
I am sure that it will be
very szczêœliwi here.
We can be szczêœliwi anywhere.
Let me also about something
I ask you.
- I'm doing a lot of homework!
- Yes, of course.
May not realize,
because we wasting the money.
Here we go!
We will uprawiaæ sex during that leave,
or rather we play in the Virgin Islands?
The need for a stronger spray!
Dewey, I'm going to the hardware store.
Nied the long back.
- I love you.
- To me the e
It's already madness.
You can not kochaæ me not only because
Also not to make you podwózek of bed.
But I can ¿.
It will not work, sir.
I know that you love me.
- I like you.
- Is that all?
I think that I were
You're a part of the man.
As you wish. You know what?
Can you should spêdziæ some time
in your room and it is a bit przemyœleæ?
- From now on, you're grounded!
- Good.
And tomorrow ...
I'll buy you a new bike.
It will not change anything.
Fight ¿Arcie!
What the hell are you doing?
Come on.
It's a fight to the ¿Arcie.
No, it is not.
You just pelt me ??are of the ATK.
Yes, because in my opinion
This whole pretty funny.
You're a moron!
Simply, I never want to see you.
As much as the prom.
Here and it, kids.
The field of battle.
Rozgoœæcie up.
Come and feel at home.
I got the rash panic
the rash of homesickness.
Biadoliæ Stop it!
Tomorrow finals y
See the outlet air conditioner?
Jefferson High School has the second ¿flows
three asthmatics.
If he succeeded in the impact we are renowned for æ
to plant them here ¿for ...
Mr. Baffert.
Again it zrobiliœcie.
- Well ¿for exemplary organization ...
- Not in the ay back of my books, Lionel. It ¿and the Amorous.
Do not worry.
We were ready with Mr. Grip the ankles,
if too much of you zapêdzi.
Hey, Herkabe.
I do not expect the sure that the you and your gang
Insert the wet Kow courageous life here show this.
Look, it's North High School.
/ Najemy them to your heart's content
/ And ask you to dock the bookmark.
O my God e
They brought Rubingera from Minnesota.
- Who?
- IBM analyzed the about it.
Rumor g of the axis, also was to someday
Siamese twins with two brains.
Come with me.
You see these freaks
the name of my friends?
They must wygraæ here,
by dostaæ to the best carols ¿y,
because it is the only way to succeed is to odnieœli
and to the end of life have not been beaten by the people.
- Do you want to deprive them of that?
- I'll do what I can.
It's good.
The judges an easily noticeably the Morse code,
So I drew up the basic code of your fingers.
- Remember it.
- Do you want me to cheat the?
Let's call it ...
the advantage to victory.
Forget it.
I will not cheat the.
Guys ...
Guys, you will not believe.
Herkabe wants byœmy cheating.
What? This is not allowed!
In precisely. It should not be the
This zapisywaæ.
This is proof in writing.
- Moving into it?
- Malcolm, you do not know what you mean.
It is important for business.
More important, than you think.
More important than you?
So already you know.
You're with us ..
or against ... We?
If it spoil
I'll be had to the Repair the.
Sorry.
- Do you work here?
- My dad is the manager.
As a bunch of geeks
You make a lot of troubles k.
I do not believe that the is used the EOE
przeciws filter the sunlight.
It's a covered swimming pool.
But we przejœæ
through the garden, there to dotrzeæ.
How can you be in the vicinity of the
by dziesiêæ seconds
and ¿might want adnemu at Insert the?
Believe me,
I did not fit.
Besides, some of them
are my friends of me.
There were two.
No, are still being are.
Just me
it does not rejoice.
What does the byœ if one of your friends the
wanted to do the byœ what robiæ not?
- Do not do this of me.
- Yes, but you see, it does not work a
Because in this case
They will do the it anyway.
And it makes me part of a
all of this, regardless of what you will do.
So I do not have outputs.
There are probably jakiœ
too complicated for me to reason, but ...
you can not just wyjechaæ?
Reese!
How many times do I have to repeat?
¯ any eating ice cream in the living room.
S get any whole carpet.
- Distraught the EOE!
- No, you owe me that.
What you can take the kid to such,
like me? Daae ground me?
¯ ebyœ knew he was
Also I will.
Sit like a week in the room.
¯ any television, games,
and contact with the outside world.
After you take
Alison on the ball.
What?
Reese promised her it EoE
and keep your word.
- But ... How are ...
- S ³ Look, Reese.
Some are well-read in the book ¿appropriate,
other deceitful and cunning.
I'm afraid you do not also must be Shaken
¿for any of them.
- S ³ I'm listening.
- Mom, przyjedŸ for me.
I have to hence the wydostaæ.
Anyway howls ¿d ¿am.
If you will not be here
the intersection of the over three hours,
find me
walk around the highways are lying. In the darkness.
Or from the catching rate.
I know of one guy with a van.
Seems to be friendly.
You should Find out more
pracowaæ at home.
I'm too tired.
Powinnaœ wydawaæ less money.
Do not have sex!
you're just too tired?
How could we, as your parents
you are still visiting us are?
I'm not going czekaæ,
until the condition gets old and shortcomings of ê be.
I'll be in the apparatus switched on
retaining more force in your attic
do not let you alone are c
his senile zdziwaczeniami.
I'll be holding a year of life and up
just the byœ suffer.
Right.
But I will not be here.
That son of a ...
Stop the car!
- What?
- Hold it!
Remains.
No one will be the manipulation of me!
You can ukaraæ me,
when I get home.
Deal.
Very well.
This Zasz of a too far.
I'll walk you to your room,
wtoczê you to him,
you expel him, but you're too much s
It carries me to you there of.
- If you say so.
- Yes I'm talking.
And now, as a father,
each also tell you "I love you".
I love you.
Now tell me this
in convincing a fashion.
I love you.
Now tell me this
without my order.
Long it will take,
I've had the AEOI the following lemonade?
I think that the'm too much s
to drink lemonade.
Just Ides.
For the sake litoœæ.
S are everywhere!
I do not know, Malcolm.
It's probably Zasz of a too far.
Do you want to cheat, right?
Since competition is one big deception,
We propose byœmy conned everyone else.
Why do I have to do?
Because you look like the most will give the posi-tion hose
dressed pielowym angle.
Not true! What about P. ..
No good.
Come on, Stevie.
Sorry.
The doors will lock me were,
I do not have a towel, and I'm very cold.
Please.
Nice to nice day.
Thank you.
P ³ ³ uses em!
Well done.
Back in a minute.
At home doing everything
earn our maintenance and I'm sorry
Also I fall from exhaustion,
when we are in the bedroom!
In precisely when it
wyjechaliœmy on vacation!
Wyjechaliœmy to be away
from your parents.
- Oh, like you have no idea.
- Because you never tell me what you mean!
/ Really, I am in myœlach to Read!
I have the answer.
Zrobiæ will go back.
Stay here and keep the door open,
until I get back.
Try not rzucaæ the eye.
Let's see if chicken out now.
- What are you doing?
- It's not every appearance possible.
Appearance Looks like you are trying to hack of his leg,
just not with me pójœæ ball.
More can not be the AOE pomyliæ.
If you do not want with me pójœæ,
are you with me not break up?
I really like you, Alison.
I just did not want em
wykosztowaæ on the ball.
I know it is selfish
and I apologize for that.
But are still being depends on me for this,
byœ to the mine and the girls are.
Well ¿... thanks for szczeroœæ.
But with the deposit of EOE s promise of me,
and you have the dotrzymaæ.
You buy him a bunch, hire a limousine,
come pick me up at seven, and go to the prom.
- Okay.
- You'll see ...
Will be œwietnie time.
Shall we dance in the light reflector.
And we'll take the picture,
so I can flow memorize the night forever.
And then broken off with you
forever.
Apparently, someone from the second day ¿
to the heavily busy yesterday.
When he reached the just about me
what should be zrobiæ.
Never was to em with you
more proud.
There was to subject.
Ladies and gentlemen.
We are ready to start the first round æ ¹.
The theme will be history.
The first question: "In the year 1803, France and the sale of
800 thousand square miles ... "
- Repurchase of Louisiana.
- The correct answer.
The second question:
"What historical document ..."
- Magna Carta.
- That's right.
- The third question: "Who ..."
- Ben Franklin.
That's right ... themselves.
Please, come on.
Let's try again.
- Question ...
- Defenestration of Prague!
- Well ...
- Treaty of Utrecht!
Please all carers
to me, in the back.
EOE give the test to all, right?
- The code that is finger ...
- I know what that means!
Good night, Dad.
Dewey, I know that the only word,
and I'm the person of the adult,
So if anything you want
to speak, do not tell.
- Thanks for your understanding.
- I love you!
But you know what?
I do not love you! And you!
I do not love you,
or you!
And especially do not love you!
And you ... love ...
Do not try to uciekaæ!
If you were just loves the ...
I hate ...
Oh, no.
Dad, we need more
toothpaste.
Dad?
River in Obuda, Dad!
Exit out of there fault!
Dad!
Dad! Come on.
Please get up!
Do not die, Dad.
I love you!
I love you, Dad!
Not of the living?
I do not is alive?
I fainted the i ..
How have you succeeded in
overloaded by tugging the æ me to this place?
Perhaps thanks to this, ¿e ..
Uros ³ em.
It's good.
Thank you, son.
Savings of EOE my force.
- I love you.
- I love you, Dad.
In the middle are the results.
Since they were also
well prepared, all the winning.
Jefferson High School ...
you win in the category of "science".
Quincy High School
- "The math".
High School North High - ever.
Secondary St. Bart Bartholomew the - in the literature.
A Marshall High School in ethics.
As you can see, it szczêœliwe
ending for all ...
hold until all the
k mouths of ódkê.
See you in a future year.
No hard feelings?
I was duped of you,
you duped all the EOE.
- He was about as cool.
- Sure. Cool.
I wonder what that was to,
if we were playing fairly.
You know, start to seriously do not.
Unless you're kidding.
Equate the c to you,
a brand of no other species.
You should be
its the mascot. Come on.
Sorry, but ¿e ..
we tried ...
zmusiæ you to cheat.
You're our
moral compass, Malcolm.
We wish you a
men chose wynagrodziæ.
Lift it and take the
on the shoulders of the bus.
This idea was œwietny.
In precisely!
In a properly, should
is the odpuœciæ.
In the case of my oœciami
middle ear ...
My scoliosis are the ...
I forgot my dentures.
I'm sorry,
I have Epstein-Barr virus.
Yes, Mr. Cutler.
GENTLEMEN: I have the reservation.
What time is it now
in Australia?
Cancels you?
Oh, no.
Well, it is a pity that the one
altercation with the ¿Panské on the spoil of a ..
Sure, can you take me
zapytaæ anything.
Part, honey.
www.tvsubtitles.net