Now Jeff says something about the weather.
In the e wieœci dear, looks as it
Also bad weather over the weekend continues ...
¿Yet it is not raining.
And three unidentified the boys
in front of hundreds of witnesses ...
Malcolm in the Middle
4x06 - Forbidden Girlfriend
/ T of Translator: Harry_man
/ Correction: polishchaser1
This is my first piston Translator
Opinions, suggestions, corrections,
œlijcie on harry_man @ newspaper. en
It's amazing how many different kids of different
You can to become familiar Be sure you are c tutoring after school.
For the last six weeks I know the
morons, idiots, g shales and morons.
My mom Each æwiczyæ me minds.
I'll tell you the one thing ...
While I had the kids ...
In truth the cierpieæ bed.
G ³ silly thing to do.
Spends his free time trying nauczyæ the c ...
- You're a Nicki?
- Part.
This does not mean,
Also anything to her about the
- Ch the boys are back for 10 minutes.
- I'll take that challenge.
No, Hal.
In precisely back from the doctor.
I have an infection
I must brothers antibiotics.
And we can not uprawiaæ sex
for a week.
What?
Not until he's dead all wear.
OK, let's look at the situation trzeŸwo t.
You can also take the ³ æ want you all at once?
No, Hal.
Or do the changes
- One day you're taking, the other does not
I'm no doctor, but I think that it would be the
Relaxed of your body.
Week, Hal.
There will be no sex for a week.
OK, everything all right.
I just ...
I'll go skosiæ catcher.
Do you still have the t the mower?
Hal ...
- Clothing.
- Right
Hey! Be careful how you go cymbal!
You said what?
Nothing.
Better to taking care for each other gogusiu,
I get a kick in the back of the books.
The bright ...
If I had of the car!
/ Ooops.
/ What a wonderful boy the baby boy.
Thank you very much for the work,
as the perform of EoE in Zesz the week.
I urge want you to take the the.
Thank you!
What will the EOE in Zesz the week?
M ³ ³ young man Young man, the nicely cope up the EOE
of these weeds yesterday.
Is $ 5 will be all right?
All right.
Thank you.
No way, yet no weeding ¿³ EOE
yesterday no reviews of weeds.
I know that.
- What's going on?
- The day of money.
Day of money?
I do not know why,
but recently it happens very often.
Deewy, people do not have the
Days Money.
I have.
These are the days of the ¿cookies
and day cap on his head half.
For those do not like too much ...
But before you know it,
Again comes the day of money.
What are you doing?
I put it g the pole fence,
for the third time this month.
We had with Earl lot of troubles k
c erases them.
What? Why mielibyœcie
delete our fence?
We have 300 cows that we napoiæ.
- We then przechodziæ to water.
- The fence is all we need.
Last escaped us were two horses
s and the whole of the busiest week for us to find them.
Our ranch in ¿uses
This watering hole for over 50 years.
We will not change the the group of
townsfolk playing the ponies smokers themselves.
It also does not mean we agrotourism,
Also I do not work in the same way you ¿ko, like you.
Hey cowboy,
œmieszna your purse is ringing.
What is it?
The co lavender soaps should be
right next to the shampoo.
He asks the EOE in servicing the hotel?
In the end I start rozumieæ trigonometry.
It is useless ¿useful.
Come on, trigonometry is needed.
You're right, it is useless ¿useful.
- I'm seeing you in school.
- Yes?
Honestly said the c ..
large for the am thinking about you.
These are ¿s heard the I!
Serious is not it?
I know you're very smart,
So I have a question ...
Do you have a planned
Each moment of your life?
- I do not think ¿ebym ...
- Planning! I know you did.
Are you sure you Know-always,
what will happen in a moment.
Do not you?
No. Not very fond of Know-
which will in a moment.
Even when it's terrible.
In a properly even likes it
when it's scary.
As for example, at the moment.
I do not know what's going to happen for a while.
- Do you know?
- So ...
- Jakieœ progress?
- What?
Math.
Wages you for $ 6 per hour.
Oh yes.
She very quickly for the apuje.
There can flow for Grip the,
when I've attempted it explained by the manufac.
Nothing attempted EOE t explained by,
EOE only the screaming at me.
Fall out of the schools were average, so for each time,
when something makes you feel also were no screams.
I'm sure that if you wanted to,
Such use would you nauczyæ trigonometry.
When?
If I was to Vietnam?
Emaciated, related the zany in a cage
tigers immersed in the Mekong?
I suppose that the no.
Remember wearing something m³ dralo.
I and many of my dead buddies
gone through the the the the a certain in death, you ¿ebyœ
and your little friends have FREEDOM,
and could uczyæ up trigonometry.
Thank you ... sir.
That was a terrible.
Come on, for each time
t his plays are the crib.
In some foreign Zesz week attempted in the Insert,
¿Eby dostaæ free set of McDonald's.
These are the I think that we should
return to mathematics.
Or you can the crap
avoid the topic and the owaæ kiss me.
Poca the owaæ you?
Apparently, you're crazy.
Your dad is jakieœ
10 meters hence the d
Do you want to lead to a situation
when at the catching me.
And they got kicked in the back of the piece
I do not think I look at it ...
Reese part, how you doing?
What are you up to?
Just as the le ¿em of bed for this morning,
c are staring at the ceiling.
I Think of em, why not pomalowaæ
kitchen cabinets?
I will make the pancakes.
Pancakes?
Come on, sit down.
We have strawberries,
bananas, peaches.
Syrup's own work,
his name the same.
Slide the o œmia
Part of baby,
Did you come to where?
Morning bra of am showers and Think of am,
Also shop with flowers
is open from the early hours.
Why not przejechaæ up
and some to Buy the freshly œciêtych flowers?
These are the beautiful!
Naleœnika?
I can not, I must naszykowaæ
ch the second opcom œniadanie.
Already ³ I will do it.
Well, they are more bed double.
Very well I'm enjoying the
Zesz than the night.
When I returned to the house, and the mom screaming at me
by the hour, but did not even go ¹ ³ em.
I know my dad almost Distraught ³.
Pop me were two of the Company ¿s and one on his temple.
Zrozumieliœmy.
You go to each other.
Steve, how you doing?
All right.
Do you know ...
What are you looking?
Yeah, so what?
Stop przechwalaæ.
I wanted to zapytaæ ...
Did I throw the Malcolm for you?
Yes, but you can not pytaæ
were in immediately under his nose, it hurts him.
Are sentences Did you come to the test?
Yes.
Three of the downside, thank you darling.
Okay, I have a fairly schools were,
urwijmy up.
Urwaæ it?
Sure, it's only in-F.
But it is ¿busy.
We will on them tomorrow, let's go.
Why pretend.
Right.
Four times we
postawiæ the fence.
Suggest the that the not
we take this seriously is not it?
Can you should porozmawiaæ with them?
Rozmawiaæ with these idiots. No!
Whether they are Suggest that the conduct agritourism
is for wimps?
These are the classes of craft and,
manifestations ¿d ¿ki racing, costume balls.
Let them therefore spróbowaæ,
change their mind.
Ignition ac are for all!
Time for the second œniadanie.
I did not want to want you and I won `t see the
able furious occur.
I love your continuity are furious.
Is ¿fury Otta
it is the great and Francis?
Try not to patrzeæ
his furious continuity.
If the Knock this semi-i ...
Will make that the cierpieæ the bed, as I have never suffered!
And can we aim considerations
showing a compromise?
Did I give you a look at the French? No!
If they want are the neighborly war
j is the bed they are.
Still do not know the
Why are you against the place!
Fine of a job, son.
Thanks.
Wait a minute.
Why did you give him $ 5?
Why?
The man was young the man wyczyœci of my gutters,
and segregate the garbage,
and even it does not ask the em.
I was not able to znaleŸæ
nicer kid.
I would like to be able Daae him more.
Please do not przejmowaæ.
It can not be day of money.
There is no such czegoœ,
a day of money.
He knew I would somehow something about this.
Unless ¿e ..
Can mom and dad do not want the,
¿Ebym knew about a day of money.
Sorry.
Get away is the s,
I'm trying something wymyœliæ.
OK, I'm sorry.
I will pass over you.
His name is Billy Prescot.
I Szed of him into the house.
He lives as the Mile œ hence the d
Looks as exactly as you are.
K ³ You're lying.
K ³ amie? It is scientifically proven
¿¿That each person on earth can have with the ego bliŸniaka.
He is my of the white twins?
Fat chance.
Dude is Holy.
You're him with the white twins
But I do not I want to be with the white twins
Do not make the rules were Deewey
Besides ... here we are fine the occasion.
¯ Eby zrobiæ what?
I do not know,
but we are talking about money and from some foreign bliŸniaku.
If you do not wymyœlimy as foaming Insert,
something is totally wrong with us.
Let's go, we jakieœ poogl the soap operas.
All perfectly
uk is made up of Nicki.
We were in a planetarium,
the mini-golf, cinema ...
It's amazing how empty is there
during school hours.
You know what?
Already better go home.
I'm grounded.
You're grounded?
Why did not you said Did you come?
When my dad found out of you
Also run away from school were, the furious up.
You know what the funniest?
He thoughts, also that you have with the s influence on me.
Yes, it's hilarious.
- Listen to Nicki ...
- Can you not like?
Why?
What is with me do not you?
- He will do the em.
- Do not we all have to lubiæ you, Malcolm.
- I know, but ...
- I do like you
And many people
This would recognize as insufficient.
Take your filthy mouth
my daughter's face.
Get in the car.
What are you doing,
you should be at work.
Okay, m the dralo. This is your first
and only warning.
Never ever For more
They did not meet with my daughter are the.
Do you understand?
No, dad! Aj cancels it!
Aj cancels it!
I can not uwierzyæ
how can the EOE me of doing this.
You know what I Narobi shame of EoE?
I'm a whole y
Just the field ¿ê
Here are a few minutes.
Hey baby.
But ¿³ I had the great all day.
I worked during the break,
when you wpad of Commons.
I started the wypytywaæ of what they do.
Are likely to get increased tablespoon.
Hal, that's great.
I had the ¿³ am a good day.
After washing windows
and cleaning the floor
am browsed through our tax returns
the last seven years.
- NADP aciliœmy in the 99r.
- ¯ kidding.
$ 800.
IRS sends the check to us by mail.
Wow! Œwietna work.
You know, I must tell you ...
Is it last?
- So we can ...
- So are money.
Œwietnie.
Stop.
Talked with his father Nicki pm
and he said to me about what the Zasz
You have to see each other non-
with t the girls are.
- But, Mom ...
- No!
He told the am he, also you will not be
For more already makes the angle of troubles. Do you understand?
Do not worry, the guy is psychotic.
I suspect that the it is ¿.
I'm not going out more
with her the widywaæ.
- Hey.
- Part.
Last night was to a œwietna.
OK, I'll be home tonight by 15,
and my dad comes back on the 18th
M³ My little brother is a snitch,
but will not be back before 16, so ...
Nothing.
I have class until 15:40 on Wednesdays to.
- And what about tomorrow?
- I do not want czekaæ until tomorrow.
- What?
- Do not you want czekaæ until tomorrow?
Quiet fault errors.
OK, can today
slip away for an hour.
Will be difficult,
but I will try.
Can we go wrong.
Dad.
See you later.
First I had to
find similar to a nurse are.
- I do not want to robiæ.
- If you do not ...
I'll be had to tell my mom
Also take the EOE are all the the money.
You'll get a fine of the KARE
Get to work.
What are you doing?
Yeah, you better run Billy Prescocie,
until the street. Train stations are 15!
Blocks west of Halifax.
That's him.
/ I'm glad you
/ Also we have decided not ...
Absolutely
All other aspects of our life
has became a so neat.
Our force is large for better.
These are the think that the the truth
successful people ...
I do not see any other explanation.
- So Bill Gates ...
- Probably never.
Does the am today All the rods
the yard.
You know, there have also
Adzik composition of the tool?
Without ¿jokes.
Definitely a properly follow.
I go to the car break loose.
Park a few blocks hence the d
Already, we had the whole quite
fine of that party, Francis ..
but it may be the best
Pirate night in history.
- What are you doing?
- Easy Otto.
What do you you think?
We have real the restaurant,
and our cows in need of water.
And we need the fence.
I will not let you zabiæ our horses!
And I will not let you
zabiæ our cows.
Just talk.
Gretchen - give me a gun.
Which one?
Ah! What am I talking about - celuga!
- Otto, this is crazy.
- You'll see.
Do not dance with a loser.
This fence will be twice Higher.
Undress them again.
Then we put a fence
to 15 feet high.
For each time as it postawicie,
We undress them.
For each time as they undress,
we we put them on again.
Do You Think of someone can
¿Eby insert a gate there?
Gate?
It can operates AAE.
Sorry.
Jump over the fence of am,
¿Eby lose the Tate
and the end of am emphasizing the blood
the Red Cross u.
I told the mother,
IDE also to the library tomorrow.
But in truth we
tomorrow to the library.
I was thinking of that the we
to meet church services.
No, meeting church services
in the next week.
It is only able to cover ¿ebyœmy
spotkaæ on a lake.
I was thinking of that the lake
is undercover for the bowling?
No, I should be
the bowling at the moment.
This is madness.
I know I can I will be even
more crazy.
Oh my God, my dad!
/ - Did you come to say that the're going bowling!
/ - Will change the am sentence.
/ - Stop me œledziæ. Do not you trust me?
/ - Quiet.
/ - Do not shush me.
/ Learn to be quiet,
/ When will someone stabs of you
/ Bamboo splinters under the fingernails
/ Byœ of your betray the comp.
- It is worth it, definitely.
For me the continuity Bosk ...
Flooding of the car with concrete
was to shocking as brilliant.
With Billy Prescot as the sacrificial goat of em
we can zrobiæ everything.
I prepared a list of enemies.
Deewey ...
Deewey, I'm talking to you.
Is that enough?
Oh, yes.
I know what you think,
but you do not realize,
I'm also
Reese true.
Just the appearance of the dam,
like me ... he did.
But if the harm us,
I mean it ...
Just drive.
Now that you've finished with the carpet
we can ociepliæ attic.
I'm telling you baby,
the value of the house as much as triple.
We can earlier
change over pensions.
- Lois, as planned Did you come?
- Nothing.
Lois zgodziliœmy up.
OK, it takes two to tango,
and I'm not going tañczyæ.
I just do not dance!
And do you think that the it will switch,?
The message I have for you, kobietko.
I do a lot of things male.
I started the lubiæ of my new force,
and I will not discount ¿AAE up
to yours, animal level.
Leave the belt for the deposit located.
I'm sick and tired
your eluding.
You're never there,
where we will also speak.
There you can take with me a fool.
Dad, you're paranoid!
Nothing much is happening.
Besides, what is sitting
in your g half.
If you know sure that the angle of You're lying,
ignition acisz for a real hell of em.
Are you all right?
I lose the feeling in the hands,
but the pain in the shoulder does not allow the myœleæ.
Poor thing ...
Listen to Nicki,
I'm not sure that's gonna work.
What do you mean?
We do all of these things:
escapes,
develop complex plans ...
This œwietna fun ...
I never feel I czegoœ of such
¿in your life, but ...
- Is this it?
- What would you tell?
Do not do this,
every other normal couple.
No I do not know about you, other than that,
Fail for ck exposed himself to danger.
And I will do the same.
I just do not know
it will be enough.
I think that precisely in the EOE offended me.
- Do not.
- At precisely that the so.
Can you not know anything about me,
but I at least I try to
dowiedzieæ as much as possible about you.
Do not like you because
I also ¹ bottom emotions.
I like you because you're
funny, attentive,
and do not leave me
same problems.
Even when you complain,
you're funny.
I never have zastanawiaæ what I say,
because it just comes straight out.
And it is that feeling of me,
I feel safe.
Wait a minute.
I like you,
because they're funny and honest.
I do not feel cheated if I was to,
When you are to me I of a
You're awesome
in the company of my friends.
're Just amazing.
OK, so it is not serious.
It's not just about emotions
or anything else.
It is not serious
I'm sorry for you also shout of em.
I love you.
Part, Daddy.
- Oh, no. I spóŸniony.
- I am the ¿.
I have the impression that also had something of em
zrobiæ work today.
- You coming home for a break?
- At precisely that.
www.tvsubtitles.net