movie info: XVID 624x352 25.0fps 175.2 MB
/ SubEdit b.4072 (http://subedit.com.pl) /
Check it out.
-What is it?
-Just read it œmieszne.
I do not read. Not until I must at school.
Otherwise, I feel like they won.
I've never read the newspaper EOE?
No.
Even the comics?
How Peanuts. I've never read the EOE Peanuts?
-No.
-Serious is not it? I've never read the EOE Peanuts?
Come on!
I promise that the j are held.
T the interpreter: michu
Malcolm in the Middle - 4x09 - Grandma Sues
Malcolm, he said am
Come for breakfast!
Francis and Piama came to visit
at the same time as the grandmother.
Eight people, seven places to sleep.
Guess who had to the paragraph The five places.
This is my reward for being in the library
when asked who wants The five paragraph the place.
Malcolm, this is your last chance!
I must there AEOI.
Œniadanie, it has become the best part of a day.
I do not believe in what you are I hear!
You're crazy if the only such of the a?
Better poder ¿press on the throat!
What an idiot
lubricates butter toast I like this?
Each knows that the it does
from shore to shore!
We'll talk about how to grow the hair you in the trousers
G the stupid animal thoughts, also knows something about toast.
Mom,
may want you indicate flow of potatoes?
It seems to me that the pathogenic Did you come already sufficient co.
Chair of the must off after the hack, ¿ebyœ ceased to jeœæ?
He says the em you also my family
is worse than yours.
¯ Are you kidding me? My grandfather has chopped the fingers were
milkman for it, also they brought the two percent milk
Hey!
Mom, Grandma and I take away the bacon.
Reese, grandmother's last day with us.
If you want your bacon, then give it to her.
Even though the is burning.
Ok, Ida.
I relieve you of already in the packaging. We can already ruszaæ.
Bus departs ¿d ¿and for three hours.
Yes, but it can be a demonstration. Whole day
We can take care of the æ passing through the city.
Œwietnie that the s been my leftovers!
It was necessary to przyjœæ of beef as you and the am.
Call me when you arrive, Mom.
-We will têskniæ
-Even is the y k ³ amie.
Reese asks the am,
¿Ebyœ raking of the list.
I wait until the rest of the fall.
Do not delay departure grandmother
by those useless discussions, huh?
Sure, You can store up doczekaæ
until I leave. Forcing the woman to an older ...
Maaa ...
mooo!
Grandma back of a
Mom asks ¿³ j ebyœ helped the packing on.
Incredibly, this wine Reese. If the clean up is the
as had the of doing this, it would be of no fixed o
Malcolm, she poœlizgnê and on the liœciu.
At one thin liœciu.
Do not be surprised if I would be the purpose of a zwichnê
clavicle, ¿Eby zostaæ here and we torturowaæ.
And I'm suffering. He was so close I was sleeping at home.
I have forgotten my already in general as it is to break loose of bed to
What are you complaining about? I've had to nieœæ j are
Car of the dress rolled up the hips.
I Szed of the blindly for 15 minutes!
Oh, it's you.
What are you doing?
Everyone blames me for the accident the grandmother.
But I have an idea of ??how all rozweseliæ.
What do you do?
I do not know if I can zaufaæ.
Come on. You can.
Okay, I'll tell you.
Hit you in the face.
Okay, you're on.
First, you can show this to me is in the disconnect.
You do not have thick fingers. Who is
the fingers? Lose their appetite as I look at it.
She can jeœæ, Lois.
It's your fault! The backyard is like a d ¿jungle!
I stairs? Who builds a house with stairs?
You think you're a better than others?
So?
My family and this is worse. My mom
posed as a cancer ¿³ ³ of the stomach, Eby ¿æ avoid the penalty.
First time.
Use language as dŸwigu Use.
Dosyæ!
Mia ³ ¿Arcie am better in a camp for refugees.
All are in the mood of the white, it's awful.
May be some way you ¿Eby rozweseliæ.
Take it easy.
Open.
It's up to me.
Wait, Mom,
I'll help you.
You eat dinner!
No one gave me even a professional of the!
What you became the face of the?
And the owl flew into the tent. If I knew he was an
Trace lunch, then it would take away the hose in the beak.
Yes?
Is the number 1233?
Come on, it's her.
Here are transmitted each.
What are you waiting for a tip?
¿St eat your fault!
Defendant Did you come to us to court!
Okay, to win the EOE.
Defendant Did you come to us to court?
Hal, quietly.
Ch the boys are in the house!
Not be so dramatic.
The defendant insurance company, the am.
We are the insurance company!
Do you think that the reason I do not have? Do you think that the
I do not feel pain? Suffer the am in silence for years.
You ¿useful useless, miserable, W ³ anna wiedŸmo!
Tell the big guy.
¿You are sued.
Okay, calm down! Mom, please.
Think what you are doing. Suing on our own baby!
I do not want the long-rozmawiaæ for much longer.
Let the lawyers it will facilitate the.
Lawyer!
We do not have a lawyer.
So better make for the atwcie.
It can not hence the odejœæ this paper!
J are the beat your own risk the weapons!
Hal, we can not this zrobiæ.
It's the end of my mother.
Crazy, horrible,
horrible, but still a mother.
What you just
do not kill the old wiedŸmy?
Stop it!
And we're not talking about anything cool the opcom.
Do you mean to kill her?
No, Hal, had the am in the process of thought.
Oh, probably get sick.
I know
I feel the same way.
No, I'm probably really going to be sick.
Well, I think I know
Why do you feel that bad, Lois ...
You ... you're in the ¿y
In those strives?
Congratulations.
That's the best part of my job. When I can see
faces of people as they communicate a good message.
It ...
fantastic.
Thank you very much, Doctor. Are you 100% sure?
Because I may mistaken my results with others?
No, it's your performance.
I swear.
Can you afford the dope you to the niæ
we are radoœæ and check again?
Yes, please retrieve a much blood
as needed. Please just be sure.
We would not, ¿Eby
you answer the us our dreams.
Relax, I'm
absolutely sure. Congratulations.
Oh my God,
it's horrible!
It can not be true.
And had to make a mistake zajœæ jakaœ each!
What do we do now?
I do not know.
We can not afford to pozwoliæ!
If the child is in the middle
so with the E as the least of the email, it's a disaster!
This is a joke jakiœ grim!
Scary. This is terrible!
These ¿are you so excited?
End of am already!
Do not make me g of the pistil.
I know that we are there!
Ok, now Whose turn is it?
This is not
my grandmother.
Okay, I Think of a number.
Wait, you write a quickie So, you're not going
(One-one, but here-"you")
One!
In precisely so win the EOE.
Good luck
-Come on Malcolm.
It's not fair!
I even do not live here.
The long-wait for much longer,
This will be worse!
I hate you all.
You know, my parents
back are only for half an hour.
-I think œnisz.
-Please, I'm going crazy.
Approx.
Hey guys, I'm going show this Piamie
posters in your room for a while.
-Good idea of
-Have a good time.
I was thinking of that the the never go.
Tell me about it!
Ok, are still being good.
I will give a gift,
and you write the paper.
There is no lock?
At my brothers? Just
they inserted a back door.
I do not know Francis.
A little strange in the room so your brothers.
No, it's all right.
Here I had the large for girls.
So what are you waiting for?
That's it!
¿No one yet that does not eat.
Ok, can
But not here.
Mom, we porozmawiaæ.
We have an interesting message from a doctor.
Yes, it's a very good message. In a certain sense.
He said I would, that even extreme messages.
I am in you ¹ ¿y
¯ kidding.
Believe me, we were
just as surprised ... like you.
You know, we had large overdraft s and more
child will make things even more difficult.
So in light of what in the burden on us
falls not carefully ck that some
action should zostaæ
thought out again?
Yes.
Of course, also like that.
You should rozliczyæ up.
What!
Mom!
It's for your own good. You can not œciskaæ legs
for 20 minutes. Listen to me, take my advice.
Sen makes my life worth czegoœ.
Œni to me that I'm also in a normal house.
Hey Malcolm, we need
your tent on the hour.
-Two hours.
-What!
Why?!
None of your business.
Just need.
No! It is enough that the threw me out of the house.
Now you want to zabraæ my little piece of privacy of the s?
Forget it.
Find the the ...
Really thanks.
Happy! Kicking in the own brother
on the outside at night in the same bieliŸnie!
We will of potrzebowaæ.
What do we do now?
We are a debt is used married to his ears.
You will need to conserve. There will be
holidays, organizing birthday in restaurants,
and do not kill us, if not
We will carry the brand-name clothes.
Hal, of whose life you say ¿?
After ¿¿we do not do any of those things!
We can not itself pozwoliæ for that child.
Where as if the spa will be about?
You will not be able to even go nakarmiæ by
are my mother. It's so unfair.
Honey, do not worry. Here's what we'll do:
First, a pile of chocolate ice cream.
It always helps.
And then we will sit down and calm are the pomyœlimy.
Hey, everything will be fine. We find
The solution, I always find. I promise.
Oh no!
Why me?!
No!
Why?!!
Why?! Why?! Why, why,
why, why, why?!!
Approx. I have already this fairly. No one seems to know that the
beetles are happy tastes better than the June bug.
I can dostaæ For more naleœników?
Mia the EOE already 10 Reese. Do not be like pigs each.
We need to conserve Each penny we have.
Dewey, do not go crazy with this juice.
It's not is growing on trees.
Wait, is growing!
That's why it's so damn expensive?
Yes Dewey,
probably do not want to be greedy?
The greedy, the western ann the bab are the star that does not have
even in the little przyzwoitoœci.
Hooligan przyzwoitoœci talking about?
But fun.
Why is that funny?
None of your business.
Approx.
Hal, I must porozmawiaæ with you about .. stuff.
About that thing?
The first thing or the other thing?
-They know about this thing.
-Shut up. It's probably about the inn thing.
Talking am an agent of the insurance company.
He said that the credit we will increase three-fold!
What?
Even with Fail
We will REPRESENTATIONS kosztowaæ!
3-fold!
Probably will have to tell the kids.
Who knows, you may be able to bed after the ¿yczyæ few dollars.
No, not yet. I know the my mother. I know that if the
give her one more chance is to post the pi's are rightly
And do you understand everything I explains the
about the process of the Switch On May poœwiadczenia?
Yes.
You do not have to robiæ.
Sorry.
No, no, no, no, no, sorry
Malcolm. You can not here now inputs.
What are you talking about?
I live here.
I'm sorry, I just do not, you can.
Now I can not inputs to home home! Why
I always suffer? Reese and Dewey are in the middle.
No, I do not have them.
Francis and Piama took them to the mini golf course.
And more than that, sound, minds
and the body of z. because the ... Do something with it.
Sir, we need only
Establish your first name and last name.
I'm sorry, but I had to of doing this, I had no
choice. Are still being'm a member of this family.
I deserve it,
¿Eby Know-what's going on here!
Malcolm, this does not concern you.
Yes, applicable.
In this house, something is happening patient.
And all I ask is that kind
not treating me like an idiot!
Your cruel grandmother
the defendant a letter to court.
S you've heard it?
They called me the cruel. Want to have it on record.
Okay, so it us of a defendant
Hold the do not have this in front of me the secret.
It's horrible, but all she does
is awful. There is no reason in principle ...
And your mother is pregnant ¹ ¿y
In those strives! Zwariowaliœcie! It is the deepest of upsza
thing as an s I heard the. How mogliœcie me to do?
To all of us,
We thought what you are wearing!
Already for the facilitated? He holds the longest I them for much longer as
³ I can, but $ 10 is not enough of a for long.
He knew about it and EOE
You said no to us?
What we do not You said?
It's here!
Can that we should zrobiæ
5 minutes break?
No Wages for a break.
Mom of sermons and did not speak.
From some reason and tried to protect the grandmother.
What is the grandmother,
Also mom is pregnant strives?
-What?
/-You're pregnant strives?
Nieeeeeeeee!
We will have another baby? What happened with you
going on? You have too little about the issues or what?
I do not believe in what I can see!
It's the t react to the wonderful information?
This b of the awieñstwo blessed!
We should wstydziæ up!
Psst ...
I must with you porozmawiaæ.
What?
No need to martwiæ of Insurance Business.
In precisely invalidate any insurance ted to us!
What are you talking about?
They said something about the stagnation of the semi-atnoœciami.
It must be jakiœ loophole.
So regardless of what your mother would do,
We will have semi-Latin from one's own pocket.
Oh, my God also?
I have a good message!
As we were all nervous lately.
I was thinking about the what can I do, ¿Eby all
uszczêœliwiæ. And then I wymyœli of it.
It's the most obvious thing in the world.
I bought the pool for all of us!
And the best part is that the do not have to
for the semi-Latin for the first 6 months.
This is an inflatable crocodile. With r the pods.
In precisely setting the pool on the outside.
And not only I give thanks.
It would also block any service Dewey.
He k ³ amie!
What's going on?
Mom is pregnant ¹ ¿y
What! It is not possible! You know how dangerous
is to have a child and the pool and at the same time?
Okay, that's it! Ch of boys into the room!
And you are you t Take the bulb out of my yard!
I can not believe it.
Another child!
We all have this fairly! Now we'll be
dzieliæ have all 5 parts!?
What you just complain? I have always been najm the younger,
and now that I will not even had the.
Kumacie not the point.
You're looking at the short term.
It all sucks.
I had the jakieœ plans. Can I pójœæ to the College!
S ³ yszycie it?
In the fine than a family of the child will be born.
Hey, we have a right to be sad! We be the losers!
Now it will be for on our brother!
Brother?
How much it cost me?
Wages not your girls!
Mom, we porozmawiaæ.
Ida, do not have insurance. Zalegaliœmy
of semi-atnoœciami and remove us from the program.
If you do not interrupt this process are tional
it'll ruin us. Do you understand?
I'm sure that the date of the Council. Agencies
The social care. And who you will help me, huh? Nobody!
Mom and Dad. We wanted you
przeprosiæ, for what we said about the child.
Yes, it przemyœleliœmy.
We can again dzieliæ Obtain a box of Reese.
And I can break loose from the baby.
It'll be fun.
Yes, and I can przysy the AAE
you $ 30 a week, ¿Eby help.
Thank you boys the boys.
Halooo! The process itself will not go
through it, also ignore me.
Where are you going?
Unsubscribe. They do not have the insurance. Do you think that the
I'll take 40% of the dziadowskiego home?
30%.
And exactly this way of thinking.
This home Such use would be in my garage I was, but then
I had to parkowaæ my Porsche podjeŸdzie.
I do not want innocent disposed
people on the street. At least not for free!
I think that I feel already
sufficient as well to travel ¿.
Francis and grandmother finally gone and all
the return of the standards. Well, not quite up to standard.
Dad he said to us that during the first
3 months strives those women stoke the hormones.
Quickly cool the boys!
Someone left a niezakrêcon the toothpaste!
T the interpreter: michu
www.tvsubtitles.net