T ³ Professional: Harry_man
correction: MoszeUsz
Hey Mom, I uros of an inch!
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x07 "Malcolm Hold your tongue"
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.3 MB
Stevie, come on,
is already 10 times in a row.
I have this ... fairly.
For me important!
, It was possible to get on my second day ¿
provisions, I must utrzymaæ format.
He could of byœ although the spróbowaæ
I lock?
It is continuously too the easy.
Can you exit the ladder?
PREVIOUS please,
You will find us transportation.
Tickets cost were
me $ 40 a piece!
To 2 x 40?
Share this by two
and out $ 40 per ticket!
It's not my fault,
Also I can not lead.
But you lose the license EOE!
Because my public defender, did not try the
even defend me, as if one were insane are.
It is better to invent something, because if not we'll be
dojechaæ could go, it will not go!
Never arrange to
with someone m³ drzejszym from you.
Okay, break's over.
We're going back to work.
Going on the circuit.
Practice your dribbling.
And this time not siedŸ idle
try the goat of the five owaæ tablespoon all around the a
My ... b of the d
Sorry.
I know that a little crazy,
but for the first time in life
I'll be doing of something, what
depends on normal people.
Being in the second ¿flows, the best
happens to me of the in life.
And I do not want to zawaliæ.
I'm just saying that if the we
wygraæ and how are money, we want to.
Looks as this, that we should
large with more postawiæ on the offensive.
I do not think I'm the only
the audience, who are today,
Also is something completely
wrong with your tactics are the game.
If you think about the second,
uœwiadomisz themselves also need to
enter some changes.
What the hell is with me do not you?
Why can not I shut the!
We are ... the same.
We're talking ... before ... pomyœlimy.
/ Malcolm!
How many times do I have to repeat, ¿ebyœ
putting up the wet towel after use!
/ Is it so difficult?
If so, can you just
throw out your towel.
Next time, after a shower prevents
the podwóku until dry.
/ Gee, Mom, or garden front of the house
/ There was to be more humiliating the months?
- I'm sorry.
- I do not want listen to ....
- You said what?
- I'm sorry.
Yes. So ...
I can see that the boys are learning the boys.
So can it not the best
time for such a conversation.
You want something to drink, or whatever?
Definitely like
you a birthday present?
Dad, boots are perfect,
exactly like I wanted to.
Listen to S that were really expensive,
Very well care for them, okay?
I'll be. Do not worry.
Once again, big thanks Dad!
- What the hell are you doing?
- Piama, an old cowboy trick.
Immersed in water shoes
and does not even take off their per minute,
time until the entire kowitego dry.
Even if it will take a few days.
As you finish, matching the like gloves.
Appearance can drastically
but believe me, I know what I'm doing.
These are the shoes for $ 300,
which is precisely destroy the EOE.
Nothing will destroy the em
so should robiæ!
You've got to zaufaæ on this issue!
Why do you always talk
to me, as the idiot.
And all of the hand of the rabbit
¿Lived long and szczêœliwie.
A mora of this tale is that, son
Also knows the yellow plant are the amanymi rascals
which will not give the his of gold.
Sure.
Dad?
It's like watching the course of the gods
returning the smokers of the Games.
- Part! Hello! Sorry.
- Part.
- What's it called?
- Walk sports.
I've never seen the czegoœ I like that.
The style, the grace.
It's not just about the good appearance.
This is the best low-æwiczenie
intensity that wymyœlono.
Contrary to what you are saying
All gogusie of Tai-Chi.
Yes, but how is it done?
The International Federation of
chodziarstwa determine the a,
Also one foot always
must stykaæ out of the ground the.
A leg remain across the back of the
must be straight at the knee.
- Something like that?
- Hey, I think for the catch of EOE.
Look at this,
I think there is a natural talent.
Look at me!
I can walk perfectly!
I am the venom of the lunch
the elderly and to me, Carl,
completely on me and the furious,
Cody j because of the cast.
I mean, I know them the am with each other,
but if it makes me the responsibilit?
/ Why are you asking me?
/ I do not even know these people.
I know, I know. Know how to
postawiæ in her situation.
But she just
Wrzeszcz me of a
Now I feel this poorly,
because it is the semi-aka a
And the crap I can not myœleæ,
or do something completely ³ ³ am not poorly?
/ Completely I do not care.
/ My parents can
/ Wróciæ at any time,
/ We can start the æ could to owaæ,
/ So we have time?
Malcolm, thank you very much.
I szczêœciar are that the you have.
You make also feels great.
/ Wow, this is fantastic.
/ I'll never be
/ Pronounce of his thoughts.
/ I must just Hold the language for
/ Teeth. No wypowiadaæ or words.
Dad, please. The concert is on Saturday
evening, you need transportation?
Reese, no!
Your mom goes to work,
and my car is in the shop.
You znaleŸæ yourself someone else.
Are my hips are equal?
Look at the back of my books when I go.
Dad, I swear, I also do not like me
You confirm, that leaves the house forever!
Or never be output.
Whatever is worse.
It's your choice, buddy.
- I think that you will smakowaæ.
- Yes, yes, I understand.
In the deposit ê it in your mouth, your nails
from the tap my foot between his teeth,
Spit everything, and you
will be had of it on tape.
- It's already to the Father
- I'm sorry for that.
But both very
dojrzeliœmy since then.
I have a proposal, which the
you can considered as a c are interesting.
You are still a warm e
Now, I know that the one
coolest guy like you
not returned the
g half of such cases.
This note's easy to use.
Anyway the and so you're probably busy.
- What are you talking about?
- In the background is the Saturday concert.
Together with Alison zastanawialiœmy
or not wanted to byœ AEOI.
¿Do you want the ebym gone
with you to the concert?
Yes, more or less.
But the coolest ever
is get there and back.
¿But yet I must not speak to you about it.
Let's look at who I'm talking.
Single, in the medium age
cy have lived with a cat.
You Know-all
Planning dating.
Clear that I know a lot but ...
Probably did not even get excited
up to mind the true date.
This is not something about which
b begged byœ weeks.
Of course, also not
Who would have took over the.
But if people are pytaæ bed,
it does not forbid me opowiadaæ?
No problem.
Will œwietnie.
And I'll Such use opowiadaæ people, right?
Howdy all.
I must tell you, Hal.
I've never seen the am, ¿Eby someone
for the catch of the sport as soon as you.
How much of a mine - 3 days?
/ And you're already on my level.
¿It is not yet a rivalry.
After ¿wyœcig not, right?
It's only a matter of time
as you will be surrounded.
We send The message to the command,
but every ¿The message will
Radio will be captured.
Do you think that the do not know that?
Pos ³ ³ em and when we are the secret weapon.
The Lord calls you, sir?
Corporal, I do not think I need to speak,
Also the fate of the entire free world depends on you.
I deliver the message
to headquarters before morning.
My God, is 100 km from here the d
Divert ê The message still
before breakfast, sir.
Thank God,
Also is on our side.
Oh my God, that Wheeler.
Probably the return of the event.
With your left.
With your left!
- With your right.
- With your left!
- Right.
- On the left.
/ Well, b-governments quiet.
/ Not important what he says, do not respond.
It can not already be simpler.
You skip, you skip, you skip,
koz of regret, the regret goats
you skip, koz of regret,
you skip and throw!
Sorry, Coach.
Please, please,
look who's arrived the.
Coach, I wanted to
przeprosiæ for that day.
I would like to return to the second ¿springs.
And so wanted to byœ przeprosiæ
and return to the second ¿springs.
/ Perhaps in precisely this he said I was. Yes!
You know what this is?
The symbol of my authority.
Do not give to the whistles such ka ¿DEMU.
This means that I'm here
government money, I'm the boss.
Do you understand?
/ Yeah, it's a magic whistle
/ Who makes you omnipotent.
All right, you come to the second ¿springs.
- Time!
- 25 minutes and 43.2 seconds.
Damn!
You're sure that the the the the the the it EoE exactly
when I call the work?
Yes, you ¿ebym you about the collapsing of?
Okay, save time, son.
Listen to Malcolm, podejdŸ.
I would like, ¿³ ebyœ helped me
Pull out the æ jakieœ conclusions from these times.
These are the last three days.
Some are made from the hat,
and some not.
Some of the shorts,
some without.
One of the two.
One only pid ¿breaks.
He could byœ Perform the jakieœ
Scientific analysis of all this?
/ Yeah, I do not have anything better
/ To do with the rest of his life.
- Okay.
- You're a good son.
By the way,
Unless you get pocket money?
/ In what you ¿family're alive!
Nothing, why do you ask?
- $ 5 a week will be good?
- Super.
Hey!
Dewey, he is older and not
complains when I ask him about the aperture UGE.
Again, biting your nails?
- Appearance let the tragedy.
- No, they are all right.
S ³ Look, I only have two minutes.
The client thoughts, also looking for
czegoœ for her in the back.
¿I want ebyœ questioning the ear with the yellow skin of puzzle
and he said that will be better on the road.
ELO, Kansas, Doobies,
the Doobies, Kansas, ELO.
I will not tell you that I'd have chosen the.
- What are you talking about?
- How the puzzle!
On our the date!
Do not get the EOE my e-mails,
voice messages,
or notes which left a knife on the door?
You know, I have a large on the set
the schools were this week.
I do not have time to ...
Simply sliding the evening listening to
and let me know how you make a choice.
Now, tell me what you think about the shirts.
I like the blue, but thinking
Also the color is too bright.
- You're not wearing pants!
- After this are the images.
¿I want ebyœ selected the
Best separately,
then decide
How are the compose.
Anything.
I'll call you yet
a million times before the Saturday.
Not that I was so excited the years.
Now I know why people
just waiting for the weekend.
/ Kazzer - "Pedal To The Metal"
/ I push the pedal to the metal and departs ¿d ¿am
/ I never get lost
/ Where do I skrêciæ at the intersection?
/ I push the pedal to the metal
/ Even more and it is terribly
/ But make sure that
/ Also hold the foot in the floor
/ I push the pedal to the metal and departs ¿d ¿am
/ I never get lost
/ Where do I skrêciæ at the intersection?
/ I push the pedal to the metal
/ Even more and it is terribly
/ But make sure that
/ Also hold the foot in the floor
/ I push the pedal to the metal and departs ¿d ¿am
/ Pedal to the metal and departs ¿d ¿am
Please!
You know that after you wash
they dry them and wymyæ top?
/ A can still buff
/ The floor of and also calculate your shoes?
Sure, Mom.
Look at me.
You take drugs?
What?
Behaves very recently
Know-odd, and I want what's happening.
/ Apparently, this house can not be
/ ¿Be polite without any suspicion!
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
So everything is all right,
everything is normal.
You do not behave
otherwise, I am the crazy.
/ She would be good!
/ Dowal it!
All right, really.
Well, give the appearance of the tired
Let it also be completed.
Right.
Dad, please lasts three hours already.
Come on, give me anything Wheeler.
What is your secret?
You start psuæ fun
the Viewing television.
³ I have studied your movements,
naœladujê are your techniques
but jakimœ miracle you're still the better.
Why?
How?!
Can be simply
better than you!
Did although for a moment about the EOE Think?
Billy spits Varagaskin
3 feet away from me.
I accept it!
Why do not you can?
Dewey may have been right.
Can not zes of God and of me on the ground,
¿Eby pobiæ the guest's, but look at him.
Perfect posture,
perfect rotation of the hips.
Wait a minute ...
Two feet without contact
from the ground at the same time!
Dewey!
Do you see it?
This air.
It is air!
I have a fairly, I'm going to Read the book tablespoon!
I hope
You're a smug!
As Janet also got the a
T-shirt for my last wyœcig.
It is believed that am that it will be fairly
Daae you girl my socks.
Oh, my God also?
I'm sorry that the interrupt Wheeler
but I Think of that the we can
the device has the beak were wyœcig.
Apparently this guy,
is up to you really like the girl.
Also, avoid using can fail napatrzeæ
on the back of my body a
It will not take long.
And one has a note of.
This time, ¿Eby was to
otherwise, try to AEOI.
What are you talking about?
Thinking of EOE, also finds no
your of a small, dirty secret?
This clever jump executed
every fourth step masks the ascent.
You can not fool the recording.
Tape sees everything,
And I see everything on it.
None of you walker.
You're just ordinary white runner.
It is completely of no ...
Do not worry.
Catch up with him.
1, 2, 3, is!
1, 2, 3, is! 1, 2, 3, is!
And when I had the 14 years,
I got the first are the velor shirt.
That day everything changes the Father
Suddenly he opened the club atronomów.
People began to sit down
on my side of the bus.
But I'm a Libra, so
myœleæ she likes best about people.
Listen to Craig says in precisely the em
Alison as the focus on driving.
No, that's precisely the EOE says that the I
I do love of me and made it possible for you ...
Do you like long-long walks on the beach Communal?
I've always liked to.
Besides, I am
grandmaster in the game ships.
I have a cap if you'd want to view a.
So Ali, you jakieœ siblings?
What are you doing?
Do not talk with me,
only could to APPROACH?
I am part of the owiekiem and deserves
For a bit of conversation and companionship
before a whole sawing.
I do not mind the about me when 2 times
stop the sure that the change Eby shirt.
But I do not think,
Also should krzyczeæ me.
Do not panic, it just makes it easier.
My family,
if it is of the owner.
You know Craig, today's girls had
like the type of strong, silent husband ¿man.
Craig, Craig, in precisely
minêliœmy reunion concert!
Oh no, do not think so.
But there was to sign and had the arrow.
And we should jechaæ
where that is facing!
Come on.
There are plenty of other cool
things that we can robiæ.
I was thinking of, ¿Eby started the ride in the æ ¿d ¿book.
Then light dinner
for me the small restaurant.
Already I give the tip,
¿Eby gave us a good table.
I was thinking of, ¿Eby end the evening me of a white,
romantic bonfire by the lake.
Craig!
We're destroying the date!
Listen to pissant!
You know how many times I gave everything I
to plan tonight?
34 years!
I will not let you,
is the damage the white bachorom her!
We'll have a ride in ¿d tablespoon
and supper and bonfire.
And it will be a magical evening
that will remain in our hearts forever!
- What are you wearing glasses?
- What?
/ Reese says the EOE also for me, I will hit them!
/ He says the EOE, also like me!
Yes, let's leave that sucker.
Okay, okay,
See you at school.
As you can see, you Piamo skeptical.
Wearing these wet
Shine the busiest of days,
but are now comfortable
flexible and perfectly matched.
Mia the EOE're right, honey.
- What means that committing fully Did you come ...
- B of the d
You know, can be even more of me
the c forcefully reminding the ideas of your tablespoon,
But I'll be a better part of the human being.
With better shoes.
- Call me when you get bored with this.
- It can be then late stage.
If you stand a few days,
athlete can eat mushrooms.
How can we przegrywaæ of the second with spring,
who did not win a match of 3 years!
/ Mo also because
/ You're a complete moron!
/ You know that the good throw!
/ Why do not wpuœcisz me out?
On the litoœæ Bosk,
dosyæ that break!
Offensive!
Okay ciamajdy!
You know why not
we can ¿pokonaæ the second day?
/ Because I will not let anyone rzucaæ!
/ Give the tablespoon of only five
/ W and t the back!
No one in the second ¿flows has no heart!
None of you!
You know that the Allies when the first
once the dowali landed on Iwo Jima.
They had better weapons from the Germans.
They had something more than a ³ ê fire.
/ Finely you completely
/ Lost his mind?
/ Wpuœæ me out!
/ Let me rzucaæ!
/ Pi ³ angle!
None of you have had to
zapomnieæ of water in your shoes,
or sand in the mask, so long
to skupiæ on
the success of the whole unit!
/ Tell him, ¿Eby up
/ Close the wpuœci and weights of the!
/ Tell him!
Malcolm, do you think,
Also you can do it in my strategy?
/ No, because you're the pore banym
/ The idiot! I hate you!
/ I want to zabiæ and tañczyæ
/ On your a shallow grave!
/ This is my tactics!
Okay, wchodŸ.
Thanks.
¿Ulcers of the stomach are?
How succeeded in you
wyhodowaæ ¿ulcers of the stomach are!
The doctor he said, also have
¿About the decline of the 60-year-old air traffic controller.
You're a teenager, on a nice continuity
the sake of what the so EOE Stress?
For your information, I will spend the
last three hours on a trolley,
next guest's, which is continuously attempted to
ignite a cigarette through a hole in the neck!
A moron who considers the contribution to my drip,
was unable to znaleŸæ ¿s were
two hands and a flashlight are!
My doorbell does not work!
It's the silly przeœcierad g of the itch!
The TV has only one channel!
And why I must korzystaæ duck!
It's great that the ¿no?
Alison and I'm the, but I must admit:
dating are much better,
only two people.
He could of the crap byœ
the nazywaæ a date?
Whatever it is, I can not
doczekaæ up faces of my neighbors,
When I return home after eleven.
Now who is the osny hose,
You Clevasol?
In precisely the mine and my
curfew.
In the night so beautiful,
not in force ¹ ¿no time.
/ Air Supply - "The One That You Love"
/ Here I am, the one you love,
/ Are asking for another chance.
/ Understand also that you love,
/ I love you in so many ways.
T ³ Professional: Harry_man
correction: MoszeUsz
www.tvsubtitles.net