For me the continuity's sake, what it was to!
Wherever you are, whatever you do the EOE,
no I think that you will not find!
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x20 "Child, part 1"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.3 MB
We are very happy,
Francis also arrived with the visits of the,
not so long ago we saw him.
And you're an added bonus.
Your Fortunately,
is my szczêœciem.
I do not know whether this annex,
arised that without the help of Francis.
Hal is afraid of heights.
I do not get, Dad.
You have inputs for the next level.
My ears are swells!
The doctor said, I must also carry the
special shoes for another two years.
Then I can odpuœciæ
nights and weekends.
But the eggs! Get the EOE
a letter from the Academy of Martindale!
What is the Academy?
It's the best, most
advanced private schools and in the world!
Do you know how many millions of the issue,
¿Eby people do not know about it?
Write the that the adoption of me,
but it consists of I administration.
Nobody consists!
Sami you are located. It's incredible.
Malcolm, your time is coming!
You're set for an entire force!
Wait, what am I saying?
You can not jechaæ.
You're too poor.
I do not know anyone poorer.
I'm such a dork.
Describe nirvana, which
you will not be ³ He could never doœwiadczyæ!
Hold on to the hope and success were
the guy in the shirt for 3 bucks!
- Take a look at t the hovel!
- Lloyd, the crap you have to speak.
P ³ though it's out of the ego, Malcolm.
£ zy are free.
Note all.
We're back from the doctor,
everything is all right, but ...
the child is a little
We thought higher than the value.
So instead of giving birth for
Two weeks, as planowaliœmy,
amy induce labor on Thursday.
- Thursday! This Thursday!
- No. You can store this zrobiæ!
What a difference the difference?
Our life I'll finish up the
Six days earlier ...
Hal!
I begin to our new,
fulfilled, the life.
It sucks.
I know that it falls upon you suddenly
and you have the right to a slight sadness.
- A very small?
- Do not push it.
Hal, you know what?
I got the idea.
Can go somewhere tomorrow
the boys of opcami and will severe?
And so I have a bit to do, ¿Eby
prepare house for nadejœcie child.
I can help with the equipment Tania.
So it takes a little d for much longer,
but I could use the company.
These are the car shows
in the Exhibition Centre.
Yes, spêdŸmy whole day to watch the giving
cool things that I never buy.
When viewing the dalibyœmy only
things that we become,
- It is continuously widzielibyœmy shit.
/ - Do not spoil the fun.
Will œwietnie!
/ Exhibitions Bride Fashion!
It is the deepest of the fair name upsza
as the car's heard the em.
- Cars that were a week ago.
- Let's hence the!
Not already ignition pays the $ 50 I
for parking. We are staying!
I know that it's your five children,
but still powinnaœ byœ bit excited?
Sure.
Any child is at exciting.
But I do not have to
as to œpieszyæ.
- Wow!
- Are you okay?
The child began to the kopaæ like crazy!
As if something upset them the o ..
Mom!
Open the door,
if I break loose on the grass and jeœæ worms?
Œwietnie!
Who opened the doors of piekie?
Mom, what a surprise.
What are you doing here?
Is introduced.
What do you mean
the "enter"?
We're related,
Take care of me are.
This is ridiculous. Do you have an apartment,
better than the house.
They slept on the up.
Mom, you can not ...
How is the burn on!
It's the sitting, right?
It's a mystery.
Why do not you go to Susan?
It has 4 bedrooms
and the satellite antenna.
Your sister should Insert the
your head for a can of beans!
What?
Has always been a favorite of yours ¹ ¹.
Only j Did you come to the informed
the death of my dad.
Already it is not my favorite of the the.
And he said that the'm bitter!
Then throw the hook and the!
Or am I throw the hook are.
Who remembers the?
Anyway,
should zgniæ in hell!
Mom, I can not afford us
for yours to keep.
Constant was the maid.
I'm not the maid, Ida.
I Piama. It ¯ Francis.
Tell s is used the more,
¿Eby does not speak to me of a
I know that was not the em everywhere, but
is probably the most boring place on earth!
What are you talking about, Reese?
You know what kusztu need
¿Eby zrobiæ a lace veil, eh?
Dad?
I wondered as ...
You have from the deposit they jakieœ savings?
I must go opowiedzieæ mom!
No, I'm not serious.
And if something is going to happen?
Jakiœ large, the unexpected expense?
- You're ready for this?
- Do not worry about it, son.
- Items will solve the self ¹.
- But ...
Come on, you're a youth,
We are at the fair œlubnych.
We should zajmowaæ matters m³ young.
Dewey?
/ Dewey!
- What are these cables?
- See that large s jupiter?
I am responsible for this baby.
Are you interested?
Really like this.
I'll tell you the short story.
Nothing you going to do with her the do?
Do not do that, right?
It's my mother.
You know my attitude towards it.
She's what you want.
This woman will be the first
Part of owiekiem you see a child.
You will come to the uœmiechaæ,
tuliæ her hands to the k
Well, they had to zmywaæ.
Mom, I must tell you something important Nego.
What is it?
You're the mother are horrible!
Did you come always to the mother are horrible!
For an entire childhood
Did you come to intimidate me and ignore Did you come.
Ignore the s Did you come to my feelings
and lower wywy ¿Did you come to the my sister,
until you feel the bezwartoœciowa am up!
Now she is bezwartoœciowa.
I have a right to change his mind.
This is also your sister disgusting
me more than you,
does not give you the right
speak to me like that!
I'll be speak as I like,
you ugly old woman!
Wynosisz hence the up!
I do not know from where they have found the am a ê ³, ¿Eby
it finally tell, but I feel great!
I will not prosiæ. I command you!
Wynoœ out of my house!
No.
- What?
- S heard the AoE am he said no.
What do you mean?
You have no choice!
And what will you do?
I pick and roll?
Throw the old man on the street,
in front of the neighbors?
I do not mind.
She will bring it upon myself Did you come to,
old monster.
You have no idea
how to tell anyone about me ...
Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
This is your szczêœliwy day.
Lessons chicken dances are held
every 10 minutes are adjoining pavilion.
Sorry, we can
porozmawiaæ a while?
Hey, give me a piece of the flower?
- I'm talking to a real customer.
- I am a customer.
- Yeah? As much enisz it?
- And someone like me?
Hey, you are 170 cm tall?
- Yes.
- Perfect.
Sells tuxedos,
one of the models does not appear the.
I'll give you $ 20, and will be here
the island of Crete in a tuxedo and handing out the cards.
Eat ¿d ¿aj!
20 bucks? He will do it!
Need my size?
It's very simple.
You come to someone,
He kneels on one knee,
you give your business card and say:
"I declare that the buy smoking
u Manchada McCaskey'a ".
None problem.
Accordion is a very underrated.
Yes, it's true!
What are you doing today at 15:16?
- Sir, can a piece of cake?
- Sure. They got out of a flower?
No. You will get the flower
and is of the, the lemon of the bee.
Mom, River in Obuda up.
Children!
Give me Insert!
- He did not want the am this robiæ.
- What?
It's the police.
See what forced me Did you come?
Of us and the police am at your own risk mother.
They'll take the thee hence the!
How can I Did you come to me to do?
After all that for you
do the am. We're related, for God's sake!
Well, it's you.
It's about them, wywalcie them.
What!
The rob me. I want them
get rid of my house!
Wait, this is my house!
- Calm down.
- I have an act of ownership.
It is a deposit box
the Federal Bank.
Number 24866, You can store check.
No, I have documents of ownership!
It is in. .. the box the shoe,
under my Insert the ...
I do not know where I keep it,
but this is my home!
You perfidious, ungrateful wench!
Ever since the d j took in the am,
k is just the breaks!
And her boys przeroœniêty the boy thoughts,
Also is tough.
How difficult it is to hit an old lady!
You mangy old ...
In doing so precisely.
You are powstrzymaæ j.
You are powstrzymaæ j!
As already said the I, is very clever.
As if you are familiar with the j as well as I,
it does not believe the byœ in t the story.
As on Monday, as the market will open,
one who has an act of ownership, may we take it.
Then you go to court, and the erection
the matter will take six to eight months.
Can you wstaæ already.
If the old lady falls
in the person of g words, I will come back here.
Following are the current is used.
I'll have the building has possession.
Do you think that the this take over?
Think about why your soup
of a different flavor, as the back of the toilet EOE.
There must be some way
to get rid of her.
- We know that the ima not fire.
- Admit it, the utknêliœmy with her.
You can not poddaæ up!
You'll be fine!
I'm sorry, but I do not know
what to do. It is too Pote be!
Each monster has a ¹ œ weakness.
Frankenstein - Fire,
Dracula - crosswise.
There must be something you grandmother is afraid!
So, what do you want,
Ebym ¿³ do for you?
Well ¿... it is difficult to specify, Abe.
- It is related the relationship with my mother ¹ ¹.
- I know something about mothers.
My always brings with each other on
Sunday dinner, apple pie with whipped ¹ ¹ œmietan.
- He knows also that's my weakness.
- Our grandmother is similar.
Besides, it is also wrinkled sack hatred,
¿¹ feeds tracting the destruction and damage.
/ We want to get rid of her home.
But refuses to exit.
I had the idea of ??this am.
You see, ...
It is the racist.
I mean, she is afraid of ...
black people.
What do you want me to do the ¿...
I see ...
because thanks to the e ..
want ebym ¿...
Well, I guess so ...
Really?
³ I will do it, but do not
there is enough dark.
Only the irritates her.
And then he said I:
"Orange, I never said the banana".
Hey.
I have found them in the œmieciach.
We can later pogadaæ,
I'm with friends of me.
Give a tuxedo.
What? No. I like the tuxedo.
This is mine.
It is not yours.
Give it back, or I'll call security.
Hey, I'm there!
Hey!
Tell me that you like.
B-governments honest.
Dad, I Know-.
Do you have any jakiœ financial plan!
Or any plan!
Malcolm, I'm talking for the last time.
Stop martwiæ money.
I'm doing you a tax return.
I know how much of the earn!
I know how much you spend. And less
So I know how much a child.
You will brakowaæ
at least $ 70 per month.
Before your child goes to school s,
We will be at the back of the 18 000 $.
Then they'll take it you are.
You'll be bankrupt!
- Something will come.
- You can not continuously as you speak!
All right.
I'm a bad father.
I'm a terrible parent.
You attempted it will hear!
No.
But I know how to help you.
What is this?
It's from the University of Martindale.
This is an amazing private schools a
But it is in London.
I offer the full half scholarship.
Tuition, housing, everything.
As I will not be at home,
to do just fine.
I'm a firm.
Absolutely not!
You do not have howling ¿d ¿AAE!
- But ...
- Malcolm, you're the only hope ¹ ¹!
- Hold this.
- Sure.
Wyjaœniê you something.
When my mother, or I say,
Also the same thing at the deposit are,
This is a code designating the months:
"Malcolm wymyœli something"!
We need you. This family of
is the family, then it is time.
Where's Dewey?
Ladies and gentlemen, please take into
Due to the of a man with a balloon.
And listening to the dispatch of holding onto more
the heart of history.
Welcome.
My name is Dewey.
/ And the part of the man with the balloon,
/ This is my dad, Hal.
Dewey?
Where are you?
I najm the younger of four children.
Always my needs are at the end.
/ Do I did not have the hot shower
/ Or in the own of bed.
I am the third person are,
who wears the pants.
Until now, I never complain of em.
Dewey, what's going on!
/ Even when my parents decided
/ For another child
I enjoyed the sure that the share
with him what I've got.
I then said,
Also speeds up the delivery.
/ I have chosen for this very
/ Cy interesting day.
Do you remember what you have selected day, Dad?
- Dewey!
/ - What day, Dad!
This Thursday, come here ...
wherever you are!
Of all the days that can EOE
select, choose the closest EOE slower Thursday.
- Something interesting in this Thursday, Dad?
- Will you stop!
You comes to mind, which can
wydarzyæ this Thursday?
Ok, Dewey, what's going on
this Thursdays!
Then are my birthday!
This is not the ...
Bo also!
Ladies and gentlemen,
That was the story of a small boy the boy,
which was stolen birthday.
If you jakieœ comments
my dad willingly send them the ear.
This is a good time for these ideas were,
which speaks of em.
I have nothing.
/ Thank you, also przyszliœcie.
- I know it's kind of weird.
- I'm excited.
As if wystawialiœmy
"Spoon River Anthology" in college.
- We need to send back the uchiwaæ?
- Wyprzedaliœmy both shows.
4 pillows on one of bed for.
That's why you can not wykarmiæ
of their children ...
Part, Mom. I want, ¿ebyœ
know of our friends and the.
This is Brian.
And this is Abe.
Nice to you are to become familiar.
If you forgive,
to be using your bathroom.
It tells of Abe am of you.
Hi ...
For the brave, the jo, jo ³.
Loosen the port, the old.
It should be ê to ...
I do not ignore the.
Abe ... relax.
Hello?
There is someone decent?
Use the I s your key.
Unless you do not mind.
After that you have one.
¯ Eby przychodziæ when you want.
Mom, you are our sitting.
Steve lives next door.
Malik on the other side,
and Trey opposite.
Lois, you sound as if you was to a ..
surrounded.
Let me.
Welcome.
Who is this beautiful lady?
So what are you doing tonight?
Because I'd like zaparkowaæ
your car in your garage u
- Mom, where are you going?
- I do not believe that the so ¿'re alive.
Will to break loose at the station,
or œmietniku.
I can not do zrobiæ,
¿Ebyœ changed the sentence, but
I got out of the broken heart.
Barely arrived Did you come. I ...
What are you not?
Nothing. Everything is
ideally all right.
Francis Listen to very carefully there.
- I have cramps. Rodziæ start.
- What?
I must jechaæ to the hospital.
And you must wywaliæ
hence the grandmother, now!
- Come, Ida, I will help you.
- You do not have tañczyæ rain dances?
¯ Goodbye, Mom. Nice to you was to
widzieæ. Safe travels ¿y
Do not forget zadzwoniæ as
you get to ... anywhere!
You also will be a few more minutes.
Dewey, I hope,
You're a happy!
I was thinking of, also I will
but not so much.
ZnajdŸmy Rees and let's get out.
Why I switched off the phone?
68 messages!
Contractions started to s about 15:27.
Oh, that knows his watch.
Hello?
Hello Hal ...
No, I'm fine.
Baby, do not get too excited, but
wracaæ you should go home, because I
Well ¿.... rodziæ start.
What!
Well, the fault Dy ¿calm.
Do only what is necessary.
Relax. Breathe in as you need.
- Where the hell is Reese!
- What's wrong?
- Mom begins rodziæ!
- See that? He was on so hard?
Hal, I do not want, ¿³ ebyœ panic.
The only safe.
There is no reason to hurry.
Poœpiech? Come on,
¿do you know me yet.
ZnajdŸcie brother!
Brewing the tea
and relax before you arrive.
Good idea was.
Chamomile always relaxes me.
Reese! Hell,
Reese, where are you?!
I think I'll go the sixth of the streets.
We are The five ribbons on the ice?
- Where are you?
/ - Here.
- Reese!
/ - I'm in a holster on the cello.
Damn!
Lift it Rot!
- So, you want ice cream?
/ - No, thank you.
Simply Return to the home.
Only carefully.
Sure thing.
Wait a minute?
Hey, what are you doing?!
Ch the boys!
Move!
Boys Ch ³ aj transmitted the greetings.
Hey!
Come back here!
You will not escape
with my tuxedo for $ 600!
The howls precisely ¿d ¿believe the garage u
S ³ uchamy old hits.
Play the Beatles from A to Z.
Do you remember the song
Beatles on the "Z"? Because I do not.
Hal, you sound weird.
Everything all right.
Yes, turn on Maple.
At the station the wheels of a church
diesel salesman stopped.
/ Shotgun.
/ You will not believe how
/ Big the hole wjechaliœmy.
Let's go, Dad!
I can not znaleŸæ keys!
Where the hell are the keys!
/ I have them, jedŸmy already!
/ Hal?
Honey, I'll call you later.
Continued following the pi ...
www.tvsubtitles.net