Previously on ...
The child is somewhat
We thought higher than the value.
So Amy induce labor on Thursday.
/ Exhibitions Bride Fashion!
Ignition em pays the $ 50 for parking.
We are staying!
The child began to the kopaæ like crazy!
As if something upset them the o ..
/ Mom!
Is introduced.
There is someone decent?
- I have cramps. Rodziæ start.
- What?
I must jechaæ to the hospital.
S ³ uchamy old hits.
Play the Beatles from A to Z.
The brewed tea and relax
Now, before you arrive.
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x21 "Child, part 2"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.2 MB
The contractions are becoming more frequent!
Lois, you have the crap so robiæ!
¿Horror ck me that!
- Yes, me, the ¿.
- Calm down.
We can not d for much longer to wait for Hall!
We need to jechaæ to the hospital!
Really makes you think,
Also still see a husband hose?
- Mom!
- The Men's events, right?
Pull out of all of you wanted to.
Already he're not needed.
If you do not have enough przyzwoitoœci,
¿Eby udusiæ in the haze of one's own the yellow ones
that you can at least zabraæ
their venom to Aunt Susan.
- He wants ebym arrived ¿³ a? To ring up
- No!
Of course, also not.
Widzieæ want, how I suffer!
Imagination ¿ck yourself how to
œmieje me, know the c
I'm also with you,
my new favorite of.
Knock, knock, Lois.
¿I must yczyæ the hanger.
Wpad of a sandwich under my
sitting in the car.
What's going on?
Lois begins rodziæ and Hall no.
I dream of at the moment!
Here's what we'll do.
I will carry you in my car.
I have one of the three original mermaids
from the series "Starsky and Hutch".
- We'll go in up to seven minutes.
- You sound like crazy!
The entire operation of the shutter release series only two
sirens, and both are the Smithsonian.
Not true.
/ - To sirens were four.
/ - I have ...
Hal. Where are you?
Come on!
Mom starts rodziæ.
We lost 45 minutes in an office environment.
We are out of luck. Trafiliœmy the bodyguard,
who wants to be a policeman.
Kaza of these sikaæ the word to the jar, only
so that the Such use of doing this.
This time we moved on themselves.
I'll take my mother to the hospital
I do not want and will hear a ¿s any of the word,
until the return of the child.
Dr. Kerr is waiting in the hospital,
you guys are pack,
and Craig equipment is the car,
¿³ ebyœ had a place.
Even two courses we can jechaæ!
/ We're ready!
Why do you need so much luggage?
He says the I, also will not be
Potrzebowo of the two dresses.
Do not look at me. When
I fly by plane, I take one suitcase.
I'm ready to ride to the hospital.
- What? Do not go to the hospital.
- I'm not going? You're not going!
So much want jechaæ to the hospital?
- Sends the you to the hospital!
- It sends the you to the hospital!
No one is going to the hospital!
Already too late!
Somebody call an ambulance.
Rodziæ I'll be here!
Ch of boys, Call the taxi.
I call ahead to Dr. Kerr,
tell him that the mother gives birth.
- It is in the notebook.
- Dad, calm down.
Do not calm down!
Hello ...
Lois? ... What!
- Do not ruszaæ.
- What he said and?
My wife is at home
and in precisely begins rodziæ!
- I must jechaæ to it!
- Born in the house!
In this state, you is not going nowhere.
Give him 10 milligrams of diazepam.
Wypuœcie me, I'm fine!
Wait! What is this? What!
What is this? What is she doing?
I must jechaæ to it!
Give him another 10
Is to be immobilized.
Can you go with me?
We are not full of interesting magazines in the waiting room.
Highlights like?
Or Goofus and Gallant?
We do not want g of upich magazines.
Our mother gives birth!
I'm sure you also have the very good
care, just like your dad.
You have nothing to do,
/ Except relax and wait
/ Until someone when you arrive.
But something must zrobiæ.
It's our fault.
You're a very nervous young man m³ of Young man.
I have no idea what you are zrobiæ,
why do not I have been the pediatrician.
Let's go to the waiting room,
as I said the.
If you do not want to Read,
that's for sure there are chairs of a,
where You can store up pokrêciæ.
/ God, if this woman s important!
- Put on the wheel are j!
- Come on, the church of bed!
On three.
One, two, three!
It's like moving a piano.
Relax, Mom. Ambulance will
for a while, they know the what to do.
Do not worry, Lois.
I write of the in google the word "child".
It is 28 million hits.
Surely there is something after ¿ytecznego.
Craig, you are part of it, we do not need
this. Trey is a doctor.
Oh no, Lois.
I am the dentist.
But to the EOE in medical school, right?
Yes, but I specifically selected the
dentistry, because the ...
the area below, for
the look, it's starting to chichotaæ.
Yes I have.
From high school.
- For me the continuity's sake!
- In the I doubt, ¿me to be the only one.
Emergency ...
- Part is Malcolm?
- Do not ...
We need his notes to
the task of biological chemistry.
It's not a good time.
Do not say hello to the old grandmother ¹?
I'm Malcolm!
Przechodziliœmy already been through it.
Bo also! Child terribly
strong pressure on the neck!
So everything is under control.
Piama and I will be
Collect, back at the ranch.
- What are you talking about?!
- Nothing. Do you think that the running away?
Do you think that the being at
one's own mother, who gives birth,
is so uncomfortable,
Wymyœli also the excuse I, ¿Eby exit!
There's even a grain of truth!
Okay, baby clothes,
baby names.
Drivers bulbs you dressed as ...
Sorry, you will help me someone
znaleŸæ notes Malcolm?
We need them for homework.
Hence the Beat, Lloyd!
Rodziæ begin!
For a while I give birth to a child!
This is a very important task.
We are the worst Child Lock
in the world. Mama mia ³ a're right!
Really we are by small,
of the young trolls,
which is not anything interesting, apart from the Sun.
I destroy everything of which we have contact.
Poszczêœci to us, as there
We will end in jail or in the grave.
Here's what we'll do.
The event begin to himself for 10 minutes.
They learn how to opiekowaæ up babies.
- We're on it!
- What do you mean?
Learn how pomagaæ.
Come once we learn
how to be good!
That's it!
Yeah. This child will not be
is continuously spadaæ on your head.
Yeah ...
what?
Wey g of êboki breath and blow,
as zdmuchasz œwieczkê!
Oh, God also!
I was thinking of, also my fingers are exploding!
Well breathes of EOE.
/ Hey!
/ ³ I have found something!
In a fraction of a percent of children
are born with tails.
I wonder if they find it easier okazywaæ radoœæ?
Where the hell is the ambulance?
The bed at any time.
Steve rang 10 minutes ago.
This is true. In precisely this
I will do the 10 minutes ago.
- Where We bought t the wallpaper?
/ - I really like.
I feel awful.
So we want to walk perfectly well on the job.
Oh, my God also?
We should themselves feel awful.
- You're a terrible Child Lock!
- We know this!
Each deserves the second chance.
You can store walk perfectly well on the job.
- Thank you!
- Yes!
It can also happen that that milk
engages in the tubule.
It is important, ¿Eby pozwoliæ
wyssaæ child obstruction of the breast.
And do not worry if your child vomits
the substance are similar to of white cheese.
PrzejdŸmy here.
If I Potrzebowo the more reason,
¿Eby nienawidziæ of white cheese.
I wrapped up the now.
But if he said and,
Also of the milk flows out?
Reese, so they are.
My God!
Women are the cows among the people!
/ Coming, Lois!
Coming, Lois!
I come!
Oncoming ...
Here they come ... Lois!
I'll get the am towel under your knees.
Piama, do not use the good towels.
What does she know about the towels?
Its people are dried up,
c throw the dirt on the back!
Thank you, Piama.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure
Also an ambulance for a while coming.
But before doing that are,
I want ebyœ ¿knew something of a
Your father had a family of the drug.
What!
With loose the waitress are in Manitoba.
This ordinary and pigs.
And those children who are with her had the!
Mom, why did you say it now!
If you were died and it did not want me, ¿ebyœ
of thinking and of him as a good part of the Young man.
But do not tell my sister.
Let the thighs of the throttle up their ignorance are.
He said am just my favorite of.
- What are you doing?
- Work calms me down, OK.
We all try to deal with this poradziæ!
Yes, Francis. I'm trying to poradziæ
deal with continuous ¹, ¹ c are born baby!
I'm sorry, I work quietly.
I appreciate the, if you are ¿
You will come softly zachowywaæ.
Can I exit?
Outputs.
I must exit!
- How are you doing?
- Pull me out of the d
This is not the place for me.
I must AEOI home.
Everything will be fine,
were a friend.
If someone comes in you are within 6 hours.
6 hours.
What happened then?
Wait!
What happened then?!
Ch the boys, the boys ch!
Przybijcie fifth TKE!
Look at this.
It's the ugliest dog
of what I saw.
Why are saliva?
It can be sick.
Look at this.
No, please, PREVIOUS here.
Please, please, please.
Is someone silenced the mutt.
So Dewey, come to daddy.
Select daddy.
We take this rotation also
and give her the the adnemu.
Ê ¿rotation? What?
No! No!
The most I'm afraid of
Also not be a good big brother.
Babies are Continuous pole
and a number of the others.
Touch the what
should not, eat all the.
After half of our Lego
Historically, and through him.
Even more.
They got a new baby?
/ Lois puœæ!
/ Or with the ap his hand!
He says the that the birth is najboleœniejsze
experience in the life of a woman.
With a little make-up jam, byœ przejœæ Such use.
But I was not able to byœ szwêdaæ up with the wheel ¿hands.
Okay, you know what?
So standing in the matter, lady.
We're better than you.
Each of us at each time possible way.
I m smarter than you are. Better
educated. So it gives the social eczeñstwu.
I have a family that loves me.
I live to a large house,
it ¿d ¿ê expensive car
and one year earns more
than you probably through an entire force.
Big deal.
So you're a drug dealer!
Hal, where are you?!
Ambulance will
at any time, hold on!
I can not withstand,
it just does not work a
The child is coming now!
Lois, I do not want to przeæ until
do not have a 10-cm aperture.
So, check as you want!
The pleasure to be looked in the mouth you would.
You know that the animals are
now in your garden,
the act, as in Africa?
If it was to my room, it's not free
It would be closer to them on the Insert 5m from the door!
I do not believe that the you are still here.
I do not believe that the my sister just
Now, get out of the room than the OCI of a
I do not believe that the I'll be had to the
Carry out into the room the boys!
Take it easy. Your sister knows
Also your mom dies?
What are you talking about?
Your sister knows that the your mom
has the deadly diseases that are hidden and the
and this may be the last chance for peace.
With her mother are who dies.
- Wipe! Powder!
- Okay.
Done!
- Fastest!
- In your face!
- We learn how to take care of the children.
- So talk the suckers!
We will best older
braæmi the world!
Sweeping in changing diapers
and we are the best in paniu angle.
I am glad that the've memorized all the popular
chemical products which are poisonous for children's hands.
You know, so many things have to robiæ parents.
Feeding, washing, changing diapers,
security and planning.
Understandable em something through it.
Mom never anything that does not hit them!
- Bottle and this was to the eczku of bed.
- It is not surprising that the tray we are.
/ 6 months, may years.
- Do you need a computer.
- Not now, shorty.
Lois is born and I am
responsible for exploration.
It's hot.
I can not pracowaæ,
as someone above me are facing!
See if I can get her the znaleŸæ.
Mom, the phone!
Border Guard will give me the shotgun?
Hello? ...
So ...
I am glad that the say so.
No, I'm fine.
I'm here P. .. you know who
and she makes ... you know what ... again.
Where's the ambulance?!
The contractions are too often!
Francis, the baby will be born
at any time.
- You have something for me zrobiæ.
- What am I robiæ?
- Do you have accepted the delivery æ!
- What? No!
You'll be fine!
Does the EOE is already earlier!
- You are still taking deliveries of Your Pet!
- You're not the CYM animal are born!
Francis does not have your father,
but I trust you!
Even I do not like!
But I love you too!
And that's why you do!
No!
You can not make me!
Francis, mom asks you to help!
Francis, you can handle.
I know that you can.
As you insert your hands on mom
and pull out the gniesz baby!
Lois.
Lois, finally you have found the em.
I miss the baby.
It's good.
The baby is healthy, Hal.
Honey, I'm
¿I was the worst husband in the world.
I do not believe it,
I'm terrible!
I do not believe that the have to Did you come
przejœæ through this alone.
I really wanted to be there then!
By the EOE there, Hal.
He was I?
We are with each other after Reunited.
Wherever I am,
that you're there with me.
I love you.
Oh, my God also?
What's this guy doing?!
- What?
- From the Day of the popaprañcu!
- What? Lois, do you ...
- Somebody call the police!
/ Dad!
Oh, my God also?
What the hell are you doing?
- See the ówkê g?
- Not yet.
He did not even look!
- Here we go uwypuklaæ?
- Yes!
Well, well.
I do not believe that the look ...
it! Die!
It can, if already grams of ówkê,
This can be przeæ!
If someone calls,
I'll be your sister.
No, do not worry.
I know, where's the door.
Come on, Lois.
Come on!
I've got it! I've got it!
I've got it!
Yes!
The position of the them on the breast.
Part of, the child.
Part of.
Thank you, Francis!
That's the nicest thing for me as the
do the EOE. I'm proud of you.
You can already zwymiotowaæ.
- Well done!
- Congratulations!
That boy of boy or a girl?
/ It's a beautiful, healthy baby.
He knew I was!
I'm your mom are.
Ok, so who is expecting a baby.
He says the I, also we should not
zatrzymywaæ for coffee.
Did you forget am, what are the no of e
I have forgotten how the nicely smelling the
Ok, dawaæ them to us.
It is 17:30,
time angle ladies child.
See how the full n is the diaper.
When was the last time
przewijaliœcie them?
We have decided up
at least the first name?
So ... Jamie.
It fits.
We'll be back as your
Bed udders are ready.
www.tvsubtitles.net