/ Jalapeno Chilies
How many are missing the record?
Two more cans.
Really there is no record
Jalapeno peppers in food.
But already suffered sufficiently at the.
For a while I tell him.
Nied the length of his will.
I promise.
97th
Seriously, I'll tell him.
Crazy world of Malcolm
4x19 "The future s Malcolm"
T the interpreter:
Charles MoszeUsz and polishchaser1
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD:
624x352 25.0fps 175.1 MB
Mom and Dad.
We will go to rural area on Saturday,
view the meteor shower?
You have pojechaæ jakieœ 40 km,
¿Eby to have a good view.
It starts at 2 in the morning.
- You can repeat?
- Meteor shower.
He says the that it will be best for 100 years.
It sounds scientific.
No, thanks.
Come on, Reese,
meteor shower.
Fire balls are flying through the air,
fumes smash the ground, just before you are!
- It's not like the appearance of the can.
- We can on jakimœ przejechaæ.
No, it's going 100 km above the earth!
But it is beautiful and interesting hands.
If Malcolm has of doing this on
jakieœ task for schools were, then we'll go.
This is not to school y
To forget it. You will not be woken up
at 2 am, ¿Eby Daae viewing the stars.
Bran? Why do you eat? Says Did you come to,
Also tastes like cat food.
I eat it because I must tyæ the crap!
Turns into the huge, a thick cow.
- Not at all.
- Even the doctor so he said.
It œmieszne, now eat for two.
What your doctor does not know?
Hal, he's right.
I'm great!
I do not understand how it's going.
It is believed that am, you're a beautiful
regardless of everything.
Thank you, darling, you're such a s the sweet.
Do not understand what I'm trying the robiæ anything.
And when you understand the,
This is the œmiej me.
But why should we expect
Also the other bed than the rest of the world?
Let's face it.
Each on this planet is ridiculous,
tracting scratching the back of the bed, half-grams of pencil.
Back off ... from us.
How can the EOE at all pomyœleæ,
Also Niemzowitsch defense Operate on me?
He tried EOE two games ago
and weights of butchered em.
He tried EOE 4 games ago
Serious does not, as you are
way home in the evenings?
Wait, where are you going? What?
Good!
Who wants zagraæ?
Eddie, come, hitting
same stone in your head.
We will even.
No?
Chaboo, you can jeœæ
one by hand, the second play.
I do not believe in it.
We are cowards!
Œmieszny Hey kid,
Want to gather in chess?
No, thanks.
No. Come on, it's not that hard, look.
This looks as
as the adniutki, little boy.
I know what a jumper.
I know these ¿as skontrowaæ
dribbling Niemzowitsch
without leaving
free way to Bishop.
Your left flank was to a
full of holes as a Swiss cheese.
Hey, I was young champ.
Read it again
chess reference guide.
As soon as the CPI byœ me a runner
¿goodbye after the byœ with aging ¹ and two pawns.
Ok, I understand.
Are you afraid of me!
Yes, I am afraid that the guest of jakiœ
in the park beat me at chess.
Apparently so!
Now, you're wrong the fear of litoœci!
Fear forces us to fight or flee.
A litoœæ allows me to flip
and odejœæ, with ¿alem your nieszczêœcia!
/ - I'll kick your rear piece!
- Okay, this fairly.
I was expecting the up ... this.
Nice to, have children ...
Dewey!
What are you doing?
- I paint the wall.
- What's with you?
- Why do the EOE?
- I'm told the child about
Child ... the child?
Select the color of the ¿.
I've preferred to more bronze brown.
Listen to my son, I know that the Worried
birth of a child, but you do not.
Yes, you will not be already najm the younger.
It is true that the child we'll be
poœwiêcaæ whole attention regarding the case for some time.
You will need to pomagaæ Find out more at home.
This will probably be
had to dzieliæ bedroom.
My dad is trying to tell, that there is no
¿ebyœ because so perpetuates the!
Now clean up this mess the Taj!
I kid you not talking to you!
He said about that the'd say.
Draw.
Draw?
Draw!
Draw.
- One more time.
- No!
Gracie ... four ... hours!
Okay, okay.
Bo ¿e
Who designed the these
damn, the cement benches.
Probably jakiœ g of stupid clerk
who never finished the architecture.
It reflects their frustration
on the back of the hands of the public.
What's wrong with this guy?
He's so upset the months. First
heat is on, then too cold.
Then go the the eba œmiesznie walking.
Do not close the the even per second!
He could be the spróbowaæ narzekaæ the crap!
You know what the worst part is ...
- 4, 9, 7, 3, 6, 7 ..
- Stop this robiæ.
Sorry.
I'll be back after a few hours.
Wait, where are you going?
He says the am you, poses
the classes of painting.
- Poses? Nudity
- Yes, we talked about it.
No. Always remember
s discussions with the word "nude".
You can not disassemble yourself against Otto.
Not waving tassels
on the catwalk, Francis.
Poses for painters, the work.
P of wages are $ 250.
Piama, I want to Know-,
if I have a good paint.
What color are your nipples?
It's very tasteful, which is not
does not matter, because you know what?
This is my body about, so do not
you can speak to me what it robiæ!
If you're not on it sufficient that
were ripe, it's your problem.
$ 250?
All that I knew of
On Beauty, was to angle the amstwem.
Morning Dewey wanted to AEOI
the schools were in the briefs,
because the child does not like his clothes.
The kid pushed me to the wall.
And you are still gaining weight, like crazy.
More than a half a kilo a day.
There is not much fatter, it does not make sense.
I know, honey, it's surprising trades,
but you skoñczyæ
of t are obsessed about the weight.
- Would you like some juice.
- I do not want the juice, Hal.
I know what's going on!
- Yes?
- Of course, I'm the idiot!
- Sorry, it's ...
- It's because I work there also.
- What?
- It is obvious, Hal.
Æwiczê not enough
as in previous continuous ¿s.
In previous children,
whole day to the bare am on my feet.
It makes perfect sense.
Celery?
Why this should be so messed up.
The celery taste like bacon!
Baby, Listen to.
Do not freak out for a few pounds.
For me, the look you give œwietnie.
Not important
how large a and of round and it becomes.
- Hello?
- Part, Mom.
Tell your child
Also have a g the pole bucket of sand,
but buses already ceased to
jeŸdziæ and I can not return to the house.
Dewey?
Where are you?
I do not know exactly.
Somewhere wheel on the pier.
- You're a wheel on the pier?
- Where?
Dewey, do not move from there d!
As soon as you come.
Okay, but a pair of przywieŸcie
socks. Drop in the ¹ ³ em in the fish guts.
What is wrong with this child?
Really starts to martwiæ.
Calm down, we'll go, we'll buy a pair of
p the donuts and przemyœlimy is on the way.
Again tie?
Casey Kasem, why not wyœwiadczysz
all aperture and services œciszysz this shit!
It is not loudly.
He does not speak of I, also is loudly.
I he said that the shit!
So, are you doing this whole young days?
You sit in the park
and playing chess with strangers?
No. I like this ¿d A long walk
on the beach Communal swimming and angle of the beam b.
Of course, what most
szczeroœæ it excites me.
So your only contact with people, the
playing chess with people who you can not stand the.
I'm sorry, I must also zburzyæ your
assumptions idea gained from schools y
But I'm not a loser jakimœ.
I have great force. I œwietn the job.
Sell ??toner on the phone.
Make some calls and the
I have a tenth of the rest of the day to yourself.
You can not so large a zarobiæ.
I was thinking of, you're a m are smarter, Malcolm.
It's not about the money, but about FREEDOM.
I am independent.
Does what he wants, when he wants to, not
I must odpowiadaæ for anything, ever.
Where's my 20 bucks, Leonard?
Mia the EOE borne in on Monday.
I, are here.
You know, I was looking for the you.
I can not be the znaleŸæ you, then
I had the important business meetings.
13, 14
- Agree cigarettes?
- He throws the em.
It's good. Well, because they know
kill the slow. This is true.
And the prices are ...
Give him six bucks!
Easy, Goerge.
What an asshole.
I'm afraid that the time is up the the.
Once again, thank
models for you ¿angle works.
Thank you.
I'm glad you also have the opportunity to
zrobiæ something for you.
- To the EOE were great as always.
- It is in precisely they are doing.
These Piama ¿and to the right, not the think?
Francis, inspired the EOE
me to new challenges.
Look how I capture a certain of the forces ê
torso and pitched the arrogance of your ass.
Francis, let's go.
I talk with people,
if you do not mind.
Unfortunately, someone is doing
is of the soul, and someone without.
- Part, Mom.
- Part, Dewey.
/ Come home soon,
/ Buster!
A child does not sermons of the
jeŸdziæ your car!
Do not use the s about exactly of the word "car",
he said about "it ¿d ¹ whole machine",
but it had the thoughts of the.
What is this?
Someone in the office had the birthday and no one
This is not the pathogenic because it is bezt the grease.
Why is there no string
"All the best"?
You know, the policy office.
Do not want you to believe the politically correct
some of these idiots can be.
/ Tony Bennett
/ - "The Way You Look Tonight"
/ Yes, you are wonderful
/ Z 's smile as a warm
/ Cheeks so soft
/ There is nothing to me,
/ Only you kochaæ
/ So are, how beautiful you look today you will give the
/ So wonderful.
/ I'll never change
/ Keep the charm
/ Please, grant, so was to
/ Because I love you too
/ So are, how beautiful you look today you will give the
- Look at this.
- I look.
This will improve the EOE to Rubio. Stop robiæ
the noises of person, if you rearrange the figure.
- Part of Leonard.
- You have to view the.
Physically hurt, right?
S ³ Look, I talked to a guy.
- For I facilitated the job interview you.
- What are you talking about?
You're nieszczêœliw the people are!
I barely have a job and completely
you're doing in dealing with people?
And it's my fault?
Rather than rest of the world?
Does not have to be!
When will we have the work of among the people,
you can get used to them æ ¹
and change their force.
Forget it!
I will not marnowaæ time
like the stupid œ g of the job interview,
because you've got to the needs of œ
I save myself.
Why not use with this device
the neurotic energy
and confronts
with in the own fear: failures angle!
O God, the sky is about to open the
and now I'll get a new force!
Thanks to your Oprah-like
psychological intuition.
Now, trying to ignore the Insert
Ironically, the real problem,
Which are you carefully ck
the GRE for an intelligent of words.
Olaa it, I'll play with it!
- What, are you still a tie.
- Not this time.
Okay, but if you do not win,
already it will never be as says the.
Stands.
Where's my money, Leonard?
George, I have ... I got her the only ...
Get out!
How are wage in this job?
What are you doing?
- You can briefly potrzymaæ?
- Sure.
- After what it really is?
- You'll see.
Distraught of EoE?
It was not my idea of ??the,
I'm told the child about!
Wait ... child have?
Baby mama talking to you?
Yes, each also robiæ me these crazy things.
I'll give you advice, you ignorowaæ
the votes, are not on your side.
I never tell anyone about them, do not tell.
Especially teachers.
The panic for no reason.
Do you understand?
- Yes thinking.
- Good boy the boy.
Will be fine.
- This idea was hopeless.
- No, it is precisely this need.
Do you remember?
Working people force.
But why here?
Because it's the only guy I know,
which will facilitate for a job interview
for the collector's box of each
Lunch in Hong Kong.
Greetings earthlings.
Unless you're kidding.
Trust me, I know that it will be you ¿ko,
but, as will be silent of the
5 minutes, you can AEOI home.
Waiting, accounting ¿Niczko.
- My CV.
- Forget it.
Nothing, contact your CV.
So, tell me
where he previously worked EOE.
- Well, I ...
- Interesting.
You know, I like myœleæ the Lucky Aide,
as a kind of family.
And in this family,
I will be your father.
As a father I can poprosiæ you
about doing things that do not have the sense,
But you do it,
I am your father.
Without pyskowania, just
do it. Do you understand?
Right now.
Who are you in the family?
You're a second cousin?
And can the aunt without fifth-staves?
I have always seen the up
m³ as a younger brother.
The large on can be up nauczyæ.
Never I had no brother.
I am, we can zaczynaæ for a while.
- Francis, do not call the am.
- Yes, noticed that the em.
I can not robiæ your
work and his, Gloria.
No Camembert cheese?
You expect that the game I'll be the
with wine, and without Camembert?
It corrupts the whole aesthetics!
- Francis ...
- Forget it, I'd worked without cheese.
Who is this?
This is Jeremy, our present
model, why not call the am.
Francis, naszkicowaliœmy
your already fabulous poœladki.
Now it's time, byœmy examined mutual
interaction of light and shadow on a fat Jeremy.
That's it?
So does it end?
You throw me like yesterday the fish?
After I give you the
What my soul?
- Francis, please, try to understand the.
- No, I do not understand!
I will allow you to view the ³ Each color
my existence, and you odrzuciliœcie it!
One day you pass the
realized what we lost.
Will be przeklinaæ
for banalnoœæ and krótkowzrocznoœæ.
But I will be already too late, because I'm gone!
Yes, I'm gone!
I can your bathrobe?
Craig tells him already almost hour.
Even the sermons of the AEOI Leonard
to the bathroom. But Leonard is tough.
/ Now, let's talk about respect.
No self-esteem,
but respect for Toggle the ¿complex.
I remember how ... orient themselves!
It's a test to check whether the
put mounting face problems if they avoid.
Which do you choose?
- Both.
- Good.
I can see that the curvature of the spi you do not have the spine.
Welcome to the board room.
PrzyjdŸ per hour, I'll give you
uniform and a sign with the name.
Congratulations,
I knew of, also you can do it.
O God, what an idiot.
That's nothing, try every day
with this idiot and his head are the UPIM cat.
Cat can not be g of upszy from him.
This idiot is used the Barbie dolls
¿Eby manufac explained by the rules of hygiene.
Brother, right?
I think I will be an only child, thank you.
Mom!
Dad!
Dewey!
And so.
I have this fairly, Dewey!
I have enough on his head at the half, ¿ebym
and myself had to deal with this radziæ.
- But he said about the child ..
- Listen to me.
This child does not speak to you.
Honey, calm down.
I'll do tea.
You have the crap in the swim ¿
as an excuse to Observe.
Because it did not operate a
I do not want will hear a sec,
Also talk to your child. Do you understand?
- The child says she turns around ebyœ of a
- What?
- Hal.
- Do not you want maple syrup?
Craig is depressed.
Did not want to exit the booth
for still pictures, for 2 hours.
Where is Leonard?
Someone saw the Leonardo?
He asks of you that I would pass the.
Malcolm, I brought out of themselves.
I want to thank you for giving me confidence in the
of what I said that the people are huge assholes.
Someday you'll understand. People
as we will never matched by the.
What does he mean with "people like us"?
What!
Do not hate it when you do that.
If you want to tell something to say.
It's so upset the box.
www.tvsubtitles.net