Hal, you're here for six hours
and only selected the EOE to throw?
No, it's only pre-selection.
Listen to. I want only
¿Eby fit onto the van in the garage u
- This is the point of having a garage u
- You do not realize how complicated.
- Hal ...
- I promise you that the fit onto van in the garage u
Unless you're owed me an apology.
/ Crazy world Malcolm
/ 4x03 - Family Reunion
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Francis visited by us
together with his ¹ ¿you set, the Piam.
Ever since d come
do the very me about the o
Tasty lunch, Mom.
Please.
It's completely overcooked.
I think I already did not have long EOE
in the mouth of a good meal the bed.
See? Mom is so busy
picking on Piamy that the soup of not forgot about us a
Uciekliœmy from the ax.
Hello?
Part, Claire.
That's my sister!
About Bo ¿e
Since the deposit ê handset.
No, Hal.
Find out what he wants.
How are you will hear?
This week on the occasion of
Birthday Dad's family reunion.
I'm sorry, Claire, but soon I had the
the operation rate, so do not zjawimy.
No, Hal. Too long us to the Father
We should jechaæ.
But you know what?
My foot feels much better already.
So am cancels this treatment,
and we'll see on Saturday.
Wait a minute. Invite us for the two days
before the ceremony? Forget it, Hal.
We are not welcome there.
But with the feet
you never know.
And therefore we should precisely jechaæ there.
What am I talking about?
Already I had the foot of the operated.
See you on Saturday.
What is the grandfather?
It's cool, but the rest of the family dad
treats my mother like garbage; bunch of matt s.
Rich mato were, and his grandfather is
the richest of them all.
I love children. Say what you say
and we'll be lined up for an entire force.
The tip you are.
S ³ Look, for me and you is already too late,
But Dewey's are still being was young and charming.
Although there has been a long time already.
For the year You will look the
dziwad as the Father
I'm sorry that the so crowded here, Piama.
The van was not the draft
Suggest a of the water to position seven people.
That has been rejected due am
seven seats and safety belts seven.
How are you doing work on the ranch, Francis?
Great. Zero boredom.
Even some foreign Zesz week
I was one of castrated bull.
What is castration?
Ask mom.
You know, I always wanted to up dowiedzieæ
How are castrated bulls.
Tell us about it.
It's a fascinating hands busy.
Use of the tool we use to
called burdizzo.
It looks as a couple
huge claws,
and the bull must be immobilized,
so as not to kick the the ...
/ So when I cut off up
/ Subsidies blood flow to them,
/ Are drying up and in their place
/ T appears the fat tissue.
The wonderful and opowieœæ, Francis.
Thanks to the last half of one and a half hours
Mine as of the score of the whip.
Clones are coming.
B-governments were me, Hal.
Here and my brother!
Part, Claire. Hello, Tom.
Hal, this shirt looks as you outrageously.
Is ¿does not look handsome, honey?
But ¿naturally.
Lois.
Hey, Hal!
- Who is it?
- Your cousin, Pete.
Pete-o!
¿Well is it?
Birthday gift your father;
Everyone of the deposit We have paid close.
We?
For this to throw in those.
Do not worry.
Will add your name to laurce.
WejdŸmy to the center.
You have to be very weary after traveling ¿y
There was to until that bad.
Nonsense. Look at the sweat stains
Lois on clothing.
It seems that part of the family,
I never watch the ladies.
Meanwhile babia that it
shopping in her bra, visit us five times a year.
We can at this moment wyjechaæ.
Just the œæ village in the car and drive.
Sandusky Caverns is just 40 minutes hence the d
Easy, Hal.
We can do this.
I can not help it.
Always, I fall into a plant of puzzlement,
when I spotkaæ up of senior family.
Part, Dad!
Hal, arrived the EOE!
Is someone you will help the old man
exit the pool?
Willingly, Grandpa.
Well, yes.
As thinkers, why is he here?
His name is Francis.
For the atwcie his brains out.
Hello all and of each individual!
Lois.
Dewey!
The heavens, the aleo wyrós!
Obtain a fail for that even
I do not remember.
But ¿so. Œpiewaleœ me kolyœianki,
when the I Ÿaœipia.
Do you remember that?!
It's cute!
Good to see you, Dad.
I must admit that the,
Also a little frustrated the em
to mind the przyjeŸdzie here
after so long-in long absences.
I expect the ...
K of troubles with the car?
Bo looks as it
Also the EOE packaged with spare wheel!
Malcolm!
I understand that in the end he reached them of the,
You're a genius.
What is your
favorite subject in school?
I do not know. History?
And so history?
What do you think of the Civil War?
It is fairly interesting ca.
I have to show you something!
- Here we are!
- Part, Amelia.
This exit killing me
- You ¿ywiæ so many people every day,
pay attention to all the children.
I swear that the cricket tournament on Tuesday
had to przygotowywaæ am not completely the same.
Tomorrow we naleœnikowe œniadanie,
Family photo of the third,
Family dinner at the fifth,
and gifts at six.
All switched on only half my g.
Yes precisely had to feel themselves
generation of Schwarzkopf during Desert Storm.
Lois, no one else
do not wear labels with the name.
It's all right, Hal.
At the moment, give him his shorts!
You're the only grandson,
wpuœci of which I here.
This is my most valuable collections.
Super.
Do not pay any attention to it.
Do not waste your time on a pile of guns.
Throw a look at these
quartermaster Book of the main g.
This is how the war has been won.
Throw on than the eye.
Noticed that the EOE something?
Yes. The numbers at the top that were not added.
What?
In this column.
The numbers are rising in until 1286,
but the sum of the bottom is 1179.
I had the hope that
Also notice about how looks as $ ',
but it is amazing.
These are the I think that the quartermaster
Edge of the number of guns.
Thanks to such things, you can trafiæ
amy on the "Quarterly Civil War."
Good work, Malcolm.
Let's see what are you become!
Never mass of a woman me.
This requires forces y
When my body is in need of,
Men's events only can this sprostaæ.
Well, one more round-the AF point.
Man, these kids really
Francis likes were.
It is not ready for children, Piamo.
Do not rush it.
- Even dough, Lois?
- No, thank you.
Do not be nieœmia each of a
I've seen the am as the SNE wtrz Did you come to a piece of first.
Sorry.
I guess you're on a diet, right?
Dad?
- Have you seen the EOE somewhere cookies?
- We porozmawiaæ.
It's about Lois.
Ever since d here we are,
Each family is on each occasion ...
- Dad, do not do mine.
- What kind of faces?
You know how the point!
Stop it. I'm talking seriously not.
A zrobiæ g of person?
¿No kidding, Dad.
So why œmiejesz?
Dad!
Nothing funny about that.
Nothing, sir!
That was about ..
Tell us something.
We are not tired.
Tell me something!
Please.
All right. Would you like tales - here it is.
It's called "Children who were not able to
bawiæ themselves. "
Well today we gone through the o
Tomorrow we will try to the song
"Good Ship Lollipop", soon after œniadaniu.
I want the pop swim in the pool.
Pop the are using each other,
they themselves will be the city of.
NieŸle mined grandfather, Malcolm.
I admit, I spend more time with him,
But when you twist,
you just leave that shit out of the American Civil War.
- Reese ...
- You can stop this,
but do not want to have it at home.
Wara from his grandfather.
It's ours.
What?
Already mined it for three years.
I will not let you up
wepchaæ and wykraœæ it to us.
What are you talking about?
This large house built, the accident happens.
And then the baby boy,
more or less your age,
has been found in the light of the moon ¿accounting,
hung on of own intestines.
I have been on it only so much of life,
to be able to tell ...
"You would then follow!"
Come out!
He's just the angle the break,
zmyœlona this story.
I want only two seconds sincere,
man in the talks with own father.
What's so terrible in me,
Also has dystansowaæ up
jokes and g upimi the mines?
Hal, do not do no reviews of progress,
if are still being Impersona will be the
other people's problems.
We talked about it.
I just do not the apiesz.
Because I kind of like?
¿You do not have any problems with the father.
I b blessed is.
There must be some way,
to the hack of the cycle.
The way his father opuœci the Garde
and make the contact for the emotional ...
S ³ ³ EOE ear at all?
Sorry.
Hal, a solution which is simple.
You just spojrzeæ on their force,
for what you will about the
You have a good relationship with your Child Lock.
They can rozmawiaæ with you about everything.
You have the wife and kids, which many people
may be those of a pozazdroœciæ.
It is these look-up of about
- So are you think?
- But ¿so.
The adult EoE already, Hal.
What?
I get wet in the Insert the box.
It destroys me, Lois.
He tells the em myself that everything is all right,
but my bladder was to disagree.
Do not depart hence the,
until it makes it easier for the father.
Are you sure you want also?
Lois, he just sits himself
when all the treat you like a dog.
- And I do not treat you like s ³ u ¿¹ ¹ c.
- It is not until that bad.
Note that s Did you come yesterday,
Did you come to when you give Helen her chair of the,
The reverse also a pillow upside down?
No.
Why frontal array of yourself fro b here, Grandpa.
It's a battlefield, serial,
and I'm your grandfather.
I'm Captain Atticus P. Featherton,
commander companions 'A' cavalry.
The year is 1864.
The bullets flying over your head.
The nostrils, twist up
the smell of semi-smokers on the body.
Can I dostaæ yogurt?
You're ravaged by dysentery.
You do not need yogurt.
Edith, where are my keys?
They should be in the ring.
I can not hose you zaufaæ any case.
On top of that edge
are Confederate sharpshooters.
We still expect the last for at orders
or the rem us one by one.
- But ...
Real Estate, Private.
Even more still!
Is it not wonderful ¿³ e
He asks the am to be ironed were.
What is wrong with you?
/ Happy Birthday Grandpa-
/ - Your grandson Trevor
/ P. S. I hope you die!
/ I love you (your the money) grandfather.
/ From Sammy.
A fine job of the "E."
You have a talent for wazeliniarstwa.
We are lined up.
What do you mean "we"?
Mom, you have to hide the letter here.
These kids ...
What is it?
Did you forget am spakowaæ
my best shoes.
Do not believe it.
And what do I do now?
I just sneakers.
I have a photo of it and the æ biegaæ barefoot
as jakiœ wieœniak in front of these people?
Mom, it's just shoes.
Calm down.
It's not just shoes, Francis.
You have no idea what it's like you try dogodziæ
jakiejœ family and always ponosiæ tablespoon time.
About to kill the wystroiæ you up
the family image?
Part, Hal.
You know, your Malcolm hates
the heat in very well.
Dad, we porozmawiaæ.
For serious not.
So I'll do better on a serious face.
No, Dad. ¯ no min.
If you deal with it can not be helped,
already never will be between us of significant ties.
With our ties everything all right.
No, it is not.
Nego missing important item.
Sure, œmiejemy in
well we play, but that's all.
Przeœlizgujemy off after topics
does not say that the camera is nothing impor-tant.
Do you understand?
Ask your £ askotkê.
Do you remember your £ askotkê?
No, Daddy! I'm talking seriously not!
Mr. £ askotka the ¿says seriously.
Robiliœmy so whenever EOE to the child.
She loves the lord EOE £ askotkê.
Already almost time image.
That was a fun, Hal.
I am glad that the already feel better.
It does not hold liquor here.
I'm not looking liqueur, only shoes.
From some reason forgot am
Output zabraæ shoes.
And now I have nothing for Insert the
to the dress, the NRA will buy the am in a hurry,
so as to be able to the appearance Daae nicely with the family,
According to anything which is not suitable.
You know what? I have a car
a few extra pairs.
In the following order ê sure that the bed you are on pasowaæ.
Really?
It's the black jaguar
parked in front of the gates.
It is not closed.
Thank you, really.
Do not you want to become your parents?
Socks are itching me.
S ³ ³ I heard about the problem,
And I'm glad that the me about it You said.
We should Know-that the'm always
willing to help you out and about all porozmawiaæ.
Once you have done the image
spends with each of you some time,
I am committed ¿Frustrated with everything
concerning the family.
Where's the mother?
Amelia?
In your car
use and no shoes.
Are you sure ...?
/ Ask all the s smile.
/ S smile three ...
One, two, three.
S smile!
Well, I'll do one more thing.
/ S smile!
Excellent.
Thank you all.
There was to you in the image, Lois?
We can spróbowaæ zrobiæ another.
You know, if we put all again,
and if we turn back the photographer
and if he wants the kateringowcy
pause up with dinner.
Where Did you come to that, Lois?
Honey?
Honey ...
Bo ¿e ..
Is Lois also help with are the atce?
About Bo ¿e More
sadness for this woman.
What are you going?
We do not know.
Hal ... What are you doing?
I defend my dignity.
This led to me hello, Dad.
My wife semi-crying at the top because of this,
j are treated as the family,
And it must skoñczyæ.
Someone here is depressed.
Never put a frontal
real problems, right?
Just you think,
That if the poœmiejesz up, go away the same.
Do not you see?
For the entire e my life,
EOE does not pay the attention to me
whenever I pass the
through a difficult period.
This already exceeds
przyzwoitoœci boundaries.
It never helped to EOE,
and when I throw the girl,
when zdech of my dog,
when my best friend
the conduct in
when the supply of the I wciry in school,
the flow of em aka the entire summer
do not even know why the c!
Come on, Hal!
And it helped to EOE me when the family
notoriously torments of the wife and me,
so, also I had to avoid them
her and you!
For Fifteen years, I had no father,
because nothing will engage ¿half of EoE!
Okay, I will throw it out of the home.
I hope that to you, he reached the Father
I love you, Dad.
I'll get you a towel.
One of those old, please.
Everybody ready?
He was born I was READY.
Cake!
Trolley!
We had to fast from there d Remove patient
for your safety.
That was the unbelievable.
Przejechaliœmy three crossings,
Aunt Claire puœci him and in the end of the handle.
We all rozczarowaliœcie me.
I do not care what they did to these people,
Such behavior is not fitting.
Right, Hal?
In precisely. I warn you.
If ever you access a wheelchair
on the set with table and into the pool ...
The sprinkle of punishment.
The terrible punishment.
I guess I ¿egnaliœmy up with the szeœciocyfrow
sum of money from the trust fund.
I said the grandfather,
Also attaches for me hello to the truck.
What!
Are still being like you.
NieŸle. We return to the game.
In precisely.
Do not blow you too much?
No.
www.tvsubtitles.net