Malcolm, Reese!
Do not throw the ball angle in the house!
Do not throw the ball angle
On the roof!
Do not throw the ball angle through the house!
It's not even funny.
I ceased to have meaning for
already a long time ago.
Malcolm in the Middle
Crazy world Malcolm
04x01 - Zoo
T the interpreter: polishchaser1
For the sake litoœæ, Malcolm.
The last time I'm talking to you:
Get up at the moment.
Stand up when the world stops
be cruel ¿jokingly, that is, never!
Malcolm, œmierdzisz as cloakroom.
It has to skoñczyæ.
Wasting the entire summer
the u ¿Alan over the Sat.
Father of thought that the height of Alio you at camp.
You're right,
I hose the osnym loser.
Honey, it's just a phase.
Each teenager goes through this.
Me and my father also.
Francis semi-aka the shower
every day, through The six months.
Reese does not come out of the dryer.
It's a difficult, painful,
and it seems that that will never end.
Now get out of of bed!
We're going to the zoo.
Why do we have a band gapiæ
Hose of osnych Your Pet in cages
and thick, provincial têpaków
animals indicate smokers and smokers are œmiej to access them
Because I have a coupon.
Is the zoo is a place where we need to be at least
this increase to a Grip the cool stuff on?
I do not know. We will never go to the I,
when was to open.
But it will be fun.
I'm so glad
Also meet the am Matt.
That was fine were lucky.
Good old Matt.
The mine for 20 years ever since the d
As the am with you both.
I can not uwierzyæ,
Also are still being're jealous.
I'm not jealous.
I'm not that kind of guy.
I just wanted to read the meter!
Not in these pants, Tarzan!
Can simply marry Tom Cruise!
Okay, enough.
Stop it.
Halo.
Part, Dad.
Francis!
How's it going?
It is better to be can not, Dad.
We visit the country,
meet wonderful people of small.
This is the best time of our life.
Well ¿...
I think mom and I myliliœmy up
As for your travel plan ¿y
These are the dziliœmy, also it can be a disaster.
I will not reproach you that the.
Too good time!
No, thanks, Joe. Does not exceed the ¹ ³ I kn
even one piece of each cake.
This trip we absolutely aperture is used of a
We saw so many things.
Majestic mountains, quiet town,
sudden occasions to demonstrate that the dobroczynnoœci ...
It œwietnie.
Looks as it
Also œwietnie you guys are doing.
Yes. INDICATIONS FOR dobroczynnoœci ...
S ³ Look, you're going in precisely the zoo,
but please call us next week, okay?
Whole located by the Piamy.
Look how cool it is here.
And it is such a beautiful day.
Wydawaæ discontinue the sound.
Well, Mom.
I will not breathe.
You know, son. I do not like
widzieæ you in the mood.
Let me tell you something.
Can you buy the wax figure of a crocodile?
We can view the tiger?
I'm going to have the porzucaæ y
I mean, popatrzeæ to have the dust.
Look, for 20 minutes back starting
Matt's show "House pets rainforest."
Oh boy, you have to view the.
Can I just zaczekaæ in the car?
I mean, technically speaking, the c is in a zoo.
No.
And since it was committed ¿half of EOE
in his suffering
you can the whole day
opiekowaæ up m³ sweeter brother.
- Do not.
- Œwietnie.
First, let's see all the animals,
and then decide,
we will see it again.
You're here wróciæ the fifth of the!
Leave me alone.
No I want to be your nanny are the.
I just want to be alone.
- You're in the s?
- I'm not.
- You sound as if you was to.
- Let it be, I'm from the s!
- What are you were with?
- I'm not the s!
- Do not understandable byœ.
- At precisely that the so.
No, not understandable byœ.
Still the ¿¿'re alive in a child
world of dreams.
You do not realize,
You're a slightly CYM the dust quite
lost in some foreign insensitive wszechœwiecie
NYM full of random tragedy.
What is a lemur?
There is Matt. Part, Matt!
Lo-lo!
Part of.
Part, Matt.
Fine the zoo that you have here.
I must admit,
Also exciting for us the day months.
I do not often have the opportunity to
spêdziæ time with your family.
You know how it is - work, work, work!
But he says the c truth,
This g of mostly wine boss.
Behaves in a very
dominant lows.
But I have a feeling
Also will soon be on the chopping block.
At least that's
Jimbo operates in the marketing.
Good to Know-Yes, Matt.
He knew pm, also will address the
somehow something like that.
I always had the EOE so cute animals.
Not believes that Monty Did you come
a cute animal.
He hates am so in the hose!
Do you remember when he found the am it in the shower?
S here are your children?
The willingness ¹ ³ I know them.
Oh, yes, turn the nearby.
You will recognize them.
-Looking as I am.
¿And what is this little one?
Want some?
Too slow.
Be careful what you do.
That was your big b ³ ¹ d ¿ko wheel!
Do you want to solo?
No problem.
What are you doing?
He began ¹ ³.
Goats do not hook the people.
Get out.
Guess what I'll do.
Leave.
If we'll be pchaæ car
until we find a mechanic
we'll be able to pay the ACIA
aluminum cans ...
Francis, pchaliœmy it for two days.
I g of renewable and tired.
IDE to Buy something to eat.
No, no! Buy lottery tickets.
This is exactly the moment
Fortunately up when s smile.
Baby, do not we spend our
last five dollars on lotteries.
It's madness.
Now I'll go and buy food.
As they eat the Doroo.
It is no wonder that the Blue Book
values ??are less than a photo on the e three thousands of hands.
Cadillac? Yeah.
Rocznik1974?
If you say so.
What œlicznotka!
I love your
American cars.
BMW may cause the appliance nauczyæ
from you a few things,
but where there ...
everything must AAE operates flawlessly.
What do you do, Otto?
Who is this handsome boy the boy?
Welcome. I'm Francis.
I'm talking with my new cars
American friend.
And yes, it is very handsome.
So, Francis. ¿You are going
the Circle K on the wonderful e hot dogs?
In a properly only running over ¿d ¿Alio
and we screw up the car.
But you Fortunately.
It's great that the place.
We close hence the ranch
Travel with cows, horses and ludŸmi.
People are not ours are the property of their.
We called it "The Grotto."
She is Gretchen,
I am Otto - Grotto.
Can you come to us, huh?
Thanks, but I'm out of work,
and in fact we are sp wash.
Wait a minute!
I Suggest!
Forfeit of a
He could be the pracowaæ for us on the ranch.
That was and my Suggest!
We need a supervisor ranch.
I have no notion of running the ranch.
You will learn.
I know that you're the smart meters.
Really, I never ...
Look me in the eye.
Yes, I'm sure.
It's a job for you.
P ³ pays is $ 200
PER WEEK plus room and board.
For the facilitated.
- I have one question.
- Yes?
It will not end up being cut me
into small pieces of
and buried in a hidden basement?
No.
Deal.
Okay, buy the lottery tickets am.
We do not need them.
OdejdŸ!
Hence the Get out!
I'm warning you.
I will not be pressed by tugging the æ your
Goat psychological games.
If all you ever
³ I will do is irrelevant,
This can not I
depending on whatever EAE.
By making you feel more despicable.
How else ever
Such use would be szczêœliwy?
Fashion, I'm a clown in the zoo.
So buy ¿giraffe
or wynoœ in hell y
See Dewey, here is someone,
who understands.
Malcolm, you're at the zoo.
Have a lollipop.
- How can you be nieszczêœliwy?
- I wanted to grape.
Tigers!
Where are they?
They're not here.
What a racket!
You see this in precisely the've said.
Closed are the only thing I dream of EOE.
You are also at the bottom.
And may never be the deposit any tigers,
and umieœcili characters after it,
by stworzyæ mood of disappointment ...
Dewey!
I'm fine.
You idiot!
What is with you not?
Come on.
Let's hence the letter with him of the api.
All right cookie, it's time to pay the ATE.
This often has to operate normally
in the rain forest.
Can I prosiæ
another volunteer?
³ pointed at me.
Very well.
He could to give us the zdradziæ your first name?
I'm Hal. M ¹ ¿Lois.
So, Hal, do you feel the spirit of adventure?
He wanted to become familiar byœ the next
Friend of the rainforest?
I do not know.
Animals can sprowadziæ rain.
So we have to poœpieszyæ.
Because senseless destruction of the rainforest
Follow the intimidation of the CYM pace.
Each year that threaten the c thousands of com
vulnerable species. How, for example ...
Beautiful and delicate,
¿eraj on the whole bird tarantula.
I know that Viktor looks as dangerous,
but it really is a tarantula
delicate and bojaŸliwym creation.
I'm so sorry.
Victor never previously
do not do the czegoœ that.
Once the swelling go down,
¹ ³ d and should odpaœæ.
It will be here mieszkaæ.
Room for Guests',
but You can store office, is working his own way.
Yes, yes.
Move furniture, powieœcie images.
You can store a sandwich przybiæ
on the wall, if you like.
Francis Tell me, do you like horses?
I honestly have no idea.
I love horses.
Their body and are so large that, with their feet so is the E,
Also œmiaæ I want.
These are the state for us so kind and generous.
It's so beautiful.
I will never wanted to and odejœæ.
It's the same thing will happen with Otto.
We were on vacation,
and Otto to the bed so the c szczêœliwy away
from the stress of the factory management.
Yes, yes.
25 semi-uco-hearts on the day
and although a little bit if you make a mistake
certainly be know about it.
Do not move, do not move ...
You say that the 20 minutes.
And are still being'm talking seriously.
Also do you think is the s?
I do not know.
I do not think that had the significance of this.
Just b-governments quietly and try to
Daae not look like the food.
Hey, kids.
I do not think we should be there Turning to.
Yes, thank you.
Let us be of a lady
tell to someone, we are also here?
For me the continuity's sake!
I do not think that these kids
should there be.
Emancipate us out error!
Well, well ...
Calm down.
Æwiczyliœmy the event of such a situation
and are suitable for this procedure.
What is the limit
our responsibility?
No, the article in the press must brzmieæ
the co-feel that for the boys
but clearly stwierdzaæ,
Also it's their fault.
No, I will give you the key
into the room with guns.
In precisely that the so!
We saw already koalas?
Well, let's see how it looks as.
How is it?
Much better.
Ceased with the æ leaking.
Someone wants przeprosiæ.
Apology accepted.
IDE rozejrzeæ out by means of opcami ch.
Can the rest?
Hal ...
Do not know what to tell.
I feel terrible
because of what happened the o
Really?
Of course, also like that.
Come on.
These are the I think that we both know that the wearing of EOE trauma,
I selected the Lois and me instead of you.
Lois selected the a ..
Wait, so in precisely do you think?
I only hope that he said that I
with a sense of, I do not feel one's own face
Hal, it's not completely the wrong.
There was to were I with you.
This whole situation is that of a while for me
unbearable, so I withdrew em.
What?
I mean, Lois is œwietna,
but I wanted to it over the switched cznoœæ,
to which she does not agree of a
I did not know of, or in the weekend
will be with me, you are, and Dennis ...
Dennis? What Dennis?
None.
I must AEOI.
20 minutes ago I was worried about the up
Which of us eat a tiger.
Now I can not relaxing to use.
All right, kids. Tigers were not reacted
to cast our steaks.
The thing is that the prefer to you,
because we are ¿feeds as their natural prey.
As soon as you say "but," right?
So ... No.
But we have everything under control.
Wanna shoot tigers arrows
with the center calming agent.
How much will it take before they start the activity of AAE?
Less than two minutes.
Sufficient as long,
to were you can Insert at us?
Wait a minute.
Okay, these people are idiots.
Malcolm, everything will be fine.
Yes, Dewey.
These are ¿I hope so, but ...
No I'm talking about hope.
I know that nothing we will not.
You can not the Know-.
In precisely that the I can.
You can not.
In precisely that the so.
Really. I know that all
will be fine.
Hang on for another few minutes.
The Ponoæ had a similar
situation in the District of Columbia.
We try dowiedzieæ up
of what it has gone through the wrong.
The most important that the all
will be fine.
See?
Sorry. I must przejœæ.
I'm looking for my children.
There is no reviews children, that's for sure.
- Lois?
- Hal?
What are you doing here?
You should now le ¿EAE.
Yes, but I talk to the
deal with Matt,
which he said me that was to have
one dude, with whom Did you come to terms,
twirling the c with us.
O my God e .. Hal ...
I'm so sorry.
Am wanted to tell you.
Should be of a of doing this.
Never can the am found throughout designed especially now
and not thinking of am seriously not about Larry.
Who the hell is Larry?
I'm talking about Dennis!
In precisely, Dennis.
It's the am had in mind.
Oh my God, who are you?
Hal, please ...
We can omówiæ it today in the morning?
I do not know, Lois.
Can then have a date.
Firstly,
That was over 20 years ago.
Second, it does not matter,
I love you for it.
And third, you regard the EOE
with t the loose are the manicurist!
There are devices dziliœmy homes for horses.
And this will be your office.
You have a long-pens in one drawer,
and paper in the other.
Initially, it stores a ³ em
in the same drawer,
but it's not going to the Father
But if you want the same spróbowaæ,
You're welcome.
Here Zeke.
Zeke, explore Francis.
Frontal em. How's it going?
It is a new oversees the ranch.
¿Will be responsible for the inventory proceeds,
for feeding schedule, consider renting hardware ...
Well, for everything.
I must AEOI and prepare a buffet.
Sure you have a lot of cowboy
things to talk about, huh?
Okay, Listen to, because he probably
for 30 seconds you know it yourself.
I'm not really a cowboy.
Not even my name is Zeke only Murray
and sure as hell do not know what I'm doing here.
You have no idea?
In life there I worked on a ranch.
Really?
Yes. Never would I in the vicinity of such
which has not thrown æwierædolarówki.
It's great.
Listen to S will hit the EOE here ¿s ³ ê of gold.
People follow the months this place
are real idiots.
I do not know.
Appear to whole quite nice.
Mili is to defective Specify the.
You do not even lift a finger ¹ æ
and they and the bed so you are semi-latin.
¯ Are you kidding me?
I'm telling you that the only thing we have to robiæ
This pilnowaæ each other,
and we can wydoiæ people
the last cent.
What do you think?
I think that you're fired.
Now, if you forgive,
I will go to convince themselves,
whether it's for me or for the horse.
With the break Did you come to a promise!
What promise?
¿Do not we had any.
That was a mutual understanding!
At least on my part!
You're exaggerating with the reaction.
It's the am with a couple of guys,
We met when he.
How does the find the difference?
A few?
How many of them was to, Lois?
Do not you understand?
It does not matter.
You win the EOE.
It's already past continuity, the end.
Your promise ring
it is not the memory of the tk are a family.
What?
Ok I of the break you.
³ I bought it.
- So go buy the EOE.
- For someone else.
Someone else?
Sorry.
I hold the secret to
for so many years.
It did not dawa of the peace.
³ I always knew that the supposed
tell you, but I did not know the how.
Who was to?
Farrah Fawcett.
I had the Fifteen years.
He knew I was, also a lot of guys
with her love of the,
but I was thinking of that if the hands her the ring
¿if not distinguished from the rest of those idiots.
I'm sorry that the earlier
you do not he said I was.
Can you just let us recognize,
That we are even.
Hey, Randy, this is Bill.
These two little ones are still being is
trapped on the catwalk tigers?
Let's all calm down the.
Coincidentally, I answer the information
of obwoŸnego.
Reese and Malcolm?
Malcolm and Dewey.
Reese has not survived to 30 seconds.
I think Stanley back starting with the oœciæ.
EOE give them the names?
This Stanley.
It Frytka.
Dewey, I want to tell you something.
I love you.
Do not say that!
This is true.
We love you too.
You say that I carefully ck,
Also killed.
It's part of your
hatred for life.
You are wrong. I love the force.
Now that the uœwiadomi of em.
It is not perfect,
but it also contains the love.
I love mum and dad,
Francis and even Reese.
I love you all.
Stop it. We'll be fine.
Why do not you stop, Dewey?
Why do not you stop pretend,
Also everything is great
and do not say that the love me?
Do not die!
In precisely that the so!
're Going to die!
This is the ultimate proof
Also all the time I had the right!
I do not need any g ¿the child play the fool
Give the fold of lying to me the false hope.
You do not need any mazgajowatego brother ¿
perishable lying the whole use these brand being in a zoo.
Oh, my God also?
Just're in with the white spirits.
We'll go with that.
Wrong.
Admit it, Dewey.
Superman did not arrive here
and will not save us.
Straight in the face, kozo.
And who now œmieje?
Since the trip to the zoo,
³ I now get a lesson from the life.
It's amazing that the something as simple
almost like being eaten by tigers
puts everything in a new light.
It's just great that the
szczêœliwym be again.
Of course, you always have to
This uczyæ the hard way?
No one else so no.
Why is the universe believes that that the needs almost
zabiæ me to it until he reached me of the?
My life sucks.
Go To of bed.
No, Francis.
Everything good in the deposit of about s
Zgodziliœmy will not pozywaæ them
and they agreed to
Reese wsadzaæ not in jail.
Simply already know.
Tell me about your new job.
It is of a great
So many already taught em up.
By the way, when we were at the zoo
will not happen to you on the widzieæ
jakiegoœ birth animal?
No. A what?
Just out of curiosity.
AD invalid.
Already almost done, baby.
Push the last time.
www.tvsubtitles.net