( fighting and screaming
on video game )
Pass the chips, please.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wow, that was a really
great move.
My head just went flying.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I told you boys
these games are too violent.
( screaming on game )
Here, watch something wholesome.
Man: ? The sun is a mass
of incandescent gas ?
? A gigantic nuclear furnace ?
? Where hydrogen is built... ?
Give me more chips!
Get your own, doofus!
Shut up! I'm watching!
You shut up!
I want more chips!
Here!
( screaming )
( pottery breaking )
? Yes, no, maybe ?
? I don't know ?
? Can you repeat the question? ?
? You're not the boss of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? Life is unfair. ??
Lois:
$90 for a toy?
It's not a toy.
It's a robotics kit.
You build a little
mechanical rover.
It teaches you about
electronics and engineering.
Does it teach you
to pick up your socks?
That I'm interested in.
Hal:
Besides, son
robots are evil.
What?!
Westworld, Terminator
the creepy maid from TheJetsons...
How much scientific
proof do you need?
Mom!
Malcolm, no!
If you want this thing so badly
pay for it with your own money.
You're starting
to baby-sit next week.
Just save up.
What will they pay me?
I'll tell you
what they'll pay you.
What all jobs pay--
less than you're worth
and just enough to keep you
crawling back for more.
Now go on. It's bedtime.
That's the way discussions
go down in this family.
I tell them my needs
and they say no.
Then Dad reveals
another cartoon character
he's afraid of.
Hey, how much time
do you think we have?
Not long enough for that look.
( laughing )
You butt-wipe,
that's my toothbrush.
So use mine.
You can't just take
someone's toothbrush.
Give me that.
Fine.
Oops.
Hal...
that is the third bug
I've seen today.
You have got to call
the exterminator!
What, and miss out
on watching you hunt?
You're like a sexy,
bug-killing panther.
( laughing )
Reese:
Malcolm, stop!
( boys yelling )
Lois:
That's it!
Bedtime was 20 minutes ago.
Go to bed!
( grunting )
Bed!
Hal, bring the spray!
I haven't rinsed yet.
Only boys who behave
themselves get to rinse.
Honestly, every night
we go through this!
Mom, can I have a story?
Once upon a time
there was a little boy
who made his mother so crazy
she decided to sell him
to the circus.
An evil circus?
No, a nice one with monkeys.
Thank you.
Hal:
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I see
where they're coming from.
Ah, you cannot hide.
Aw...
Aw!
( tiny munching sounds )
Okay, come on, boys.
We're all camping out
in the den tonight.
Here we go.
Hey, Francis,
aren't you going to open up
your mom's care package?
Give me a minute.
I'm still savoring this.
I swiped Commandant Spangler's
master key.
It opens every door
in the academy, Stanley.
Every door.
I think it's cookies.
Who cares?
I'm about to expose
every secret sin
this place conceals
to the harsh light of day.
So, can I open it?
Yeah.
What'd my mom send me?
Bug-infested cookies.
As usual, a mixed message.
And this is the living room.
This is the biggest,
nicest house I've ever seen!
Wow!
Pomocanthus imperator.
We call him Barney.
Malcolm?
We saved you some dinner.
Dinner? Me? Saved?
Dinner?
We weren't sure
which you liked better
turkey or roast beef,
so we fixed you a platter.
Platter?!
Okay, kids, what time is it?
- Bedtime!
Boy:
I'll race you!
They're going to bed?
So you're just paying me
to hang out here for three hours?
Well, maybe three and a half.
We'll round up to four, of course.
Come on,
there's got to be a catch!
Oh, and Malcolm,
you can't watch television...
unless you turn on
the satellite first.
Otherwise, all you'll get
is pornography.
It's weird...
I think I'm having a spasm.
The muscles in my face
keep pulling on my mouth.
Oh, I think I'm happy!
I just don't understand
how it got so bad so fast.
Well, it's been
pretty hot this year.
That's part of it, but, uh...
mostly it's that giant
pile of candy wrappers
and half-eaten cereal boxes
you have in your crawl space.
It's like there's
some kind of creepy hobo
living down there.
Whoa...
there really
is a lost bomb shelter.
Wow, this is almost as exciting
as that room
full of folding chairs.
Let's get out of here.
Aw, come on, Francis.
Don't you want to explore?
We might find
the abandoned furnace room
or the old Civil War amputorium.
I didn't want to say this before
but you've confirmed it--
Marlin Academy is the most
boring place on earth.
We're not going to find
anything interesting.
I take that back.
Look, the circus!
The circus is at our house!
Say good-bye for a few days, boys.
We're moving out.
This is humiliating.
Why can't we just stay
at a nice hotel?
Because we're giving
all our money
to the exterminators
so they can stay in nice hotels.
Craig...
thank you so much
for lending us your trailer.
Oh, I'm just glad
someone's finally
getting some use out of it.
I bought it 1 5 years ago
to take on my honeymoon.
You were married?
No, I live on hope.
Well...
thanks again.
You're welcome.
Bye.
Good-bye.
Aw, this is cozy!
It's 1 50 degrees in here!
My butt is sweating.
Ah, it just needs
to air out a little.
The trailer!
Come on, let's make
the best of this.
I'm going to go baby-sit.
It's still early.
They don't mind.
They paying you okay?
Yeah.
It's okay.
I can't believe how much
these people are paying me!
I did the math...
I'm actually making more an hour
than Mom does.
( sighing contentedly )
I got to stop doing this.
It's creepy, right?
''Lester.''
Looks like he was the janitor.
How long you think
he's been down here?
I'd say May of'85.
You can tell that by tasting?
No, the date on the newspaper.
Then why did you lick him?
How often do you get
to taste a mummy?
We should tell
someone about him.
Uh, no, you can't do that.
Commandant will know
you took the key
and he'll punish you
and then he'll punish me
and I'm going to have
to punish you.
Yeah, but don't you think
that's kind of sad?
I mean, Lester's family will
never know what happened to him.
They probably still set a place
for him on holidays.
Yeah, well,judging by
the empty scotch bottles
and German dungeon porn,
I don't think so.
Damn. Beta.
And you made fun of me
when I bought
this mesh underwear.
Who looks like an idiot now?
I stand corrected.
Close the door.
Were you raised
in a barn?
But it's cooler outside.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Will you please
make up your mind?
There's no need
for that kind of tone.
It wasn't a tone.
There it is again.
Look, Hal, it's hot.
We're all cranky.
Will you please just drop it?
Fine.
I think you should apologize.
I didn't hear you apologize to me
when you used up all the liquid
in the chemical toilet.
Well, we have
your taco casserole
to thank for that, don't we?
Boys, will you step
outside for second?
Your father and I need
a little privacy.
Lois: Look, I didn't want to say
anything in front of the boys
but you are behaving
like a giant ass!
Hal:
Oh, really?
Well, as long as we're
on the subject of giant asses...
I'm ready to go.
Hey, you want
to see something?
That's okay;
I don't want to break it.
Ah, don't be silly.
Come, take a look.
Wow.
That's a spiral galaxy.
These people are amazing.
They're rich, they're smart,
they're polite...
What are they going to do next,
give me a million dollars?
Malcolm, do you want
a million dollars?
What?!
I said, do you want
a sandwich to take home?
Oh. Close enough.
I only asked out your sister
because you said
you weren't interested!
And I was thinking of you
the whole time!
Aw, don't give me that!
I saw the charm bracelet!
This isn't even mine!
What, are you insane?
You're throwing out stuff
that's not even mine!
What are you looking at?
Hey, this is a private
conversation, buster!
Hal:
Huh?
Oh, yeah, like you've
never seen this before!
My mistake.
I'm on the next street over.
( Lois and Hal arguing )
You were right about Lester.
I checked him out--
no wife, no kids.
Poor guy didn't have
a friend in the world.
Here you go, Lester buddy.
Did you tell anyone
about this place?
No.
Huh.
Must've been me, then.
All right, that's enough!
Party's over!
Don't you guys have
any respect for the dead?
You took his wallet.
Lester would've wanted me
to have his I.D.
But that's not the point.
This man was not just
an alcoholic pervert janitor.
He was one of us!
He hated the Commandant
as much as we do.
He was filled
with impudent rage, like we are.
This man
was a hero
and heroes do not rot alone
in basements.
They're immortalized in song.
They are sent off to Valhalla
in flaming ships!
They are not put
in beer hats
or used as photo props
or given fake moustaches.
( thumping )
Oh, man...
Oh...
That wasn't fake.
My bad.
What do we do now?
Go for the spare.
( bubbling )
Francis, I'm sorry
I'm calling you so late.
I had to talk to someone.
Hey, no problem.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Do you ever feel
like you don't really
belong in a family?
Dude, I'm in military school.
I think that question's
been answered.
Right.
This is good.
At least someone else
in the family is normal.
Hey, listen, while I got you...
you're in school
with all those science brains.
How would you reattach a head
to a dead body?
( paper rustling )
Keep it down!
Huh?
Don't talk to her like that.
Would you go sit in the corner?
There are no corners!
You ready to make up?
No.
Me, neither.
Oh, hello, son.
I barely see you anymore.
That baby-sitting has turned
into a full-time job.
Well, sometimes I just
go over there to hang out
and watch TV...
live in a house...
Dad, does this seem okay to you?
Gosh, no. Your mother and I
have never fought
for this long before.
It's been days,
and we still haven't made up.
I don't even know
what the problem is.
Something's missing.
Boy...
look at that sky, Malcolm.
Just think
somewhere out there
in all those stars and planets
there might be at this very moment
a space dad who just got kicked out
of his space trailer
who is looking down at us.
Or would it be up at us?
Or maybe sideways?
Trust me, Dad.
They're all looking down on us.
The matinee gets out at 4:00
so we should be back
before dinner.
Okay.
What do you want me
to feed the kids for lunch?
Whatever you want.
We trust you.
They trust me.
People like this trust me.
I obviously have to say
something nice back to them.
This is why my family sucks.
I have no training in this.
This job...
me... like.
We're thrilled
to have found you, Malcolm.
The kids love you.
You're great to have around.
You've really become
one of the family.
I may not have been
switched at birth
but I should have been.
I love these people.
( speaking Chinese )
Okay, come on.
Wait a minute.
Sorry.
Well...
let's see what our little
friend did today.
( whistling )
Oh, hi.
Don't worry.
I'd never hurt Barney.
He's part of the family.
Just like I'm part
of the family, right?
And since a big part
of this family
is being such a huge phony
and launching
secret investigations
against each other
I thought I'd join in.
Personal computers are great.
You can file tax returns,
medical records
embarrassing private E-mail...
A little security tip, though.
Never use your birthdate
as your password.
And hiding things
in a fake salt can?
That's just silly.
I don't know who Melissa is
but she sure wears
a lot of lipstick.
Anyway, I think I hear you guys
pulling up in the driveway
so let's just leave it at this:
I quit.
Bye.
Who's Melissa?
( arguing in trailer )
Hi, son.
Didn't hear you drive up.
I decided to walk.
So, how's the job going?
They were jerks, so I quit.
Well, that's pretty much
what work is.
Welcome to the club.
Dad?
Hmm?
I'm really sorry.
What? About quitting?
Nah...
no big deal,
especially for you.
Malcolm, you should
set your sights
as high as you can.
If anyone in this family
has a shot at greatness
it's you.
Just, uh... do me a favor, huh?
Look after your brothers?
Okay, wait, wait.
You mean everything
you just said, right?
Why would I say something
I didn't mean?
See? That's what
I'm talking about.
This family may be
rude, loud and gross
and have no shame whatsoever...
Anyway, with them
you know where you stand
and when I have a problem,
they're always there.
Oh, my Lord.
- ( dish crashing )
- Sex!
( car pulls away quickly )
Things didn't work out so bad.
I made enough money
to get my robotics kit.
Or maybe I should do
something nice for my family.
Take them to dinner...
treat them to a movie...
Naw, then I couldn't do this.
Lois:
If you don't change your underwear
this is exactly what happens.
Like the ancient
civilizations before us
we send off this noble man
with the riches he had in life
so he may enjoy them
in the afterlife.
Farewell, noble Lester.
It's burning really fast.
How much gas did you use?
Half a can.
Where'd you put the can?
( explosion )
Oh...
Look.
It's heading
toward the boathouse.
( explosion )
What do you think?
Run?
Yeah. I'd run.
( door opening )
I figured it out.
Hal, you okay?
Whenever we'd fight,
you'd yell, then I'd yell
but then we would...
you know?
Well, you see, we haven't
had a chance to...
because we're in that
trailer with kids...
Oh, my God, Hal,
you're right.
What are we going to do?
We've got the kids...
I've got it all figured out.
? La, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la ?
? Means ''I love you'' ?
? Oh, baby, please ?
? La, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la ?
? Means ''I love you''... ?
www.tvsubtitles.net