Photographer:
Squeeze in.
Little closer together.
Chins up like baby birds.
- Boys: Move.
- Shut up.
Malcolm:
Stop touching me.
I'm not touching you.
I was clipping on my tie.
While touching me.
Stop it!
Why do we have to do this?
We don't have a single picture
of us all together.
That's ridiculous.
We're a family.
We should have a family portrait.
Well, Francis isn't here.
I'm not going to cough up
$200 bucks to fly him in
for one silly picture.
Where's Dewey?
Dewey, get out of there.
That's not your family.
You sure you want
autumn leaves as a backdrop?
Yes.
You didn't even look
at happy windmills.
It's more colorful.
Space shuttle.
Photographer:
Next.
I have a coupon
for one eight-by-ten
and two wallet-size
for $9.99 and
that's what I want.
Not the Golden Moments collection.
I don't want
the Family and Friends collection.
the Lifetime of Love.
One eight-by-ten
and two wallet-size for $9.99.
Fine.
We have an installment plan
if that would help.
I brought a picture of Francis.
He's going to be in the portrait.
Cool. I'll hold it.
No, I'm going to hold it.
- Let go.
- Come on.
Dewey, pants on, mister.
I'm sorry.
- Coupon's expired.
- What?
It's expired.
What you want
will run you $39.50.
Ooh, lonely beach.
Hal.
For another $5.00
you can have
the Instant Memory set.
That comes with
double exposure silhouettes.
Look, could you please do
what I'm asking you to...
- I'm older!
- It was my idea!
( Both Grunting )
That is it!
Get up!
Get back!
Come here!
Go there!
Okay.
We are going to take this picture
and it's going to be good.
And that means no faces
no tongues, no crossed eyes
no bunny ears.
We are going to smile.
We are going to look good.
It is going to cost us $9.99.
And all of this is going to happen
by the time I count to three.
- ( All Arguing )
- One, two, three.
( Arguing Stops )
( Arguing Resumes )
? Yes, no, maybe ?
? I don't know ?
? Can you repeat the question? ?
? You're not the boss of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? Life is unfair. ?
( Phone Rings )
Hello.
( Heavy Breathing )
( Breathing Continues )
Listen, pervert,
this is the third time you've called
and I have just about had it with...
Is Malcolm... there?
Oh, hi, Stevie.
Sorry.
Uh, Malcolm, phone.
Hey, Stevie.
You're coming... tonight?
Yeah.
And sleeping... over?
It's a sleepover.
That's what you do.
I'm just... excited.
Never... had one.
We can...
read comics
and build...
models.
Stevie, I never thought I'd say this
but slow down.
Ha... ha.
Forty-one...
forty-two...
forty-three...
Okay, stop.
I can't do any more.
You think later on
you can manage
to stand on my stomach
while I do sit-ups?
Oh,just give me a minute, okay?
Finley, what are you doing
in the cupboard?
Poquito cabeza.
Get out of there, man.
I can't.
I've been marked by the brothers
of the apocalypse.
Poquito cabeza.
Brothers of the apocalypse?
It's ridiculous.
It's five seniors
with limited imaginations.
Yeah.
That's easy for you to say.
You've got Stanley protecting you.
And you're not holding
poquito cabeza.
Stop saying poquito cabeza.
I can't.
And I'm not coming out.
Oh, could you turn
in my math homework?
These guys are so lame.
Amateurs.
Poor Finley.
He's good at math, right?
( Chanting ):
Finley, boom-ba-yay.
Finley, boom-ba-yay,
Finley, boom-ba-yay...
Oh, no! Please!
No! No!
Please! No!
...Finley, boom-ba-yay.
Finley, boom-ba-yay...
- No!
- Stop.
Froot Loops.
Finley, boom-ba-yay...
Please, help me!
Help me!
No...!
Hey, Mom, I'm going to Stevie's.
You be nice to that boy.
He can't walk.
If he's got to go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night,
you get up and help him.
Yes! There's a Chucky movie
on tonight.
Not in this house.
You know how your father feels
about evil puppet movies.
Please, Mom.
It's not a school night.
I can stay up.
Think you're old enough?
I totally am.
Well, if you really think so.
Aw, Mom, no fair.
What's the matter?
Afraid you can't
beat your mommy?
She's just a person.
Oh, no.
He's finally going to win.
What's he playing for tonight?
Bedtime and a Chucky movie.
Stop screwing around and pin him.
Oh, you'll have
to forgive the mess, Malcolm.
Mmm, when our Stevie
enters a room
it's like a typhoon hit.
( Chuckles )
Well, uh,
we'll leave you alone.
Check it out, Stevie.
The T-Rex is three feet tall
with a movable jaw.
Red paint for blood.
This is so cool.
I heard screaming.
Yeah.
I said, ''This is so cool.''
Is that a switchblade?
It's an X-Acto knife
to cut the pieces apart.
I use it all the time.
We'll lock this up
with the scissors.
How about a puzzle?
Stevie, it's been a long time
since you did
the Arc de Triomphe.
We'll just give that back
when you go home.
Puzzles are... fun.
You think we can order some pizza?
Mom's making... pizza.
Cheeseless... sauceless pizza.
That's just bread.
Pizza... bread.
Wise poquito cabeza.
Who shall your next victim be?
I am so sick of these guys.
What's that?
You're not sure?
I think we have a winner.
You are cordially invited
to attend...
Hey!
I don't have
a problem with you
Francis.
Look, Stevenson
this place is horrible enough.
So the poquito cabeza
thing stops now.
Okay?
Just stop.
Just stop packing.
You were protecting me.
I know we don't have, like,
a formal agreement or anything
but my act of courage
was kind of dependent
on your role as my bodyguard.
I'm sorry, Francis.
You're sorry?
Do you have any idea
what these guys
are going to do to me?
Four words:
Nana has a fever.
End of discussion.
So what am I supposed to do?
Remember that move
I taught you?
Yeah.
Don't even try it.
( Chanting ): Francis, boom-ba-yay.
Francis, boom-ba-yay.
Francis, boom-ba-yay...
I have to admit,
it's kind of catchy.
...Francis, boom-ba-yay.
Did you have
fun tonight, Malcolm?
I guess, but isn't it kind
of early to be going to bed?
It's not even 8:00.
Don't worry.
That puzzle will still
be there in the morning.
Now I know you boys
want to do a little chatting
before sleepy time.
Let's say four minutes.
Mrs. Kenarbin can
be a tad strict.
She doesn't know
that sometimes boys
have to be boys.
Am I right?
I can't move.
Welcome to... the club.
I'm never going
to fall asleep.
It's too early.
Want to tell...
ghost stories?
No. I want to do
that dinosaur model.
Ms. Kenarbin:
Everything all right in there, boys?
Um, yeah.
A plush toy just fell
on the floor.
We're fine.
( Gasps )
You can't.
I just did.
Your parents need to cut you some slack.
They just... want me... safe.
No, they want you to be four.
Stevie, parents
aren't allowed to control
everything you do.
- Sometimes you just have...
- ( Bell Dings )
Sorry.
Conditioning.
Come on.
I got an idea.
We're going to get you
out of here.
Don't.
It's alarmed.
- You got me?
- Yeah.
You got me?
No!
I didn't know... you cared.
Okay.
You want maturity.
Here's three weeks
of social studies homework.
Now I'm one week ahead.
Plus, I called Grandma.
Woman ( On Tape ):
Hello.
Hi, Grandma.
It's Reese.
- Who's this?
- Grandma, it's Reese.
No, I won't accept charges.
It's Reese.
I'm very tired.
Please.
It goes on like that
for another ten minutes
but I still want credit.
Honey, I'm very proud of you
but you still haven't proven
you're old enough
to extend your bedtime.
Come on, Mom.
I'll do anything.
All right.
Tell you what.
You can stay up
and watch the movie...
if you put Dewey to bed.
Oh.
Anything else.
That's the deal.
You give him his bath,
you put on his pj's...
you read him a story.
Lois, have a heart.
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it.
( Chair Scrapes )
Come on, Dewey!
It's bath time!
You know he doesn't
stand a chance.
I know, but at least
it'll give us the night
to be alone.
Oh.
I love the way your mind works.
( Yawns )
Honk.
( Chuckles )
Smoothie.
I'm... winning.
I... lost.
Yes.
I got... another quarter...
in my chair.
They stole his wheelchair.
What's it look like?
It's a chair with wheels.
I'll go get a form.
I don't need a form.
I need a wheelchair.
I'm screwed.
You're not screwed.
We just got to get you home.
We'll deal with
everything else...
What are we going
to do now?
Carry me... like...
a backpack.
Stop! Stop!
Gonna... puke.
Dewey:
Ow! Let me go!
Come on, Dewey.
It's me.
You like me.
No, I don't.
Dewey, please!
How much does my head weigh?
Zero.
( Chuckling )
Remember the last time we...
had a quiet moment
together like this?
Bob's funeral.
Yeah.
Oh, that was nice.
And you look great in black.
Oh...
You do. You do.
( Chuckling )
( Phone Ringing )
Let the machine get it.
Mmm.
Francis:
Mom, Dad, hi.
Listen, something's come up.
Sorry about the way I sound
but I'm calling
from inside a washing machine.
Don't worry,
I think I'll be fine as long as...
Oh, hi, guys.
How's it going?
Hey, hey, what are you doing
with those quarters?
Hey, you guys,
you don't want to...
Hey, come on...!
Morning dew.
You know all my secrets.
Mmm. Well, we've been
together a long time.
Well, don't worry.
I know all your secrets, too.
No, you don't.
( Chuckling ):
Oh, yes, I do.
No. I'm a man
of mystery, Lois.
Okay. Let's hear one.
Let's hear a secret.
Well, it's not really a secret
as much as it is a fantasy
but it's a little
embarrassing, so...
Well, so...
whisper in my ear.
Aha.
( Chuckling )
Just kidding.Just kidding.
Saw it in a movie once.
Don't want to do that. That's...
( Chuckling )
Oh, God.
I gotcha.
We can do that.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
( Dewey Screaming )
Reese:
Get back here!
( Screaming Continues )
Okay, I just have to
pick up a few things.
Give me 20 minutes?
I'll be waiting.
Yes!
Honey? Honey.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Thank you! Thank you!
Your car keys.
Right.
That's a nice cart.
Thanks. It's new.
Downtown rocks.
What's that?
A stripped car.
A naked man arguing with a wall.
What's that?
A nudie bookstore...
with my dad
coming out of it.
Hmm? Oh.
Here you go.
? Daddy is gonna get
some love tonight... ?
Stevenson:
Perhaps you'll survive--
perhaps not.
Many have perished
at the hands of
the grand executioner.
They are the lucky ones.
( Whispering ):
Are you scared?
Actually,
now that you mention it... no.
What?
Scared now?
No.
I'm just kind of itchy.
Huh?
You are hanging over
a bottomless pit.
In five seconds,
I will cut the rope.
Are you scared now?
I'm really not, no.
Why not?
This stuff is way scary.
Sorry.
It just feels so... amateurish.
I mean, I know you guys
are trying, but...
I've been tormented
by the best.
Let me tell you
a little bit about the master.
Lois:
Traveling?!
He wasn't traveling!
Why don't you put
your glasses on?
You're missing
a great game!
Oh, oh-oh, you're going
to give me a technical?!
You're going to give me
a technical?!
You can't give me a technical!!!
Look at that little pee-pee.
Oh, Francis,
I forgot how tiny you are.
Oh-oh-oh-l-l...
That's the moment
of his birth.
You see?
See him coming out feet first?
Doctors said it was the biggest
mucus plug they'd ever seen.
An eight-inch scratch
on the car, Francis!
Do you know how much
that'll cost to fix?!
If you think you are ever,
ever borrowing my car again
you are sadly mistaken!
And I saw that tattoo,Jimmy!
I'm telling your mother!
And that's just the stuff
I didn't block out.
Oh, man!
What have we been doing?
This is all so wrong.
We've got to stop
treating people like this.
Yeah. If we're going to do this,
we're going to do it right.
You will never
amount to anything.
Why can't you just
apply yourself?!
Do you enjoy seeing me suffer?
Is that what this is?
After all I've
done for you
and this is the thanks I get?!
We passed that
couch an hour ago.
I know where we're going.
Oh, no, I don't.
This sucks.
You complain a lot.
I'm sorry, but tonight
hasn't exactly been
the most fun in the world.
Not tonight.
All the time.
You never stop bitching.
Okay, great.
You're going to
do this now? Fine.
You were right.
We shouldn't have snuck
out of your house.
We shouldn't have
gone to the arcade.
It was stupid of me for
even thinking about it.
It was a dumb idea.
No. Good idea.
Execution sucked.
( Laughter )
( Laughter Continues )
Your chair. Hey!
I'm slowing you down.
Get them yourself.
Okay.
Uh... uh...
Get out of the chair.
Right!
You better be running!
Hey, Stevie, I got your...
Oh, my God!
Stevie, are you okay?!
Can't feel... my legs.
That's not funny.
Lois:
Is there anything I can do
to get out of the ticket,
Officer?
Hal:
Just love me.
Aw, geez, Hal--
Is that it?
Can't he be a
sensitive cop?
Woman:
That puppet-- It's alive!
Tonight was...
awesome.
Well, we kind of
got lucky.
I was sort of
hoping to get caught.
What?
Never been in trouble.
Like to see
what it's like.
Sometimes
you're such a Krelboyne.
I guess we are
in trouble after all.
Malcolm?
Malcolm.
www.tvsubtitles.net