( Drill Buzzing )
Dewey:
I hate my brothers.
I only like me.
( Boys Yelling )
Stop it right now!
I mean it!
( Yelling Continues )
When are you going to be done?
Soon as I can, honey.
I said, stop it!
Dewey:
I hate my brothers.
( Thud )
I only like me.
I hate my brothers.
( Thud )
( Drill Whirring )
( Whirring Stops )
''Five across.
My mother the... blank.''
? Yes, no, maybe ?
? I don't know ?
? Can you repeat the question? ?
? You're not the boss
of me now ?
? You're not
the boss of me now ?
? You're not the boss
of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? You're not the boss
of me now ?
? You're not
the boss of me now ?
? You're not the boss
of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? Life is unfair. ?
I know a lot of kids
say they like school.
But honestly,
I just find it exhausting.
I mean, when I am in school
I'm either bored, terrified...
or confused
aboutJulie Houlerman.
Hi, Malcolm.
Perfect example.
What does she mean by that?
Is it just ''Hi''?
Is she trying to say
she likes me?
Is she just being nice?
And now I have to figure out
a secret way to answer her
without A)
acting like I like her
or B)
acting like I don't like her
or C) acting like I've never
even thought about A or B.
Just be pleasant
and noncommittal.
Hey,Ju...
She's doing this to me
on purpose.
( Girls Squealing )
Hey, how are you?
Stanley, you are incredible.
I thought Malcolm was a genius
but this is off the charts.
The school asked
for an honor guard.
I figured you'd like a few weeks
without drill practice.
A pageant, though.
Beautiful girls
with self-esteem issues.
It's perfect.
Easy. Let's start with
the obvious runners up.
They're going to be
the neediest.
You know, uh, this
is a little intense.
You, me, working
this shelf... together.
( Chuckles Nervously )
What's intense about it?
I guess nothing.
Excuse me.
Mom!
You're not supposed
to yell in the store.
Not supposed
to do that either.
Life's funny that way.
Hey... the Three Musketeers.
Athos, Aramis...
and you must be Porthos.
You're creepy.
You really shouldn't say
hurtful things to grownups.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
We're still friends.
Craig...
you have got to redo
the nail polish.
The crystal pinks are mixed
with the frosty pinks
are mixed with
the God knows what.
Right away, Mr. Pinter.
Okay. I'm off work
in five minutes.
Don't touch the register.
Don't touch the candy,
the price tags
and don't touch the microphones.
That includes by accident.
That includes just looking.
That includes hovering
with your finger
a half inch away from it.
Fair warning.
Dare you.
Go ahead.
You do it.
- I'll do it.
- Yeah, right.
I will.
This isn't baby
stuff, Dewey.
Go ride the horsy
out front.
( Chuckles )
Horsy.
I got to remember that.
The microphone, register...
candy... price tags...
steam cleaner.
Boys!
It's not what it looks like.
Oh, hello, boys.
How long you in for?
Another hour.
Yow.
Hi, Hon.
Hi.
Did you see Dewey outside?
Oh, what's wrong?
I don't know,
but something's upsetting him.
He didn't say a word
on the way home
and now I just can't
find him anywhere.
Hmm.
Hey, I'll check
his special place.
Dewey?
You in there, buddy?
No.
What's wrong, pal?
I did something bad.
They told me to ride a horsy
and I'm not a baby
but I would have played
with the carpet cleaner
and I didn't have
a quarter anyway.
Uh-huh. Dewey, honey
Daddy's getting a cramp
in his leg.
What did you do?
I took something
from Mommy's store.
Well, that's very serious.
What did you take?
A candy bar?
No. It's not
a candy bar.
Oh? Well, what is it?
$1 50 bottle of cognac?
How could you take this?!
I'm sorry.
My God,
would you look at this thing?
Can you imagine the man
who spends $1 50
on a bottle of cognac?
What do you think a guy
like that pays for socks?
Dewey, what am I
going to do with you?
This works
pretty good, Mom.
Get your jacket, we're going
back to the store.
You are going to return
this bottle to Mr. Pinter
apologize and accept
the consequences.
What do mean, ''fired''?!
You can't fire me for this.
Sorry. Store policy is
very clear about stealing.
But he didn't steal it;
he returned it.
Right there.
The bottle is perfect.
You can just put it
right back on the shelf.
I already marked it
out of inventory.
Pinter:
My hands are tied here.
What are you
talking about?
You don't even do
inventory.
You foist if off on me because
you make so many mistakes.
You're not exactly making me
regret my decision here, Lois.
Mom?
Oh, honey, it's
okay. It's okay.
This is just an excuse.
You have hated me
since the minute you got here
because I was first choice for
your job and I turned it down.
You know, you think
what you want, okay?
At least I didn't raise a thief.
- ( Loud Ripping Sound )
- ( Pinter Yells )
( All Gasp )
Velcro. I win the pool.
( Reciting ):
Sweet home Alabama...
( Piano Accompaniment )
where the skies are so blue.
Sweet home Alabama...
Lord, I'm coming home
to you.
( Playing Licks )
( Applause )
Oh, very, very
nice, Bridget.
That was very nice.
Oh, Francis, I wanted
to thank you again
for being so helpful.
Usually, the honor guards
just sit around and gawk
but you've really
thrown yourself
into this whole hog,
haven't you?
What can I say?
I love the theater.
Francis, will you help me
decide on my leg extensions?
Which do you think
looks better--
right leg...
or left leg?
Mmm...
Can you... do both?
It's been ten days
since Mom lost her job.
Yesterday for dinner,
we had macaroni and rice.
Today it's rice and macaroni.
Mom, I can't eat
this stuff anymore.
Reese, this is not the time
for complaining.
I'm not complaining;
I'm constipated.
I'm sorry, we can't afford
to live lavishly anymore.
Drink your milk.
It's lumpy.
Then chew it.
Hey, come on, we can do this.
We've had to economize before.
Remember when Grandma drove
into the living room?
Or last year, when we were
saving up for Disneyland?
We're going to Disneyland?
No.
It's like that.
Except this time, we're just
trying to keep the house.
Okay, everybody, stop worrying.
I am going to find
another job...
another cashier job
with flexible hours
that allows me to leave whenever
I need to take care of my kids.
Well, can't you get
unemployment or something?
No. I only worked
38 hours a week.
They consider that
part-time.
You know, I hope
you are at least learning
something
from all this.
Yeah-- ''If you do
something bad, don't tell.''
No-- ''We did
the right thing.''
That's what's
important.
Can't we at least do a load
of laundry or something?
Everything I have stinks.
Yeah, he wants to smell
good for... Julie!
( Gagging )
Malcolm.
Yeah, yeah.
It was worth it.
So we can't do laundry,
we have to share baths
and yesterday, she had
our cable turned off.
Our cable!
How's your... love life?
What?
So, basically,
everything I tell you
in confidence as a friend
you're going to use
to make fun of me?
I have... nothing else.
Hi, Malcolm.
You want to split lunches?
What?
Yeah, sure.
I have a Chinese chicken salad,
a tangerine
and, ooh,Jordan almonds.
What do you have?
Leftover eggs
from breakfast.
Oh.
Uh, I'm on a special diet...
for sports.
Oh, I forgot.
I have to go...
work out.
I'll see you later.
I can't take
this anymore!
Everything I want,
I can't have!
Anything that's nice,
I can't do.
Everyone in the world gets to do
everything except me!
Malcolm...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know there's other people
worse off than me.
You know what?
I don't care.
I'm sick of going to school
every day smelling like feet!
Malcolm...
I hate being poor, okay?
I mean, is that so bad?
Why is that like
some big character flaw?
It's not my fault
we're poor!
Malcolm!
You, um...
left... your backpack.
Maybe you should try taking
a really deep breath
before you start talking.
Yeah.
Francis, where have you been?
I've been looking for you
for days.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I've just been buried here.
Okay, listen, I've got kind of
a bad news/ good news thing here.
( Sighing )
Your mom lost her job,
and we're pretty broke.
The good news is, that makes
your tuition an issue.
Now, I think I can talk her
into letting you come home.
Dad, no, I can't come home!
Marlin Academy
is the best thing
that has ever
happened to me.
I am at a crucial point
in my rehabilitation.
Uh-huh. What's her name?
That's the thing--
There's, like, ten of them!
( Knock At Door )
Check the peephole.
If they've got a hand truck,
don't open it.
( Knocking Continues )
( Door Opens, Then Closes )
Craig, what are
you doing here?
Lois, I just had a meeting
with Mr. Pinter--
well, more like an hour
begging, really--
but the point is, you can
have your old job back!
Yes!
That is such good news!
And all you have to do
is apologize
and let him dock your pay
1 50 bucks
and you have to work
the graveyard shift
for a couple months.
Oh.
Sounds good, Mom.
- No, thanks.
- What?!
- You're kidding.
- Why?!
Because that's like admitting
he's right.
I'm not going to do that.
Lois, if this makes
any difference
I will work every graveyard
shift right alongside you--
every single one of them.
Oh, hi, Craig.
What's going on?
Nothing.Just business.
Take it easy, tiger.
We're working.
Well, I am.
Hi.
Back to the grind.
Nice guy.
Thank you,
Tanya.
Tanya, that was
fantastic.
I swear, when you
put tap to it
the Pledge of Allegiance
just comes alive.
One suggestion:
Do you have a tube top?
Oh, Francis, you are
just wonderful.
I mean, you're so different
than the local boys.
I mean, I haven't even
known you that long
and I already feel
so connected to you.
I know. It's almost mystical.
Yeah, and I'm so glad
the gay thing isn't an issue.
You're gay?
No, no, silly. You are.
Wait. You think I'm gay?
Oh, you don't have to
hide anything, honey.
I mean, we're a lot
more liberal here
than you think we are.
I mean, it's not
like Birmingham.
Wait a minute.
You think I'm gay?
Why do you think I'm gay?
Oh, come on.
You like the theater,
you're good with decorating
and, well, you're completely
obsessed with your mother.
Can you undo my hooks?
Tanya, I'm kind of having
a dilemma here...
Oh, great. Frannie,
can you spray me?
My suit keeps riding up.
( Giggling )
That's why I'm here...
girlfriend!
So what did you
want to talk about?
I'm your teacher!
Can't we just talk?
You know, that
Julie Houlerman
is a very special
little girl.
Oh, come on!
Caroline,
I don't want to...
Caroline: Malcolm, Malcolm, Malcolm,
so private, so guarded.
But you don't have to
be that way with me.
I'm on your side.
Julie knows that.
She's not even in my class.
She talked to you?
About me?
What'd she say?
Aw, nothing that wasn't
obvious already.
You know, when you
open up to people
you will always
be surprised
just how well
things turn out.
- Surprise!
Isn't it wonderful?
Julie organized
the whole thing herself
and everyone in school
responded.
Dear Malcolm,
this isn't just food.
It's an expression of how
we all feel about you.
Our hearts go out to you
in your time of need.
( Applause )
- You're going to keep the food?
- Yes.
I'm not going
to throw away
perfectly good
pie filling
and... lamb chutney.
Don't you even care
how humiliating this is?
We've done can drives.
This is just the
crap people find
when they clean
out the garage.
Okay,just stop it.
I know how
hard this is
but no one ever said
life is fair.
Sometimes decent,
hard-working people
get dumped on
for no good reason.
They just have
to wipe their eyes
and keep on walking.
Something will
turn up.
We just have to hold on
a little bit longer.
And in the meantime
be thankful for small favors.
Anyone want the last olive?
Those aren't olives.
Those are peaches.
( Siren Wailing )
Well, you got him here
early, that's good.
He'll be fine
in a few days.
Just like
when this one
ate the frog.
I only ate half of it.
I won't put
the stomach pump on the bill.
I mean, he did most
of the work on the way over.
Thanks, Don. Uh...
listen, as far
as the bill goes
what kind of neighborhood
are we in?
Well...
the emergency room
couple of days
of observation--
probably three or four.
Three or
four... hun...?
Okay.
You boys take
care of your dad.
I'm going to go see Mr. Pinter
and beg for my job back.
What? Mom, wait.
You don't have
to do that.
Yes, I do. I don't want to
shouldn't have to,
but guess what?
I do.
But I want you boys
to understand something.
I am not going back
on anything I said before.
She's completely
going back on it
but I'm not going
to kick her when she's down.
You're totally
going back on it.
No, I am not.
Everything I said before
still goes.
You know, sometimes
bad things happen
and you don't
understand why
and you just have to trust that
there's a good reason for it.
Sure, it's easy
to work in mysterious ways
when you have a job.
( Long, Gassy Whine )
The first one who laughs
gets their ass kicked.
( Moans )
You have
incredible hands.
Well, it's easy
on such a beautiful back.
Not to mention
the most talented...
sweet...
and sexy...
What?
Francis...
are... are you sure
you're really...
how you are?
Tanya, I'm so confused.
I mean, I thought that I was,
but when I'm around you
I have these...
strange, new feelings.
I feel like...
maybe I could... change.
That you could be
the woman who changes me.
Oh, Francis...
I was hoping
you'd say that.
I want to be that woman
for you.
Mm, and don't
you worry, honey.
If there's one thing we
know how to do down here
it's how to fix this.
And with God's help,
we can say ''no!'' to weakness.
We can say ''no!''
to all things unnatural!
It is procreation,
not recreation!
And when Satan tempts us,
what do we do?
Pray out the gay.
Get to it!
I have to say, Lois,
I'm surprised
by this change
in your attitude.
Yeah, well, me, too.
I know we've had
our differences
but I hope that we
can make all this
water under the bridge.
So, if you'll just sign here...
Mm, what's this?
Your apology.
I think I've captured
your voice rather nicely.
You want it in writing?
Yes.
Look, Lois, you can
tell these clowns
whatever you want--
that I got on my knees
and begged you to come
back, I don't care.
I just want you and I to
know how things really are.
That's not a signature.
No, it's more
of a suggestion.
''The horse you rode in on''
is optional.
Now, look--
No, you look.
I don't deserve this.
The only thing
I ever did wrong
was all the work I did
to cover your butt.
We obviously have different
definitions of''wrong.''
Yeah, I guess we do.
For instance,
I think it's wrong
for you to put your name
on sales reports
that you didn't write.
I think it's wrong you keep
a little bag of''herbs''
in your bottom left drawer.
And slept with
the district manager's wife.
And you want
to know something?
You don't even
have to worry about it
because I also think it's wrong
to blab this kind of thing.
You know,
you should be so glad
that I'm
the only one that knows
this stuff about you.
Anyone else here would sell you
down the river in a second.
God, I am so much
better than you.
( Clearing Throat )
Yeah, he just ran off
and quit for no reason.
Huh, who knows why?
See, you do the right thing
and everything
works out for the best.
Clean.
I have Ho-Ho's-- real Ho-Ho's.
You know,
I'm sure I'm neglecting
my spiritual side, but...
money rules.
The best part is
I can finally get everything
straightened out with Julie.
Hi, Malcolm.
Look, we're not poor anymore!
So I don't want any more
of your stupid pity, okay?
That helped, right?
www.tvsubtitles.net