Malcolm:
This is the world--
1 96 million square miles.
If I covered 1 00 square miles
an hour
every hour
for the rest of my life
I'd still only see half of it.
( Squeaking )
This is the left nostril
of my brother Reese.
It squeaks all night long.
These are the freezing cold feet
of my little brother... Dewey.
This is my oldest brother Francis.
He's the one I really like
so, of course,
he got sent to military school.
My name is Malcolm.
You want to know
what the best thing
about childhood is?
At some point, it stops.
Malcolm, Reese, Dewey,
get in here!
- Stop!
- I'm not touching you!
There's only two toaster waffles.
One of you has to have cereal.
It's mine!
Come on!
Give it!
You cheated!
Give it! Give it!
Huh, look at this.
They're sending
an unmanned probe to Venus
and letting a bunch
of schoolchildren name it.
That's going to end badly.
These clippers are dull already.
Honestly, Hal,
you're like a monkey.
They do this every month.
He has sensitive skin.
The hair gets itchy under his clothes.
It always seems like such a shame
to just dump this in the trash.
Maybe birds would like
to make nests with it
or maybe you boys could
use it for school projects.
Arms up.
Dude.
Malcolm, come right home
from school.
I made a play date for you with Stevie
Kenarban and you have to take a bath.
What? Mom, no!
Malcolm has a play date?!
Shut up, Reese!
With Stevie ''The Wheelie'' Kenarban?
Oh, man!
( Coughing )
Breathing.
So, Malcolm,
why is playing a problem?
First off
I don't even know Stevie.
His mother said
you boys ate lunch together.
One time.
He rolled his wheelchair
over next to me.
It's not like
I could say, ''Go away.''
He's not even in my class.
He's in the Krelboyne class
in the trailer
next to tetherball.
You listen to me, young man.
That one lunch obviously
meant a lot to Stevie.
He's a human being
with human feelings.
Now, you are going to be friends
with that crippled boy
and you are going
to like it. Understood?
Yes, ma'am. Understood.
If I give up now,
I won't get the lecture.
You kids...
Dang.
You just take
your legs for granted like nothing
could ever happen to them.
That is just wishful thinking.
There's meningitis.
There are car accidents.
I could be giving
you a spanking
and accidentally snap
your spinal cord.
Every day is a lottery
and first prize
is that you don't have to scoot
yourself around town on a skateboard
with your hands.
You think about that.
I don't take my legs
for granted, Mom.
I know, honey.
You're a good boy.
Stop playing with yourself.
( Boys Arguing )
Go on,just go.
Lois:
No, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, I ran out of ham.
One of you has
to have egg salad, okay?
And don't ditch
your little brother.
I don't want him
getting kidnapped.
Yeah, Mom,
that would be terrible.
It's your turn to walk with him.
I walked him yesterday
and the day before.
I walked with him
when he wet his pants.
Okay.
Mom said to hold hands.
She did not say
to hold hands, Dewey.
I'm not holding hands.
Come on, hold hands. Please?
No! You're in the first grade.
You're too big for that.
Look,
I'm walking right next to you.
You'll be fine.
Damn it! This is why
everyone teases you.
Hey, Malcolm.
Hey, Richard.
So my mom was telling
my dad last night
about your brother.
She said he's in jail.
He's not in jail.
He's at Marlin Academy.
It's, like, one of the best
private schools in the country
and it's totally unfair.
Everyone acts like Francis
is just this big troublemaker
and he's not.
Dad, I know what
you're going to say
and believe me,
I totally agree with you.
There is no excuse
for what I did.
It was idiotic, immature,
totally reckless
and I'm really sorry.
I'm just...
I'm hoping against hope
that you will give me
another chance, which, I admit
I don't deserve
but if you could just
find it in your heart
to forgive me
I know I could earn
your trust back.
It's not like
it was even our car.
Spath, Spath, Spath!
Spath:
All right
here's how it works.
You can beg for mercy
on your belly
lick the bottom of my shoes
or take a beating.
You must pick at least two
but... but-but,
if you pick three
you get a pass
for the next two weeks.
All right?
Now, that's your best value.
Malcolm:
Dave Spath.
He never gets sent anywhere.
What do you do
if he catches you?
Roll in a ball.
What if he starts kicking you?
Stay in a ball.
Okay. Come on.
( Kids Yelling )
Wait.
Never mind.
( Kids Continue Yelling )
Woman: Those of you finished
with your tempera paints
may bring your work up here
and start on
your charcoal still lifes.
You may take two pieces
of fruit only
and please be careful with them.
I bought them with my own money.
My own money.
God, Malcolm, that's so good.
Oh, Malcolm, this is wonderful.
The perspective is good.
The composition is clean
and it even shows signs
of actual technique.
I have to say this
is the high point of my day.
( Laughs )
How's that for sad?
( Squishing )
Are you okay?
Um, yeah, I'm fine.
Hogan:
Malcolm.
What?
They need to see you
in the office.
Okay.
I think they mean right now.
Get up, Malcolm.
( Kids'Laughter Echoing )
Hi. I'm Caroline.
Want to have a seat?
Are you Malcolm?
Yes, and I didn't do anything.
You're not in trouble, Malcolm.
You're here
'cause some of your teachers
think you're, um... You know what?
I just want to play
some games with you.
Puzzles, stuff like that.
Why?
Boy, oh, boy
you are a suspicious
little dickens, aren't you?
Now, you can look
at this picture for 60 seconds
and I want you to tell me
everything that's wrong
with it, okay?
The man only has four fingers.
Right, but this time
I want you to take your time
and really look...
The car shadow's
going the wrong way
the steering wheel's
on the wrong side
there's no brake pedal
the words in the mirror
should be backwards
the guy's watch wouldn't say 1 2:00
if he's looking at a sunset
and I have red paint on my ass.
That's right.
Red paint all over my ass!
( Intro To
''Tie A Yellow Ribbon''Playing )
These are good cookies.
( Breathy ):
Yeah... they're good.
So what can you do?
I mean,
what do you want to do?
I know... a joke.
Yeah? Okay.
A guy...
goes into...
a bar...
and he...
has a... frog on
his...
Frog on his head.
On his head.
And the... bartender...
Wait, I screwed up.
A frog...
goes into... a bar.
You want to watch TV?
Can't. Not allowed.
What? You mean, ever?
Mom says...
TV makes you...
stupid.
No, TV makes you normal.
How can they do that?
He's in a wheelchair.
So what do you do all day,
homework?
Mostly... read... comics.
You have comic books?
Whoa!
You really have
Youngblood, number one?
Want to... read it?
No way. I'd wreck it.
Oh... did you read
the last Savage Dragon
when they split him in two?
Yeah. Brilliant.
I like how he never has to
learn a lesson or anything.
He just gets to pound on everyone.
You're under galactic arrest.
Think again, space flatfoot.
You cannot escape.
Give up or be annihilated.
Saturday morning
is the only thing
my family does better
than anyone else.
Damn!
You boys,
you keep this house clean
till your dad comes home.
Two of you can have
slices of pizza for lunch.
The other one can have...
I don't know.
I think they're peas.
( Phone Rings )
Somebody get that.
- Not it.
Hello.
Young Master Malcolm.
Francis, hi.
Hey, man
I wrote you guys
a really long letter yesterday
but, listen, they only gave me,
like, three minutes
so would you put
the special prosecutor on?
Mom, it's Francis.
Hey, Francis, how's school?
Oh, couldn't be better, Mom.
My new roommate showed me
how to kill mice
with a hammer yesterday,
so, you know, between that
and the general atmosphere
of simmering homoeroticism
I think I'm really starting
to turn around.
Honey, it's only until summer.
Come on, push it!
Give it up, prom date.
Yeah, listen, um...
I know I shouldn't ask
but would you be able
to send me my allowance
like, a couple of weeks early
'cause I kind of need some...?
Oh, my God! Are you smoking?
What?
You're smoking.
I can hear you smoking.
You're smoking, aren't you?
Mom, I'm not smoking. Geez.
After seeing the anguish
your father and I
went through to quit
didn't any of that
register with you?
Okay, listen.
I'll talk to your dad.
Maybe we can send you
part of it.
Honey, I have to go.
I'm late for work.
I'll call you later.
Okay, thanks, Mom. I love you.
( Dial Tone )
Oh... I love you.
He's so lucky.
I know.
We never go anywhere.
He gets to be in Alabama.
Is Alabama nice?
Look it up, Dewey.
It's got Sequoia Caverns
the biggest cast-iron statue
in the world.
Plus it's right next to Florida
where Disney World is.
I bet he goes to Disney World
all the time.
Hey, moron, he's 1 6.
He doesn't do kid stuff.
He goes to parties,
drinks beer and goes skiing.
Right, genius.
They do lots of skiing in Alabama.
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
- No, you shut up!
- Make me!
I'll make you right--
( Screaming )
Not my face!
You'd better not be fighting
in there, Reese, Malcolm!
I said, you better not
be fighting--
( Doorbell Ringing )
For crying out loud!
Reese! Malcolm!
( Doorbell Ringing )
Yes. Can I help you?
Oh. My good... um, hi.
Hel... hello. I'm....
Are you...?
I'm... Caroline Miller
from Malcolm's school.
I sent you some letters
and left some messages
on your answering machine.
Okay, fine. You caught me.
What do you want?
Um... well,
it's been three weeks
and you haven't responded
and it's really important...
I mean, well, for Malcolm's sake
that the parents be
as involved in...
So you're here to insult
my parenting skills?
No. I'm sure you're
a terrific parent.
( Screaming )
Who's the baby now?
I'm here because I think
that there is a tremendous
opportunity for...
Could you, you know,
maybe put a top on?
They're just boobs, lady.
You see them in the mirror
every morning.
I'm sure yours
are a lot nicer than mine.
That's actually not...
Let me tell you something else.
The reason I didn't respond
is because it is a load of crap.
What?
You are not going
to stick my Malcolm
in some special ed class.
What is it with you people?
Why do you have to label everybody?
Malcolm may be a little strange
and, I know, I know,
he never shuts up
but he is not disturbed.
You know, he is a good boy...
Please!
You know what?
You don't understand at all, okay?
So if I could just
come in for a minute
I could explain everything,
okay?
Reese:
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Good, hon.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's something
we have to talk about.
I thought we weren't
going to mention that
until after the biopsy.
It's not that.
It's about Malcolm.
I didn't do it.
He did it. I saw him.
A teacher from school came by
and she ran
some tests with Malcolm.
He has an IQ of 1 65.
Who?
Malcolm. He's a genius.
He's going to a special class.
What?
Malcolm's special?
Where do you think that came from?
They have a special program
for gifted children.
They have advanced textbooks
and devoted teachers
and good things they don't want
to waste on normal kids.
You start on Monday.
In the Krelboyne class?
Mom, no. I don't want to.
What are you talking about?
Of course you want to.
No. I want to stay
in my own class.
I don't want to be a Krelboyne.
Mom, seriously, Krelboynes
get their butts kicked.
Just stop one minute.
There's nothing wrong
with being smart.
And there's nothing wrong
with being cut from the herd.
It makes you the one buffalo
that isn't there
when the Indians run the rest
- of them off the cliff.
- Huh?
Mom, this isn't fair.
If I don't want to go,
why do I have to?
Because it's not just up to you.
We have to do what's best for you.
Is Malcolm going to Alabama?
Mom, please!
Don't make me go! Please!
Malcolm, calm down.
But it isn't fair!
That's right. It isn't fair.
It's the first time
anyone in this family
has ever been given an edge
and you are not going to waste it.
Dad?
Honey?
Well...
look, honey...
Malcolm, you see...
Oh, for crying out loud.
How come there's never
any iced tea in this pitcher?
I make a fresh batch
every morning
and it's gone
by the time I get home.
I want a better family!
Malcolm...
Go get yogurt.
Look at that.
Gone.
Can't you make iced tea?
No!
I don't want to go
to a special class.
People think
I'm weird enough already.
I know.
I like where I am.
I want to stay.
That's because you don't
understand the world yet.
Sweetie,
life does not give you
a lot of chances to move up
even if you deserve it.
Look at your dad and me.
Malcolm, I'm proud of you.
You boys are so lucky.
You have so many gifts
that other kids don't have.
And I don't just mean
Stevie Kenarban, either.
I mean, look at those
Parker boys across the street.
They may be healthy,
but honest to God
those are the ugliest
little boys ever born.
They look like boiled beets,
don't you think?
And those Henderson kids?
That electrocuted their dog
when they were trying
to get free cable.
How smart can they be?
And your friend Richard.
He's not ugly or dumb.
Yes, but he's very effeminate.
Just remember
any kid who makes fun of you
is a creepy little loser
who'll end up working
in a car wash.
This shouldn't make me
feel better, but it does.
You'll be all right, sweetie.
If you don't make
a big deal out of this
nobody else will either.
And I just can't say enough
about how proud
we should all be of Malcolm
for getting into
the gifted program.
Now Malcolm may not look
different than the rest of us
but he is.
Very different.
In his brain.
And I think we should
recognize him for that.
Bye.
Caroline: All righty,
today we are starting a new section
on the Peloponnesian War
which I know
you are all going to love.
Malcolm?
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Fine.
All right.
Excuse me.
Stop staring at me!
Why do they keep doing that?
You're new.
Oh, great.
So I'm the freak
of the freak show?
Pi to 50 places.
Mark. Set. Go.
3.1 41 592653
5897 93 23--
Turn around,
or I swear to God
I'll kill you.
Just... chill out.
Don't tell me to chill out.
You chill out.
Nobody can live like this.
- I'm okay.
- Oh, sure.
You're okay because it doesn't
make any difference to you.
You've always been a freak.
I used to be normal.
Wait.
Who just said that?
You're going to take that
the wrong way
aren't you?
You...
suck.
It's so cool!
Around here, being smart is
exactly like being radioactive.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Stevie?
What?
Look
I...
Score!
( Laughing )
Hey, Spath!
Why don't you stop
being such a buttwipe?!
All:
Ooh.
What'd you call me?
You heard me!
I don't care anymore!
I just don't care, Spath, okay?
Alls you ever do
is make everybody miserable!
Except for your little
monkey-slaves over there.
Who, by the way,
only pretend to like you.
They hate you as much
as everyone else does!
And you're just too busy
being mean and stupid
to ever figure it out!
I keep trying to run,
but my legs won't work.
Mom was right:
They are important.
Wow.
I don't know about you
but the Krelboyne
really hurt my feelings.
( Nervous Laughter )
Hey...
Go away, Stevie.
It's good you two are friends.
He won't mind sharing
his wheelchair.
Okay, this is where something
good happens, finally.
So we're going to slow down
and make it last
as long as possible.
( All Gasping )
Dude, you hit a cripple.
( Gasping And Shouting )
I didn't mean to...
I wasn't trying...
Stevie, I'm sorry.
( Stevie Groaning )
Ow...
aah...
ow!
What's your problem?
I mean, he's in a wheelchair
and he has glasses.
So then, the principal comes out
and everyone's
all talking at once.
So the story he puts together
is that Spath attacks Stevie
for his lunch
and I'm like this hero
that stepped in to defend him.
It was beautiful.
Okay, it wasn't funny
when Spath started crying.
No, wait, it was.
Dad's hair... ugh.
Yeah, I know. It's gross.
But, hey, if a bunch of birds
can make the best
out of what they get
then so can I.
Dewey:
Malcolm?
Like having to go to special class.
I can make it work out, right?
Malcolm?
Not now!
Or my family.
We're not the greatest family
in the world
but we can get better.
I mean, it's not impossible.
Malcolm?
What?!
Can I get out?
No, stop asking.
So basically, I think
everything's going to be okay.
( Pounding )
A bug went up my nose.
So what do you want me to do
about it?
www.tvsubtitles.net