Everybody up!
( Screaming )
Let's go! Let's go!
I got to do laundry before work!
I am taking breakfast off the table
in five minutes!
I know this kid...
his mom wakes him up
with a kiss on the forehead.
? Yes, no, maybe ?
? I don't know ?
? Can you repeat the question? ?
? You're not the boss of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? Life is unfair?
Okay, I've been up for half an hour.
I've had my cereal.
It's time for Mom to ask
the same annoying question
she asks me every morning.
So, Malcolm, what are you doing
in your genius class today?
Nothing. It's just as dumb and boring
as being in regular class,
except now I get ostracized.
Ostracized? Oh, you're
learning such big words.
Hey.
They want to know what I think
about caller I D blocking.
Do I think about that?
Oh!
What?
Nothing.Just a sharp Cheerio.
Oh!
Hah! $21 0!
Look at all the calls
that Francis is charging to us.
60 minutes. Oh!
Oh, 80 minutes-- And every one
of these calls is to Beebee.
$21 0 on Beebee!
I know. Now, honey,
just try to understand.
He's off in Alabama.
He's all by himself at military school.
He's lonely, so he calls
his little girlfriend.
She's a tramp.
No one's saying she's not a tramp.
Didn't you change our code number?
Three times.
I don't know how he's getting it.
65 51 9.
That'll be good till
the bill comes on the 1 5th.
Thanks, man.
You are a good brother.
I was taking money
out of her wallet anyway.
He is doing this just to upset me.
Oh, come on, Lois.
He's 1 6 and thinks he's in love.
What are you going to do?
Oh, man, never ask her that.
Beebee, you can't imagine
how much I miss you.
It is like a white-hot fire
burning in my chest.
The only thing that keeps me going
is just the thought of holding you
and stroking your hair
and being with you
in a perfect, golden moment.
Oh, yeah.
I'm totally the same way.
Oh, I'm just so...
Are you watching Buffy?
I can do both.
You know, I think of things,
too, like...
No, it's too embarrassing.
Tell me.
It's not the kind of thing
you can say over the phone.
It's something
I'd have to show you.
Beebee,
I think it would be better
if you told me,
and then you showed me.
Stanley, what are you doing?
That was Beebee!
Sorry, man.
Commandant says your phone privileges
have been revoked for a month.
Your mom complained
about the bills.
Okay, let me just tell...
Francis, do you remember
the thumb thing?
The one you did to my thumb,
or the one you did
with your thumb?
( Phone Rings )
Hello.
Malcolm! Thank God.
I don't have any more quarters,
so just listen.
I need you
to swipe Mom's credit card
and I need you
to buy me a cell phone.
What you want to get is
the unlimited off-peak plan,
and then FedEx it to me.
Francis, no. I can't do that.
What?
Dude, don't bail on me.
I'm sorry, but Mom
is totally on the warpath
about the phone calls.
Her radar is up.
I can't do anything.
Seriously, you've just
got to find a way to live
without calling Beebee all the time.
Hello?
( Scream )
( Dial Tone )
He understands, right?
Dearest Beebee,
something wonderful has happened.
The pain and confusion
of the last few months
has disappeared, replaced by
a single glorious purpose.
From the ashes of the
old Francis rises a new man
filled with boldness
and determination.
I fly to you on angel's wings,
knowing I follow
the mandate of my heart.
( Shrill Screaming )
( Groaning )
Every night
for the past two weeks.
He thinks there's a monster
under the bed.
It seemed so funny
when we thought of it.
Oh, sweetie, not again.
The monster!
It tried to suck my brain out!
All right, I have had it.
You two are banned from Nintendo.
Okay.
We're already banned from Nintendo.
The sad thing is he thinks
he just outsmarted her.
All right, fine. Pillows.
What?
That's right.
I'm taking your pillows.
Come on, come on, hand 'em over.
And I'm not getting up again.
If that monster wants
to suck out your brain,
you just let him take it
and you go back to sleep.
I love you.
We're all...
( Animal's Voice Fading )
Hello?
Don't scream.
It's me.
Francis!
Way to go, dipwad.
You got me in the nards.
Francis, what are you doing here?
I'm taking control
of my own destiny.
I'm just picking up Beebee
and we're going to head off for Canada.
You're going to visit Grandma?
No, a different part of Canada.
Someplace wild where people
don't have to destroy love
just 'cause they don't understand it.
You just ran away from school?
Mom's really going
to kill you now.
No, she won't because
she won't know.
Malcolm, you can't tell anybody.
I'm placing my life
in your hands here.
Did you roll around in something?
You'll get used to it.
Look, I need you to get Beebee
to come see me tonight, okay?
Give her this.
Let it air out
for a while first.
Try to get me some food, 'cause
I haven't eaten in, like, 36 hours.
Francis, this sounds kind
of drastic, even for you.
Malcolm,
I do not have time for doubt!
The die has been cast,
my future is set.
Now, there's one
question in my mind--
Can I trust you?
But...
Yes. Yeah, definitely.
I'll toss my lunch bag
over the fence before school.
Oh!
Uh!
Mmm!
Can I have some?
Can't.
It's a...
prescription... sandwich.
''Prescription sandwich''?
Stevie, that's not even a good lie.
If you don't want to share,
just say so.
Don't want...
to share.
Let's play...
Ironside.
I'll be... Ironside.
I don't want to play
stupid Ironside.
What's your... problem?
It's my brother Francis.
He escaped from military school
and hitchhiked all the way here.
He's all scraped up
and smelly and hungry and dirty,
and now he's hiding out
at the creek.
If my parents catch him,
he's dead.
He's talking like he's crazy.
I don't know what to do.
Squeal.
What?
Rat him out.
I can't do that.
He's my brother.
I promised him.
I can't tell anybody.
You told... me.
Yeah, but by the time
you tell anyone
he'll be a thousand miles from here.
Tou... ché.
Beebee...
What?
Oh, you're that kid.
My name's Malcolm.
I'm Francis's brother.
You met me, like, ten times.
Yeah, you're
the freaky little brain, right?
Just be cool.
What do you want?
Here.
Francis is back home.
Well, he's not home.
He's hiding.
Huh. Three pages?
Both sides.
He loves to make me read.
What's that word?
''Consummate.''
It means he likes you.
Oh.
''Assignation, rendezvous, tryst''?
How the hell is anyone supposed to
know what he's talking about?
Beebee,just meet him
at the creek at 7:30, okay?
See? You can say it in English,
and you're, like, ten.
What are you doing?
I'm wearing a tank top.
Beebee, I don't think...
Don't think.
Just walk. Go.
The worst part is,
I think I'm stealing panty liners.
Gosh, I had such a good day
at work today.
I got to work the cash-only line
for the first time in a month,
and my register
came out to the penny.
Plus, that creepy
new assistant manager
sliced his hand open
with a box cutter.
Spent the whole afternoon
in the emergency room.
Here's to him.
Honey, this chicken
is absolutely delicious.
Oh, well, it's a little recipe
I came up with.
It's Shake 'n' Bake--
but for pork.
How about that?
That's one for the recipe box.
Let's call it, uh, ''chork.''
All in favor?
No one for ''picken''?
Chork it is.
Brava.
Oh, cut it out.
You big talker.
Will this make me taste better
to the monsters?
Sure it will, son.
Get out of here!
You're not eating it.
You haven't had a bite
in two minutes.
I'm saving it.
There is no saving.
Malcolm, he's right.
The rule is no saving.
Oh, yeah, I care.
Cut it out!
( Phone Ringing )
Come on, it's mine.
Boys, boys, stop it.
You're going get
your mother out of...
You're going to ruin
her nice day.
Francis did what?!
Another night in the chat room.
That kid!
He thinks he can run away from school
like some kind of escaped convict?
If he thinks he can just vanish
in the night and I won't find him,
well, he is sadly mistaken.
Lois, you just calm down.
There's nothing
we can do right now.
Yes, there is.
I can call the police.
They're not going to look for anybody
unless they've been missing 48 hours.
Not if I say he has drugs on him.
Lois, stop it.
You have to accept the fact that,
for now, this is beyond your control.
Francis is going to have
to sink or swim on his own,
and frankly, I don't think
that's such a bad thing.
In the meantime,
we just have to leave it up to fate.
Fate.
Fate is just what you call it
when you don't know the name
of the person screwing you over.
Mom, I'm sure he's okay.
Uh-oh, tactical error.
Why do you think he's okay, son?
Because... he's always okay.
Malcolm, this is a very
serious situation here
and I know you love Francis
as much as we do,
so if you have any idea...
Oh, for God's sake!
Where is he?!
He came here to see Beebee.
Oh, my God,
how'd she do that?
I knew it.
When did you talk to him?
Don't look at her eyes.
This morning.
And Dewey shoved a sandwich
in the VCR.
Malcolm, where is he?
Got to think.
Diversion...
Delancey Park.
He's meeting her at Delancey Park
by the soccer field.
Well...
we'll just see what fate
has in store for Francis.
( Rustling )
Francis, I have to tell you...
Is Beebee coming?
Yeah.
But I have to tell
you something first.
I ratted you out to Mom.
What?!
I didn't mean to.
Mom did... her eyes...
and her voice, it was...
I didn't mean to.
Malcolm, how could you do that?
I trusted you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Look, I sent her to the park.
You've got an hour to get out of here
and have a head start before...
Are you crazy?
I can't go anywhere.
Beebee's coming.
Beebee.
Francis, what's wrong with you?
Why are you getting
in trouble for her?
You don't understand.
Duh! No one understands.
She's not nice, she's not smart,
she's a thief,
she's not even that good-looking.
And, oh, guess what else.
She treats you like crap.
I know.
You do?
Of course I do.
There's something you don't know.
What?
That no one in her whole life
has ever loved her
the way that I do.
All she has to do is see that,
and everything will change.
I really thought
he had something better.
Look, Malcolm,
you'll understand when you're older.
Now,just go.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Mind your own business.
Who were you talking to?
I wasn't talking to anybody.
You're imagining it.
I heard you talking.
Okay, I'll tell you.
But you have to keep it a secret.
You know the monster under your bed?
It's called a Sasquatch.
He hunts back there
during the day.
I was throwing him some raw meat
so he wouldn't come get us tonight.
I don't think I gave him enough.
So, if I were you, I'd keep very quiet
and stay the hell out of there.
Get it?
( Loud Bang )
Move!
( Tires Squealing )
Beebee:
Francis?
Beebee?
Don't move.
I want to remember this forever.
Where are you?
No! Don't look at me!
I wanted so much to be perfect for you,
but I couldn't find any soap.
I'm hideous.
Really?
Yes. But it's okay.
Everything is okay
now that we're together.
I can't tell you how beautiful
you look at this moment.
You look like an angel
or a perfect dawn
or a galaxy of stars.
I don't think we should
see each other anymore.
And... my heart soars
when I think...
Did you hear what I said?
I... um...
What?
Look...
you're a nice guy,
and all those letters you sent--
The stuff that I understood, anyway--
was sweet, but I don't know.
It feels different now.
It's hard to explain.
Would you try?
Well, maybe I just like
the long-distance thing
'cause, you know,
you'd call and you'd talk
and you'd make me feel
so good about myself,
and I didn't have to do anything.
Yeah, that's it.
Beebee, please.
I just think it's better we end it now
before anybody gets hurt.
I'm sorry, Francis.
Ow.
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
( Moaning ):
( Screaming )
Get out of here!
You stupid, dumb monster!
This is my house!
Ow!
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Ow!
( Tires Squealing )
You.
You there.
What do you think you're doing?
Excuse me?
Do you know how dumb and careless
you're being?
- Well, I brought...
- I''m not talking about that.
But shame on you.
Don't you know how
this is all going to end?
Do we know you?
No, but I know you.
You're young and pretty.
You love to get 1 6-year-old boys
so twisted up
they don't know what they're doing.
You think it's all in fun.
You don't care
how bad you hurt him.
Let me tell you something,
young lady.
Hearts are precious things.
You should be careful with them.
You!
You there!
What do you think you're doing?
The monster started growling,
so I threw rocks at him and killed him.
He started flying around
on rocket boots,
and I got to ride inside his head,
and now the monster's my friend,
and we went to get Slurpees.
You did not.
You're just lying.
If that's what Dewey says happened,
there's no reason to argue about it.
No one believes I beat
the last level of Mortal Kombat.
Because that's just ridiculous.
No one beats Sub-Zero.
Leave it off.
So, Beebee broke up with me.
Oh.
You okay?
I think I'm fine.
There's a strange sense of peace
that comes over you
when you give up
that last shred of dignity.
It's nice.
I'm really sorry.
Well, if you're going to love women,
you have to expect
the occasional flaming wipeout.
It's in the fine print,
but you agree to it
when you sign up.
So what are you going to do?
I'm going to go back to school.
I only missed a day,
so it should be too bad.
There's a pack of farm girls
that hang around outside the fence.
Probably check that out.
Later days.
Wait.
I'm sorry I ratted you out.
I just got scared.
Dude, it's ancient history.
Don't worry about it.
Well, can't you at least hit me
or something,
just so I feel like we're even?
You want me to hit you?
I don't know. Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks.
Psych.
Ow!
Now we're even.
? Don't cry?
? Dry those tears
falling out of your eyes ?
? Don't cry?
How'd you find me?
Malcolm told me.
You know, you should
probably rethink the whole
''trusting him with secrets'' thing.
How mad is Mom?
Well, let's just try to get
a couple states behind us
before we ask her.
So, how'd it go with Beebee?
We broke up.
Does it hurt?
Oh, yeah.
Well, son...
I wish I could say it gets easier,
but I honestly don't know.
I've never been dumped.
? Don't cry... ?
www.tvsubtitles.net