Who wants to make five bucks?
All:
How?
I need someone
to take the fall.
- Lois: Oh, my God!
- What did you do?
I can't tell you.
Yes or no,
no questions asked.
Lois:
Oh, my God!
Make it ten.
Done.
Lois:
Oh, my God!
You're a good son.
I got him, honey!
I got him!
Don't worry.
? Yes, no, maybe ?
? I don't know ?
? Can you repeat the question? ?
? You're not the boss of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? Life is unfair. ??
There you go--
all pink and shiny.
Mm. Boys?!
Uh-huh. Mm-hmm.
Ooh! Feel ten pounds lighter.
You ready?
Oh, yeah. Go.
Uh, aah...
( rapidly breathing )
Dad got us free tickets
at the water slide park from work.
It takes two days to prep him,
but it's worth it.
Ooh, smooth as a seal.
Ready for that water slide.
You know, we haven't been
on an outing in a long time.
It's nice when we can do things
together as a family.
Do what together?
( sobbing ):
Why can't I go?
Dewey, we discussed this.
You have to stay home
because of your ear infection.
I never get to go.
Honey, I know it seems
like a pattern
but it's just this.
And Disneyland.
( whimpering )
Oh, and that
chocolate factory tour.
Maybe it's time to stop sticking
dirty things in your ears.
Reese:
Hey, Dewey.
How's the ear?
Stop teasing him, Reese!
If your father doesn't find
a baby-sitter, nobody's going anywhere.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's just the little one.
Yeah, the other two aren't
going to be anywhere near you.
Ever since I can remember
we've always had trouble
with baby-sitters.
( cooing ):
Hello!
Goochy, goochy, goochy, goo.
Goochy, goochy...
( screaming )
Woman:
I don't know, sweetie.
What do you have
behind your back?
( screaming )
Man: You little losers.
I've had enough of this.
You open this door right now.
Okay, look.
I'm a little claustrophobic.
Just open the door!
Let me out! Come on!
I don't know.
I'm starting to think
it might be us.
Well, you'd think I'd get bored
wiping the floor with my cadets.
God knows we enjoy it, sir.
Do you know what
your problem is, cadet?
Discipline.
Anything worth doing
is worth doing well.
Whatever I do,
whether it's teaching you boys
or mastering tai chi,
or playing pool...
I focus.
I push myself.
But you don't commit
to anything, son.
You're never going to be a winner
because you do everything half-assed.
Oh, regrettable.
You may have spoken too soon, sir.
I think you'll find I play pool
with my whole ass.
Eight ball, corner pocket.
Damn.
Ah, the fatal scratch.
Once again,
I waltz with Lady Victory.
And until you focus, Francis
she is never going to be
your dance partner.
Lois: Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
It was so nice of your agency
to give us a second chance.
You two are going to have
so much fun together.
( quietly ):
Don't you dare hurt her.
Hurry,
the sun's coming up!
Do you want to play something?
No.
Hey, hey, look, kids.
- Only 1 2 more miles to Wavetown, USA.
- Yay.
So, Malcolm, you going to go
down the Liquidator this time?
Don't pressure the boy, Hal.
I'm not pressuring him.
I'm just asking.
He's scared enough as it is
without you making
a big deal out of it.
Hey, Mom, doesn't
Malcolm have to wear
- his nose plug for his sinuses?
- Shut up.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot it.
Listen, you just be
very careful then, okay?
Don't worry, here it is.
Oh. Thank you, Reese.
( whispers ):
Jerk.
Oh, my gosh, look at this!
Reese:
This is awesome!
I can't wait
to get on the rides.
Malcolm, don't think you can
take off that nose plug
just because I'm not looking.
You're going
to wear it all day.
- I'm not even in the water.
- If I catch you
not wearing that nose plug,
you're going to spend the day
in the kiddie sprinkler.
What do you want to do first?
What makes you think I want
to do anything with you?
What's your problem?
That nose-plug thing was bogus.
You crossed the line, Reese.
What?!
You sold me out to Mom.
It would've been different
if I had done
something to you, but...
that was
totally cold-blooded.
Don't be such a baby.
What you did to me
was an act of war.
And believe me,
I will get you back.
You won't know where or when,
but you're gonna pay.
You sound funny.
You wanted to see me, sir?
I just got a call
from the sheriff
that a cocksure,
smart-mouthed youth
looking very much like yourself
has been hustling pool
at the local bars.
Really, sir?
You are in serious trouble,
cadet.
I can explain...
Why have you been holding back
when we've played pool?
What?
I want to know why
you've been letting me win.
Sir, if I played for real
I'd just end up humiliating you
in front of the school, and...
and you'd, you know,
torture us all for it.
Really, nothing good
could come from it, and
and besides, winning seems
to make you so happy.
I am not a child.
Do you really think me
so petty that
I would throw a tantrum
over something so small
as a game of pool?!
My mistake, sir.
We are going to play again.
And you are going to give me
your best game, cadet.
And to make sure of that,
if you don't win
picture yourself, 0400,
awakened from sweet dreams of Mommy
sent outside
into the bitter cold
to raise our school colors
and stand at attention
for three hours
until reveille is called.
Now, picture that
for 230 consecutive days.
But what if I try my best
and I still lose?
Then you shall be miserable indeed.
Dismissed.
Remember, honey,
how I promised you
that exotic island vacation
but we had to go have
children instead?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I was thinking
maybe today could be
our little island getaway.
We've got the sun,
the sand, the palm trees.
And I brought the cocktails.
It's Malibu Rum
in a lotion bottle
so no one will know
the difference.
( chuckling )
You are so cute when
you sneak in alcohol.
Hey, Reese, I think I just saw
that girl you liked.
You know, the one with
the really long blonde hair.
- April?
- April, that's her.
Why'd you say you liked her again?
She's real trampy.
I hear she kisses with tongue.
Is that true, April?
Jerk!
Now we're even.
You geek!
You deserved it!
Malcolm:
Ow! Get outta here!
I think those are ours.
No. I'll take care of it.
Lois: Malcolm, Reese,
knock it off!.
Can I watch TV?
No.
Can I play video games?
What can I do?
Something quiet.
( wheels clicking softly )
Quieter.
( man screaming )
( screaming continues )
( crowd screaming )
I can do this.
( man screaming )
Keep your arms and legs
crossed at all times.
Do not bend your legs.
Do not raise your head.
Remove all piercings.
You may not wear
anything around neck.
Enjoy the ride.
Okay, here it goes.
On three.
One...
two...
three!
Hey, there, girlie.
Let me adjust your bra strap.
- ( smacking loudly )
- Now we're even.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
First, we sort
by the number of holes
then by color.
What's in your mouth?
Nothing.
There are at least 20 things
I will not tolerate
and lying is one of them.
Spit it out.
You're eating my buttons.
I wasn't eating.
I was saving.
What are you?
A hamster?
What were you saving it for?
I don't know.
It's pretty.
It's my favorite one.
You know... actually,
it's my favorite, too.
What do you think of this one?
It's ugly. I hate it.
So do I.
My, you're a smart little boy.
( clears throat )
You seem to be practicing
pretty hard.
I hope you're not planning
on doing something stupid,
like winning.
Look, guys,
I know you want me to lose
but Spangler insisted
I play a real game.
Francis, you can't win.
If you do, Spangler's
going to take it out on us.
Remember when Hendrix
beat him playing horse
on a lucky shot?
We couldn't watch anything
but PBS for a week.
And that was during
pledge drive, man.
Guys, come on.
Do you have any idea
what Spangler's going
to do to me if I lose?
Do you know what we're going
to do to you if you win?
Ew!
Where were we?
Mom! You have to stop Reese!
He's being a total jerk!
Malcolm, does it look like
I'm open for business?
You have done nothing
but pester us.
Is it too much to ask
that your father and I
enjoy one day?
But Reese is...
I don't want to hear it.
You either take care
of this yourself
or I'm going to lock the two of you
in the car for the rest of the day.
I mean it.
( giggling )
Lifeguard, help!
My brother--
he can't swim.
( whistle blowing )
Out of the way, guys!
Drowning boy!
Give him some air, guys.
Give him some air.
Back up.
Sir!
Let the people
who work here do that.
Now we're even.
And then, I was playing
with my imaginary friend
and Reese hit me
because he said
I shouldn't talk to myself.
Well, Reese
is a horrid little boy.
There's nothing wrong
with having an imaginary friend.
I talk to my Harold
all the time.
- You do?
- Of course.
He's here right now.
Would he like a cookie?
Sure.
No, no, no.
He's over there.
- Yes!
Sorry, sir.
It's understandable, cadet.
I've seen professionals
do much worse.
I guess the pool gods
are smiling on me today.
( all sighing )
But then, the pool gods
can be fickle.
That's okay, sir.
You'll win the next one.
Sir, what are you doing?
I think I'm losing.
And gracefully,
I'd like to be noted.
But you could have
made that shot.
I could say
the same thing to you.
There were at least a dozen
shots that you've held back on.
But since you seem to be
motivated more by losing
I'm going to beat you
at your own game.
Huh?
I'm going down, cadet.
I'm going down hard.
But sir, these guys are going
to kick my ass if I win.
Well, that's just gravy.
May the best man lose.
Fudge! It seems
I've scratched again.
Well, you seem to be
on a roll, cadet.
? Ah-ooh ?
? It's Christmas with leather?
? Christmas with leather?
? Freaks fly together?
? Makin' all the big boys scream ?
? All right ?
? Turn it up now ?
- ? All right ?
? Ah-ah-ah ?
? Went up to the... ?
? She's always... ?
? Rising up the dance floor ?
? I just want
to watch you dance ?
( ''Fernando''by ABBAplaying )
? Can you hear the drums,
Fernando? ?
? I remember long ago
another starry night like this ?
? In the firelight, Fernando ?
? You were humming to yourself?
? And softly strumming your guitar?
? I could hear the distant drums ?
? And sounds of bugle calls
were coming from afar?
? There was something
in the air that night ?
? The stars were bright,
Fernando ?
? They were shining there
for you and me ?
? For liberty, Fernando ?
? Though we never thought
that we could lose ?
? There's no regret ?
? If I had to do the same again ?
? I would, my friend, Fernando ?
? There was something
in the air that night ?
? The stars were bright... ?
( record scratching )
( siren wailing )
Before you say anything, Malcolm
I just want to tell you,
I don't want to hear it.
Can't you give your mother
and me five minutes of peace?
You know what?
You can have the rest of the day
because I've given up.
I'm not going to have
any fun anyway, so why try?
As long as we're on the same page.
Today sucked.
I've done nothing
except chicken out
get laughed at
and fight with Reese.
So now, I'm just
going to lie down
enjoy the sun and wait
for them to take me home.
Now we're even.
( laughing )
Now we're...
Boys!
Reese, I've done
some soul-searching...
and hereby offer my full apology.
It was very wrong of me. I'm truly
sorry for my inappropriate behavior.
The terrible guilt I'm feeling
is punishment enough...
Hey, no cutting in line.
Oh, it's you again.
Reese, I am so sorry.
I really, really mean it.
Do you think we're wealthy?!
What?!
Do you think we're wealthy?
Wealthy people
drive fancy cars.
They buy fresh pasta.
Do we do any of those things?
No! Wealthy people
can afford to have
their vacations ruined.
No big deal. They just pick up
and they go again.
Your father and I
work so hard.
We work so long.
What is wrong with you two?!
Are you aborigines?!
Every time I turn around,
I hear someone
screaming and fighting,
and I pray to God
it's someone else's kids,
but it's not.
It's always you!
Sane children
would appreciate this
but you have to keep going at
each other like rabid monkeys!
It is not enough
that you do this every day.
You have to make me suffer, too.
So help me!
Don't you dare!
( Lois screaming )
Arms and legs crossed
at all times!
That is the bravest thing
I've ever seen you do.
Yeah.
You're going to die.
I know.
So, do you think she's okay?
( Lois growling )
( screaming and shouting
continues )
Lois: This is the last time
I take you boys anywhere!
Good playing.
Same to you, sir.
Hey, who won?
Who cares, man?
( horn honks )
www.tvsubtitles.net