What are you looking at,
monkey boy?
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Reese!
What are you doing?
Help! Ow! Help!
Mom!
Cut it out. Cut it out.
Ow! Help!
It hurts! Ow!
Knock it off, you little...
Reese, what the heck are you doing?
You can't leave that kid alone
for five minutes without picking on him!
Reese:
I didn't do anything, Mom.
I gave him that.
? Yes, no, maybe ?
? I don't know ?
? Can you repeat the question? ?
? You're not the boss of me now ?
? And you're not so big ?
? Life is unfair. ?
Honey, which juice don't I like--
apple or grape?
- You don't like either.
- Oh, right.
Malcolm, what is all this stuff
from your teacher?
That woman sends home
two or three fliers every day.
She says she wants the parents...
to be as involved as possible
with the children.
At school?
It's the only break I get.
What exactly is
''Personal Fulfillment Week''?
Square dancing.
That's right, square dancing.
You should see it.
The Krelboynes dance
on the tetherball courts...
in front of the whole school.
We laugh our asses off.
Excuse me?
Butts.
We laugh our butts off.
Open.
Swish.
Spit.
This tastes like crap.
Reese is right.
This class is turning me
into a total weirdo.
You are not a weirdo.
You are gifted.
And if gifted kids are supposed to
square-dance, then you'll do it.
Probably teaches you geometry.
Don't forget to mail these bills.
They're late.
Two blues, one pink.
We're doing better.
Don't get cocky.
They're hot until
I deposit my paycheck.
You kids, let's get going.
You don't want them
to do-si-do without you.
That's it.
For the sake of my manhood,
today I'm ditching school.
Hey, why don't I drive you boys
to school today?
Uh, that's okay, Dad.
I don't mind walking.
Oh, no, no, no.
I really want to.
A chance to spend a few extra minutes
with my sons, enjoying their company...
Honestly, son,
it'll be the highlight of my day.
Come on.
Great. Now I can't
even be mad at him.
Aw, Stanley.
Let me show you how it's done.
Uh-oh, eyes down.
That was good.
You didn't give them
any satisfaction.
In another six months,
they'll be bored with you.
Man ( on TV ):
...get out of this one.
Patterson has just reversed...
( Laughing )
That's got to hurt.
Mom was right.
I do get some sick thrill
out of trouble.
Ow!
That skinny guy!
Come on, get him!
Commandant on the floor.
Ten-hut!
( Snarling )
I smell smoke.
Who is responsible?
Very well.
We'll do it the hard way.
Patton.
( Growling )
( Barking )
Francis, please lift up
your right foot.
Son, you have the worst attitude...
I've ever seen in 1 5 years
at this institution.
You seem compelled to break every rule,
to flout every convention.
You are never going to make it--
in the armed forces or anywhere else.
Now, I was never fortunate
enough to serve in combat...
but I do know what it requires.
Look at this dog.
He is vicious, he is ungrateful...
and yet even he understands
the importance of obedience.
Do you hear what I am saying,
Francis?
Yes, sir.
I'll try to be more like
a Jack Russell terrier, sir.
There will be no hot water
for this floor for the entire month.
You can thank the cadet
after I leave.
( Snarling )
( Blow Landing )
Francis:
Ow!
Reese wiped his booger
on my lunch bag.
What have we taught you
about snitching?
''Only snitch when asked to snitch.''
Good boy.
So, looking forward to school?
I guess.
That's a shame.
'Cause we're not going to school.
( Chuckling )
Where are we going?
Boys, I'm going to share
something with you...
I hope you'll remember
for the rest of your lives.
Now, I don't want
to spoil the surprise...
but I've been planning this
for years.
I just had to wait until you were
all old enough to appreciate it.
Hookers?
If it gets me out
of square dancing, fine.
Just sit back
and enjoy the ride, boys.
We're rebels.
We're wild men!
( Cackling )
Whoo!
( ''Sukiyaki''Sung InJapanese )
Where did I put
the damn paycheck?
( Gasping )
Yeah.
Those guys are wimps.
That's not even half the size
of the one I gave you...
just to get you out of riflery.
Hey, thanks
for pulling them off me.
I owe you one.
One?
Hey, you want to see
something very, very cool?
Oh, boy, what have you done now?
Francis:
Oh, isn't he beautiful?
He only cost me $20.
I'm calling him Otis.
Did you listen
to anything Spangler said?
You're already in enough trouble
as it is without bringing in a pet.
Well, Spangler
has that oversized gerbil.
And besides,
Otis is not a pet.
Otis is a symbol.
Of what?
Of everything that is
beautiful in the world.
Independence...
free thought.
I may be stuck here in
this militaristic loony bin...
but at least some part of me
can stay connected...
to the things
that give me my humanity.
You're not going
to turn me in, are you?
I don't know.
On the one hand,
you're probably going to get caught...
because you always do.
Then, of course,
I'll be involved...
even though I had
nothing to do with it.
On the other hand...
it's a snake.
Good man!
I think I'm starting
to bring out the rebel in you.
Touching.
Right.
Sorry.
( Bell Ringing )
Stock car races!
Oh, cool!
That's right, boys.
The real field of dreams--
only with concrete
instead of all that grass.
? I don't want to work... ?
Here we go.
Excuse us, please.
Oh, boys, boys.
You see that blue car down in front?
- Number 1 6?
- Yeah.
That is Rusty Malcolm.
Greatest man
in the history of the sport.
Maybe the greatest man ever.
1 5 NASCAR titles.
Six world records.
Inventor of the in-car
urination system.
The list is endless.
And he came from nothing,
just like you boys.
You see,
this is Rusty's last race ever.
He's retiring.
So, I wanted to share him
with you before he went...
so that you can see for yourselves how
much you can accomplish in this world...
with a little persistence
and determination.
Did you read that article in People
about him getting a divorce?
Shut your filthy mouth.
You know, you were named
after Rusty, Malcolm.
I was?
Yessiree, Bob.
Took me two kids
to win that argument.
Announcer:
And there they go.
Whoo!
Gentlemen, start your excitement,
because here they come!
( Whooping )
He won!
Rusty Malcolm won!
No, sweetheart.
That was just the pace lap.
How many laps are there?
Oh, hundreds.
We've got four hours of this.
Four hours?!
Uh-huh.
Do we at least get
to see any flaming wrecks?
Reese, it's not about that.
See, it's about
strategy and technique.
It's about the melding
of man and machine.
The wrecks are just sort of a bonus.
Dewey...
you can keep track of the laps.
Can we go get sodas?
What? Already?
Well, okay.
Guess it can't be a special day
without sodas, huh?
Here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Get your dad a beer.
Take my I.D.
Come on, Rusty!
( Vacuum Cleaner Running )
Firecrackers.
Malcolm.
( Vacuum Cleaner Stops )
( Chuckles )
I'm going to say Reese.
Three rooms to go,
and already I have enough evidence...
to ground them for life.
Dewey, stay with us.
You're going to get lost.
No, I won't.
Yes, you will.
You always do.
You know you could help.
I'm watching him.
He's right over...
Man, how does he do that?
Totally your fault!
He was right in your eye line.
You don't pay attention to anything!
I pay attention.
Score!
What are you doing?
( Muffled ):
Too slow.
Come on.
Let's just go find Dewey.
This place sucks.
It's hot, it stinks...
nobody's T-shirts
cover their stomachs...
and I'm bored out of my mind.
Hey.
Look at that.
Let's check it out.
I don't know.
It doesn't just say ''keep out.''
It says ''forbidden.''
And they wouldn't bother
making it ''forbidden''
if it wasn't something totally bitchin'
on the other side.
Wow. I can't find
a flaw in his logic.
Come on.
What's the worst that could happen?
We didn't do anything!
I'm a diabetic.
I need insulin.
Sit down!
You are such an idiot!
It actually was pretty bitchin'.
And I'm totally getting
one of these for Christmas.
( Doorbell Rings )
What does the sign say?
Woman:
''No soliciting.''
Well, that includes Jesus.
No, it's Caroline Miller,
Malcolm's teacher.
I need to talk to you.
Yeah, come on in.
Oh, spring cleaning?
Oh, ho.
Yeah, I'm cleaning house, all right.
I'm sorry to bother you at home...
but when Malcolm didn't show up
for school today...
What?
Malcolm cut school today?
Yeah. Actually, not just today.
Now, your first reaction is probably
going to be one of understandable...
Wait!
''Ditching.''
We have a winner!
( Scraping Sound )
Anyway, this week...
we've been doing a lot of work
on folk movement...
and I-I think that Malcolm may be
ditching because he's afraid that...
well, that he may
not seem... graceful.
Oh, you're serious.
Yes, I'm serious.
I think he may have body issues.
( Chuckling )
Look, honey,
you're probably very bright...
but you've got a lot
to learn about boys.
First off, they're able to think maybe
three minutes into the future...
and it's our job to make sure that
future comes crashing down on them...
within the time limit.
Otherwise,
they never learn anything.
Help lift.
Eew! What is that?
Don't be such a baby.
I'll get the tongs.
I'll be Kevin.
You be Clyde.
Think you can cry?
No. I got to feel it.
Ooh, I got an idea.
No!
Just follow my lead.
No, Reese.
Whatever it is, no!
Well, I guess you boys had some time
to think about what you've done.
Yes, sir.
Look, I, uh, used to be your age...
and I understand how tempting
a place like that can be.
And I guess you kids
really didn't do any major harm...
so I've decided to let you off...
You idiot!
Open it!
It's locked!
Okay, I think I can cry now.
Announcer:
...And Rusty Malcolm...
has retaken the lead
with only 1 00 laps to go.
Rusty:
Great beverage work, Hal!
My pleasure, Rusty!
( Voice Echoing )
Here comes Rusty Malcolm
into the pits.
It's going to be four tires...
Hey, how about that, boys?
( Sighs )
Well, this just plain
hurts my feelings.
Oh, man.
Oh, ma...
Stanley,
I'm sorry, I...
Wait.
I'm trying to see if I'm inspired
by its symbolic bid for freedom.
No. I'm just really pissed.
Okay, don't overreact.
It's just a snake, right?
So, it's got to be
around here somewhere.
No big deal.
( Dog Barking )
( Whimpering )
Spangler:
Oh, my God! Patton, no!
( Two Gunshots )
Hi, Mom. Uh, I was just thinking
about how much I missed you guys...
and... I was thinking I should come
for a visit, you know, like today.
There's a flight leaving in half an hour
and I already booked it...
so I just need
your credit card number to...
Well, honey, here's the thing.
Right now you are actually better off
being as far away from me as possible.
But...
You got to trust me
on this one, Francis...
or, uh, should I say...
''Olaf Mortenson''
of Wheatville, Montana?
( Dial Tone )
You know, I have learned more
in two hours with you...
than I have in six years of teaching.
( Sighs )
So, did your life...
turn out anything at all
like you planned?
Oh, God, no.
Oh, when I was a girl...
I had all these crazy,
romantic dreams.
I wanted to be a blackjack dealer
in an Indian reservation.
Didn't work out.
Stubby thumbs.
Well, at least you have your home
and your family.
All I come home to every night
are three howling cats and... Bob.
Who's Bob?
My shower head.
Do you have anything stronger?
I'm way ahead of you.
...and it looks like Rusty Malcolm
will win his final race!
Rusty!
I can't believe
they're missing this.
Rusty Malcolm maintains the lead
high off the third turn...
( Tires Screeching )
What...?
Oh, for the love of God!
What happened? What happened?
Rusty do something?
Missed it!
What'd he do?
( Metallic Squeaking )
Men... a terrible tragedy
has befallen us.
At approximately 1 7 00 hours...
our beloved Patton was set upon
by a serpent and devoured.
I, myself, fired a few rounds
as it slithered away...
but, hampered by a lack
of depth perception...
my efforts were useless.
( Sniffles )
Now...
after an incident such as this...
certain questions arise.
Leaving aside for the moment...
why God feels the need to
take away everything that I love...
that leaves us with the matter
of who is responsible.
Can you explain that, Francis?
Yes, sir. I believe you lost that finger
trying to start the school lawn mower.
What is in the hand?
They appear to be Raisinettes, sir.
They are snake droppings,
found in your footlocker.
Now, what do you
have to say for yourself?
Sir, I'm obviously the victim
of an elaborate conspiracy to frame me.
It's just too perfect, sir.
Two months!
No hot water, no television...
and an 8:00 p.m. curfew
for the entire academy!
Feel free to thank the cadet
after I leave.
Could I ask one favor?
Send a picture to my mom
with ''I told you so'' written across it.
Yeah! Whoo!
Way to go, man.
What?
We hated that yappy, little rat.
Let's hear it for Francis, you guys!
( Cheering )
This is an improvement, right?
Reese!
Rusty Malcolm wins the stock car...
Malcolm!
( Grunts )
Hi, Dad.
Hi. Where are your brothers?
Oh, geez.
Come on.
Uh... what seems to be the trouble here,
Officer, uh... Karl?
These your boys?
Yes, sir, that they are.
Couldn't be prouder of them.
These are two of the worst kids
I have ever encountered in my life.
And I work the state fair.
Really?
See, that must be fascinating--
Seeing people from all over,
the different cultures...
I don't want to be a hard case here,
but these kids physically attacked me.
Plus, they completely destroyed
a $300 pneumatic drill...
which someone's going to pay for.
Well, this all sounds pretty serious.
But don't you worry, Officer Karl.
They are going to hear all about it
when I get them home.
I'm just sorry that they had to put you
through all of this. That's not fair.
And I, uh, see,
I fully intend to pay for...
( Groans )
Clyde, Kevin!
Get to the car!
( Moaning )
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Ooh!
( Chuckling )
Okay.
All right, men.
Well, I hope you've all
learned something today, huh?
I learned my dad is actually
capable of doing something cool.
I'm not saying violence is cool,
but that was cool!
I always wondered where we got it from.
Program... tickets...
Huh.
Your mother's paycheck.
Now, boys, remember,
as far as your mom knows...
I have been at work all day.
( Laughing )
Okay, go on.
All right.
Well, at least she doesn't know
I skipped school all week.
www.tvsubtitles.net