[ Birds Chirping ]
Let me go!
Get off it!
I can't breathe.
Ow!
[ Crashing ]
[ Loud Arguing ]
[ Glass Breaking ]
[ Snoring ]
Leave the squirrel alone
and get the fire extinguisher.
Reese, no!
[ Crashing ]
Blood tastes funny.
You better be naked
when I get back.
Done.
?? Yes, no, maybe??
??I don't know??
?? Can you repeat the question???
?? You're not the boss of me now??
??And you're not so big??
??Life is unfair????
[ Reese, Softly ]
Malcolm...
[ Screaming ]
How was that even remotely fair?
That's for us all having to go
to your stupid Krelboyne picnic today.
You think I want you to go?
My special class is having a family day
and, if that's not bad enough,
it's on the weekend
that Francis is home.
I'm going to look like
a total idiot in front of him.
Pretty bunnies.
Luckily, I've got a brilliant plan
to get out of this.
[ Gagging ]
Oh, poor baby.
Yeah, I'm sick.
No, you're grounded for pouring...
perfectly good vegetable soup
in the toilet...
and you owe me 49 cents.
[ Flushing ]
I don't understand
why you don't want to go...
to this picnic, Malcolm;
I think it sounds like fun.
Yeah, sitting on the grass,
eating barbecue.
It's Krelboyne.
It's not going to be on the grass
because half the class is allergic...
and don't expect any meat either,
because they all voted not to serve
anything that ever had a mother.
Cousin Nancy doesn't have a mother.
That's right.
She has two daddies.
Oh, man,
two guys as your parents?
That house has got to be
a dude's paradise.
You know, there are a lot
of proven health benefits...
to the vegetarian lifestyle.
In fact, I've been seriously
considering it myself.
It'll be nice to meet
the other parents.
I'm sure they're better than
the carnival freaks in Reese's class.
What a horrible bunch of people.
Amen to that.
Well, this just sounds
like a blast to me.
Why do I have to go, again?
Because it's a family picnic, Francis,
and you're a member
of this family.
Right, see, I just keep forgetting
that, being forced to live...
a thousand miles away
at military school and all.
Well, I can't wait to see
this academic circus.
I bet it's really cute.
It's not a circus.
It's a bunch of social misfits
doing a bunch of weird stunts...
to show off how smart they are.
What's your weird stunt, honey?
Just some lame thing--
nothing you want to see.
You've got to get me out of there
before my turn comes.
Why? What's the big deal?
It just is, okay?
I don't want to do my act.
All right, relax.
We'll hang out for like 1 5 minutes,
establish your presence,
then we'll go over the fence
like at Grandma's wedding.
[ Sighs ]
That's why I love this guy.
Welcome!
Welcome, one and all!
Run away with us
and join the circus!
The academic circus!
Oh, no.
My teacher.
Malcolm, thank goodness.
I was so nervous.
I had a dream you didn't come,
and I was...
being chased by something big
but invisible and-- Never mind.
You're here,
and that's all that matters.
Hello, little guy.
Ready to leave your family
and join the circus?
- Oh.
- Huh?
Little lower, son.
Oh, look at all
your little friends.
Hi.
Hi there.
They're not my friends.
They're a bunch
of geeks and losers.
Malcolm's in the house!
Malcolm! Malcolm!
Malcolm! Malcolm! Malcolm!
I'm going to kick
so much Krelboyne ass today...
it's not even funny.
Go, Malcolm! Go, Malcolm!
Go, Malcolm!
Easy.
You got all afternoon.
We're getting out of here
in 1 5 minutes, right?
Make it ten.
Yeah...
Ooh, hello.
[ Francis ]
And who might you be?
What?
Nothing.
Hello. I'm Lois. This is Hal.
We're Malcolm's parents.
That's very nice.
I'm Dorene.
These are the girls.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Yeah, it's really...
Whatever.
Hope everybody likes brownies.
Oh, my,
that is so thoughtful.
Are those nuts?
Walnuts.
Oh... gee...
we can't have that.
Some of the children
are severely allergic to nuts.
Oh, my gosh, I had no idea.
Whose child is allergic?
Well, no one
in this class specifically,
but you can never
be too careful.
Believe me, this isn't meant
to publicly humiliate you.
I'm sure they were delicious.
Oh, hi, fellas.
Hey there.
What's your pleasure--
nature dog, health patty, tofu square?
Good God.
Want me to brown that chicken leg
a little more for you?
Well...
looks like I got here
just in time.
Gentlemen...
behold.
Is that...
meat?
Nothing but.
Hi.
Hey.
So, uh...
you here?
Yeah.
You?
Hey, Stevie.
[ Panting ]
Can't stop... to chat.
Got to get... my chemicals...
in the shade.
I thought you were doing
your report on oscilloscopes.
Changed to... catalytics.
It's more... exciting.
Right?
What do you care?
I'm up...
after you.
So?
Following you...
is like...
following Streisand.
Well, don't worry about it.
You won't be following me.
Why?
Have I been... bumped?
Francis, what are you doing?!
Come on,
the coast is clear and...
it's already been ten minutes and--
We're not ditching out, are we?
[ Children Conversing, Indistinct ]
A small pack of Krelboynes
has ventured out of hiding...
to bask in the afternoon sun.
Their defenses down,
they're an easy target
for nearby predators.
[ Sniffing ]
They sense danger,
but it is too late.
Their hesitation is fatal.
[ Roaring ]
[ Frightened Yelps ]
[ Panting ]
And the circle of life goes on.
Kafkaesque, isn't it?
Huh?
Never mind.
Kick his butt, Alphonse.
Wait... wait.
Here it comes.
Yes, there!
I've arrested the cellular mitosis!
Thank you, Dabney.
That was riveting.
Our next act needs no introduction,
having been the buzz
of last year's math fair.
Please welcome Flora Mayesh...
and Fermat's Last Theorem!
Hello? Is this...?
Testing.
So, I understand that Malcolm
has quite the vocabulary.
Yeah, he's just yap, yap,
yap, yap, yap all day long.
Well, that's not
the vocabulary I meant.
It seems that he's taught...
several of the children
the ''R'' word.
The ''R'' word?
I'm sure it's just something
he picked up off the street--
certainly not at home.
Yeah, well, ''R'' you, lady.
So, this is going well, right?
It's pretty much
everything I expected.
So, you ready, Malcolm?
I mean, you're all set, right?
Sure.
Good.
I'm... ready.
Thanks for... asking.
You know what's so great
about our relationship?
It just still feels so fresh,
you know what I mean?
Totally.
All right, take it away.
I need two burgers and a dog, Hal.
Coming up. Dewey?
Thank you, sir.
All right. Thank you.
What have I told you
about raw meat, son?
I'm not.
Dad, I want you to meet someone.
This is Jody.
Hi.
Oh, it's so great
to finally meet you.
Francis talks about you
all the time.
Oh, yeah?
You, too.
Oh...
I'm so glad that went well.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give to you
the Nixon electromagnet.
[ Whirring Hum ]
[ Loud Clang ]
[ Muffled Yelling And Sobbing ]
Turn it off!.
This is going dreadfully.
Am I wrong?
Please tell me I'm wrong.
Excuse me.
For what?
[ Sniffing ]
[ Liquid Bubbling ]
This is it.
You're almost... up.
Stop reminding me.
Nervous?
No, I just don't want to do this.
Don't you ever get sick
of being a Krelboyne?
Of people thinking
you're some kind of freak?
You are...
what you are.
Accept it.
Not without a fight.
You're harshing... my buzz.
Don't let... anyone...
mess with... my stuff.
You know, in the wrong hands,
these chemicals can make
a pretty powerful stink bomb.
These hands look wrong enough.
And this field trip
to the historic ghost town,
I think we all know
what that leads to--
the occult, devil worship,
state colleges.
So then it's agreed
that the trip will be canceled.
Wait a minute.
You can't decide that.
You didn't even vote.
I was only going
by the general tone of the group.
General tone?
I haven't heard a peep...
out of any of these
other women all day.
What, you all agree...
with what Mrs. Control Freak
here is saying?
Well--
Phyllis!
My name isn't Phyllis!
And, no, I don't feel that way.
[ Woman ]
I don't either! I never liked--
My husband told me
to stand up to you...
after I came home
from that bake sale in tears.
[ Women Arguing ]
My soy burger...
it's bleeding!
This is meat!
We're eating meat!
Oh, my God!
[ Yelling ]
[ Reese ]
Get out of the way!
Come here!
[ All Arguing ]
[ People Shrieking ]
Okay, the difference
between a stink bomb...
and a level-three toxic biohazard...
is apparently two extra drops
of sulfur tetroxide.
I'm totally suing that web site.
- I didn't do it!
I want... a receipt.
[ Sobbing ]
I'm kind of conflicted.
On the one hand,
I ruined Caroline's picnic...
and very possibly endangered
a hundred lives.
On the other hand,
now I don't have to do my act.
[ Whimpering ]
Did you miss me?
Mm-hmm.
So who was that girl
with her hands all over you?
What girl, the paramedic?
She was making sure
I didn't inhale any toxic fumes.
Oh, I'm sure you loved
every moment of it.
God, would you quit nagging me?
Maybe if you paid a little
more attention to me.
More attention?
You're smothering me.
I need space.
Oh, you'll get your space.
We're through.
Fine by me.
Here's the school ring
you gave me.
The teddy bear key chain.
- Your shirt.
- Your two poems.
The book you lent me.
Your Depeche Mode tape!
And here's your gum.
I love Krelboynes.
And I swear,
I'm not just saying that.
Why would I?
Nice hang time.
Well, it's really a simple function...
of the tensile strength
of the elastic waistband.
[ Sinister Chuckle ]
[ Crying ]
I brought you a hamburger.
This should make us even, right?
[ Sniffling ]
Thank you.
Is this meat?
Uh, it might be.
Look what I've been reduced to.
[ Sobs ]
Okay, well, um...
I'm going to...
Oh, Malcolm, I'm so sorry.
Huh?
I know how much...
you were looking forward
to doing your act,
especially
with your family here.
I failed you.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
After today, they're going
to fire my ass so fast.
[ Crying ]
My parents were right.
I never should have left
the cannery.
[ Sniffling ]
Want another hamburger?
[ Gasping ]
Yes!
I do. I do.
I really, really do. I...
really... do.
[ Sobbing ]
Can you believe it? Meat.
I don't know about you,
but I'm outraged.
I want you to know...
that I am going to see to it that you
never serve on a school committee,
hold an office
or even so much as set foot...
in a P.T.A. meeting
as long as I can help it.
Is that a promise, lady?
'Cause I'd really like
to get that in writing.
I should have expected as much...
from the mother
of a foul-mouthed thug.
What he's even doing in this class,
I don't know.
Oh, I see you made a friend.
Yeah. Tomorrow we're
going shopping for shoes.
Academic circus?
You got the circus part right.
This is the biggest debacle
I've ever seen.
I guarantee you Principal Littledove
will hear about this.
[ Man ]
He sure will, from all of us.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes. All women suck.
No, I mean...
you'd still like me...
even if you found out
I was a freak, right?
The family wouldn't treat me
any different, right?
Dude, we already know you're smart.
Yeah, but-- Never mind.
Just don't say I didn't warn you.
Look, it's Malcolm!
[ Girl ]
Hey, hey, Malcolm's going to do it, Dad!
The P.T.A. is on-line, missy.
Are you aware of
the power of the Internet?
[ Everyone Talking Excitedly ]
Hey, everyone look!
Look, Malcolm's doing it.
He's doing it.
Hey, shut the hell up!
[ Talking Stops ]
Um...
could somebody, please,
show me some credit cards?
Okay.
The numbers on them are:
3699-7 41 2-6823...
91 40 and... 342 4...
1 804-1 83 5...
3668.
He's right!
Okay.
If you add the individual digits
on each card...
you get 7 4 and 66.
If you multiply those numbers,
you get 4,884.
How do we even know he's right?
Oh, he's right.
4,884 squared...
is 23,853,456.
The square root of 4,884...
is 69 and 885/1 ,000.
The square root of that...
is eight and 3,597 /1 0,000.
Factor it!
The factors are 23 2 and 73.
Multiply it by pi.
26 and 261 /1 ,000.
- Cube it!
- 584 and 21 4/1 ,000.
The arc tangent!
89 and 9/1 0 degrees.
Natural log!
6 and 3,699/1 0,000.
- What's the reciprocal?
- 1 7 /1 0,000.
In base eight!
1 1 ,431 .
The capital of Iceland!
Reykjavik--
but that's not math.
[ Cloth Ripping ]
Why can't you do that?
Cellular mitosis.
What are we paying your tutor for?
Do you have any brothers?
No.
Ow!
Hey.
Hi.
So, um... how you been?
Fine.
You look good.
Yes, it was.
It was a wonderful circus.
So many people were worried--
Was it as bad as I think it was?
Man, you killed.
That's what I was afraid of.
Sorry you didn't get
to do your act.
Shove... the sympathy,
showboat.
He fell on his butt
and everything.
He was just, like, dazed.
Is Malcolm a robot?
No, son, he's just smart.
Very, very,
very, very, very, very smart.
Hey, Malcolm...
how many fingers am I holding up?
[ Everyone Laughing ]
Shut up.
Analyze what I had for lunch.
[ Burps ]
Get off me, you moron.
You know what I don't understand?
You rattle off those numbers...
but you can't remember
to brush your teeth.
[ Hal ]
Hey, who's for Burger Barn?
[ Cheering ]
Burger Barn!
Burger Barn! Burger Barn!
www.tvsubtitles.net