- You have to change the diapers Jamie.
- I want of doing this!
Even you!
We had a robiæ you to change.
Mom and he said that the Jamie
the ³ ¹ ³ kn her diamond earring.
Whoever finds it
get a $ 20 reward.
Let Reese has a chance,
long time do not do the.
Damn!
Men chose not noticeably lived that the mother
no diamond earrings.
It smells like a ticket to the easy life!
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x08 "Feast Street"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
512x384 23.976fps 174.4 MB
Since five years, every year, spending
a week in a cottage by the lake.
This year's trip will fail the
and come back three days earlier.
I'm just saying that the do not ask for much.
Once a year,
one wants to œæ on the porch,
gapiæ on the flash
and jeœæ sandwiches on the container.
The problem is
Also cool the boys are gentle.
The would be useful to them
little interaction with the nature.
I blame video games.
/ What's going on?
- Sorry, but the street is closed.
- We live here, what's happening?
You live and you do not know?
- The annual Feast of the street.
- Annual?
Every year, from five years.
Part of Lloyd.
What's going on?
Hal.
Earlier wróciliœcie.
What is this?
Why did not we know about it?
Well ¿... wyszliœmy morning from home, our sun
the lights on, people began to rozmawiaæ.
- Is the higher of the spontaneously.
- According to the inscription, it is already five times.
Office of the Feast of the street dzacie
Every year when we do not have?
No I am responsible for the planning.
It's a whole committee that cares ...
I will not be boring you of.
Polly, so wróciliœmy earlier.
We can wpaœæ and podrzuciæ
Jamie for a few hours?
We have a street Feast
and we want to entertain.
Great, thanks.
Entertain! No one other than
I do not understand?
And the whole neighborhood hates us!
So much so that the devices are your ¹
big party when we do not have.
Malcolm, it's pretty nowoœæ ¿.
I'm surprised you are also organized.
You do not mind,
Also despise all of us are?
No. People in need
be on someone lived.
Nienawiœæ us of the whole or the surrounding area.
My mother is right, son. Groups
Find people are common enemies.
If not us,
This znaleŸliby someone else.
Probably like the minority œ.
Malcolm, you can not whole e
Martwiæ force other sentence.
Can you lubiæ, nienawidziæ,
or even something else,
and then you die.
- It had the rozweseliæ me?
- I do not know why you need it.
You're a teenager
the fete at the door.
You can zostaæ and striving saæ up as
you want, but we're going up entertain.
Come on, baby.
O my God e Parade mowers
Part, Otto.
What is this?
It's called "pokrywacz".
This artificial cow's rump.
This will allow us wydobyæ
precious seed of Bruno.
The cost me a fortune,
but here is the j are those kernels!
We can not simply go
wpuœciæ to cows?
No! Bruno is too rough for
my girls, one of the living in a bubble.
Most of them ashamed of milking.
- I shall be had to it do?
- It's not as bad as you think.
You only inputs to the center.
Bruno you will pay, offer your the
mêskoœæ and score semen.
It's a million times worse than I was thinking of!
Francis, there is nothing to be afraid of.
I wonder why they gave to the goggles?
/ They were students
/ Class Mrs. Michelson.
I speak on behalf of all
with maple and Jefferson.
The whole area is a large on
The nicer this time of year!
No, no.
Carry on.
And so already skoñczyliœmy.
Never thinking of em about us, as the most
hated people in the area.
Dewey, most of the people
force passes through unnoticed.
Their names are not in the newspapers,
the name of the rights does not come from them.
It is sufficient majority of people,
but I want more.
Hey!
This is not always the easy.
Will not have many
the friends, the bed c unpopular.
Someday with you
count, Reese!
What is it?
This kid toss of me
the excellent idea!
We do not do this often.
Do not walk on the area.
I'm on the right?
Do you remember what was to
jakieœ 20 years ago?
Issued a $ 70 EOE, ¿Eby wygraæ for
plush me the mascot worth the $ 3.
Especially does that have little hoops.
If I did not play to the effect of,
that it would not have learned.
Besides, I did not try the up
wygraæ plush mascot.
I used to try wygraæ you.
Oh, Hal.
I urge all of you to keep
peace and enjoy the sights.
/ Otherwise, they
/ And their children win the awful!
- Let me help you.
- You do not have robiæ.
No problem.
Willing to help.
Thank you, I the of of you.
Really?
Can I have something for you do?
I'm just saying that the children should not be
winiæ out by means of terrible parents.
If Saddam Hussein had the son ...
This may not the best example, but ...
Son, I do not worry about it
according to others.
You're a very caring young baby m³ Men Everywhere are.
Thank you. I'm glad
Also you know of em!
Hey!
What are you doing!
- Who was the man of the man!
- What, you mean?
Oh, my God also?
Robbed!
Fixed EOE here when robs us of!
Move the hose, and he Potrzebowo the help!
- The EOE'll help him!
- The barely copes!
And you believe the EOE, also his house!
No, he said that exactly.
That was a guess.
I have so much to g half!
You're in this family
out of the house, right?!
- Yes, but I'm not like them!
- You know what to do the EOE!
Something you think you're thinking of!
I just wanted to, Eby ¿³ someone like me!
Thank you, Jim.
Already for a few minutes will take place
5-eating contest of heavy bass!
/ Sponsored by the brothers Stavis.
Kie ³ ³ basa is added!
Eating contest of heavy bass?
I remember a certain the girl
the tail, which can flow zjeœæ dozen.
- That was a long time ago, Hal.
- Do not complainers, Lois.
A woman has reached the peak
¿capacity of the stomach of your age.
Sign up along with you.
I think that the failures you are afraid to book with me.
Hal, you are good in many
things, but it's the bass heavy.
Let's go.
This lizard,
or were no alligator.
Swims in our cesspool of the month.
Unless the feeds up heaps.
- Where is he?
- Hi all.
Do not be afraid. If I wanted to you solicitation,
is already on your wisielibyœcie my underwear.
Zebra ³ I was here,
¿Eby with Insert the offer.
- How the Offer, Reese?
- Good question, Dewey.
We all know,
Also torturing you for years.
Some of you May the
scar on the outside of a body
Some of you are damaging the
in places where you can not see.
Each one of you wants revenge.
And you know what?
You got that right.
Reese, revenge is œwietnie.
But how can we to do?
Another customs question, Dewey.
For $ 20 I ¿DEMU each of you the opportunity to
beat me by 30 seconds.
Reese is tempting the hand.
But how do we Know-the,
That after the way you have been accumulated,
- You will not get us tomorrow?
- That's the best part.
For all the time I'll be had of the complexities associated eye.
Registration will start to inevitably carry garage for I hour.
I will not tell you from where they took the æ money.
May we have your the purse.
Except you, Freddy.
Your journey is called ¿ny strip.
All set?
I think so.
How do you want her to play the?
How is "the play her?
You'll be sitting here the, wait the c
Bruno will be as many as had the fancy
and enter into an artificial debt.
And then can
move your hips a little,
can irritate it ¿niches tail.
I hope that you will support the fire.
It s important than 1800 kg.
As he runs out of patience,
This can uderzyæ from the destructive forces are.
I want ¿ki increases.
Yeah.
All right.
He could calm down the byœ?
Not only are sitting!
The whole world!
The way you treat the people themselves,
why it must be!
There is so much hatred!
What about pulling out of hair?
No, g words will obstruct the oniêta.
Too much of this do you think.
Let nienawiœæ will lead your body em.
How are we doing?
23 kids that you save the y
We have $ 460!
Oh, my God also?
Note that $ 20 must zostaæ
a taxi to the hospital.
I'm going to spend it all on the head of stupidity!
It's the best nation in the world!
Today we have a beautiful day
/ And start five brothers contest
/ Stavis in the eating heavy bass!
I will try to jeœæ
¿them without any interruptions.
The space between the heavy bass,
tell the body, also is full.
This year we are our old friends:
Louie, Jerry Jackson,
Lois and Hal
and Zesz the year-round winner,
Big Tony!
Players ready!
Will already right?
Already can handle.
Hey!
Œpieszy me up!
I'll be beaten for 15 minutes.
- How much do you want for it?
- What?
Buys each donut what you have.
Eat ¿d ¿aj hence the!
I'll give you this bag.
You do not need bags.
But I wanted to listen to the statue, and sings.
/ Well, ladies and gentlemen.
/ We lost Jerry and Jackson,
/ But Louie sixth of them already are!
/ But he's ahead the long service a road to
/ Hall and Big Tony, who eat the ninth such.
Ma ³ e upgrade,
Lois is a ³ ¿ate t the ninth!
You're awesome!
/ And we lost Louie'go.
/ It was the the only three!
- Unbelievable!
- What's going on?
Hal and Lois struggling
with the great Tony in the eb eb!
Wait a minute.
¿Is that the end for Lois?
No, I want to dock the bookmark sauerkraut.
He was a theft and helped to em.
No charges will bring,
we want the zapomnieæ.
And so you have to jechaæ to the police station,
fill the few papers.
Does not look like that the large bending of the Father
Just a little trash in the garage u
It is difficult to tell what exactly.
I can tell.
I have a photographic memory in the.
Replacing all
which was to the car.
Can we call and say later?
He was about nine boxes of.
35 to 30 to 50 centimeters.
Computer, two high-
quality color printers.
Signature machine, the machine
to the manufac virtual consoles, two bottles of ink.
The three reams of paper of high quality
with fluorescent in the windows security.
You can swim them in ¿
for counterfeiting money.
But you do not need
machines for manufac the virtual consoles.
Unless you also want to ...
podrabiaæ securities!
Oh, my God also?
It kryminaliœci!
And you know what's the saddest thing?
¹ ³ I take to heart
You have said that to me.
I tell the truth are c
Just a little of this has been about
/ Ladies and gentlemen,
/ This is amazing the sun!
Zesz the year-round record has been beaten!
/ Oh, my God also?
/ Big Tony bankruptcy on the table!
They were only Hal and Lois!
You're going down, baby!
We'll see, honey.
No good. You all know the rule y
Each is 30 seconds.
Ban items
that can pos Insert is used for weapon.
Okay, see if it is ready.
Reese zaczynaæ time.
This is your first anonymous customer!
Bobby Markovitch.
Not so much!
Hurt my brother!
Ok, your time is up the the!
Hey!
Reese! What are you doing?
And who is this?!
Jakiœ kid, I have found it on the street.
- Can not remember the name.
- Chad.
Chad.
'Scuse me, the ope ch.
How can the so-bla me hello!
You're my brother!
And my partner!
And it pays the ignition EOE!
For him!
/ Johnny Mathis - "Chances Are"
/ These are the chances
/ I is continuously g the s smile stupidly up
/ At,
/ When you show up
/ It seems to me that also makes you think,
/ Also I'm in love with you
Mine were 2 hours and nothing happens.
Wypuœæ him of the tablespoon.
Hey, Listen to this. I should
a greased cow's pheromones.
It should lead to lower the u,
No wonder, also had no desire to.
I saw the EOE bottle of pheromones?
/ It seems to me that
/ Also seems
/ Awfully good
/ This day elapsed ¹ ³
/ Us to eat the heavy bass.
/ Hal and Lois Keep clear the
/ Up to the end of 21
/ It's an amazing show!
Two great competitors
pushing each other to a better result.
What's going on?
Oh, my God also?
Are cheering for a family of mine!
With the bad and g play the fool
reason, but the cheer!
It's incredible.
/ It was the last of the heavy bass
/ And is on a plate Hall!
The title of his will, if the will eat her.
Not mogliœmy wyobraziæ
each such is finished.
How mogliœmy have
them so the are of the opinion?
They are good, good people.
Strange is not nienawidziæ
already Lois and Hal.
Œwietnie, also live here.
This is the great and the area.
I'm sorry, also not helped to em
ha, the ace in the fifth reflect the property the night.
Finally Œciszyli music?
Wait ... that you called on EOE
The police are at my party?!
Do not invite Did you come to me
on his the party?
Do not push it.
You're such a large baby?
Do not call him a kid!
At least you do not have it prosiæ
about mowing the lawn every two weeks!
From what I know,
he mows your lawn!
Not so important
speak to her!
- To hell and with you!
Honey, there is no trace
the great eats ¿d ¿alni.
That's okay, honey.
The position of the ê here on the road.
Mama mia ³ yet're right.
Robiliœmy aperture UGE are neighbors
for all these years.
Reese, you will help me can fill with
This inflatable house?
No, I will close the jakiegoœ
Devil dog m³ liquid.
www.tvsubtitles.net