Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 174.3 MB
- Oh no! Parents are kill us!
- I know what to do.
"Wynoœcie out of our area,
hate you. "
It Millers, The Andersons,
Or Thomas Cooper.
It Hacketowie. Suggest the that the it
restore the cat to life!
We'll see how you feel the,
when the tide of the avoided them tit for tat.
/ I'm gonna get a car.
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x14 "Malcolm's dating the family"
Every other Thursday, we eat supper
at the pizzeria with Luigi.
It was only two nights a month,
where p is not the crying at bedtime.
This already fairly, stop!
We fight for the wins.
Is not that great of an?
Every 14 days magically
turns into a family of szczêœliw.
And here's the reason.
Pizza with Luigi is so good,
Also not only brings out the people,
g the hidden Eboko good
but immediately
creates the not completely new.
Another great of an experience
culinary, Alfredo.
Doctor's orders.
Alfredo, you still have a tip.
Excuse me, what is
"DZO" at the bottom?
This add-on for handling the UGE.
Operating supplement UGE!
What add-on for handling the UGE?
We add 15% for maintain, many
person is trying to cheat the waiters.
We are doing so for years.
Forced into semi-paying tip
without notice!
So long double semi-aciliœmy
tip, do not know about the c.
Here is the information.
This little chit.
That you want to give a reason!
Oh, no. Will row as
in a shoe shop, or like in a circus?
I think that bad, as
in store, "all the $ 5."
Car on fire? I think
s I heard the sirens, you better let's go.
Umieœciliœcie were no stamp, no one
it does not read and are justified theft!
Where is the manager?!
I want rozmawiaæ the manager!
/ Do not look at me!
Better not show up
here for a while, Manalo.
And then I became a half-hour
parking lot, the dissuasive c cars.
My mom is horrible!
My mom ... call of a drunk ...
on my birthday ...
¿¿So that I yczyæ money.
Sorry, Stevie.
I should not narzekaæ.
Escape your mom is inexcusable.
But you know what? Real
friends will leave the.
Hey, Angela!
Angela Pozefsky.
³ It is very pretty.
I think I have a chance with her.
From some reason
with anyone not dating.
Can be so without the pretty,
It also deters other guests.
I do not mind.
Part, Malcolm.
Part, Angela, well, you also
with the apparatus of em. I've been thinking of em.
Want zaprosiæ me on a date?
I first wanted to something pomamrotaæ
a few minutes, but ... Yes.
Want AEOI the spring dance?
OszczêdŸ the angle of troubles.
Do not you want with me outputs.
Because before you go out with me,
My family needs you accept your.
What not to do without making the
œledztwa giant.
So odpuœæ now and let
I umrzeæ in loneliness.
Worried about your family ¹ ¹?
I do not mind.
Yeah? My family is
extremely burdensome the longer possible,
bossy, control and humiliate the whole the whole.
You're talking to a guy with proper.
Francis, explore Jordan
your new assistant.
- My what?
- Thank you for the background a chance.
Sure.
Can you forgive us?
- You do not need an assistant.
- But boy the boy needs a job.
And all the other posts are
already doubly occupied.
Please, Francis, for sure
jakieœ find him busy.
- Okay, I'll try.
- Thank you, Francis.
I know that I employ too many
employees and that is the problem.
But heal.
Come to this for three psychiatrists.
I'm starting zapominaæ,
tastes like pizza with Luigi.
He says the em ¿ebyœ not we the teeth.
Hello?
Yes, it's me.
Really? Really?!
Yes!
Call of the owner pizzeria
¿Eby przeprosiæ mom.
Clothe jacket!
Lois! God pizza
sent from the ear to our prayers!
Hello?
Hi, says Lawrence Cabrusi,
of the owner Luigi.
S ³ ³ I heard what happened at the
and I wanted to personally przeprosiæ.
For what exactly do you want przeprosiæ?
The way you treated
You are in Zesz were Thursday.
There is no excuse,
awful you feel about it.
I'm on it's the will hear a.
I wonder why two weeks
Aje were you an apology.
Sorry. He was on a trip I
in Europe and did not even unpack the em.
The most important is that the lady
families are a valuable customer
and really want you back.
Apologies were exceeded my expectations.
On the refunds as we can liczyæ?
/ What?
/ Add up the am that the flow aciliœmy
/ $ 300 over the years.
Mr. sends the check, or give as the discount œ tablespoon?
We can not Daae your refund.
We do not have such funds.
If you become a day trip
to Europe, is 5% of the price,
would suffice for the zadoœæuczynienie
This fools the customer!
There is no God pizza.
For sure you will never be
jeœæ in a pizzeria with Luigi.
At least we have the brightness.
Ok, that he wanted to EOE.
Do not tell me you also will not warn the am.
It's all right, I'm ...
This is my mom, my dad,
My grandmother, aunt Leila
Synalar Aunt, Uncle Zach,
Nick, Max and Alexandra.
The rest is in the basement.
This is Malcolm.
Welcome, sit, sit.
- So, you want the poœlubiæ my daughter.
- What?
I can not of themselves oprzeæ.
I'm sorry that the need for this przechodziæ,
but it is very protecting of the Angel.
We have dowiedzieæ,
What are you boys of Caucasian teenage boy.
Well, ... I'm normal.
Walking with the Angel to school y
I have good grades, for 3 days
a week I work in the shop have.
I have healthy teeth.
I have all the graft.
Religiously I would name the
szczêœliwym agnostic.
I think that the main g filizoficzne question ...
We can is the crap!
He's a genius.
It's the smarter najm
in the entire school, and it's definitely.
Really? Genius?
Say something m³ drego.
Inflation writing her cosmology.
This theory g of the axis that the universe
therefore it is a homogeneous,
because just after the Big Bang,
to the short period of rapid
than normal expansion.
I hope that the mention of the role of
Scalar fields in the concept of symmetry breaking.
Not bragging, but
I worked on it someday.
Please!
Until the discovery of the Higgs field,
it must be clean speculation.
Yes, dear.
Those women.
It fits me.
You fit?
- Grandma?
- Yeah.
I adore you!
Come on, let's see if the baby boy
your age can zjeœæ.
Later we'll be sing along. Be warned,
I have a few œwietnych soloists.
How about your story are the Middle Ages?
Well, how's the money.
Malcolm is on my team!
- Lump of Sugar, as you like.
- Thank you, Jordan.
- Francis.
- Part, honey.
/ W is precisely to ring and my mom.
He was a worried also not been sent from the EOE its
Thank You Cards for Bo ¿Christmas.
And the height of the I j yesterday.
Sent from the master of the tasteful card
with the manufac embossed flower inside.
- I think I deserve an apology.
- It's good.
Please pozwoliæ.
/ Hal, ch ³ boys, dinner!
What is this?
It's a family night fiesta!
He was am in the Mary Archie.
I have 4 types of enchiladas, beef of these
and chicken taco and a tray piero ¿NEB.
Malcolm!
No, ¿Are you kidding?
Œwietnie I really enjoy the.
Wednesday? Yes, definitely.
Okay, part.
- Who was to?
- Angela's dad.
What's going on?
It is not fun?
You're right. We do not need
music, ... We chips.
The most important that the time we spend together.
So, let's talk.
Who are the good stories?
- Yesterday my mother and lost his mind.
- Reese!
A lot was to the west, I know that the
is like, so ... what's the problem?
Mom, you do not byœ of a,
do not copy Luigi.
Pizzeria Luigi is the core.
It's not the food that matters.
What matters is that the sit here together
and we enjoy each other's company!
If you believe that, then why
Did you come to buy Mexican ¿Arcie?
Good! Mexican ¿Arcie
l the lands in œmieciach.
No, I'm not Copernicus.
Isolate the EOE something,
Then what about you kill the?
No, I'm not odowsk Sk ³ ¹-Curie.
It œwietnie.
When we play at home, then
we use the only cartoon characters.
The cartoons that we saw that day.
Approx. Do you believe
into force of continuity after me?
No, I'm Cher.
- Upiekliœcie cake?
- The nuts as you like.
Did you come to do it for me?
It's beautiful!
It's lovely.
I love to walk perfectly well with the Angel.
Where is Angela?
Gone through the wheel and the cup as the ¿œ hour ago.
Approx.
- Smaller are better, right?
- The large o Thank you.
I do not have a very open the paragraph.
What does Did you come, Mom?
Ripped off of us 15% add-on
Operating for over three years UGE!
Well follow boycott the c
them, are not you think?
I do not know, I think we all suffer from the over
something that you just what y depends
I do not know about you
rings, Francis.
³ Dhabi would you give me support
in a case in which I have the obvious're right!
Can you blame me!
You know what ...
If you're so sure,
why do you want, you ¿ebym of support?
J We are, sir.
Not stop
to win, Jordan.
Again, I have the hair in his ears.
I was thinking of that the already not
Feel the smell.
Mom goes back for two hours.
We have plenty of time to eat
and destruction of evidence.
But ... wyjaœnijmy yourself something.
What we do is not all right!
It is morally reprehensible for each time
possible way! We should wstydziæ up!
Yes, yes, yes,
hate each other.
Whatever happens,
that we're in this together.
- Where's Malcolm?
- From the inn the family.
So for us.
I do not believe how much zjedliœmy.
I do not believe how well the flavor of o
That was a taste of the, son.
Sticky, delicious with the Father
I know that I must zamaskowaæ breath
but by eating mints Suggest,
causes gagging.
We all have.
Part, all I have supper!
He was am in the Pizza Connection.
Had to am przejechaæ an entire city,
but to the pm you d is used for something of my ego.
I know how difficult it is to deal Luigi
and large to me for your support.
In these klopsikach is cheese.
I have never met the people I
so fascinated
The Copenhagen interpretation of the
quantum mechanics.
I was thinking of that the grandmother hit someone.
Œwietnie bawiliœmy yesterday.
I watch the can of em ... Dad burns the ...
your music œlubny.
- Part Malcolm.
- Part of Sarah.
Wanted to pm you zaprosiæ
the Spring Dance.
- I know that this late stage ...
- Wow! With the pleasure.
- Super! So to Friday?
- To Friday.
It is wonderful,
when she invite ...
Angela.
I completely forgot! Hell,
I have two dances dating for Spring!
This, as in the old section jakiœ ...
Well, each show.
But this whole quite interesting trades challenge.
Ergil fairly well describe the
attracting strength up cousins.
As long as you do not do the greedy
and became the prince.
Stevie, you me at all you are listening to?
Two girls ... 2 families ...
I do not have ... Two lungs!
What does this have to do with ..
People P. .. your fluke ...
Do not ... dziwad be the em!
Just ... choose!
Yes, well.
Ok, it is 19:35 ... 5 minutes
will take you access to Luigi.
Minute will order pizza
so they should indicate flow j are at 19:56.
Mom sends the store at 19:50
and destroy the evidence
before its return.
Ignition someday the avoided that.
And it is high.
Yeah.
But today the avoided ignition.
Whatever happens, it's a conspiracy
I was very close to you ¿y ³ a
- In addition to Malcolm and Jamie.
- They are different. Now go!
Part, honey, what are you doing?
These are the keys?
I'm going to Luigi.
What!
Why would the want you to do?!
I give up.
It takes too long.
I'll go, I'll go up to the cashier
and post the pie for the good of the family.
- Over my dead body!
- What?
You can not now poddaæ!
I was thinking of, that we are a team of em!
Hal, we were wonderfully
supporting the old, but fairly so.
Women, who love the ever
says "fairly it"!
A woman who does not love the close-up ¿s
to this place by the hour!
We believe in you, Lois!
You have to continue fighting |!
Thank you, you're right, I will not give up!
Malcolm!
WchodŸ! WchodŸ!
Look who came of!
Angela, came the boy of your package!
Spread over ¿y ³ am back board.
We can odegraæ battle
Lepanto olives and celery.
I can not zostaæ.
On Saturday, you have to connect the letter with the Angel.
In the town the Taiwanese acrobats bed.
I do not think I can.
So You can store the Connect to us on
films the night and do not take rejection.
I can not.
Why?
What happened on?
Breaks up with me ...
and I do not mind.
There we talked for two weeks.
What does Did you come?
No, it's all right.
The breaking up with her?
Just like that?
Yeah, ... is very difficult.
My life is now complicated
And we need the space.
But I ¿ebyœmy were friends of me.
Friends of the me ...
It's not you, it's me. The last few
week was to œwietnych, but ...
Please do not.
No, really.
You know what kind we are great?
Angela will differ with a lot of spotykaæ
ch better than me the pack ...
You treat us condescendingly.
The Ides already.
Will be widywaæ?
We both know that the not the way it operates a
This is the only butter le ¿s on
I toœcie as a block.
It is ... so done,
how Jordan is doing.
- Disseminated?
- Yeah!
Francis, it must skoñczyæ.
Like me were the flowers, the sermons of it EoE
I send, and the line was to me the very y
But changes to the helpless infant.
If it was not for Jordan yesterday
in the men's room, then you are still sitting there the byœ.
Domyœli of what I'd be zrobiæ.
No, not true.
You're right. Release him.
That would be best.
Jordan, we porozmawiaæ.
- It's about ..
- You have to release me.
Well, yeah. I. ..
I feel terrible, but you can not me
stop, even though the do well.
Yeah.
I ...
Sorry.
Of course, also like that.
But I wrote a wonderful EOE were the months the list of commands,
and I and the Shift of I thank you, for
basket of muffins which I donated to the EOE.
There was the too expensive,
but I appreciate the gesture em.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye.
Now you need to œcisn æ ¹.
ChodŸcie, chodŸcie, sit down.
It is a pity that the Malcolm is
at the dance, miss it.
What is it?
He was am ready to surrender
in the case of Luigi,
but your dad inspired the
me into action.
Today I'd like to call the
"Clyde on your side."
Who?
This reporter from the channel of the fifth.
Y do whole program of Luigi.
Is to be on the air at 22:20 ...
Already season.
It may look like the friendly Daae on the pizza,
but thanks to our
informatorce odkryliœmy,
Also visit the dive
can clean out your wallet.
Informant, it's me.
It turned out,
Also secretly restaurant
bear 15% of the fees for handling the UGE
for each account.
I want, ¿Eby was to clear this
The case does not reflect the Italians,
where most of the decent,
¿you are hard working Americans months.
But before the visit of swindlers
with Luigi, here is a little advice:
przemyœlcie that really
przyjœæ want here.
/ Who is a victim of this scam?
Retirees with fixed income white.
Local teens at the dance.
/ And, of course, suffer most are ...
Oh, my God also?
Traitor!
How can I trust that the zdradziæ
family, especially you, Lois.
- He does not know what you're fighting!
- The traitor!
See how the clogging pizza in place,
when we we had to
chowaæ in the garage at?
What?
All right. He left it to black em the hour.
Tata naœladuje your behavior
the toilet for 5 minutes.
I'll give you a recording,
if we make the ad layout.
It turned out that the rupture
with the Angel was to the terrible b edema.
It is sad. Sometimes you do not know
what you have until it's gone.
- Malcolm?
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
He was em around,
Think of I, also can e ..
Œwietnie appearance date.
It's very awkward.
So ... I Count ... Sandwich.
www.tvsubtitles.net