Honey, I'm fairly for today.
Let's go break loose, OK?
- Wait, We bought 10 gifts.
/ - Yeah.
Why are 11 parcels?
Oh, my God also?
Zorientowalibyœmy up
before sending it, right?
Yes, absolutely.
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x07 "Christmas Tree"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 174.4 MB
Do not move.
- The EOE Dhabi him?
- What killed the em?
S been three weeks to the world of t
Reese refrain from
Dewey beating their end.
Guess what's happened?
I got the two weeks of compulsory
free of paid holiday.
What?
Thanks to the opotom k of the government demos sent from ali
all the house until the new year.
Myœlimy, also thanks to this management board will
Such use alone niszczyæ documents.
2 weeks without pay
and that before œwiêtami!
It means that any gifts.
December 2: refused to eat
smarkami sandwiches.
I know that it of a season, but I have a plan thanks,
who earn sufficient that money.
- I'll be sold the Christmas tree.
- What?
In college, every year I sold the
Christmas with the co-tenant, Victor.
- The am thinking that the sell of illegal decoders.
- ¯ Eby to Buy for a Christmas tree.
Accumulated from the coconuts!
Already I talked with the provider.
Constant us on 130 trees
at $ 15 apiece.
And Ed's office, I made it possible for free
korzystaæ with his business of the Company.
Really?
If we'll be salesman them at $ 20 per meter,
it comes out on average $ 45 per tree.
- Lois, we can zarobiæ to clean $ 2600.
- If you think that the succeed?
Reese and I have a little bit of of the loaded box.
How do we get it, you buy
200 trees and earn $ 4,000.
- In the deposit of byœ s in it are your money?
- Sure.
I've had the zainwestowaæ in the interest of the
proposed to me in e-mails of Nigerian generals.
- But what the hell, family more important!
- Really?
Do you want to lead interest
your old man?
Never thinking of I,
Also it will be possible.
- Dad ...
- When I was a kid was to ...
b I begged her Tate
of common interest, a lot of times.
But he never answered by the intercom.
And now you want zrobiæ deal with me!
It will be green grocer grocery ¿!
You know, Dewey,
you have $ 20 in your œwince.
I think they already enough, Mom.
No good.
¿These come in!
Oddly will spêdziæ
Public holidays without our families.
I know, I feel ... wonderful!
As if the whole ugliness and hustle of k
related are associated with the y disappear œwiêtami
My family! Finally
they arrived, straight from Stuttgart!
"Do not pack warm clothes small,
the desert is hot as. "
I defrosted the the ass!
Do not blame me! I have two children,
You do not need a third!
Calm down. We come.
Enjoy.
I have forgotten my! Everything has
be perfect with Gretchen.
Podnoœ not vote at Gretchen!
Each who is not an alcoholic,
ck accused of perfectionism!
/ Hal and Sons.
/ Christmas.
Hal and Sons.
So you are ¿, Jamie.
I know that it is only badziewny,
wooden sign, but ...
Ch of boys, I want to know ¿ebyœcie,
Also is the best day of my life ¿.
I'm so szczêœliwy
and proud of each of you.
And I want to be ensured that this is not an zawalicie.
We will have many wonderful of small
shared memories,
until the worst zawierzycie
instincts and you do not play the fool of czegoœ g.
I love you
and I want to continue you kochaæ.
Dad, do not worry.
We'll be fine.
Summarize the c our expenses, we go
to your sell the c 67 Christmas trees.
- Sell more Christmas tree number 1
- What are these tools?
Will show the guys.
These are for making trees.
The first five of the Circular
cut off the bottom inch of the trunk.
Then the gun,
sticks to nails to stand ...
Once again, I'm proud of you
straciæ and I do not want that feeling.
/ Sleigh full AD savings!
I do not know why not
Let me help you, Lois?
- Craig, I do not want anything done ebyœ ¿³.
- Why not?
'Cause every time when you have
contact with me or my family ¹ ¹,
it meets you something terrible.
- Can not cope with the guilt again.
- I do not know what you're saying?
¿No joking, if not us,
that are still being had the byœ your teeth,
byœ not afraid of the fans on the ceiling.
Your car would not be the full tion of bees.
Coincidence.
Craig, with the break of EOE feet,
c search for the phone number for me.
Please, Lois, are Public holidays.
Here you go. You can take
from the beard of Santa ajowi.
Thank you.
I wanted to tell,
I'm also surprised.
- Ok, You can store jechaæ.
/ - Sir, it's dead tree is not?
Of course, also not.
Upewniliœmy sure that the world also œciêto trees,
were in immediately to the ground, ¿Eby had were large on the water.
Your tree is suspended
nor in the abyss, between life ¿and death.
Hold the c until you open presents.
How many trees we sold?
- 15
- 15?
We are not even close to 67
I do not understand this!
We are a good location,
Use the correct tree.
- Excuse me, after how many Christmas trees?
- $ 20 per meter.
- Oh.
- What?
Churches of St. Make the corner,
sells for $ 17,
but there is a long service line,
Think of So I'll try also with you.
Can you believe that the churches of the snowdrop us?
I have never offered a mass for half-price!
Why we have not lowered prices we aim?
For example, for $ 16.
Then earn on average $ 31
per tree and a total of $ 3457.
Wyszlibyœmy to its original ... wait ...
tree number 91
- Tree 91?
- Tree 91
Sir!
/ Hal and Sons.
/ Christmas. $ 16 per meter.
- Come with me to the.
- We have a very nice ... the
Traditionally Wrestling tree on the roof.
Traditionally given to
tip to the one who fixed.
That was a tree number ... 79!
We are very close.
Ch of boys, I love you all.
But this kid ...
It's just a light bite.
He'll be fine?
Absolutely.
But I need injections to wœciekliznê.
- Injections?
- 5 uk the UAE in the stomach.
I had of them a few years
I take a bite of this skunk.
When they put the first
10 centimeters ¹ ê needle in my belly,
This sensitive em like I got shot.
How to cut the gnêli the latest,
This le ¿³ em and on the floor
, keeping the legs up from the chair and
and to cry the c, like a child!
The Navy taught us
znosiæ as pain, but ...
not as many as that.
Always you can with Grip the
Squirrel and zanieœæ to the vet.
How will not have a wœcieklizny,
This will avoid injections.
No, I'll take the injections,
Lois otherwise, proves his thesis are!
Craig, Listen to me.
I promise you.
In the background are catching a squirrel, I'll take to the vet
and to prove that there is no wœcieklizny.
¯ ¹ ³ ebyœ avoid these injections!
Already we will never suffer the
through it, also do you know me?
EOE understandable?
- You're standing on my foot.
- I'm sorry.
- You are still the OC of K ¹?
- Yes, it's a fascinating hands.
I had the same as the angle of the canvas
a million times in my ¹ I ¹.
For a while she will say:
"Do not take that tone with me."
And he will krzyczeæ.
Now the father tries to reconcile them.
And he is for this to get it.
/ It will be good ..
Whose involvement in the k œ the canvas,
¿Eby rozdrapaæ old wounds.
This is a primitive version of my family.
- Take a step to the left.
- Why?
Weirdly.
Ok, It has to be $ 7 the rest, right?
One, two and piea.
Larger denominations were the hide I was there,
where no peering the bottom!
Let me help you with that.
Ok, this tree number 89, the boys ch.
Already I feel the end!
It forces you try owaæ up
b blessed with the churches of the awionym I?
- What are you he said?
- We are the St. Mark around the corner.
Sell ??cheaper than us
and we do not like it.
So we want ebyœ ¿ceased.
You shut off your tablespoon, is working
and odejœæ .. immediately.
During this period, Holy,
Daae savior better what he wants.
As if you did not know,
then you have to deal with a wicked ¿MANAGING pagans.
Declare your stories elsewhere.
We'll give you 20 minutes to clean up the cheap.
Then we take
matters into your hands on our own.
- What is the laugh of znaczyæ?
- Do not worry, Dad.
This accounting hose, which can do?
Get in the car
and close the door!
Do you jakieœ change?
Hey, Panther!
Is it looks as infection ¿up?
I'm sorry, it's my Christmas tree.
Already her the mark of I,
if you know what I mean.
Wait a minute! No!
What the hell are you doing?
- Father McCluskey sends the greeting.
- What are you talking about?
Mentioned at the dinner, ¿ebyœmy
came here dzieliæ the spirit world t
S of a cute baby!
Would you like some homemade candy?
/ Dad, I'm leaving all the.
Whatever you give of the churches,
we will double it!
You can double the eternal salvation?
- Yes, I can.
- You're funny.
Selling Christmas trees?
These ¿³ em someday sell Christmas trees.
- So what?
- What do you think?
No one will give us rozstawiæ trees.
Unbelievable! We thought that the
cemetery will be a good place?
Can we'll be salesman
you straight from the bulb?
You would have to take into account the æ
fuel price. 2 km per liter of fuel ...
Malcolm, let ¹ æ genius rest.
We are so close.
89 trees!
Only two of the lack of profit.
Story of my life!
Not important what they do,
not important how hard you try, ...
always miss two trees.
We should salesman
them with us in the yard.
Reese is a serious issue ny, you can ...
Oh, my God also?
It was not of the pole of g.
Reese, my father continuity to cause
Also your brain operates like a laser!
Give him a hat.
People, somewhere in the store is a squirrel.
It is agile, elusive
and probably has wœciekliznê.
But her are from the apiemy!
We have to.
I have the feeling of that, Lois.
Too long is quiet.
It has something planowaæ.
So, why bring the am meal of the Company.
- Thanks for your help, the boys ch.
- None problem.
Our previous job quickly
and the end, so we have free time.
So let's get started!
/ Closed.
/ The Harry Simeone Chorale
/ "The Little Drummer Boy"
/ They told us przyjœæ,
/ Pa rum pum pum pum
/ View the new-born King,
/ Przynieœliœmy our best gifts
/ Pa rum pum pum pum
/ ¯ Eby with Insert the king of them ...
We are all wonderful!
Excuse me, also I ate the
your food from the refrigerator.
You're there.
I know you're there.
Directed to cash!
/ I j are!
Do not let it get away!
There it is!
PREVIOUS!
Headed out the door!
It is believed that ajcie has looked killer!
And a nice fluffy tail.
Checkmate!
And three others.
Feliz Navidad. (Spanish Cheerful the world ¹ s t)
So at $ 12 per meter,
we make the tree ...?
- 112
- 112, the tree of the profits!
- Repeat with me, baby the boys.
- Hal.
- Part, Phil, cheerful of small world.
What you're doing that.
You do not have permission.
Take the Christmas tree in the courtyard.
Phil, please ...
I know it is unusual of a situation,
but I'm in trouble.
I have been released
and I have no money.
Come on, are Public holidays!
I do not care! You do not suffer
and that will not change.
Phil, can we take one
tree. On the house.
- Please.
- You give it to me?
- Even I will carry, as you wish.
- No, no, that's enough.
- So, zrozumieliœmy it?
- Yes, we have an agreement.
You zabraæ hence the the tree.
Dostaliœmy complaints
and do not have permission.
I have too much of the garbage containers.
It will be fine, right.
He can not narzekaæ!
I bribed him of the Christmas tree!
You can not lead interest
the yard without permission.
The ladies at the adzo, in the of We have paid close
it our all the money.
We lack a single tree
the output to zero.
Only here please.
One tree.
Please pozwoliæ me
sprzedaæ one tree.
- Do you have a tree?
- Pass.
It's you!
Never would I of this show dogs.
And from where they had the high school to the temptation.
- Is that your son?
- It depends on whom you have decided carefully son.
You have half an hour for the equipment tniêcie
each tree in the yard.
But we lost you the bulb.
We have no where to Daae.
It's not my problem.
Get rid of them,
Public holidays or you will spend in the cell.
I can not stand it!
Screams, shouts!
- I'm starting ... têskniæ behind the house.
- I am the ¿.
My mom's the catch as well as the Tate's throat o
I renounce all of you ...
all!
Never thinking of em, I'll be also
ashamed of being German.
See? All disappeared the y
Now are you happy?
I remember. I'll be the patrol
t the street every 15 minutes.
Cheerful the world ¹ s t
I want, ¿³ ebyœ redeem my share.
Dewey, a temporary failure.
If so carefully ck,
the redemption of my participation.
- That's it, Dad.
- End?
We lack a single tree!
Dad, you do not have the light bulb,
we can not u Insert the lawn.
The cops are watching us.
Admit it, przegraliœmy!
So, let a little
reality you stop?
The only way I succeeded in what I
przejœæ through my crappy force
without losing the remnants of one's own
value of denial.
If I give up pokonaæ one of failure,
This would end the one child.
You are you still count on a miracle.
And if a miracle does not appear
on Public holidays, when?
You see! Here it is!
Our world the festive miracle, I knew of!
Part, my kid
he found that the cat is yours?
- No, I want to Buy a Christmas tree for $ 10?
- No, I already have a Christmas tree.
I need your help.
In precisely the I convince my children,
¿¿S life is worth something.
If you go, without giving me $ 10
the future of their will not be worth anything!
Desperately I must nauczyæ their
perseveres occur. And you, you can help me.
- No. I think that e ..
- Wylie also those shoes!
I saw the EOE, ¿Eby someone
This will of, because I do not.
- It must be worth $ 10. Even ...
- Please, wey the money.
Wynieœ, as far as possible on the pavement.
Interests with you przyjemnoœæ itself!
You see what's happening,
When he believes. Zarobiliœmy!
Yeah!
I'll take a frame from the hamster Dewey.
Squirrel chew through the crate o
They have to j the zabiæ, ¿Eby dowiedzieæ
whether a wœciekliznê?
Want injections?
Wait for me in heaven.
Oh, my God also?
/ - Honey, is that you?
- What's going on?
Good wieœci.
We succeeded in up! Zarobiliœmy.
Really?
How much?
The numbers are not important, but profit is profit!
- Look, a squirrel.
- What?
He's getting away!
Squirrel ... fled a
Craig, ... of the apiemy j are!
The chip is as follows:
this time, $ 10 on your head and one
item from the store pharmacy.
This time it will be more difficult.
We are on the ground.
- Let's go.
- It is believed that ajcie.
Thank you, also You attempted spêdziæ
Public holidays with my family ¹ ¹.
Next year we'll go to mine.
In a ³ ¿eñstwie about compromise.
/ It is believed that ck, also is dirty?
/ It is dirty!
/ You're a courageous on,
/ When I do not have the the loaded leg.
- Are having a good time, we should connect to the.
- Let's do it.
I'm worried about Gretchen and Otto.
I hope that I will not worsen the case.
Thank you for be invited. Nice to
is be with the families that get along.
You really freaking out in Public holidays.
The Trinity are even in the bathroom!
Compared to previous
the trip were quite nieŸle whole.
Nothing will burn the o, one
will not come to the jail and zarobiliœmy.
www.tvsubtitles.net