Ch the boys! I have found the beer,
which schowaliœcie in the garage u!
After all these discussions,
continue thinkers that the drinking is cool!
There it is!
Sit down and look!
Look at me!
I'm a cool dude!
Everyone likes my style.
I am most twisted
guy all twisted.
I love you so much, the boys ch ...
Przytuliæ you?
The busiest him a little to find the beer.
Yes, but it's worth was to czekaæ.
/ Crazy world Malcolm
/ 5x12 - Softball
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Guess what!
Again, I got the increase tablespoon!
Mr. de Silvio he said,
Also when cleaning meat grinding machine
vomits less than anyone else.
Looks as it
Also czyjaœ career develops.
My company can even
the crap to exist.
What he said Nat?
Usually well versed in these matters.
Nate fabricated of his are in death
and fled the country.
True, also will do the Jamie?
He'll do it the ...
Take a look! Is that-looking
idler your hands?
- See all the prints?
- What are you doing here?
- This morning, on the phone,
Did you come said that the I was to lazy!
Look at my hands and admit
Also confuses Did you come up!
Again, biting your nails?
- Przeproœ!
- I will not apologize for telling the truth.
And precisely because I spend the
eight hours venom of the c here!
To show this to you how far you are
able to move over the æ æ to avoid the apology!
I can not uwierzyæ as twisted
is your system of values!
S ³ I'm listening? Part, honey.
Szczêœliwej anniversary.
No I am not yet on the road,
precisely in the collection.
All right.
See? Francis behavior
it is just sad.
I mean for him ...
For us it's fairly entertaining.
Come on, Malcolm. AEOI's time to work!
Do not forget about the shoes for a change!
All right. I can zjeœæ
my cake in the car?
I ate them in the car, regardless of the fact
and he said that a "yes" or "no."
This hose of Amorous, viewing the Daae Francis
the semi-lying coat with this before I got the.
- How jakiœ puppy.
- Yes, it's terrible how she manipulated him.
Oh, I savor the the vanilla!
Why are people doing something like this?
- There is a przyjemnoœæ of clandestine
g of controlling people upszych from you.
You know what's cool about the Francis?
How to invent all of these crazy things.
Yes, it was to brilliant.
Yes, I wish that the now
nothing like that happens.
With the exception of the omowiska Kopelman.
- You mean that those frightening cymi dogs?
Do you remember how Francis has reached the
semi-ot of the omowiska
and return of the eleven
risers?
If only someone else had the
courage, ¿Eby of doing this ...
By "someone" I had in mind of you.
- Are you serious?
The busiest for me four hours,
znaleŸæ to the old spelling test.
Three plus!
Is lazy getting the Trojans with a plus?
No!
I must ruszaæ back ...
About the mom coming back?
After a tenth of that.
Better I will meet the ...
I'm just saying that the the yellow and pink ¿those of these
do not you solve the UK according dates.
There will be no later
Such use their znaleŸæ.
Yes, I know that the studying
You'll want the mieszkaæ dorm
but as an easily distracted.
Over the last three years continuously at
criticize all of my decisions.
You fall in the continuity.
We'll take a break.
Look, already a half of work for us!
Are not you glad that the odpuœci of the EOE
POJO to the toilet?
Malcolm! Do you want to save
the second day ¿softball?
This is an opportunity to view the
old gold satin M ³ in action.
And each year, I take one
The yellow todzioba under my wing a
I already have under control.
When you sign up you will not have the
przyjœæ early weekend shift.
My mom works then.
You sign up!
- Part, Lois. It records the second day ¿?
- I do not need. This year, I'm a coach.
- Really?
- Yes. Stu had this take care of the æ,
but it ¿birth to him and
and all the damn Sundays.
Malcolm, you're in the other ¿flows!
I just can not get away from you, right?
/ Note all the staff!
/ Immediately after the funeral
/ District manager Kelsey'a
/ All windows above the third
/ Floors are closed bed. "
/ - This is the basic semi-pays?
Dental care provided?
Sounds nieŸle ...
Where are leading the call?
Thanks, I owe you.
So three days before the
I go to the interview.
Nick will not have a problem
finding another job.
S is used to overload the NAVY SEALS!
Of course, the ethical when looking
You can nazwaæ to the theft.
But look at the hip-hop!
Use the sail are still being the same samples,
and this is art or not theft?
Hal, you're family.
The Ides of conversation in the background.
I must zdecydowaæ or uderzaæ stick to the left,
to speed up the top five of the Company,
or biae bottom so that have the advantage
on their runners.
Please! Twenty year-install puzzle
scale models and writing sproœnych Haiku!
Lazy people are doing so?
I do not think.
That proves you're a me
an apology!
Francis, it all shows
Also have a compulsive obsession.
K ³ ³ k amstwa interspersed amstwami!
Your house of cards will collapse!
Are still being here?
I Piamie he said, also leaving for the this morning.
Mom, but I can not joined the The five
the second day ¿softball.
Before you say that your
I have reason to believe
let me tell you are the truth.
I have so large on the set ...
- You do not have to play!
- Did you come always tells me that my grades are ...
- Well ... - Too bad, because of me you can
help low-ball the hands.
- What? - Low-ball of the Company.
Do not even bend the knee to a beautiful piece.
Kids your age are Suggest,
Also get the medals are nothing without taking, but ...
Coped well with the low five hands!
I do not have the ¿no problem!
- How fault the service is heard Did you come?
- It does not matter, Malcolm.
How You said,
you have too much to learn.
As soon as I figure out a how she succeeded in
I here by tugging the terminal æ, getting out of the d st
Invalid Debt, I'll j ignores the
and working out the lessons.
- What are you working, honey?
- End essay about Wuthering Heights.
Wuthering Heights?
Pisa am about the final exam.
- Not true! - I hope you did not write the EOE,
Also Catherine and Heatcliff are kindred spirits.
Have entered the perhaps slightly
hostility to romanticism, right?
At the end of Catherine is torn
between Edgar and Heatcliff ...
Well, yes ...
- The place for prisoners?
- What?
My dad is on the field.
She likes to have me in the eye,
I'm too lekkomyœln are.
I Steffany.
- I am ...
- Malcolm, you go! Move, move!
And better for Obtain a helmet!
I know you are you've heard the rumors,
and I can only tell,
I can also be Scott
of the Kyoto Crazy Phantoms.
But do not worry,
I play the Lucky Aide.
Now watch carefully not
because for a while would reach the lightning speed b.
This is for you, Malcolm!
Try again!
Flies Next!
The reflections of her?
How am I supposed to ...
/ Good job!
Craig, it was to amazing.
What do you expect of EoE?
He says the em you also I'm good.
/ No wchodziæ.
/ Wœciekle which attack the dogs
I do not know, Reese.
Dewey, why are you always trying to
odwieŸæ me of such things?
If you do not want has been supporting me,
well you can odejœæ.
So it is fairly obvious,
Also do not like the shoes.
Make a note of it.
- Do I ... here here ...
- We should not rozmawiaæ.
I'm sorry,
- Excuse me ... I ...
/ - For three seconds will take care of you.
/ Please become straight.
Three seconds?
So I understand that you wanted to
pracowaæ for us?
I just ... if someone ...
This job opportunity is œwietna
for people with the right zdolnoœciach.
Good earnings, three-week vacation.
Full A benefits package.
Plus awareness of,
Also really change the world a plus.
/ Code two, code two
/ Repeat, code two.
I'm sorry if it was to o ..
Please interrupt with questions,
as long as I did not ask mine.
First, do you have
the photographic memory in?
I do not think.
Are you allergic to the ginseng uk
the NEB venomous spider?
- How do I ¹ d Know-?
- I get it.
- Do you have a brother bliŸniaka?
- What? No.
All right.
That's all.
Please go to the next door.
He'll do the cast of your face.
Then we can zaczynaæ.
Thank you for your interest in us.
Any sense of paranoia in continuous over
the coming few days will be the normal things are.
Remember: the first hip
then his arms.
It's like this dance,
who are doing the underpants.
/ Who Think the.
Looks as this that the shop no 617 really is going to
zjawiæ on future otygodniowym match.
Taking into account the fact of what's going to happen with the Last year we,
is a fairly brave of you.
Przegraliœmy three points
and waiting for us the grill.
I am not by the then coach.
- Can I view the dance in underpants?
- Jane, and wanted to view the byœ it.
Wanted to want you?
Slow down, you still
even whole owaliœmy.
Malcolm, poœpiesz up. We have before the seventeenth
ISAE with your pimples to the doctor.
- Mom!
- What?
Your friends of the Company
do not care.
Look at her face,
probably visit the same doctor.
Hello, Mother.
- Thinking of am also leaving for the EOE this morning.
- Because I was leaving for the.
He was already em in the middle of the road,
when I was suddenly reminded of himself,
Also when I had the three year old became sick Did you come to,
or Did you come to say so, and can not zawieŸæ Did you come to me
Donnie's birthday party Dinesco.
So I test drove the bike on the 3 km
in heavy rain to be there dostaæ.
Lazy? Do not think so.
I'm not leaving until I
do not apologize.
You just want an apology?
That's the point of the?
You should tell this to the
a week ago.
- But ...
- Adam hereby composed of a formal apology.
- All right?
- Do not. Not all right!
This is not the apology.
These are just some of the
cleverly constructed apology
which sounds like the apology,
but they are not.
Now you przeprosiæ for an apology.
And then przeprosiæ!
You know what your problem is?
Do you know why you do not accept
my apology?
Because you can not feel up szczêœliwy!
- What?
- Dependence of EOE differs from the angle of troubles.
Always Potrzebowo the chaos EOE
¿in your life.
Anyway the look at you.
You œwietn the job, cozy house,
The wife, and you could not znieœæ.
You wracaæ here and wszczynaæ
k of the canvas with his mother are.
That's not true.
³ I will come back here because you Did you come to destroy the chances of
any of us Luckily.
Tell her, Malcolm.
Tell her how horrible is the mother of the.
He's right - making their way
to every part of our life,
so as to make sure that the there is no place
where we are not nieszczêœliwi.
You can not change me zaœlinion the orphans,
how to do Did you come with Francis.
In precisely! What?
- Go with the second day ¿softball.
- Do not do it, Malcolm.
Had a chance of EOE odejœæ,
but now we have a game to play.
EOE gave everything up second ¿flows,
and some of its parts, members counting on you.
- Do not force me to play.
- No, but I can skonfiskowaæ your checks with outflows at the.
Will you take should be to the city which the money
due to play softball!
I do not know. You can e ..
- You're clear of the em.
- How can you break loose at night?
Hal, you can porozmawiaæ of the opcami ch?
Not now, Lois, too many
I g half.
What, for example?
I guess I'm an international spy
and do not even know on which side I was on.
I can even be a villain
and zdawaæ not realize it.
Can the EOE just tell,
Also do not want to help me.
Appearance You look very handsome
in this outfit.
It is a pity that the will not allow the EOE
zwêziæ it to me in her arms.
I have a good wieœci for you, Lois.
Our right zapolowy of playing up the labelers
and a staple of wbi him in the eye.
We lack one player.
We oddaæ walkover.
Yes!
Too bad. Of course, the biggest
losers are the fans.
Not today, Tonto.
It just does not make sense.
We are here, in costume, and Each wants to play.
- Malcolm, go to the second day ¿Mel.
- What?
And this is my aperture Service.
No, no. Podszkoli of themselves.
Right, honey?
After all Gadki
about my poœwiêceniu for second ¿blackberries,
Did you come to decide oddaæ of me?
Malcolm Each you nervous
before meeting the new friends.
B-governments are Sat.
Accept the city.
Knock saved with the tablespoon of five so far out of the park,
Also the hose mom loves the ...
Wait, what was I supposed to
zrobiæ with hips?
- First b ³ ¹ ³ d pa karza!
- What?
Everything will be fine,
only discontinue myœleæ.
You can do it, honey.
The second b the error!
Stop me speak.
Just tablespoon Throw the ball!
Also I do not believe it does.
I hate it when that treats me
in front of everyone.
- It's so ...
/ - Third b the error!
/ S of I'm listening?
/ No, my dear, are still being here.
I have a few things to straighten before I wyjechaæ Such use,
But I promise you that it will be œwiêtowaæ
our the anniversary, as soon as I get home.
That's right, if are still being
there you are.
Is Reese and Dewey already out?
- They went accurate fault?
- On with the omowisko Kopelman.
Reese wants pobiæ record
with risers.
¯ s what!
Are still being have the one signed by you, the
for my brother.
After that probably will lose value.
Just tell them,
Also do not want to work.
There Suggest what can you zrobiæ.
Just tell them!
Thank you for taking me into account.
It's very flattering to me.
But I decided to up the zostaæ
in the present work.
Where is he?
Looks as this that the pit bulls
I fold it toward the Dobermans.
It's really beautiful
as co-operating with each other.
Succeeded in me?
Are still being is alive?
Why do I have bacon in your pocket?
Reese Damn you idiot!
You know who you are?
You're the me!
Mama mia ³ a're right,
we love being inconvenienced.
That's why you do these g of silly,
stupid things like that.
- What are you talking about? I'll be s the Orthodox.
- It's not about the awe s.
Only the issue myself
the danger for no reason.
This dependence on pain and suffering.
And you know what? I end of it.
And you are you should ¿,
because it's not worth it.
£ readily tell you.
Already you are shrouded in the glory of.
Glory to the? ¿Do you think that this g of stupid stunt
przysporzy of glory were me?
Ê will show you what I can of.
Awful, is not it?
Only the central still operates a
Now I can odejœæ,
rid of em up.
Goodbye and good luck.
Eleven .. twelve ...
Won the twelve!
Reese Pobi the record!
It does not matter!
There's the yszeliœcie what he said I?
We are confident that the ma ...
What a difference the difference?
That's not it!
I'm trying to tell you ...
Give me the bacon.
I do not want an asterisk (*)
at my record.
M ³ young, please. This last change,
wyautowali of four times,
not with the catch of the ball EOE six books, jakimœ miracle
hit the EOE up the elbow, the other in the groin.
The message is so good,
Everyone also uœmialiœmy.
Stand there, close your eyes
and waving.
This is because it also is continuously ...
damage resulted from actions look at me!
Someone needs to teach her a lesson Daae.
Your second ¿yna loses
sixteen to one.
- Do you want to hence the urwaæ?
- He wanted the order, it will ebym ¿³ not it?
I will not give her the satisfaction.
Teach sure that the can not
kontrolowaæ me.
You know, Malcolm? I do not go with the boys opakami
Ask the cymi with other women.
Especially when it's their mother.
¯ egnam.
Okay, this is your last chance.
S ³ I'm listening?
Sure, I have time,
¹ æ to take part in the study.
I do not support.
³ I will do it! I hit the ball in the tablespoon!
/ Run, you idiot!
Finally!
This will show her that!
Must!
Oh boy.
Invalid AD, I will.
In the following order ê sure that the planning of and all,
so that the end of that way.
The only way to do it, I would have won the point,
This uderzyæ your own risk mother in the face.
I can not.
Think of Who?
Wyautowany!
Honey, if you want someone uderzyæ,
you have to remember to expose the heel.
/ There's the heard Did you come to me, Piama?
I won the 14 toilet seats.
Record again belongs to me.
Mom and he said that the react
in exactly this way.
So I read the interesting months
article about the ¿eraczach a glass ..
Anyway are not you care.
Dewey, when you learn,
I also take the decisions here?
- Go on.
- Apparently, the trick lies in the fact ...
That was fairly annoying slideshow
today on the south.
- S ³ Look, I ...
- All right.
I will not ask you lately
so they behave, because I think I know.
You're jealous of the new baby.
And you're right.
Not sanctification of those recently am
sufficient at large for attention.
But do not worry.
Tomorrow we will go to the hairdresser,
we'll buy you some new T-shirt ...
Just the two of us, okay?
Thanks, Mom.
www.tvsubtitles.net