/ In the previous episode ...
I love you.
I want with you zerwaæ.
/ Welcome to the U.S. Army.
Not poœlesz k of amstwami to prison
someone who may be innocent!
Do not give him even Insert the gatek?
As soon as we finish paradowaæ
with him in front of the cameras.
/ S Recommendation Board must be
/ At a distance of up to 9 meters away from her.
My jewels and breath
I do not care about the!
/ I know you're innocent
/ And I can prove they are.
Not only backpack feces
further than 10 meters.
Explain the recruits how to
worst a soldier ashamed of them all!
Just myœleæ I ceased.
I najszczêœliwszym
tool used in the world.
- Mom, you're there for three hours!
/ - Wait a minute, I'm in the shower.
/ I think it's a bomb!
Please odejœæ on
the distance min. 50 meters!
I can not!
I'm ...
I'm in the ward engineers.
Crazy world of Malcolm 5x20
"Reese joins the army, part 2"
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
/ Correction: MoszeUsz
/ You're not alone!
Wezwaliœmy all available
police officers from the county!
/ Are you sure you do not need
/ ¿Any devices?
We have miles of cables!
No, not podchodŸcie!
Let's all keep the away!
This thing is very sensitive to vibration longer possible!
He said I ¹ æ go back up!
Velocity you to the cemetery?
I'm Lieutenant Surtino,
with a branch in the bomb squad.
I'm here to help.
What is your name?
There is no time to introduce yourself!
I have the charge
explosive fifth such an extent
gravity sensor
igniter and secure!
- Which branch of the sappers are you?
- The Millbrook.
I'm s current is used. I arrived the
oddaæ the book ¿book to the library.
May the larger selection here.
Accrue the 50 cents
per day for detention!
I know that the punishment booster
financially a library,
but it is very small y
percent of their budget!
So if already not playing 20 questions,
I'm going to save human life!
If you, in Millbrook
We are so well trained,
I go zadzwoniæ
to your Toggle the loaded.
- Check the can aperture AAE meal of the Company.
- Of course!
If you can handle it znaleŸæ!
Very well.
I will try to disconnect from the wash load.
No!
The intersection of the I niew Specific gravity pipe!
Going to blow!
Tell ¿my hands, also the love of her em!
Piea, four, three, two, one ...
See? You do not need money
shopping, if you're idea halfway.
I would like to have for
you better wieœci, Hal.
But the prosecution has 30 witnesses founder,
who want to avoid the c ¹ æ
scroll to the prison for you.
And my mysterious stranger?
He has been a half-year of life and
wants umrzeæ of bad conscience.
Completely oczyœci me of the charges!
And it is not a product of my imagination!
So more or less
Last May the things.
The dad starts tomorrow.
Are still being we have no idea where Reese.
And my mother was a little behind the break of a
Do not worry, slowly working
going back to the normal senses of words.
S I think that that new hobby
this helps her.
This name is Sam Gandelbums.
Grew up on a farm, where
the friendship up with the turkey and duck.
Niedowidzi, so you are still confusing me.
Everything will be all right, Lois.
We find Reese.
Look, the break up of the flower.
He goes to court.
Return to the right!
To the left! In the back of the face!
Do the right fan by hand!
Bounce on the left leg!
Kettle!
In the back of the face!
Forward march!
Will just make the whole day.
It has no more sense than a worm.
It is enough to restore the mine
faith in the future of the army.
So does the subliminal æwiczenia her.
Are not using the subliminal exercises.
Ease!
In a few days we have a very
æwiczenia important training ground.
And I want to byœ of my number two,
because you're a statue of auricular my orders
like the beautiful, brainless, zombie robot.
It's an honor, Aug. ¿Ant.
And now let's work on the march
toward the fence energized!
/ I've seen the am accused Superior
/ Hacking the firewall proxy lying
and erases all files lying
"Medicines" without leaving traces.
Not until the end of it I understood,
but he said,
Also can u g Insert the corporate upiej
to money laundering,
that it will bring the.
You can zastraszaæ my children
How do you like it, do not care!
But I must tell the truth!
/ I'll kill you
On the litoœæ sake, do something!
Patience. That something
It's called "too much evidence".
At the end of the jurors get bored.
Accusation calls Gordon Walker.
That's it!
It is said about him the em!
I was not sure of what I say,
if gets here.
But in grams of the EIB heart I knew,
I must also tell the truth.
Here we have a conspiracy.
And for all the strings
train the ga ... This part of the man!
Indicates someone behind my back?
And after you destroy the last documents
Throw in the end
another racist a joke!
/ I have no more questions.
But I'm not dying.
They checked with the image of an x-ray.
If you were so scared by the like myself,
byœ knew of what is most important.
Avoiding prison.
Good luck.
/ Howdy!
/ Kwik, oink!
When so many of breaks k must be jakaœ
gap in the testimony of one of them!
Do not get your hopes up!
Mom, I know that the you are you ¿ko, and your
s is the project helping you with this uporaæ.
My dad has a serious being inconvenienced!
You must start the pomagaæ æ us!
Honey, I know how this crisis,
and believe me, I do my best!
Buy the am extra fast drying the adhesive months.
So not important how much shock œniesz,
that the contents will not fall out!
After the explosions of the continuity, Rebecca
must seriously sat there on the popracowaæ!
These crackers are not doing
impression on me injury.
For the good times
u ¿ywaliœmy real bullets.
Give the appearance of like in the movies.
/ 20 meters in front of,
/ Night half-west, 20 meters.
On the opposite,
Night half-west, 20 meters!
Half the night, half-night east, 5 meters!
In the face ... I get the!
I die myself here, in the shade.
IdŸcie to a meeting!
/ Bravo, opposite!
/ Alpha zajdŸcie them right!
IdŸcie to a meeting!
Bravo, opposite!
Alpha zajdŸcie them right!
Ideal in charge, ¿of the flange!
Ideal Leadership!
I'm allergic to those of grain products!
Will ride, swollen like a balloon.
Hey!
Approaches the second vehicle ¿blue springs.
- Commander ¿second day, przechwyciæ this vehicle!
- Yes, sergeant ¿Ant!
/ Oh no!
My God!
Are you all right?
God, I love this boy the boyfriend!
Hypertension are ga For more heavenly.
We run?
Aug ¿Ant?
Forget the hair ¿Ant!
Just say if we wiaæ!
Aug ¿Ant?
You idiot!
Ruszaæ up!
Faster Reese!
We can uciekaæ!
Aug ¿Ant?
Ladies and gentlemen, the service yszeliœcie Trim words including the c of the
Qty charges against the defendant.
Let's summarize what we know.
Three members of the management board of testifying about,
Also sued the deposit of different s
May the testimony Cheap Aug. 9.
Vice President's heard the defendant credited as the
assets of tax havens ...
/ December 6.
Chief Operating Officer of saw it
destroy the documents lying on the staircase
February 21 i ..
June 27, Director
faculty in the computer testify,
Also the defendant to show him
the image of his new yacht,
that the name of the "Beyond the Law."
July 11 sec of yszeliœcie,
g as the principal analyst in the western ...
What are you doing?
Not asleep! I'm trying stworzyæ
grounds for appeal!
Mom?
Are you coming for dinner?
/ Penelope measure the temperature.
/ I think that is allergy to ragweed.
Penelope is a foreign
correspondent or nurse?
/ No, it's just a housewife;
/ But enterprises confectionery
/ Interesting its regulations.
Can I dostaæ potatoes?
You can have anything you want, son,
if you're ready for it zapracowaæ.
Mierzyæ the stars
and never odpuœciæ!
Should I was to tell you that a long time ago.
And when you decide to have to write with the continuity
letter, wait for this one day.
In the morning you can be of a different opinion.
And never invest
in a restaurant a friend. Never!
You know what, I'm not hungry.
Come on, Dewey, I will teach you how to goliæ.
Super!
When you give the waiter a tip
Always Collapse bill in a roll.
When you realize how much
give him the EOE, we will already far away.
Dad?
- I brew the coffee you want?
- Willingly.
I sang the ...
Always have sang in my heart, son.
Thanks.
You know what the worst part?
³ I always hated that job.
I wanted to odejœæ dziesiêæ years ago
When they potr caæ for the disease.
I wanted to odejœæ years ago when they started
We zmuszaæ to the low-cost equipment in their boxes.
If I do the, found their to another
The elk and I had no such k the troubles.
They should just release me!
He was em terrible employee.
I've never read the notes I,
falters ³ em up, I is not coming in the Fridays.
What is wrong with these ludŸmi?
Promise me that you will learn
on my b the missing information.
No one tkwij
work at constant e, Malcolm.
I will not do so.
I'll go for the last time
kochaæ to hearing from you are the mother.
And so I probably would not sleep today ¹ ³.
We porozmawiaæ, Malcolm.
Unikaliœmy topic
but the time spojrzeæ truth.
You sfa the signature szowaæ dad on the
document indicate an CYM about of diminished there.
When my dad would go siedzieæ,
You will be usamodzielniony,
and I will take over parental rights
of Dewey and Jaime.
Funny.
We always are the tools I that the mother will go to
in prison, and my dad to the loony bin.
The life, huh?
I can not podrobiæ signature Dad!
Counterfeit signature we have,
and Reese - dad.
What? Either we should
podrabiaæ both signatures!
What did I say about making the
a small deep reserves in this system?
Wait a minute ...
- Oh, God also!
- What is it?
I must immediately porozmawiaæ with the tat!
Can wait twenty minutes.
- What will get the EOE orders, Corporal?
- I do not know, ask hair ¿cask.
- Betrayal of your password and frequency!
We do not have this robiæ
in a bad way.
Let's take a pause
and calm down a bit.
Do you want a glass of water?
- I do not know, ask hair ¿cask.
- Stop it to repeat!
This can not be real war,
but tomorrow I must hence the wyjechaæ,
and I have a girlfriend in high school models!
The school models!
Now start gadaæ, or
Feel like a real hell!
Thinkers, also wants it?
It sucks!
I want to be a good a soldier!
Shutting whether the em your brain
as the army wanted to!
Everyone said that the œwietnie
I'm doing, but it's not true!
I want spend it all of my boat, the boy wrapped
who are lean on me, but I can not!
You know what? I do not care
Army wants you! I've had fairly!
As of the Cham back my brain!
Succeeded in?
- What had become of the?
- Wait ...
I think it's ...
No, it is not.
¿But yes!
¿Is that?
The hell! I would like to,
¿Eby to the difference was greater the difference.
You can pretend crazy
How do you like.
I have a lot of time,
and no one will you uratowaæ,
or your hair ¿anta,
or a branch of u,
and the mom does not come
wipe the nose and change the diapers!
Mom!
Of course!
Suspend the breath until the bruising and the faint.
A long time already that I was not doing the.
- Are you all right?
- All right.
I know how to us hence the wydostaæ.
It is not possible, take a look around.
We are in a prison, part of the Young man.
You wrong, we are not in prison,
We only barrier.
A is always a way
to get rid of the barrier.
Wyrwaæ a pair of boards
from the floor, podpaliæ of bed w ...
Two things you need to memorize:
need for diversion
and a guy who has fucked.
All right.
It is too small would postawiæ s.
You zjeœæ a little sand,
tor jakieœ a half pounds.
What is the purpose of diversion?
We are related the disappearance.
Your brothers probably never left
related you are related in a container on the export garbage.
Start jeœæ ... is not
killing for which the appearance of the can.
Need more the cost. I Bring
All buckets will find.
Remember to roll up the legs æ.
Will still spew the half hour.
Good wieœci.
Dru ¿yna red soon lose.
Two branches were s been captured,
The rest przygwoŸdziliœmy here, here and here.
Now we just
Pull out the æ key to their bags.
Test, test ...
The microphone operates, the chair of a comfortable,
hair all right, we can zaczynaæ?
Hal, the service yszeliœmy many testimonies from
people argue that the smokers do the EOE this company.
Tell us in the with his own with the words
what kind of worker you are.
Little is efficient.
The form of the Supreme.
You can explained by it?
If you work in a large
impersonal corporations like this ...
You know those natural
TV programs
where the wasp paralysis loves g the caterpillar
and injected into the larvae her?
G the caterpillar's dead for weeks
Feel completely the c Each
mouthful of ¿j eraj the more the larvae from the center.
He sits in the pit of em every day,
I envy the c the g the sienicy,
because at least
j are shown on television.
³ I hate this job.
Disappointing to me the employee.
Yet many of the witnesses present
You as the brain przemyœlnego conspiracy.
These dates, however, indicate an
about your participation in it.
Do you have some way
to reject these claims?
I did not have. Who remembers the
What does the 25th January 2002.
Or 14 March 2003.
But my son wpad of the something.
Arise, Malcolm!
I know it looks as normal, but
my son is the lD card zar mathematical genius.
Its head half should be
pi size of the Company doctor.
Get discouraged him are an arbitrary date on any
years, and he will tell you what a day of the week.
What does that have to do with t the issues are?
Well ¿... I perceive the that the Each
day at the plate this Friday.
Each.
You can store check the calendar.
Excuse me, but why
it is to be such an important matter?
For 15 years I did not come of
to work on Fridays.
Do not show up for work the
on Fridays from 15 years!
It did not make it
the protocol in, right?
Do you have any evidence
in support of this twisted warp?
When you have what I knew of
search for a, in the opinion of've realized
Also almost all you need
in my memory box with the tkami.
Accusation claims
Also presented the EOE part to members of the management board
the pacific szowan the Book of
financial position of 9th August?
Yes, during my
stay in the Land of Bavaria.
And when the EOE allegedly hiding the money
in foreign accounts December 6th?
I went to the
"The Nutcracker".
/ Unrealised of a thing,
/ How to present academic.
/ February 21?
I got the license wyœcigi kart.
/ - June 27?
/ - Village of pilgrims.
/ 'Cause of panic attack
/ Close the Haunted House. "
/ 11 July.
In my cart to the spirit.
Really there was to!
Finally, on August 22?
They chose me m³ younger
trainer at the aquarium.
It does the hard work and all that
I just fixed em ...
Sorry for the slip-up on my end.
But they should tell they were "innocent"
instead of "found not guilty"
to confuse the box.
Lois wygraliœmy case.
Now, everything in our
¿Life will return to its former place.
There he worked in the EOE Fridays?
After all my
poœwiêceniach family.
For 15 years, the bra am
double shifts,
jeŸdzi the am on foot, the hardware is the am home
while you feeds the EOE Shamu!
In a properly is called Keiko 2
It is smaller,
but equally well sprayed with water.
It really œwietny show.
We should view the it someday.
Okay, let's get this behind us are.
My second ¿yna gives up.
Come Hendricks,
in the Put in a little more affection.
That's it.
That brings us to the question of trophies.
I guess I can spodziewaæ up
you tomorrow morning
smokers are marching in the courtyard
in high heels and with fake breasts.
I have always preferred to red,
But I will say the ladies as ubieraæ up.
Captain, I suggest you surrender.
If not, I've got sufficient as
a large flour to bake 500 cakes!
All right, not strzelaæ!
I give up.
And what the hell ...
/ "We need an assistant manager"
Everything finally comes back on to the standard.
Not the one fact
Also are still being no Reese.
Mom and Dad are still being the do not have the work
and we are jakieœ
20 000 $ in the cartoon.
Letter from Reese!
Oh my God, the beautiful ribbon of the army!
"Dear Family, I'm fine.
I was waiting for the letter to the
moment until I succeed.
I he completed basic
most of the second training ¿blackberries,
and my hair ¿ant he said to me,
Also I win some kind of prize money. "
Okay, gentlemen, wkroczyliœmy
in the Afghan airspace are!
We expect the blade in
both enemy and of our troops!
The better zapamiêtaliœcie
training, including long-survive for much longer!
Woken up!
- How are landed dujemy?
- That depends on you!
Remember to cut by tugging the green æ ¹
the line before the green light!
/ CI CONTINUED NEXT G ¥ ¥ PI ...
---------- Hi guys, this is my last eng subtitle for malcolm as 6 & 7 seasons already have eng subs. I couldn't find eng subs for seasons 4 & 5. So I "google traslated" the available polish subs. Hope these helped you atleast to some extent. Bye
------------------------------ dp
www.tvsubtitles.net