Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 175.3 MB
Come on,
we can not obudziæ child.
After that I bought the t compact disc
a relaxation of the musician are.
Besides, at this age
¹ remembers nothing.
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x05 "Malcolm films Reese"
/ What is wrong with you guys?
/ You two are destroying everything!
Look what zrobiliœcie of the t shirt are.
We saw the price tag of the price,
So we knew that the is new.
Every day is the same.
It focuses more attention on them than on us.
It may do with the ego.
Thinkers that the STAA me
on buying new clothes?
Enough of that. I want, ¿ebyœ
buy, a new washer and dryer.
You know that the us can not afford.
Little did I not speak of, but ...
Do you remember these narrow options,
I have supply of premium instead?
I think the bed finally worth something.
These people are continuously flying to New York
is not full of meetings behind closed doors.
I think I finally following the merger of five.
Hal was to be great.
Part, Mom.
Part, Dad.
Not spóŸnijcie up today to school y
Show their dinosaurs.
No, no, no!
16 weeks foundations of psychology,
and you have not placed zaklasyfikowaæ
simple conditions.
I was thinking of that the least ears
you acting, Kenarban.
You will learn ... What is the complex
castration, ... when they see one.
I'm trying sure that the ebyœcie people became confident.
Quote the c Blake:
"He generalizes, that is g shales."
- The Idiot.
- Excuse me?
Blake wrote:
"He generalizes, this is the idiot."
Thank you, Malcolm.
Next week I want dostaæ report
of your semester projects.
I must pogadaæ of Herkabem, wait?
I have a WF ...
I must change ... tires.
Mr. Herkabe, are still being does not appoint the
me project topic.
I ask this of the month.
Malcolm, you sound as if I wanted to
sabotowaæ your impeccable ¹ ¹ ¹ average.
Please Daae anything
He could ebym ¿¹ æ ³ started.
Come to my office
After lunch, it'll give you something.
Your office?
Why is everyone afraid of the up
my office?
/ Lionel Herkabe
/ Dean disciplinary
I remember that the things received on
zostaæ lessons can be returned to the Secretariat.
Basketball training the bed again
odbywaæ in an annex of the gym.
And Patty Lyn resulted in a Code 9
in the library, for which he has been a hold.
I hope that the glue
rubber was to be worth it.
Malcolm, patiently waiting for the EOE
about your project.
And today, your patience pays up the pack.
Here you go.
- What is it?
- You have the hands of the camera.
The lens is in the logo,
and the recordings are wirelessly
being transferred to the recorder.
What can I do?
We will secretly carry the
research on the warped minds em.
Most CYM which differ from the norm
umyœle what we have available.
Umyœle, unable to
¿distinguish good and the filling of a
- Sick ...
- You're talking about my brother!
- Yes.
- I have it secretly filmowaæ?
If you will be quiet,
lowered the czujnoœæ and you talk.
These files misdemeanors, nothing
says are the real Reesie.
That's what you want me to do ¿³
is the email for each time possible way.
You have one week.
/ It is the newspaper!
It is the newspaper!
You know that the day is coming, right?
No, no, today reviewed the ranch
appears in the tourist section.
Charles Cutler was to personally here.
Only then it was to dirty.
Francis, read,
too nervous.
A visit to the Grotto raises a lot of questions.
The first of them:
As such ohydnemu monster
licensed hotelier?
Obleœni you people call the months up employees.
And quality of food,
which is to embarrass the orphanage.
Grotto is the worst hotel
in the history of the world.
I'm sorry, I'm nervous too,
even listens ³ em.
Read it again.
I saw the EOE Dewey?
I want on it potrenowaæ.
/ No.
So ... How are you?
I'm just curious
How are ... feel.
- How the d the hell I Know-?
- You're szczêœliwy? You're sad?
For example, when you œmiejesz,
you feel that the something is œmieszne.
As if the old man for his stumble the
Grace and fall face to the pile of dog?
That was a fucking great.
So, when people Happens
harm, it is œmieszne?
- We will œmiesznie as it closes!
- Approx. Approx.
Œmiej are with me.
- People at you œmiej are?
- Yes, the œmiej up.
- But not long.
- So, you want to tell, ¿e ..
when people are with you œmiej are,
it hurts.
And if you want,
¿¿Eby they are suffering?
No, I'm just saying that the way you want gadaæ,
the girl is the Find the girl!
And Wey it with each other!
See?
It's fun.
Model 4400 has two rinse cycles?
No, no, of the deposit of s am ordering 4 days
ago, wanted to am just about pomówiæ.
- Part, Dewey. As was to school?
- Good. Œwietnie!
I'm definitely going to the em.
8 times 5 to 40
What are you ...?
/ Hello?
/ (Advice letter from the school s)
Part, honey, what's new?
¯ kidding!
- Who'd of the meeting?
/ - Everyone.
People running around the office the whole day.
No, I play Tetris.
Here it comes.
- Hal.
- Mr. Fortinberry.
For you insert my jacket on your head?
Sure.
Part, Mom.
Part, Dad.
Do not believe it.
The whole and the company is under investigation.
They used the pension fund
¿Eby recording studio to Buy
Director for the girl.
Hal, it's awful.
Ok, do not worry about it.
Men chose can handle it.
Hey, Gene, this is Lois.
Order 387669289/1.
Unfortunately I have to cancel.
Super. Press Contacts
in precisely cancels ali its convention.
Do not blame them.
A review by the terrible.
Part, Otto. How's it going?
PojeŸdzimy riding today?
Menada hotel ¿er year.
It's a lie century.
Otto, what are you doing?
The curtain is used for the EOE t the prize.
Really, Francis? Your g of the person has been
zag of uszony by the noise of my failures book.
I have a dream in which he sings.
I very much like the guy
Gor the coma Saturday night.
Approx.
Previously, he asks me hello yet o ..
You know, stuff.
- I was thinking of that the Know-you.
- Know-I want.
- How's your hair, because mine is terrible.
- No, it's cool.
- So, sang EOE including œnie?
- Yes, and floating around in the dances were a cloud.
- Do you like the clouds.
- Yeah, I like clouds.
I call her soaring kittens.
This is so weird.
Never tell anyone about this I do not speak of.
- It's like another hole ¿be seen.
- What is the opening ¿be seen.
- You do not have yczeñ ¿hole?
- Do not.
Part of Young man, you have to znaleŸæ.
Mine is in the tree on Jefferson Street.
You can prosiæ ¿hole yczeñ everything.
I never called you g shales,
or pervert.
My hole always provide
¿wishes of my safety.
It's like a bank for ¿be seen.
- This is an extraordinary recording.
- Yes, but I have them thanks to fraud.
- Already I will not.
- What?
Why stop now?
How can you even g of inputs êbiej?
They took me to the opening of his ¿yczeñ!
Malcolm, he wants with you pogadaæ.
B-governments friendly.
Trust of me, and I'll use the em.
- So called good interview.
- So we call k being the amc are!
- He's my brother!
- I will not give you another task.
All right. Make up for it
the school year. I'm leaving.
/ Magnificent were part of the rubber man.
There are ... 50 types of ...
against ... transfer.
- Starting with the ...
- Very well, Stevie.
I think that we can all rest of doczytaæ.
We have time for one more the presentation.
Our friend Malcolm tells
with a fascinating CYM Milgram Experiment.
- Milgram Experiment?
- Is ¿byœ czegoœ did not know of?
Milgram experiment examines the
statue of uszeñstwo to authority.
Tested by the teacher who strikes the
load current of the PERSON PER b of Edna answers.
The Milgram prove that the people
Bed are blindly listen to authority,
even if it means suffering ...
an innocent stranger.
What are you doing?
In our version, the stranger replaced the
a member of a close family.
And failures up current of replaced the
cy the devastating emotional trauma.
Let's watch.
Yeah, I like clouds.
I call her soaring kittens.
/ Disturbing, is not it?
As someone in good faith,
can sprzedaæ in the own brother?
Despite the knowledge of this type also juicy
diffused the rumors around the school, such as a fire.
- Hey, it's not ...
- Malcolm, I'm learning.
So we call k being the amc are!
This is my brother, and I'll use the em.
K ³ ¹ amc! This is my brother,
and I'll use the em.
/ I I took advantage of it.
Never You said,
I also record!
I never said I was the,
Also taping it.
I would like, ¿were ebyœmy
Malcolm friends of me forever.
Breathtaking, is not it?
None of us knows if that will do the
the next ¿Szeja person just because
Also a white guy in the white coat, asked us.
The only thing we know for sure ...
it also will do the Malcolm.
Tomorrow, Katty talk about the Team
post-traumatic stress among houseflies.
Because of you, I came out of
the finite jerk!
- Cheated me hello yet!
- I ripped off of you?
How am I, a humble school
I can curator porównywaæ up
with great and Pote ¿NYM Malcolm?
Do not ignore the enemy!
You can myœleæ you're a
me honest and m are smarter,
but this situation clearly deny it of a
Zagraliœmy game and I will win the em.
Well, it seems that ¿s none of us,
is not going anywhere.
Perhaps also am something he said,
Did you come to that answer were in the way.
Briefly, the am buy you something.
Brand fabric softener.
Listen to this.
Our Director of Finance,
of its stores a dog in the manage-day!
I had to change the by
him their reports.
Mom and Dad,
I have a question INDICATIONS FOR schools y
Obtain a we also earn a lot of money.
Such a large of that the walking
the schools were becoming ...
You have to walk perfectly well to school y
But, if I earn the 400, $ 500 a week?
Dewey, as we continue to earn the 400,
or $ 500 that you can rzuciæ ê schools.
Approx.
/ Reese, the ¿I have a hole
/ With which you can porozmawiaæ.
It's the official apology.
I'm horrible the people are and I'm sorry.
That's what I would do was to the awful,
even in our standards.
A fault fumes honest,
zawiesiliœmy the bar very low.
B ³ I beg you!
Tell me how I can to Repair the.
Whatever!
Tell me and I will do it.
Sure.
Obleæ of the Earth around the table and,
like Superman and back time
for a moment before
as We thought fail for like.
Are still being do not believe also persuaded the EOE
the journalist for another review.
Honey, you know best,
How can I be convincing the months.
- P ³ ³ aka EOE.
- Like a baby.
³ arrived!
We all behave normally are!
Welcome to the Grotto!
Ah, the Grotto.
Exceeding the threshold causes
brutal zgwa the price of one of the five senses of words.
I had the pan of the journey ¿?
The view and the smell immediately bursting into a half.
Obœlizg were of the owner
gives the background the paragraph, the long-sweaty one.
How niedŸwiedŸ, I manage the ego
counting at a lump of sugar.
- Mr. Cutler, may be to you the ...
- A vultures immediately begin to circulate.
Costumes from lumpeksu causing a vortex of poverty,
by which to run the
collection of fees for parking.
I'll take that, sir.
¯ and the OSN are an attempt to offer differentiated differentiation
the employment of native inhabitants.
This is my wife.
Not fairly that the almost ruined
Vacation previous generations,
some workers decided to
happen to them spotykaæ and assumptions.
In g half up not within,
Hoteliers also like baboons, spread the ...
Otto, I'm sorry,
I do not know what happened the o
Like someone else to hit the.
That was I myself.
I give it in the hair, as if you wanted to
a Insert the them on ice or something.
This reminds me of a fight
on the school playground.
The wounds are superficial,
and the learning niegroŸne st.
I've never seen the em
such grotesque ceiling.
/ Blue ...
/ 17 more arrests ...
This is Mr. Curtis. Use the seller uses
muffins, as ¿of a live disc.
Come on.
You only have a pair of socks.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God also?
/ Look at those the money.
- Hal, when they hide the EOE?
/ - I have no idea.
It had to be a year ago.
This is my the money on a jet ski?
No, no, it wykorzystaliœmy
easy remote control of Rees.
- There must be jakiœ $ 1,000!
- $ 1473.
Who cares from where they are coming from.
Let us sure that the there are.
You're part of a moment, son.
Here, buy yourself a pack of baseball cards.
- Why do the EOE?
- Why do you do the EOE!
A fight, fight, fight!
Animals.
/ Hello all students
/ Says Malcolm.
We all know how horrible the the the
I will of his brother, Reese'owi.
I would like to publicly przeprosiæ
for making it poœmiewiska.
I never should ujawniaæ his
secrets. And I can not undo the æ time.
But I can at it, change the rules of the game.
Sproœne I had the thoughts about Shirley
our cook.
In Zesz the month of white, I saw the,
disguises himself as the a and since then fantasize.
After that he said I am
poœmiewiskiem the same as he did.
/ Unfortunately, it will not protect the rest of the students,
So bringing all
to our level.
Look at the files of other students.
The first of the shore, David Abernathy.
The holidays not worked on the construction site,
but that of the theater workshop.
/ Cheryl Adams.
The reason for her dismissal from the WF-u
this week was to a herpes.
/ Charlie Agnew, soak the wheel of bed
/ Ka ¿each night during the finals that.
/ Leslie Albert, pacific of the SCO
/ Signature parents, ¿Eby have a new nose.
Mr. Zyzyx, we jakieœ half hour,
¿Eby clean the hard drive.
/ James Allen ...
James Allen, like zjadaæ your ...
- What kind of things?
- Have you seen the newspaper EOE is wonderful!
Da of us are good review?
¿There is no any review. Poœwiêcili
us a more interesting article months.
"Local attacked reviewer crazy"?
From where they are all the flowers?
It's thanks from restaurants,
hotels, art galleries.
Charles Cutler, the most
part of the hated man in the entire state.
See how many places were reserve a
at our other hotels.
We have a vacancy until May!
This guy is impossi-happy.
We reviewed the hospital.
Oh yeah, that sounds awful.
Do not go to him.
As provided is charging, it will burn engine.
Mia the EOE pour two scoops ...
Give me of doing this.
I'll be back after the three week suspension
and I have to przyznaæ,
schools and would change the a
I think I've created a
najgrzeczniejsze high school in America.
And most importantly:
Hello, Mr. Pulling off the grove lying.
Hello, you are who spew of bed in the bed.
Hello, sir, which left a father,
because my mother was to a lesbian are.
He has an amazing memory in the
for such things.
www.tvsubtitles.net