As the furious and byœ to the a, if someone
your the shatter of the antique music box?
What do you mean?
He does not play at all?
Œwietnie! Smoothed the silly EOE up
in my bedroom?
I do not expect them also come
Here ¿¹ æ Eby accepted with humility the punishment?
Hal, is that you?
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x19 "The Experiment"
T the interpreter of hearing protection: Harry_man
Correction: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 174.6 MB
/ Stevie, come on. Jonas Salk
/ Solve the for the to the already long ago.
/ He had to ...
/ Pracowaæ P. .. the idiot.
Call me the idiot?
Do you want to obtain a restriction enzyme
the second type without using bacteria.
And I'm the idiot?
So ... and yes!
We have ... spróbowaæ czegoœ.
And are you think that the what I tried to
robiæ the last two weeks?
When I get my own room?
I can not pracowaæ the sexiest
look, when Mom is watching.
What are you doing here anyway?
We're trying a new type of enzyme stworzyæ
restrictive, and that it looks as?
Ba ³ aganicie in my room
for something like this?
This is important. Such enzymes are
Used to map the chromosomal
DNA tests reunion genes.
It's all in the national competition.
If we win, our work will be
czasopiœmie published in the scientific community.
Probably get Introduction
for all universities in the country.
And then everyone ... Bed the semi-Latin.
Only our incubator is continuously breaking down.
We are of the agar.
And we will end the blood.
We are fighting with the continuous pollution of a white ...
Can I help you?
All right, Reese. If you'll want to
obcinaæ g half of the trash that you know the lady.
Why are you doing this? I want to help you,
and you turn it into Continuous my stupidity!
Not serious.
I look to czegoœ przydaæ.
Why do not you give me a chance?
It is two units.
Better not Pulling off gajmy Details.
This is so at exciting.
I feel like I had the zemdleæ.
- $ 4, right?
- Thank you, please pozdrowiæ Dewey.
Who was to?
Jakiœ kid in class
Dewey sells chocolate.
Tasty pulp, maluszku.
Is it that time of year again?
Mom, please, do not make me.
/ Wonders of am up
/ What does the EOE with a backpack.
I do not want to walk perfectly well from the door
doors, sell the c g of the sweets are silly.
Dewey, the father przegapiliœmy
all school events this year.
Collection of waste paper, car wash,
sale of homemade pastries.
You have to move the pa æ ³ safe place.
- You do that.
- Dad, do I?
/ The 275 tablets you get it.
/ Dad?
Of course, you do also.
Well impact of flows on your
character, and sell ...
How will you?
275 plates.
There's still half an hour to
S west of the sun - what are you waiting for?
Okay, I got it.
But I want to know ¿ebyœcie that the
if y jakaœ the bniêta pair steal me
and later brought up girl
it will be on your wine.
No, I will not.
Hello?
Part, Dewey, what's up?
Do not believe for at
Going by the mother.
What is it this time?
The School organizes sales are the sweets.
And we have tons of chocolate to sell.
- He hates the em that.
/ - And you know what my mother would do the a?
- What?
- Prohibit me of a salesman.
And he said, also will never be able
I sprzedaæ even one!
So he said a?
This is terrible.
I will take from you a dozen places, Dewey.
A comparison of even me, sell the lying
s the sweets to your Notes This is the ¿.
You know what?
I'll take two dozen.
Just do not tell her,
pomyœli also because I want the U of Rozz oœciæ this.
/ - Say that the someone else will buy the.
- Do not overload the hack k?
It does not matter,
This is no excuse.
Over than the one in the
family does not have faith in yourself.
Roz of the Cham sure that the Eby unsubscribe you a check.
Fred, where are you going with this pig?
It can not zostaæ in a pigsty,
sow it rejected the a
So you take him home?
Yeah, in precisely what they'll do.
Oh no!
You?
Listen to S is a half of the size of siblings,
which does not allow it to eat.
It's only the right thing output.
Fred, you can not this zrobiæ,
look on his face.
I do not even know that the want to zabiæ.
Now you already know.
- Ralph!
- What?
You can not zabiæ if it has a name.
This is Ralph. Ma ³ y Ralph, piglet.
Oh boy ... my kid
has such a name. Here you go.
- Branch of it?
- Not at all.
So you still do not have the enzyme.
Where is the problem?
Do we tried ...
All varieties ...
a warm .. and pressure?
Yes, yes, yes.
We tried acids,
we tried the rules ...
- How much blood has been with us?
- A lot.
Pick out the em ... Another unit of the ...
when the spa.
- Stevie!
- After ¿wants ... pomagaæ.
I know, but I'm on it.
You can not namawiaæ me
¿³ ebym giveth his color jakieœ
the food and tells that the chemicals it.
Guys, guys!
I make the discovery.
How to confound the blue with the yellow that
not completely get the new color.
Name it ... The yellow sky!
Listen to this. The sales Dewey
already 52 chocolate bars.
You are still a lot more to him has been about,
Lois. Hold on earth ...
So far.
Baby, from there zejdŸ d
Do not worry.
Keep your pet safe.
Nice to that the Dewey so you ¿ko works for schools y
If the pace continues, it will be
the best in the school fair.
- Good morning, sir.
- I'm sorry, I do not eat are the sweets.
This is not the ordinary that's the sweets.
This is the akocie America.
- What are you talking about?
- Do you know the akocie America.
But the will of a properly
Sets the akocie freedom.
- America loves you, right?
- Of course, also like that.
There are plenty of people,
who also counting we fail.
- What do you mean?
- Well you know, people.
People who do not wish for the ¿
this country best.
So these are the sweets for Assistance
zwalczaæ terrorism?
With each bite of chocolate-peanut.
- How much are?
- The four ...
- $ 9.50.
- I'll take two.
- Thank you.
- No m³ odzieñcze, I thank you.
Separate up!
Welcome ... schools of Trade.
I would like ¿Eby Reggie killed at the end of the
Archie comics and the ends of.
Malcolm, you have to take care of themselves æ ¹
Jamie for a while.
Mom, this is the moment Toggle ohm
in our experiment.
Excuse me, are you new? Stevie,
Explain how things are here in May.
Anything?
No change.
¯ None of these has not tripped o
Can that we should ...
Oh, my God also?
Separate the o .. themselves.
Zrobiliœmy this, we have created an enzyme.
Unbelievable! What will the EOE?
I do ... ³ I will not do.
What?
¿It is not.
The yellow sky.
Part, guys.
- How to ... do the EOE?
- I did not do the em.
S ³ Look, we are not for you lived.
We just want to Know-What do the EOE.
Why do you always blame me?
Reese, do the EOE are good for!
Jakimœ miraculously make the EOE
separation, had to add something EOE.
What was that about?
I just ... I do not know whether
I can remind myself.
No returns of em too much attention,
so many other things operates about
I probably will not tell you if
do not you share a success!
What?
This is a great contest.
Adequate at large s for us 3
So, either we divide it
three, or say nothing.
You mess from unintended aœciwymi people, Reese.
So ... donieœmy.
I will not tell us what to do the,
unless the curtains will add it to the services.
It's so unfair!
All it does is read the comics,
We worked and we weeks.
-What do you want me to do the ¿a, Malcolm?
- Zmuœ him to tell us!
Wait a minute, if Reese for the solu-your
experiment should be something for it receive the.
What? No! He does not even know
why it tripped o
I have been working for 20 years,
do not know why the c.
Append Reese to block any services!
I am here Ralph,
already all right. Will be fine.
- What happened on?
- Other œwinki that were for him the silent e
Francis says the EOE in some foreign Zesz week
Also leave it in the yard.
I used to try, but he's so mild the
and s the sweet that the pigs do not get the zjeœæ him.
Do not leave it there until
I do not teach him to be more assertive.
But he spends every ¿d are briefly
day to his care.
No one speaks of,
Also raising pigs will be easy.
We will also bring up pigs!
Listen to Francis. Or reference
Ralph to the farm in the evening,
or will be looking out the will of
at you with an omelette.
Come on Ralph.
/ This is the moment of truth.
Your brothers are judging that the no
give them advice, they ¿ck so carefully?
Come on, I know you can do it also.
You have to be just tough.
Will show your the furious of the mine.
Well it ¿?
Smell failures book.
Reese Okay, I give up. You will get
its share, just tell me what to do the EOE.
Okay, just sign it.
Reese has a full ny part in this experiment
and fully share our success with it.
Because without the aid does not
the axis gnêlibyœmy success.
Outmaneuvered ... by the wana ba.
- Everything looks good.
- Now tell us, what do the EOE.
I have not the foggiest idea
I do not remember doing the ¿ebym
the anything special.
What?
But now, as I will be the wyœmiewa
and been telling the that the I g of stupid,
I have proof of your handwritten signature
Also I'm as smart meters are like you.
Justice, it has become ...
Mother of the child is 13 years old.
Profit from each sold chocolate
going to buy the book ¿ek and heat small
the NEB meals for the children of such mothers.
I'll get my purse.
- I tell you, I do not remember!
- All right, let him wstaæ.
Reese, this is important.
It's for medicine.
This enzyme can help uratowaæ
¿someone's life one day.
Please, try the
recalling what then do the EOE.
I can not, sorry!
I just do not know!
Normally, the island of Crete em up
the room as usual.
- Try ... play back.
- Yes, that's the idea œwietny.
Do everything you do,
when you are alone in the room.
Close your eyes and pretend.
Imagine everything
in myœlach and do it later.
Me and Stevie is not here.
You're alone in the room, as he was then.
Ok, let's see.
First thing - opuœciliœcie room.
Then I walked up the tubes ...
¿Savor TO SEE how the enzymes.
But after that I get tired of.
And later ... I saw something spark of the lying.
And I throw the spark into my box of the lying meadow.
And then ... Oh yes.
I took the one of the shirts with Malcolm.
And then ...
Oh, my God also?
Then I was up playing the Game Boy Dewey.
To ring and your teacher and speaks of a,
Also sold the greatest number EOE chocolate.
And he said that the all
I hate the rówieœnicy.
I'm so proud of Dewey.
You know, it's a good product.
So the really sell themselves.
I can not believe it. Dewey
sales of more than 1,500 bars of chocolate.
In 1500.
Page 12
The bed in the chali for you the exhaust.
Part of that live here
ch the boy sell the eco-cy chocolate?
I'm sorry, were finished in
PREVIOUS later.
Here you are. We want to Buy
so those who save the forests.
- You must be so proud of his son.
- I do not know what the Lord says.
Of course, also you know.
You said that the ¿ka da plate is
tree planted in burnt part of Yellowstone.
I like that the 10% of the profits allocated
to fight with the abortion and euthanasia are.
Wait a minute. He said to me that the 10%
go to organizations supporting the trades abortion.
- I did not know the am, also have the views of the.
- And I did not know the am, you are also the same.
I'm sorry sir. I must
to someone tell how I feel.
You have a great being inconvenienced.
I hope that will be the idea of
about what you will do the EOE, for each time,
When we saw of me,
the venom of the prize lying yours are.
¿Do not get any prizes!
K ³ ³ break EOE all
¿Eby sprzedaæ they are the sweets?
What do you say about the K ³ am amstwie?
That's the worst thing, as the you can take the.
A lie destroys osobowoœæ, Dewey.
Destroys the trust that people
Darz themselves are. Do you understand?
- Yes.
- And how they intend to usprawiedliwiæ?
- Francis sermons of me so zrobiæ.
- Should domyœliæ.
- Kaza ³ ³ k EOE brother's hack of the odyczach?
- ¯ ebyœ knew of that the so.
I'm already fairly your
sabotage everything we do.
Finely you lose the reason, Francis!
/ Who gives a sick brother's advice!
It's all your fault!
I'm just trying to help the kid,
which is the sawed at each step.
And I'm fairly your talking about
Also everything we do is g the pole.
Okay, Ralph, be aware of your's image.
You're in the s, hard,'re The largest
the pigs in the yard and you are not afraid of anyone.
WchodŸ there, wether you jakiœ of books and eat,
like you've never venom of EOE.
And this is it Ralph. WchodŸ œmia of the,
well you're doing. Well ...
OK, enough, Ralph.
Ralph, without biting.
No!
Not at your own risk mother!
It's hideous.
No Ralph, not to ... shed.
If I were you I'd start of the
nadawaæ names of the cows.
And then my ear
in the end was to clean.
Then I will update the list of my enemies.
Note that I do the math.
I do not understand, do not understand,
I do not understand, do not understand.
G of UPI, the UPI g.
G ³ stupid, hate each other,
hate each other.
Then I worked on the triceps.
Hey, no one likes math.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
So, what does the EOE later?
Nothing, I started the odbijaæ five of the tablespoon.
- I do not think there will be more ...
- Throw the j ... again.
- What?
- Reese ... throw away.
See!
Branch on up!
The ceiling must be asbestos!
Of course!
- What are you talking about?
- Reese, succeeded in you!
Asbestos is a highly
mutagenic material em!
You can also change the way
cell reproduction. These cells.
And by the by here all the time.
We have asbestos in the ceiling!
What?
Will soon be an omelet.
So we live here until
until the asbestos is removed.
I wygraliœmy competition.
It turned out that the company is sponsoring the whole
retains patent rights.
Use the Jobs are our production
a new drug, which will earn the billions.
And you know what we dostaliœmy?
Pencil cases.
It even has a built-in compass.
Mom, Dad - no need for the pencil?
No, Reese still
no need for the pencil.
When will you know where pytaæ.
Ok Francis, how long we'll be
dzieliæ Obtain a box with Ralph? This is ridiculous.
Really showed the courage of the,
but I think there is still confident.
Da know the when will be ready.
www.tvsubtitles.net