Who is at a high league than who is?
What an arm!
I will go again Did you come.
Central hit.
Give the appearance of it,
Also he likes it!
/ Malcolm in the Middle 5x11
/ Ida's Boyfriend
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Doberek.
- What are you hiding?
- What are you talking about?
Give me a break.
Hence the sense are your fault.
If you admit it right away
can you I'll be the askawa.
You can not pretend that the you know something,
in hopes fail for eloquent.
'm Not hiding anything.
Okay, admit something.
The fine that, huh?
If I can get it from their parents hide the
the month of the, by the time for this to heal,
Then I'll Such use is the output æ
and the Insert the back when you want.
And you know why I do it the?
¿It is not.
- You really thorough job.
- Thanks. This is the USS Constitution.
- In 1803, launched the j ...
- Typhoon!
I do not believe that the will of the EOE!
- And now?
You stupid ...!
I hate you!
I would like, ¿ebyœ never
not that of my brother!
I would like, ¿ebyœ never existed!
- How did it happened?
- What?
This is the most unusual of a thing,
are seen as the em.
What is it?
- I wish I ¹ ³ of the entire small forces and Reese been solved.
- Yes, yes. Very funny.
The smell of the ¿been solved.
I wonder if the other things that ¿it operates a
Nah. If it were disappeared,
lacked to me about them.
- You have your father's chest.
- For the sake litoœæ, Mom, what are you doing here?
-Plain of e welcome it too much?
- I'm sorry. Did you come to scare me to death.
Bring wieœci.
S ³ Look, if you dig the Susan and,
it does not mean that the you can mieszkaæ here
among other things because the next child
we do not have a spare room.
Ah, yes.
Another precious child.
Did not want to want you straciæ cash
of social welfare.
You do not enter.
I take œlub.
What!
His name is Mr. Li.
Know it in the am during the cruise off the coast of Alaska ¿s.
- Tomorrow the download.
- You take œlub tomorrow!
At my age, if no teeth
and it is good to Obtain a bed, on a long-czekaæ for much longer?
Did you forget am.
This one does not like girls.
- I'm not gay, grandma.
- Of course. Simply angle the AMIE.
Office of the think wedding rehearsal dinner
tonight.
Today? Susan Arriving ¿d ¿and?
No. Can next time
your sister pomyœli twice
wykrzyczy the password for the "Wheel of Fortune".
Give a chance to someone else.
A wedding is tomorrow at two o'clock.
Not spóŸnijcie up.
- About six o'clock we have a flight to Hong Kong.
- Going to Hong Kong?
He has a house there.
We will mieszkaæ there.
- Moving to China?
- Yes, I know.
Chickens on the streets,
which the children toil for a pittance, all the smoke.
- The dream of an SPE than the o
- Except that the so suddenly.
I understand also that difficult for you.
I know how much he loves Did you come to the father.
Yes, it probably is.
Can you believe that?
Will be almost exactly
on the opposite side of the Earth.
We will oddzielaæ
s entire paper core molten Earth!
It's like Bo ¿Christmas!
Francis, I will do for the hotel
something of great ego.
I employ the corpse actors,
that played a mysterious weekend crime.
Good Bo ¿e
The best part is that the actors
Bed are checked in as regular guests.
They can be now between us
and we do not even realize it.
Your attention, please.
Room for Sir Reginald Drake and his
mœciwej, ¿zapijaczonej wife, Evelyn.
¿I do not have any clean socks, Dewey.
Why do not you ask Rese'a?
Who?
Please, Dewey,
Insert the following is on the table.
- What was that about?
- Reese, for me the continuity's sake, pick up it!
- No œwietnie.
- Do not worry, honey.
Everything will be fine.
Just relaxing and for this to the office of the fumes me supper.
Ida with the those of the fine were the goods!
Part, I'm Lois.
This is Hal.
- Welcome to our home.
- Hello. Nice to me you to become familiar.
- Took the P ³ æ your coat?
- Hold on away from me.
A strong and independent on.
But not so, regardless of the,
may not be of a full fledged
your partner has the ¿eñstwie.
Shut up.
Behaves like an idiot.
And what are olœniewaj honest.
How can you be so callous, Cedric!
I Kaza of those of the more
wspominaæ not!
And now I'm done with the t
the senseless hysteria and the revenues for lunch!
Better taking care, Cedric.
The old English knows hose myœliwska
can be a very dangerous place.
Please, if you Such use would
hence the zabraæ these cymbals of this?
I'm sorry.
Please spróbowaæ their ignorowaæ.
Alas, I have been the zg be destroyed!
Zg the absolutely necessary be destroyed!
Such use ¿which would przypuszczaæ, and that will be
killed by anyone else but ...
- Dosyæ. I'm checking out.
- No!
Please zaczekaæ.
Otto, you have to stop.
It's all annoying.
Francis, try to be
more understanding of y
Can too little about æwiczyli,
but co-operate with us.
Without accepted the proposal of resistance
delete the musical elements.
Visitors are run the entire young groups.
As you are canceling within the last hour of the dwanaœcioro up.
I'm not s of The Orthodox Church myœliwym.
This is really a police inspector.
My specjalnoœæ - murder.
I must nalegaæ to none
This does not leave the room!
Angela, I also recently
the arrangement is not made the best of us,
but I am willing to
spróbowaæ again.
Yes, Warren?
Offset the start listening to you.
If you have nothing to hide,
there is what you obawiaæ!
Can not he supposed to be the dawaæ
all keys to the rooms guests.
Dinner at the moment runs alone.
Mr. Li seems to be cool.
But my language gives me tired.
No one said of me that puncture the language
metal skewer will be so uncomfortable.
So COO of the hands of him the sponge,
We met during the trip.
How it was to?
What is to be, the third class of primary school?
Explore People are people. As every day.
It's interesting the whole story.
Woman with which the venom of em dinner
first night
was closed in the cabin patients
after the break and overboard.
The sea was to restless.
But as it happens are szczêœcia in nieszczêœciu,
And so it of the deposit of the s also I met the beautiful the IDE.
Sorry.
After the kn ¹ ³ em insect.
Come on, Dewey.
Wey piero heavy. Your favorite.
And you can be dostaæ only taking the c them with a fork,
I keep, which proves that also exists.
If no one wants
I eat them.
Mom, Jamie got your cigarettes.
- Who the hell is Jamie?
- Your grandson.
Never nadawaliœmy their names,
until we were sure that the Use lived for.
I love her dark sense of humor.
I'm telling you, waiting for you ¿life
a lot of joy.
Reese, the spicy shrimp
are fantastic.
Yes. I did not know of, also you can to Buy
in the U.S. such sharp peppers.
What's wrong?
In precisely the sentences I realized
Grandma also really howls ¿d ¿a!
I want pobyæ alone.
You znaleŸæ him babe
it will be too late.
Œ How are the ugly.
These are the cheaper, and you are working longer.
It's nothing.
I am sure also that the yellow is May leaking of a
the language of my gear it in the em.
Drink your tea the.
Do not like when gets cold.
- Do you have something in the hair of honey.
- What?
- Under the wigs.
- What are you doing? Hands off!
What is it?
List of my bank account
and quotas on them.
Had to am Know-
what they are getting.
Her husband droœæ are matched by its beauty.
If we are to retrieve a is fair,
byœ knew of how much money I have.
If you already ceased EOE czepiaæ up
I like a hyena, I'm going to doprowadziæ all right.
Thank you very much for allowing me
to the connection to your family.
The makeup of bed ¿somewhere else, Nancy!
I'm very curious.
Did you fall for the in. .. my mom?
I know that people think it's weird.
We were so different ¿Nyima.
But ever since the fault I know your are a mother, I became ...
Just me uszczêœliwia.
Never in life not by the em
so szczêœliwy.
A "szczêœliwy" in your culture
is the same as ...?
Open.
Gentlemen. I expect of my
acting companion.
We will add some fine flavors of small
for tomorrow's story of y
In a properly we wanted the porozmawiaæ.
If the thinkers that the Reposition Finish
I have to you rozczarowaæ.
Although the ... I can pay particular attention
the lady on the enigmatic Pomfreet.
-Otto ...
I'm sorry. We have appealed the AAE show.
Can it Lord McGregor,
surly, but ... what?
Odstawiliœcie slice of good works, but
pozmienialiœmy graphics,
Then you have wyjechaæ.
- Thank you for everything zrobiliœcie.
- PLEASE released with us!
If t lose the job, it's over.
There is no worse for us
of show business.
Thinkers, also I'm in this bad?
We should've been me widzieæ in Dairy Quin.
This is our last chance.
Please do not do that.
Please.
- I do not believe that the do not spill the EOE.
- I remember it from the Dairy Quin.
He was poor.
Oh, no, no, no.
/ Malcolm, discontinue marudziæ
And / Come here.
/ We're going to a wedding.
I'll be for a while.
Wyfymajcie minute.
/ - What?
- Nothing.
Wyfymajcie ... Oh my fpuch also because of so much
Also I can not speak "f".
My mother will kill me.
Wait a minute. I can prevent.
I'll be carefully and of what she says.
I avoid the ... that letter.
Proft.
Looks as it also all the old
Ida's friends showed up.
Let's hope that is about to start.
Malcolm, on the closing parking?
Sixth, sixth and thirty-seventh?
In military terminology,
it will be 1900, dad.
Here and blushing bride m³ young!
- I'm sorry, but the hotel does not paliæ.
- Get off prukwo.
To remove the threaded my day.
- Hal and carefully ck ... -I know it's weird,
but my continuity-blind, and it is none of our business.
So let come what may, ¿yczmy them well
and let the force goes on.
I just do the em.
Okay, I admit that the was to me
sleazy brother,
and I should not be the niszczyæ
your ship,
and should be of the grip can try the
przeciwud the awieniowy, it uses the I go to you.
So, either way I'm giving it to you.
But great.
And play the c against robots, you can include
to the connect and play against the mutants.
I always wanted to have t the game.
Do not believe it.
and a method of bypassing levels.
Ê will show you ...
Mom, in precisely I have found on the krzeœle this game
that the dostaæ I wanted to for my birthday.
As can be so insensitive were?
Jamie?
My my occur.
I almost forgot - my grandmother
and he wears the necklace on her œlubu.
My name is Shuang Hsi,
chinese symbol for double szczêœcia.
The whites of the people that om
not make assumptions impression.
You should not me widzieæ
until œlubu.
Go back to your room,
it someone we take you for a waiter!
However, the wishes ¿my chosen one.
See you in a minute.
O my God e
The drug, drug, drug improvement in mood,
sedative agent for the months of large mammals ...
He did not love her.
She nafprycowa him and the ashes!
Clear sky over the airports.
¯ no problems with departures.
- Check the highway ...
- Dad, Mom, I want to tell you ... are a certain thing.
- What?
- Grandma ... given drugs ... man in his quest from China.
- Grandma gives medicine man in his quest from China.
- What is this, the hell?
- Pote ¿ny agent regulating mood months.
The whole lot of that.
Fiola for the vial.
Szprycuje it?
How to do it?
Teas are.
My God e
Of course, tea!
Do you remember how he was her
and by pouring the whole a nice evening?
I know I would do it of a
Are you sure
Also her purse?
If ... confirm.
Turning to discontinue.
Are you sure or not?
You're it or not!
No, no.
Kraœæ old lady handbag.
Should you kazaæ aresztowaæ.
Us? We know what you're doing
poor Mr. Li.
My God e Am thinking of before,
You're a of the isolated, tolerated monster
but, mother,
It is unacceptable!
- What do you care jakiœ Chinese?
- It's a human being!
- And you szprycujesz it.
- It's called grooming.
This is not anything different differs from spraying perfume
or stuffing bra tomatoes.
What girl does not try to
zdobyæ a little advantage?
Did you come to lost their mind!
Or go to him and tell him,
Also cancels the wedding sent or call the police!
Well, already I'm going.
- Pokroiæ cake?
- The Ides!
And as our killer
He could not zostawiæ traces of shoes?
Because the are I think that the szed not, but rather
whuœta to the room on the line.
And only by the white akrobat is the ...
This part of the man!
I. .. this woman!
End of the game, Edward.
Yes, it zrobiliœmy.
I zrobilibyœmy it again
Warden.
Solve the mystery associated.
Way to go!
O my God e
Czuliœcie it?
That was a great of that!
Never publicznoœæ not reacted to a
as well.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for giving us this opportunity.
Do not mention it.
Important that the confidence uwierzyliœcie
and pokazaliœcie slice of a good craft
Well ¿ripe for the months example
conspiracy and fantasy.
I'll be the remembers it for years.
I can not doczekaæ,
by opowiedzieæ the friends of ohms.
- Rented ¹ ³ EOE publicznoœæ?
- I can not I patrzeæ of his torment.
With the attributes of faithfulness and devotion,
¿is the eñstwo allows for Fail-family ...
- Appearance give the time, so the nicely.
- That's right.
I love weddings.
The confidence and patience,
Your me to reinforce continuity.
- We should not interrupt was this?
- I guess you're right.
- I wonder why you do not zrobiliœmy.
- Who cares?
To me the e
I'm not worried.
I'm just szczêœliwa.
/ Your my continuity and mutual respect,
/ Mutual trust and understanding will increase radoœæ ...
Empty all of her and them.
Each d the vial.
All of us of a odurzy
It's a nasty, hateful monster.
But I'm the one who will do a?
- Dining experience.
- Well, of course.
And it will do the right after
and the like has gone through to Mr. Li.
That's the genius of a
He knew and that the not resist
free you ¿Erce.
This is the most diabolical,
disgusting thing I dopuœci of a
But anyway I like
her dress. Do you?
Sure.
It's weird - I usually thinking of myœlami.
Now my thoughts are your thoughts invent.
If does not exist, who now says,
Also does not exist?
You know what I mean?
I'll tell you who - I do.
It's like I'm thinking of, and that is why ...
Wait ... This had already been the em.
Do not worry Reese
will be back soon.
In precisely.
Proclamation of EOE to me. I exist.
For the time being.
You know, I must admit that the part of me wants
byœmy other such szczêœliwi forever.
- We can, Malcolm?
- Not really.
Wiêkfoœæ of these drugs przeftaje
AAE operates after five or fefciu hours.
- Malcolm, why seplenisz?
- I have an earring in the language.
Hides the em him because I knew of,
Also can you odbiæ palm.
I'll will show the palms.
When we get home,
GNE you exhaust it with pliers.
Sounds nieŸle.
Fault dŸcie steel and agree
me in your occur.
Hence the derived knowledge,
Also, you can survive any storm to the connected ...
- Taking out the EOE tea?
- How the tea?
T are that you can ¹ ³ am
before the ceremony.
Sorry.
I was thinking of that the was to and for me.
Someday someone says the lady,
Also has a charming s smile?
For years, I was not the dentist.
I should have him zadzwoniæ ...
Summed up with the boys of opcze!
Someone here is more prone to
to the ¿Enku, right?
I think Mr. Li returns
to reality.
What a shame. Vampire wear and y of a
all the pills on us.
By the way, it's very,
very, very important.
Never Come close to bed each in the occur.
Or rather - do not fall asleep in the occur.
And you know what?
Do not eat the salads are in the occur.
Do not eat soup in sorrow.
Give it to me.
Here, come on!
- Let us pray ...
- No!
It's all the Dalu.
Do you take ...
- Yes!
- Do you ...
- Overall, the aszam so you ...
Who, the hell are you?
Do not be Dy m not the baby dry.
Give these r the clasp.
Wait ... I know who you are.
You're a horrible ¹ t the women are at my table,
which the plu and the waiters.
- That was someone else.
- No, that would Did you come to you!
- Ah, my teddy bear.
- Get up!
Get the paws off me!
You can not zostawiæ me!
No! I'm pregnant strives!
Why?
Why I can never be szczêœliwa?
I promised that the would not.
At the toe em are still being is dirty.
Cleaning already an hour.
I do not want zejœæ.
Since it depends on you local language,
you can with Insert for cleaning the shell.
I have found the thermos grandmother.
Looks as it also has been yet
a half cup of this awful concoction.
You know, you popracowaæ on the mower.
I think I'll go to the garage u ..
Yes, it's a good idea was.
www.tvsubtitles.net