/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Do you think that the children are œni?
/ Malcolm in the Middle
/ 5x21 - Reese Joins The Army (1)
Jamie finally fell asleep ¹ ³!
Not yet finished the review of the EOE Daae bills?
How I Know-error which of them
are most urgent?
Strict warning is obviously urgent,
than a final warning,
¿but different color is pink
the more serious backlog of oœciach.
And in this case
are still being said the "please".
Can somebody I przynieœæ
Legend of the car?
- I'll go!
- Let me help you!
It's Beth.
From the month girl Reese.
I'm beginning to really operates AAE nerves.
First, their faces enchanted children
then the faces of kids chattering on the phone,
and now faces constantly banging the smokers themselves are the olatów.
In the end I will not knew of whether it is the
the entire sawing, or by the angle shared bath!
The Reject. Now what does the vet?
Dewey restore the bird to life?
The feds arrested today Morrison.
Turn off the skin in the adziku and had wywarzaæ door.
God, has not yet finished
of these arrests?
Dewey, He could not play the byœ
for a moment?
S ³ Look, I must opanowaæ
Debussy and Ravel until tomorrow morning.
The selection panel for the festival m³ young musicians
not impress themselves up etudes.
- What?
- I'm just saying how it is.
Thank you for your attention.
Well, you go uczyæ.
Moment, where my calculator?
- I'll get it.
- I'll go with you!
Fasten your seat belts!
I am an agent Stone, this is Agent Scurry.
We're with the FBI.
I was thinking of that the only squirrel
because no retention of em up.
God, give me all the,
Eby ¿æ undo the time.
It's about a company,
for which you work.
Over the past eight months
prowadziliœmy 230 criminal cases.
You are still the target strikes the new people.
It is beautiful!
In addition to your faculty em.
But we are on the verge of planting Ken Wickstead.
Ken Wickstead?
We have already what you need, you only need to
Confirm keel key Detailing.
I've seen the Ken someday you Wickstead
change are lying their data
Directory section 13 B after
as has been signed by the company s audit?
What? No ...
You also mentioned the case of foreign
account, for example in the Cayman Islands
or a villa?
He says something about the villa?
Probably not.
Hal ...
Look good in memory.
Think about what a properly memorized the EOE,
or about what you should confirm.
You want me to break k ³ ³?
It depends on whether you acknowledge it,
what we all already know the,
or can you want sprowokowaæ
Furi U.S. government?
So ... or can you podjechaæ
ê at schools for my child?
I have forgotten my second œniadanie Daae them.
Beth!
- Your parents already fallen asleep?
- Yes, but what are you doing here?
Thinking of am also working to póŸna.
- Why are you so clothes the EOE?
- Because of d is used some time I was thinking of at this moment,
And I want to be and the ideal.
Beth, I want to tell you something ...
I love you, Beth.
I love you.
God, it will be awful for you
and very sorry for it.
- What do you mean?
- I want with you zerwaæ.
All right.
No problem.
And that ¿³ em joking about ..
Yes, no problem.
S ³ Look, Reese.
It's not your fault, but mine.
We just are money,
I can also trafiæ better.
We should zerwaæ now
before things get the ...
You can uciszyæ this music?
I'll go better already ...
Reese ... I can a discount of up Insert
to your level, and I will make of it ...
What is it?
Reese, discontinue. You'll wake my parents!
You do not want to zrobiæ ...
It's not like ...
She flew me hit them!
Do not kill me please!
You can hack me on the fingers,
... Or if you're tired,
be the same after the breaks!
I want, byœcie were szczêœliwi ...
³ am thinking that this will be a fine of piêœci fight.
I mean, I can ¿³ ebym and its oczekiwaæ,
but understandable and I would.
- They wanted byœ angle of the break?
- You do not say.
This large s nothing at all, he said.
Visitors are not ¿you are joking, Lois.
And are everywhere.
It's frightening box.
I like the them.
I qualified for strict ego finals u
I must just tell them,
How many members of my family comes.
Dewey, we are talking about somehow something
large a serious important.
So I'll I and all
were interested in?
One.
Do you know how to
Visitors are working are those?
Find the jakiegoœ mollusk,
Which of the amine are under any pressure,
so to save you the effort of the bed.
- Shame on you for both of us.
- This is America, Hal.
Not poœlesz k of amstwami to jail someone,
who may be innocent!
You're right!
And you know what? At the moment, I'll tell them.
Unloaded the EOE me your hands and feet!
What more do you want!
Your eyes,
in my chocolate dessert!
But I'll œlepy!
A dessert will be just a little better!
I'm the worst brother ever!
Malcolm! Malcolm! River in Obuda up!
Reese been solved.
What? Where are the gone?
Not that I wrote.
"My own brother in the wbi of my feet in the heart, blah, blah, blah ...
a few drops of ez ... blah, blah, blah ...
¯ Goodbye forever. "
S ³ Look, Mom and Dad are very
this will be taken over the.
Do not mention it,
until he is my musical festival.
/ Leave him alone!
What's going on? What are you doing?
Wickstead give-away of you, Hal.
He told us all of your account information
the Cayman Islands, the authorization of the documents, the villa ...
Everything.
Do not give him even Insert the gatek?
As soon as we get
an agreement.
This is ridiculous.
He does not fit into the prison.
I do not even know how to have to write
is a word in the crosswise cafeteria.
I love you, baby!
Ignition AAE phone bill
Such use would you zadzwoniæ!
And closing the push house key
before he switch the ...
Sir!
Please calm down.
You need a lawyer.
Not this from Reese. Jakiegoœ good!
- Please become easy!
- Ch ³ boys, go home!
Ch of boys, daddy loves you!
Do not worry, the
- I warn you for the last time!
- I believe in the American sprawiedliwoœæ i ..
I must skreœliæ Tate ...
Do not worry, Hal.
I'll be in the morning.
Yes, I'll get you shaving
and a toothbrush.
No, Hal.
Do not get it off.
Repeat.
Well ...
I love you.
This is not proof!
It's my birth control pills of the Company.
I'll bring the am it with each other!
Dog tracking the months pointed to them.
I can not help it.
What is wrong with you?
Zostawiæ me although the one the.
Francis, we need not
more problems.
And you let it s not important
przychodziæ here!
When this is all over,
We will paliæ hence the rubber, until the Montreal!
Please do not straszyæ, right?
Bed herein represents the c ...
Are ... and your flashlight!
The lawyer is to zjawiæ at seven.
If falters up, give him something to eat.
But the gratin with tuna,
must starczyæ for the next four days.
Let us hope that
Also if your father ...
- Someone needs to pozmywaæ.
- Do not worry, Mom.
Do what you have to do,
and we will take care of the house.
I must AEOI.
Remind me to Feel invited the father of medicine for allergy
and suit the interrogation of listening.
You want me to do the something I?
You can ukraœæ brother's girlfriend.
- Wait, it already does the EOE.
- I know that what I do of was to awful.
You know me, I know it!
And I do not want forgiveness.
But we should Daae me a chance,
I can prove the that the'm not in the y
My eyes are here ...
I must only znaleŸæ Reese, that's all.
It should not be difficult.
Because the dock d like poleŸæ Such use?
Welcome to the U.S. Army.
Your home for the next three years!
Under the force behind the yellow goose with the yellow line when
the admissions office!
Do not struggle can try Kow d ¿¹ c
domyœleæ to which s is used the other lines!
Ruszaæ!
Dosyæ not good?
At this place enough!
Standing!
Surely you have Eighteen years?
To prove this, I have a driver's license.
All right, Corporal Jetson!
Wracaæ the formation!
/ I'm rubbish!
/ Fits the garbage bin!
Fit into the trash bin!
- It must carry the?
- The choice was to house arrest or imprisonment.
Unless you selected a well.
Well ...
From the rim of semi-famous signal to the base station.
Board's recommendation must be from the
at a distance of up to 9 meters.
- Can I brothers in the shower?
- Now you yelling at me.
We limit is about 3 meters.
- What are you doing?
- Wyjaœniê you how it operates a
Can you have judgment are large,
I tell the truth ... but the c
I can adjust it as I please.
300 km,
or 10 inches.
Look, it's your vacation in Las Vegas!
Oops, you can not exit the the bathroom!
Lois, I work as a defender of
ex officio of ten years,
and I can tell that the settlement is
not that of a disaster are.
We can pójœæ to admit it
nionego to committing fraud in cahoots!
After ¿about it in precisely
is accused wife!
You or pen?
S ³ Listen, I know how busy you are,
but since then have only one client!
Innocent of a man with four children and that are on the,
which force can popaœæ into oblivion.
Please, grant that this is not about the doshas
You have a family of my ocaliæ!
- You're the only person ¹ ¹, which can help to m!
- Lois, I swear I'll be also worked day and night,
to Pull out of the æ ¿your husband a
My scenario may Wait a couple of months!
I'm sorry, Hal.
I must AEOI to work.
Do not worry, it will survive.
I love you.
- I have the most wonderful the wife.
- Now that you throw me in the face.
Subtracts those half-tor meters.
Next, ¿of the flange.
You're the next one.
The chair of the!
I was thinking of decisions actually like that ...
Take a look at the lifeguard.
Do you take this hairstyle in the hair can be simple,
because they were to fit me perfectly.
If at this stop
I think I can handle it zaczesaæ.
When tempers are, will give up the long-Longer, right?
Do not take me to the the wash each other,
I knew he was also there will be something like this.
Are you afraid of your mother's underwear?
What problem do you see in bieliŸnie mother?
- Stop speak "beautiful mother".
- I do not know how long my mother will still do the trick.
Double change, bills,
interviews with police officers and lawyers ...
- Do not forget about his missing son ...
- Find it!
If someone cares that I'll be
in room piea ...
Part, Mom.
For a while the equipment we cut it of bed,
byœ can flow off after Insert the.
- To which the nastawiæ alarm?
- At the half-past five.
We are ¿Wash with her teeth.
Good morning, maggots!
I want, byœcie understand
why call you maggots!
The larva is of a oœliz, full hare larval form
popular housefly!
We all know what the larvae eat,
And I'll be the one to give you ...
Good God also! In the following order ê sure that the there's a
ny really important reason.
- Wait a minute ...
- Of course ...
Already.
Wyjaœnisz me what happened serial of the
of your inventory?
Replace the I go to the
and piea other kadrid ¿s!
So just give the EOE your backpack
and semi-repellent coat?
Backpack as domyœlam up
Pulling off was achieved with the corpse, and semi-coat ...
Is going to rain?
/ How does he do the.
Oh, God also! Jamie!
Jamie, darling Come to daddy.
Come on.
Look what's in your cart!
Look, it's something that you like best!
Jamie wchodŸ not there!
It's dangerous!
No, no ... Stay away from this away!
Do not touch it!
That's my boy the pack
- S ³ I'm listening?
/ - Hello, Hal.
/ I have information that can help you.
- What? Who is this?
- You do not say.
But I know that you are innocent
and I can prove they are.
/ We spotkaæ up
in jakimœ zat of embossed place.
- But I can not ...
- Do it if you do not want to hit the pud hit them!
- Why do not you come to me?
/ - Your home is the observation.
The phone may
pods have your hearing.
We will meet on Thursday, at noon, on the site,
you're talking about when you go to the new toner cartridge.
- "The world P donuts"?
- Well ... Plan B.
Place of which you speak,
when "you have a dentist appointment."
/ - Do not tell me where it is!
/ - I understand.
Hey, I know who you are!
You're ...
My jewels and the breath does not care about me!
Plug the I or the base station to the battery.
I remodel the cell so that
that operates and the like landline phone.
Not only backpack feces
farther than 30 feet.
Do not worry!
I masked the bracelet perfectly!
Can you believe, for your mom
and wanted to oddaæ is blind?
Note that you need to be at home
before the fourth, the mother will come back.
You understand how important it is to Hold the
in front of her the secret?
Francis, make sure that Malcolm would not betray the me
as is the custom.
Of course.
Well, rookie ...
EOE polished the shoes faster than others.
How on earth will the EOE this miracle!?
³ I will do just exactly that,
What do you me the sermons.
Pull out the æ laces, and language,
to Insert the past ...
pressed by tugging the æ language and laces,
Repeat.
I will do the same thing with the Put quite
and the mailbox for personal items.
This is the most amazing transformation of the whole,
are seen as the em.
Explain the recruits how to
one a soldier ashamed of them all!
Just myœleæ I ceased.
I figured the concluded
Also the problem was to Using the brain.
Not only here, but in the entire ¿my life.
When I'm doing exactly what I also ka,
... Then everything becomes easy.
It's not even about being m the Drym,
or g of UPIM ...
I just turn into a tool.
I feel this way szczêœliwszy.
I najszczêœliwszym
tool used in the world.
You must be proud of yourself, son.
I do not know.
I'm looking to you to me he said.
Bo ¿e .. ¯ a soldier like you
appears once in a thousand years.
- Mom! Did you come to come back earlier.
- Yes! I got fired.
What?
Issued a pm to someone two thousand dollars the rest,
instead of twenty.
But you know what?
Get used, we'll be on Insert,
I'll find another the job,
and in the meantime I'll start robiæ dinner.
In the morning they took to repair the fridge ...
All right!
We'll get through this ...
All right, he's fine.
Just briefly been solved my eyes ...
We'll get through that, too.
As long as we have each other, we are together,
we are the family.
Where's the father?
He is not ...
I think I'll take a shower.
Left, right, left, right ...
Up, slide, ¿shots ...
From left to right!
From the front to the back of the!
Schyliæ up ...
Zasun ¹ æ!
/ Library
"Cases brought after searching"
One ... two ... three ... four ...
Twenty dziewiêæ ... thirty-.
S ³ Look, I do not have much time.
I know all those who are involved in this
I know exactly what they did,
- Because they helped to em.
- What?
Ignition ACILIA million.
The rest of em and sat looking at the can of em up
like you for it gets hit.
But then I found out the August that the dying.
I have been on top of the above-half years.
- God, I'm so sorry.
- I will not go to the grave with all that on my conscience,
So all of them annoy and tell the truth.
We can not zdradziæ our intentions.
These are the very Pote differs.
If only he had found out,
fabricated to new documents, and we we would be finished.
Do not see you already
pending hearing are going.
No herring to me.
These ¿I must load the oddaæ a pair of hose extensions my conscience,
the overdue books ¿ek.
- You can although the porozmawiaæ us?
- I'm in the shower, honey.
Yes, we do.
You're there for three hours.
The water's probably cold.
Am I bothering you your head,
when you're in the shower?
/ First Place
Mom, Listen to.
I know how difficult this is for you.
I know how much you're scared.
But you know what?
Your family relies on you.
And though it seems impossible,
you have to take the æ in garœæ again.
One time only please!
You know, also you can do it!
One of the jiffy ...
I'm in the shower!
Excuse me, sir.
Œpieszy are you?
- I'm busy today ... you know.
- That's your bag?
- No, of course, also not.
- Check the j.
I think it's a bomb!
Do hence the leave!
- I can not.
- Please odejœæ on the distance min. 50 meters!
I can not! I'm ...
- I'm in the ward engineers!
- What?
That's right.
It is better to take care of this are professional.
Damn it!
In the week before retirement!
- You take the security, it bombs are.
- Of course.
/ CI CONTINUED NEXT G ¥ ¥ PI ...
www.tvsubtitles.net