Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.916fps 175.3 MB
You ¹ æ load by inch on the sides,
zostawiæ tip and wygoliæ rear.
/ Reese, doing the am is already a million times.
Mom, look! I now burst of the shirt,
Another place to look when you are I will give the drains.
Where Did you come to forbid me to walk perfectly well.
I do not know why I do these things,
that you are angry.
But the funny thing is,
Also I do not care!
Damn, Dewey, to the room!
- Let's get this behind us are!
- No, Mom!
Count to 10!
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x04 "Thanksgiving Feast"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Tomorrow's Thanksgiving Feast.
I'll tell you what I will give thanks to for the.
Finally, the em up zaprzyjaŸni
with ordinary young kids. Ordinary white.
We sit here an entire afternoon of the South, and no
mentioned of having an allergy to grass, or pollen.
Malcolm has not noticed that the am before,
of which have no eyes.
Really?
Kirsten Stewart. I think he likes me,
but I'm not sure.
Scatters and I ogromniasta the g words.
G ³ mainly by such things.
I must lecieæ people. Tomorrow I am doing
events. Thanksgiving Feast.
3-packs of beer, we need to wypiæ.
- Your parents are away?
- Do not.
NieŸle, yeah.
Of course.
£ adniutki back of the books.
Why would spoil the EOE?
I know what I want zrobiæ.
He wants me zmyliæ.
Wyprowadziæ balance.
And you know what? It does not ...
- Reese!
- Wear an apron.
It's 6:30 in the morning.
I know that. This means that I have
exactly 12 hours to create
Best world the feast of Christmas
in the history of the world treats the holiday season.
Why the przeœcierad of a?
- I can not rozpraszaæ me.
- Not thinking ...
Do you remember chocolate soufflé,
who will do the I 2 years ago?
Yes, that would be the o ..
This rat compared vomit
to present plans!
- A year pancakes?
- To the y ..
Shit at dinner tonight!
Do not take it as the meal to.
It will be, like eating the Mona Lisa.
Reese, you can not compete ...
Oh, my God also?
What do you need?
Bezmyœlnego, automatic
perform all my ¹ dishes.
And we can all zjeœæ
which falls on the floor of.
Go To Dylan.
I'll be back for supper.
Dylan, whom we met there,
because you are afraid
I find also sure that the selected the EOE
to deal with the ego colleague?
It's all right, Mom. The bed is as from other
the kids from school y It's something like a party.
- I really want to AEOI.
- Your family is ¿is some kind of a party.
This is called Holy Thanksgiving.
There will be band of colleagues,
EOE know where the last week,
the only people who years
labored, ¿ebyœ had the house.
There will me a few hours, okay?
You mean a few hours, when
during the birth of EOE lock up in the middle?
Half an hour?
I do not understand what is so
of the ego in our family.
Well understood.
Why do you prefer spêdziæ Feast
Thanksgiving with someone else?
The love her!
And if we are such dead from the center,
To understand the ¿Eby, it's me you ¿al!
No, Dad, I understand.
How to buy up a toothbrush,
it does not want its opuszczaæ.
- Œmia of a, say it, Lois.
- Szczêœliwego Public holidays of Thanksgiving.
- I'll go out there and say that the do not come.
- Do what you want.
Despite that the beat of your brother
hundreds of miles along with her are.
- With the Piam.
- I know her name.
There will be a whole family and spend the
lovely Thanksgiving Feast.
/ I will not say the quieter!
Do you think that the domyœl are not off after
5 minutes fail for divorce?
- I'm sorry, we have no problems of that.
- Ma ³ s problems?
So call it figured out
I also our continuity and that the angle of amstwem?
Part, Mom.
Malcolm, the better professional aj father.
Malcolm!
Whole event is pretty cool.
And you know, I think I chewed the Kirsten.
It's some kind of a friendship.
And not seksualnoœæ.
Again, it does.
Beer! My stepfather as many drinks
Also never counted.
Malcolm?
- Yes, of course.
Part, how you doing?
Need czegoœ,
¿Eby warm the cold of the boat.
But no offense to your mom,
I love the very j.
- Cool, Art
- Okay, go have fun.
Somebody will lose the beer?
'Scuse me. My parents in relation to
beers are a little less at ease.
In the following order ê sure that the whole regret, as nine-year-old.
What?
What? Approx.
This time, I know what he's doing.
This invitation.
Ê will show her how kisses 9-year-old.
Hey.
/ Do not forbid me to semi-AkAA!
/ My tears of it fills the ocean, and the back of the padlock
/ Pop it in the yniesz new force without me!
- How did it happened?
- This is terrible.
- What's the look, Hal?
- Come on, Lois.
From the beginning he wanted Did you come to exterminate the Union of,
and now you are getting a divorce, and you
you do not have anything in common?
Please.
Really do you think that the'm so Pote be,
¿Eby dyrygowaæ other ludŸmi?
In addition you are?
I know our son also speaks of the end
Notes This is the ¿he never supports Did you come.
Hal, this is ridiculous!
- Well, I pogadaæ with Francis?
- Yes! No! No, no, no ...
In this way, you have reached your goal æ ¹.
All right.
They did not say to them are the word.
Wait a minute.
Nothing to say
and allow himself to rozlecieæ.
- I understand your the GRE, Lois.
- Hal! What do you want me to do the ¿and?
No, no. There are still gniesz
me in its insidious plan.
Thank you very much.
No, she is all the jumble Did you come to this, Lois.
Itself from the payment of the part.
See? A true taste of balsamic
otherwise feel in the mouth.
Well, back of EOE.
I'm starting przygotowywaæ
And Provencal herbs and fried mushrooms Insert.
You have again wyszorowaæ these pots.
What?
No, I have just finished the em.
Dad, Imagine:
the core toasted tuna,
or in a Mexican stew,
or any of the dish,
break the cymi, the background ustymi banks.
But not today!
Today, the axis of the gniemy top.
- You're with me, Dad!
- No!
This pot is adequate clean, Reese.
No one will feel the difference the differential!
No good.
So one does not taste the it!
O my God e
Dewey, you have something for me zrobiæ.
No! Nothing more.
I've had fairly.
If I have the oskrobaæ Another radish,
Another wypatroszyæ or the Shrimp ...
- Dewey, ... trust me?
- Do not.
- Are you afraid of me?
- Do not. Not for long-u ¿s the long run.
Come on, Dewey.
We need a few things that
I do not want my dad zawracaæ g halfway.
You have $ 80 from the wallet dad.
Components of the $ 240 cost money.
So you have to be cuddly.
Can you handle?
- I'll take the rest?
- Consent.
Mom, can we porozmawiaæ?
No, darling, please.
Do not talk with me about it.
Not important what I say, then I should.
He must deal with t poradziæ the women are.
- With the Piam.
- I know her first name.
Send you listen to me only?
- If Piama and I we take divorce ...
- Francis, do not even say it.
Serious no, really you should not.
What had the EOE tell?
When we part, I will
Such use here a while pomieszkaæ?
God, Francis,
I do not want even the myœleæ.
But yes, if it will become this horrible
thing, it will be here mieszkaæ Such use.
Thanks, Mom.
That was a silly k g of the quarrel, but that of a
symbol of all of the ego in that of the Union.
- I mean, there are rules.
- Rules are important.
I know that. So what if
Also I enjoy a couple of beers,
I looks as the front of colleagues,
I give the woman a lead?
- What?
- I do not care about the her my feelings.
What!
What?
Of all the grams of stupidity that
You said ever, Francis,
This is the worst.
- I was thinking of, you're a mine.
- You do not even have a party!
Now go and apologize to the women's t!
You say fail for the EOE mistake,
and she is absolutely without fault!
- Really ...
- The Ides!
Approx.
Yes, it's an idiot.
Okay, Dad.
Pull the bird.
- Such an EOE buy the turkey?
- It's perfect.
It is very small y
As was to be larger, ...
it would not fit onto the to observe this!
As you insert our dinner at this monster!
This ¯ Monkfish.
Juice of ¯ abnicy after the connecting up of the turkey.
The taste of turkey satisfy fish.
Create two are one fantastic dish.
Reese, it's probably not a good idea was.
I do not know, Dad.
Can you're right.
Can I have no idea what I'm talking about.
This should Operate AAE.
S ³ Listen, my beautiful beast.
Yesterday sucks Did you come to trash the ocean floor.
Today, you dance tango with the Gods!
Yes, sir.
I'll be for you delicious.
Ok, the situation looks as much better.
I'm definitely more or
less certain that the likes me. So thinking.
Looks as it
You're a leaded by the aperture of the figure eight.
Jesus, the aperture leaded?
Can not noticed that the a
Malcolm, you give me the chalk?
Le ¿s next aperture unleaded cheese dip.
Ok, ok
I know that I was to a little artificial.
No, I think that in terms of the
the aperture leaded the money.
That's it.
Sorry, hit the am
the aperture to owiowy's the point?
Can you think that the a flirt, but
that's not true. This ordinary and wrogoœæ.
No, I'm pretty sure also to flirt.
Really?
I do not think I'm in this
as good as the thinking of am.
Before old age.
Son, these truffles are very expensive,
and as the EOE lose the money it's not my problem.
But ...
They told me to Buy truffles.
I do not know why, but ...
Parents said that the it
Cheap output will be the Feast of Thanksgiving.
My boss is a jerk anyway.
Thank you ... very much.
³ I saw him talking Did you come with Francis, Lois.
I can not powstrzymaæ Did you come up, right?
Did you come wbiæ had to wedge.
Hal, he said am he that the Piama
He's right, and sermons of his przeprosiæ am.
Approx. I'm not that smart meters are,
¿Eby wymyœliæ what you're up.
But, as will become something of the ego,
This blame you.
- Dad, what is it?
- Chopped onions.
Chopped. I specifically asked the
of diced!
- Come on, Dad!
- Not for me podnoœ Voice, Reese!
- This is not funny.
- Hilarious!
No, Dewey, it's not funny!
I guess none of you do not understand,
nothing here but we do not play!
- Are at stake the life!
- Not true.
Okay, but it's very important.
We create something special.
Something wonderful. Something Beautiful!
- Why do I have a wallet in another pocket?
- You can skupiæ up, Dad?
There was to $ 80!
I had to!
The cheese from the refrigerator to the uneatable!
Reese, you have a great being inconvenienced!
And you know what, I've had fairly.
Go!
From helping.
Are still being spelled with the food!
Well, the Ides! Do not need you!
Are still being have Dewey!
It is two times better assistant
than you'll ever be!
Why are you still with her are not talking of EoE?
He will not let me. As to her
approaches the am, then leaves the room.
Piama, I know also that were
between us various differences.
You mean the oziêb e, uncomfortable silence,
interrupted the insults are disguised?
No kissing of me as that.
Here's what I'm trying tell.
I believe in is the ¿eñstwo.
I believe in every time you have the ¿eñstwo.
And if you listen to Francis H,
you will love what you hear.
All right.
Francis?
I'll leave you alone.
Did not want to interfere am up the caæ,
But I'm glad that the will do the am.
- Something you do the a, Lois?
- Talking on the am of the Piam.
It is interested in
what Francis wants to tell.
He will tell her exactly what he is told the am.
What's it to you, also I do not want carry the strings?
- What?
- Piama, I have not finished the em!
See what's going on, Lois?
I do not care
as I cut into the mushrooms, go!
We will always have some foreign
Part of the owiekiem Use embracing in a world over!
Do not need you!
I do not need anybody!
/ This is the worst
/ Feast Thanksgiving ever!
This is the best
Feast Thanksgiving ever!
Remember that as
¿Eby never zapomnieæ.
This is the best
Feast Thanksgiving ever!
Remember that as
¿Eby never zapomnieæ.
Where are we all?
Fireworks?
The bastards! None of us said no!
The hell with them!
I'll be talking of.
Good evening, sir.
Part of.
Where are we all?
Learn the up, probably.
I think so.
And he asleep?
I think I ate too much of a turkey.
Or is kryptonite.
At the top of the pie.
Thank you.
It's a very generous gift.
/ I know that e ..
Malcolm, the already gone.
I really appreciate a piece of szarlo ...
I think it reads better signal y
Are you all right?
He will return the am.
Next, ... let's do it.
Start?
I must AEOI.
My brother will kick your ass,
how do you say to someone!
- What kind of things?
- Piama, well, I need you.
Stir it all the time.
Well, well.
I must wepchaæ to circulates Kow
pumpkin baked peppers,
dokoñczyæ stuffing ...
¯ Monkfish!
Where's the kitchen gloves?
- I poszukaæ?
- No, you are still swirling!
There are no washers, paper
towels! Need czegoœ!
- I'll get a towel from the bathroom!
- No, there's no time!
I must j are drawn by tugging the æ exactly at 17:38.
Not at 17:37, not 17:39.
What do you do?
Only one thing can I do?
- Reese, no!
- Yes!
- Make room!
- Where?!
Move kitchen gloves!
/ Where's Malcolm?
He knows that the should be here,
This Thanksgiving Feast.
Yes, definitely not
wanted to be the przegapiæ.
End of em.
It starts to treat.
- In the same time.
- I'm g of the hungry.
Can I exit?
/ Turkey with ¯ abnicy.
Refusal to prayer?
Thank you, ladies, for talent,
which expresses the continuity ê me to your
family in the only way I know how.
- Amen.
Part, party goers.
God, you're drunk!
What the hell is wrong with you are wrong?
I'll tell you what's wrong with me are wrong.
In hell.
I'm drunk because I'm a coward.
I probably gay.
Wyœlizgnê the perfect opportunity and I
between his fingers.
And you know what? I was thinking of,
Also forget about getting drunk the c up.
What do you think, what your
darling do now, Mom?
What darling? The room!
Reckon up with you later.
I go into the room where the
I finish what I'm trying to tell.
Hey, come back!
Shrimp are still being are good.
I left a j are on the floor
and the I went, the c staggers home.
¯ Eby spryskaæ us with his affection.
Yeah.
There is nothing to wstydziæ.
Distance was not the large white achievements,
but the noise that the months are impressive.
- You'll see more than the?
- ¯ Are you kidding me?
I do not believe in it.
We were alone, she wanted to and of doing this.
I would I were in immediately the next.
Why chicken out of em?
Do not use the EOE that also was to a drunk?
Mom probably still asleep.
I have a ban on television and computer games.
I have a semi-clean the tiles in the kitchen
and the bathroom to brush the teeth.
Wymyæ every time you window in the house
and change diapers
Jamie for 6 months.
No, as you pass out of it EoE
he said a 9 Any more things.
You need something zrobiæ, Lois.
Piama and I ask the
a ride to the station.
Am thinking of, I also will not interfere the caæ.
Ok, take back everything I said the.
You can up the caæ interfere as you want,
just fix it!
I'm ready.
Piama, I want to tell only one.
I know that separation are painful,
but in the long-in the long run,
This is best for you.
Best?
Francis fault than serious smoke.
This is the ¿eñstwo was to doomed to failure tablespoon.
You'll be better friends of me ...
after the divorce.
Who speaks of a divorce?
I love Francis.
You can not znieœæ as
someone is szczêœliwy, right, Mom?
Come on, baby.
Let's pack my things.
These are the in œmieciach.
I'm sorry, honey.
Nothing is fixed on, baby.
Once again, we do not appreciate Did you come.
We are not well trained
is the pkami as thinking Did you come.
Thank you, darling.
www.tvsubtitles.net