/ Can you see it?
/ (Trampoline - $ 250)
I want a trampoline for my birthday.
It's the sweet, but we can not afford.
/ (Skateboard - $ 79)
You can email her the dostaæ,
to resign from the party.
/ (Dr ¹ ¿ek pogo - $ 19.99)
This is perfect.
Will be so surprised!
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x15 "Reese apartment"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 175.6 MB
That's the best part of my day.
16 minutes between horror at the school,
and horror at home.
Malcolm!
Here you are.
It Ira James, do you know him?
Best months of the attack,
best wings mid season?
Who am I kidding.
Probably never talks to him the EOE.
Hiya.
Ira ends this year ê schools.
Get a lot of calls from college.
All right, but I want the ¿Eby
wrote an essay on the application.
- So ...
- So, Ira's an idiot.
It is at the level of the hamster.
And only if we take
very g of hamster play the fool.
Mom says I have also other advantages.
Since you're a najm are smarter in school,
that you will help him You have to write an essay.
With the willingness, but I have three tests
in the next week.
You do not understand.
Ira is a footballer.
This means that the when czegoœ needs
are those non-athletes, as you are giving it to him.
Cheerlederki to understand the.
It may a little potrwaæ, so
relieves you of the WF-at the end of the semester.
- WF does not bother me.
- Of course, also not mózgowcu.
/ Part, honey.
You need to calm down.
- Jesus. Who this time?
- Do not speak until you calm down.
Reese. Okay, g the êboki breath.
What does the?
All right.
Reese ...
Honey, I want tea,
or drink?
What happened with your dad?
Found out of what she would do the Reese.
And what do the?
Your brother ...
Oh, my God also?
They had ewakuowaæ?
What a day. Features a large lose of your ¹
the second hand machine meat.
I close the sanel of us for 15 minutes.
The whole of that afternoon south graliœmy.
Sit down!
I want to Know-how
do the EOE something so horrible!
And thinking of EOE, also get away with a semi-otal!
You said:
break free or suffocate?
What are you talking about?
You know what we mean.
In some foreign Zesz week ...
In the developing world
these things are happening on the ound of!
What I have with you zrobiæ, Reese?
I will not say
Also it was to complete the inflection,
because when you say that,
to treat it as a challenge!
You know what?
I labored like the ox of 6 hours!
I do not like the screams to me
Upon entering the house!
Not complaining!
Do not complain, oœle!
Hal, give yourself another the minute!
You can store both up close the!
Oh shit. In this family so
is called "closing the door".
What is certain is that the Reese will not be
living here for the next six days ¿.
The only question is,
Who will get the ball this honor.
- Going out
- Come out!
No, if first we get to the knobs!
- Wynoœ hence the up!
- The elevation of the hence the!
I won the I!
/ Again dug Reese?
Yes, I've seen the with him
for two days. It's impressive the box.
Usually after this time eats
Karma cats Mrs. Harvey.
This is terrible! How can such a
robiæ in the asnemu child?
Yeah, it's very traumatic.
Do not worry about the the fact
How causing injury to his psyche?
/ Home is not czegoœ dependence niony!
The house should be friendly,
safe i ..
- Really?
- What?
They kicked me, and I had the 15 years.
/ I already I will not return to the house.
/ They can not zrobiæ this Reese'owi.
I must zrobiæ something.
Someone has their powstrzymaæ!
Only I understand it,
what they are monsters!
For the rest of the family, it is not
such a big problem as for you.
Can exaggerate.
I'm exaggerating? Dewey, as we will
haunted you will understand.
S are in life certain things,
called priorities.
Wyjaœniê you in a few
hours when I arrive.
Now I must zadzwoniæ
to Otta and make it easier to break.
Exaggerating.
Œwietne timing,
muffins are ready.
Thanks, also rang EOE.
I do not believe for the hell of the
you przejœæ by their parents.
/ Whose cottage?
This is mine.
Fully furnished and with the cable.
I he said that the 18 years I have
and they gave me two years the lease ¿awe.
Do you like banana, right?
Reese, you can not mieszkaæ in such a place!
In precisely that the I can.
They are special offers.
The first month of the free, then
$ 375 per month, utilities included.
I can zarobiæ for rent
A week, as I'll get overtime.
I should of doing this a half years ago.
Reese, come, let's go to the roof.
Students from the school were nursing
are taking a break for a smoke.
I can not.
My brothers are will come for breakfast.
Francis, this is Teddy, Lou, George.
Divorced, separated,
¿Asleep with her best friend.
He was a white best friend.
I'm sorry.
Okay, you know where we'll be.
- Hey, it's the wedding meal?
- Yeah.
You better start already chowaæ the money.
Part of the Young man.
This place is awesome!
Reese also know this seems to be great.
But Each objective observer,
also say it's not true.
This place is awesome!
One thing is certain, in your place
I would live here permanently the E!
Who wants cupcakes?
- Me!
No!
¯ no cupcakes!
Reese, you can not
bawiæ in the house!
Parents have done something terrible to you,
as much as I did!
But you do not, you can them that popuœciæ!
This is not your place,
your place is in the house!
No good.
Replace the one thing in my life ¿, which
to be the better if I had been at home.
I was thinking of that the toilet seat is not
require heating the whole is a good argument.
Approx. The most important is that the essay
the application looks as you would any other essay.
You know, like homework.
In one of the lessons.
Next, Ira, I know also that sounds abstruse,
but the best fast start æ.
As if you had one of opisaæ
s the word, what would it was to the word?
Ira.
Approx.
Already we have.
Ira.
You see, we started.
- What else?
- I do not know.
I'm not a writer,
or reader.
I do not like of words, the stare and me
the plant of puzzlement. These are the hundreds of them.
Calm down.
You'll be fine. You know what?
Ask for something and you answer
what you fall into g halfway.
Najwczeœniejszym my memory is ...
Blue ... something.
Something blue.
Well, you can it to use.
How to ...
Sometimes my childhood
is vague and distant e
As something surrounded by the blue mist are.
- See that?
- Yeah, that's cool.
My greatest fear is ...
The spider book.
No, waffles.
I let my fears obmyæ me
and check whether it is branded
repetitive pattern
optimism and despair.
It is not poorly.
I hope that someday
emancipation and search for ...
I do not do?
You AEOI to this
housing and Pulling him here by tugging the æ!
- It does not work as a
- I know, how does it work?
As soon wykopaliœcie me to school were
military also did not co-operative I will show the shampoo of the votes!
When a child becomes for you
the UCI be obtained, it kicks it!
Francis, it's not your business,
already do not live here!
Because I wykopaliœcie!
Now do the same with Reese!
He sits now in the house of the cable,
stack of video games and is nieszczêœliwy!
If there is a nieszczêœliwy,
This alone is provoked!
So 10 times he is provoked?
And Malcolm provoked it 6 times
with my 28 blows out
40 dug out of the house,
3 different Debt children
and are the only fixed the variable
We are the two of you!
Francis, it's not fair!
You also do not want dzieliæ
home with creative Child Lock!
So when Dewey himself to provoke?
When Jamie?
Where is Jamie?
- In a babysitter.
- Only the fifth.
/ For me the continuity's sake, Jane.
/ Zwróæ me are my godnoœæ!
/ Okay, wey the godnoœæ,
/ But let me widywaæ with the children!
/ Just pull the the trigger!
/ He turns her on the ound on!
/ Come on, do not the DY coward and do it!
Dave, is that you?
/ Yes.
Which channels are watching you give?
Sounds better than what I have.
/ Lucille Armstrong
/ Doctor of Psychology
It's for us .. new situation.
Never previously not egzaminowaliœmy
our parenting.
We thought also that something
what comes naturally.
Yes, the animals on the planet
had children were billions of years.
Let us take in also, I never had the s
zajêæ of education, and there are not full.
How exactly do you want,
Eby ¿I help you?
Popadliœmy in the habit of that.
Our sons are poorly we behave,
So we punish them.
Later, the act even worse,
So we punish them severely.
And then keep up the men chose
bizarre, surprising as poorly,
and if we byœmy them so punished,
This landed the dowalibyœmy in jail!
- End the options we have.
- Of course, also like that.
We hope, also thanks to your training,
may want you nauczyæ of us jakiejœ
subtle tricks, ¿Eby their powstrzymaæ.
- Tricks?
- Yeah.
Jakiegoœ secret
psychological trick,
which calms the to them and makes the,
Also the bed we listen.
My husband ¹ ¿ages, but
are still being deal with them one by one,
but as if the connecting forces y ..
You can not traktowaæ children as
criminals, or how furious the e animals.
Do not know Did you come to our sons.
¿I can not imagine what the ck are capable of.
I am a psychologist for 40 years.
I do not surprise already.
All right.
In some foreign Zesz week, Reese ...
Oh, my God, why would he were cats?
- We do not know.
- Give me a minute.
Even in the most extreme
deny the smokers breath,
terrible cases
acting certain techniques.
He says the I, also do not
waste of 90 bucks.
S ³ s yszeliœcie of the active uchaniu?
No.
Most teenagers behaves poorly,
Suggest as are also no one on them depends not y
The active are the uchaniu repeat
everything the child says,
which shows that the you are listening to it
and at the same time understand.
I know it sounds corny,
but trust me, it works wonders.
Reese probably would not reacted to the.
- Worried sure that the he can not help.
- Yeah, and what if matters worse?
I do not know whether the stand k For more troubles with it.
- I'm so confused.
- You're confused.
Yes, I am. Usually
I'm so confident,
but by t the wonder Affairs
over each time the aspect of ...
This is good.
This is very good.
I've understandable that the blue
it is not wrong color,
but also is the color of hope.
Yes, I finished the.
These parts, which are understandable I are cool.
Now that we have written down ideas were,
you need to have to write them with the words that you ...
Thanks, Malcolm.
You're fantastic!
Think the people that the'm so m³ dry.
Not yet skoñczyliœmy.
Wait ...
Blue is definitely
my favorite color.
Hey, collected, Reese!
We have a free shrimp
the Red lobster.
Can meet you there.
I must dokoñczyæ task.
Hey, opuœci the already EOE night air hockey
and Wednesday ob ¿arstwa,
but today we are counting on you.
Someone must zagadaæ
the trick with my tongue.
Ever since I'm from independent,
I feel more responsible.
I have three children, not
you speak of responsibility.
Come on, we do not accept the refusal.
Ok, ok
Mom, I have a problem and I want to pogadaæ.
Well, you can speak,
And I'll listen.
Footballer wants Insert an essay in which
I wrote your application to university.
I know also is unfair,
but in the of ¿y ³ em a lot of work.
I wanted to poradziæ of you.
- Nothing else matters, also will help you.
- Yes, in precisely that he said I was.
It should not dostaæ up
to study the szerstwu thanks fa.
But is this really the fa szerstwo,
if no one believes that it's m³ drego?
No I want to be part of a scam, but
I do not want also prevents easy storage
pójœcia him to college.
I do not know what to do.
You're not sure ...
their intentions.
Yes.
Why are you talking like a robot?
Want to Know-why ...
I'm talking like a robot.
I have a problem and we need
your help!
And you only bezmyœlnie
repeat my words.
You say something, and I shall be recorded.
Forget it, do not want to help me,
but do not you mock me!
Do not come from a family of criminals,
do not let him oddaæ this essay!
He knew am also Listening
children are b ³ ¹ d
Hello?
Hello, is the home of the least care,
gruboskórnych parents in the world?
For you.
Hello?
In precisely to ring me your son, Reese.
Min are already the week and even
We talked with him.
Congratulations, separating families
is complete in 40 per cent.
Francis, a very heavy
and complicated situation.
You do not need to your screams!
There is nothing complicated
idŸcie to his apartment,
also tell him baby
and please suggest to return home.
Distraught of EoE?
We're talking about Reesie!
So what?
Come on,
you know how he thoughts.
The presentation of weakness, it's like
show hyena abdominal antelope!
Reese comes home
without any limits or barriers.
In 5 years we will speak to him
last of the word by a police megaphone!
I only know that the child you have,
that you need!
/ That's not true, he is there
/ Szczêœliwy, just like us!
Dewey, from Insert the hook!
Mom, I understand your concerns,
but the gain, if so post the drink!
I wanted to in this wierzyæ.
Honey, I must koñczyæ,
I have another call.
Hello?
Yes, on the phone.
Says Peter Noyes,
Chemistry teacher Rees.
Remember me
Zesz orocznego of the interrogation of listening.
This is something new that I must of you are omówiæ.
Oh my God, what he's gonna do the?
Your son ...
It has a fifth of TKE for the semester?
They compared the letter, told him to repeat
experiment, the will to yourself!
Mr. Noyes never
saw the bigger the breakthrough!
Wow!
He said that we should
be proud of yourself!
Part of Ira, Listen to, you
with the essay that I wrote?
I wanted to zrobiæ one of the,
Fast the changes.
Yes, you are.
Changes that are zrobiæ I want to ...
- He was for a long?
- Do not.
Listen to Ira, all give you the head start
are doing what you want.
I guess you think that the it is good
but this is not true.
He says are you're a idiot are,
and you're not really him.
You can have to write an essay.
You can have to write in the essay own!
Remember the story of the pound
steak that You attempted zjeœæ?
Thinking of EOE, also is not possible,
but the venom of EOE slowly and you succeeded Fr
You zrobiæ the same with the essay.
Ok, I'll try.
And then the I pretended that the'm Rocky'm
and he said I to Mr. T: "Come on."
I wanted to, ¿a way that its Iroquois fell,
when it hit. The end.
Thanks, Malcolm. Earlier
never the ³ ¹ I or the back of words!
Yeah, that It can,.
This is fantastic. Lemon really
adds this new taste.
- How was your dinner?
/ - I have a half of jakiejœ frozen foods!
/ Less than the last
/ Dinner with you!
- What are you doing here?
- We can inputs?
- Yes. Give dinner?
- No, but thank you, Reese.
Serious not have oven
with hot air.
I can upichciæ frittata in 10 minutes?
It is immaculate.
Reese przyszliœmy zrobiæ something here.
I do not agree that our instinct
and even now, I do not feel good about it,
but ... as that the last instinct
fails us, so I'll say it.
What is it?
Reese, I love you and We believe that
Also will be better if I stay here.
Really?
Honestly said the c
you're doing better without us.
Over 17 years with us, spend the EOE For more
time are going to minors than in school.
But now, for 10 days on my own ...
're functioning the CYM
a member of the society.
Wow. I had to be very changed.
I did not have any difficulties ¿.
Mail. I confiscated the your
Victoria's Secret catalog,
at your age ... you show apartment.
Teddy, my parents.
Mom, Dad, you are my neighbor, Teddy.
Welcome.
These presentations give the nieŸle in koœæ, huh?
This place is not that of the e
Next time
jakieœ will bring the plant was.
Super.
Wait a minute.
Hi, I got your ¹ ³ ¹ platinum
card and I want to activate the j.
In 2471.
As early as 3000 I fracture of receivables
/ From my Federal Charter
/ Bank card to Spring Mill,
because I have a $ 8,000 limit there.
But ever since the of K d is the OCI with you
that I wanted to przenieœæ all
to you, because you have $ 20 000 limit.
Sure, willingly talk to the manager.
Hey, I talked to!
You are using a credit card?
How much will the EOE?
10, 11 thousand. But are still being
far from the $ 20 000 limit.
How can the EOE spend it all so much in 10 days!
I bought the oven with convection,
and then the refrigerator looks as of and with him miserably.
Well, I must kupowaæ new clothes,
When looking to the Dirty contacts.
I have a big bell in the bathroom.
And, how do you do it?
Reese, I owe you an Acknowledgement
for giving me confidence.
Over the next days, I will speak
very little about, I'll wymyœlaæ punishment.
Ideas were already flies to me by the
your head, it's very at exciting.
But I do not want AAE operates lightly
and thus we rozczarowaæ.
- Incurring gniesz me so at home?
- We take only your ear.
Like the rest of the ¿wants AEOI,
This is the card may e
Min of the month of the law, and my mother
are still being invent new penalties for Reese.
Says she never was to a
so creative.
Something must robiæ well, because the pop-
it is white streaks in the in the hair.
Malcolm Hey, guess what!
- Adopt me! I'm going to college!
- Really, at that?
To all. A & M, Georgia,
Stanford. And for the full scholarship ne!
Stanford accepted the your essay?
No, I forgot to Insert the
it in an envelope. And so I accepted it.
Do not worry,
essay will not wasted the.
I will give of it as the Semester
at math and I got the fifth ECT.
Thanks, also taught me hello
confidence wierzyæ, Malcolm.
Prove the EOE, also you do not need
help others. See ya.
Stanford, the poor dude.
You probably do not know that the faculty of Astrophysics
takes only three in the country.
www.tvsubtitles.net