Your aunt Felicia supplies the a
2 gifts for the baby.
Ballerina costume ball and the tablespoon?
I did not know of and what to send.
Jamie is a first name for men and women of those.
This will give to the poor.
This g of stupidity! The doctor clearly he said,
Jamie is also ...
Hey, how cool is the small dinosaur.
That's right, just once spojrzeæ
It can, and that the Jamie is ...
Reese, for me the continuity's sake!
No one knows who you are.
Fine of a trial, buster!
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x01 "Vegas"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 175.0 MB
/ Come on, Gordo.
/ One bite and the end.
- What are you doing with my rabbit?
- Gives him the afternoon of Southern bacon.
It's too thick,
karmiæ the crap you have to go.
That I'll take it to the competition
youth of these farmers
and all the bed with me œmiaæ!
This g of stupid poor people who
do not know what we are zrobiæ.
- And what we want to do?
- I do not know.
I had the vision of how the jeŸdzi em on it
the town, smashing the car em.
But this is unfortunately not possible.
What you happened?
Jakiœ idiot not close the the Baku
the tractor and the engine explode.
- Whose is that of a robot?
- My.
The entire operation is a disaster ranch!
The furnace is clogged,
fuel generator is not even
cows from the farm gate is falling apart.
You are responsible for all this.
I do not know what's with you lately
happening, but Wey yourself together.
Otto is a very tolerant boss,
but even he has a limit.
- A fire, a fire, a fire Francis!
- What? Where?
For your cake.
- It's already been a year?
- From 9.31.
So far, the d first 3 hours of the second
year are better than oczekiwaliœmy.
Congrats!
To win the jackpot EOE.
O God, look at this.
What Reese does with his gatkami?
¯ no the money is not the Cause that the look.
What is this?
Diploma for success in science!
- From the state?
- It's nothing.
- Give the them like candy.
- Do not be so modest Dy is wonderful.
And I think that it confirms
Also you can not have earrings.
- How to ...
- Malcolm!
I must with you pogadaæ.
You are reading scientific journals.
What you can tell me about the importance of dreams?
Dreams?
Some people are judging that the expression hose extensions
podœwiadomoœci desires ...
No, no, another type of sleep.
Prophetic, which provide for the future of.
I had the one.
Lay em on the big machine.
This g of stupidity, Dad!
He was so real!
I had the mystical mark on the shirt.
And the balloon and the music
and win the giant jackpot em!
That was sign my son, I know it!
- This is my destiny.
- Dad, are you still have strange dreams!
How to sing this with the cymi œmietnikami.
I never said I was the that the to the prophetic.
He says the I, also was to cool.
- What did they say about Gorda?
- They called him a monster.
Then he said that the
than of committing the crime against nature em.
And may the opposite.
I remember only that the semi-aka the em.
You oczekiwaæ such resistance,
when we try to be God.
Wait for the national competition,
There you will gain respect.
We're not going to the national!
He is in Las Vegas!
Las Vegas?
What's in Las Vegas?
The chance that the by Rees
come to an idiot in front of a white whole country!
Do not worry, son,
do not miss it.
Of course, also go to Vegas.
S you've heard, Malcolm?
It's another sign!
I must only foaming Insert our
insurance, Eby ¿¿borne in travel ...
Dad, are you sure ...
Son, you do not have insurance,
When you're zylionerem.
- It does not make sense.
- First you need to tell your mom.
I will say, I will.
I must just be careful ny.
If it is a good interpreter of manufac ...
$ 1000 bonus at work?
Hal, I'm so proud of you!
Wey into account that the mine
save the idea of ??the 12 million to
Outsourcing flow regulators.
At least it could zrobiæ.
This roast is the part of your Malcolm.
Mr. State's success in science.
It's no big deal.
It is that of a, the great uroczystoœæ in school?
- Reese!
- What ceremony? He was a ceremony?
Yeah, by the mayor,
ali cancels some lessons.
Stop me kopaæ!
For a while I say about TV!
Malcolm, how can the EOE not
decisions actually tell so impor-tant?
We are your parents!
- You're exaggerating, it's great.
- Not for you to decide!
- How can you be so selfish?
- I'm not selfish!
I did not want you there because you oœmieszasz ...
Stop it, stop!
Me ...
All right.
At least I know.
Give Gordowi the piston seal.
Mom, I want the rest of my milkshake?
It is very good.
Thank you, you do not need.
- It is strawberry, also know it's your favorite.
- I'll take him.
Hal, look!
Boone Vincent occurs in Las Vegas.
- Who is Boone Vincent?
- Guys we have.
- Stop it!
- It's a complete idiot.
Women are crazy for him.
He plays all the instruments
and sings in four languages.
And you like it as much as I do.
Please! He said I was so,
¿Eby AEOI with you to bed each.
Then, when you Did you come to a very sick
Did you come and needed rest.
Look, even 12 km to Vegas.
Hal, look at this place!
It's so elegant.
What happened on? Never
EOE saw the 35 pound rabbit?
I was a little spill of about
/ Here.
Honey, you can e ..
O My God!
It is!
Yes!
He knew I was!
God, Hal!
EOE win the Jackpot! I do not believe!
And that, Malcolm?
What you and your learning about it?
We say also have another dream, Dad.
- Do not believe him.
- It is true.
Not about the break of ybyœmy you.
I do not I hear you, Otto.
Too much noise also. Shouting does not help e
Otto Yes, I know about the sump.
I had the j the Repair the week,
but I did not have time.
Otto, do not I hear. Reparation
well, as you are I'll find her.
It's me you hear?
God, look at those tiny rabbits.
What people are doing with them.
I do not know. May the love, hug the
and see the how the kicaj the yard,
because they are capable of so robiæ,
¿when their feet touch the ground.
In the following order ê sure that the Gordo
would this fit onto the mouth.
- Mom ...
- He found the EOE father?
No, I'm ...
It does not matter, Feel invited the am
his wallet on the state line.
We'll see if the damage caused to the tools
with 20 bucks and SD the library.
S ³ Look, as you're a marvel as the are,
Also do not want to send a listen to my apology!
Did you come to will force me to buy them!
Tickets for this idiot, Boone Vincent!
We'll go together.
Respect of the better than I was thinking of.
Seats for VIPs!
Part, I'm Dewey, and this is ...
Good, God, something you will do the
this poor animal?
It's the ugliest specimen of what
I evaluate the judge in my career.
You should wstydziæ up!
/ Disqualification
- Oh, my God also? Oh, my God also? Oh, my God also?
It will help us a photo! Wpadliœmy
to the well, and we can not exit!
If there is someone very nieœmia were,
let them not fear,
He will not krytykowaæ.
When I was to have the white boy of Caucasian teenage boy ...
Otto, please!
No one will hear a!
This leads to Score the d
We can briefly pomyœleæ?
- You never blink?
- Can blink then what are you?
It is not possible!
From where they knew the byœ it?
Can spend less time
Suggest that the camera is my blink,
And so the repair well!
Germany hates the umieraæ in wells!
Good! If you do not like so much
you like my work, then go!
- Imagine that the go!
- I imagine the.
/ God, I do not believe
/ Also see Boone Vincent!
Look at those seats!
/ - It's amazing!
- Another fan?
The tour "Bad Boone Rising"
Did you come on to her?
Sat in the am at the scene,
as had the first heart attack.
They are my sons, Malcolm and Jamie.
¿My Joey is here,
can cool the boys are up zaprzyjaŸni.
Two cocktails with apricots.
/ Ladies and gentlemen!
/ Get ready for a head of wasps,
/ That represents America!
/ It Booooooone!
/ Pink - "I'm Coming Up"
/ Coming, so you better
/ Fire away t the events
/ He's coming, coming
/ Coming, so you better
/ Fire away t the events
/ Go ahead, t are the events on Saturday night
/ We are waiting until I arrive
/ I were fine style, see
/ On my diamond pierœcionki
/ I can do this for hours,
/ If you know what I mean
The worst part is
Also my first concert.
/ I'm coming ...
They are not for you!
Pass it on!
/ I'm coming ...
Did you come to Mia someday dream
that do not meet the than the of?
Surprisingly the sun, but did not.
- Dewey, where would the EOE?
- Part, Reese. This is Crystal.
It turned out that the wystawiliœmy
Gorda in the above categories.
Dalio it to Your Pet pet
and we should to Your Pet breeding!
- The exhibition I go out there and win the!
- What?
Jakiœ Chez Richard ignition pays for it the 3,80 / kg.
Zarobiliœmy 150 bucks!
Chez Richard!
It's the restaurant!
How can the EOE of doing this!
Kill him and eat the the!
Do not you understand?
That was my best friend.
My those ¿!
Do not worry, honey.
My best friend
shot in the restaurant.
Someday you will go.
/ Madonna - "Papa Do not Preach"
/ Dad, do not g axis of the sermon,
/ I'm in trouble
/ I lose the dream
/ But I decided the out
/ They are my children stop
/ We stop his children
P ³ though! Scream!
Throw up, bylebyœmy hence the left!
I'm sorry, Mr. Vincent
appreciate your enthusiasm.
And you are invited to a meeting behind the scenes.
O My God!
You'll see his wardrobe!
In the following order ê sure that the will be very ashamed of,
¿Eby colleagues tell about it!
/ Please, Daddy!
/ No, Daddy!
/ I love Tate!
Ok, I will distract,
and you IDY to the kitchen and Wey Gorda.
God, he's choking!
We need more forces y
I'm stronger.
Once again Sorry
for problems that spowodowaliœmy.
I know that we are not able to
zrekompensowaæ been broken on one of this.
Neither the ambulance arrival,
or that they should a fire.
Neither guy who really choke the,
but no one noticed that the.
/ (Am going to spend the night in Boone Vincent)
The touch of my arm!
I do not believe that the it's happening!
Hence the feel his cologne are.
God, I'm next.
- I have a good hairstyles are?
- Compared to the?
Hello, sweetheart. Thank you for
support, it means a lot to me.
No, I thank you for your the music.
Especially for "cinnamon the Rainbow"
of always been the favorite and mine are.
Really?
These are my ¿.
No one I have not previously he said.
WejdŸ.
Come in, not important what they see!
Important!
Who am I kidding?
Really he said that the no
you wanted to at the award ceremony?
I advise the wearing of the continuity of the.
But this ...
As much as heartbreaking.
Therefore, see the am your performance.
Son bought the tickets, ¿Eby be reconciled.
This is not the branch of an olive twig,
but that whole goddamn tree.
As I say, when I
dressed as an astronaut:
I believe that the children are our future of.
It is ¿.
You can not seriously brothers for not
everything that he says are. This teens.
I'll tell you a secret, Lois.
Even my 14 year old son is ashamed of me.
- No!
- I know, it's hard uwierzyæ, right?
But you can not Insert the past are, Lois.
You Insert today's date.
Because as of today,
is a special, special gift.
That's why I call it:
teraŸniejszoœci are.
- Otto ...
- Are still being here you are, I was thinking of that the EOE went away.
Mia the EOE're right.
It was my fault.
From some reason lately
sabotaging all of em.
I've been here a year already i ..
the people rely on me.
And I also, at some point they will fail.
Do not be ridiculous errors!
No one expects perfection from you.
If I wanted to perfect it
I employ the robot. Or Swede.
But I will employ the you,
I ¹ m're smart, you ¿ko working,
and when committing niches b the error,
that you fix it.
If from time to time committing niches
b jakiœ the ad, it does not bother me.
- Thanks, Otto.
/ - Here we are!
/ - Thanks to God!
- As we have found the yœcie?
- Connect the hose of a fire yœmy!
- What kind of fire?
One of the cows and fled through the gate,
that does not fix the EOE.
I fall over and the one with the torch,
you do not attach the EOE.
Which ignite the gasoline and trace
Baku to open your car.
Which is for this to burn.
You see, Francis.
And he says the EOE, also all knocisz!
90 000 slot machines
and that none of them fit the.
Already I can never believe in a prophetic dream.
Once again, thank you, Malcolm.
Do not say anything to his father.
How to meet the am Boone,
This foot long ...
No, no, no ...
- Hal! What ...
/ - I love you!
It's all here!
- Would you like pulling the free?
- Yes, willingly.
- He knew I was!
- Hal, what's happening?
It's destiny, Lois!
He knew I was, also it happens!
Are you not speak of I,
because I knew of, also do not believe it.
Foaming ¿y ³ em our insurance
the force, but he pays the pack of about
- We're rich!
- What will the EOE!
- Congratulations!
- What is it?
It's a coupon for a two-night stay
the Breezeway Motel in Carson City.
/ You just send a listen
/ Four-hour presentation
about the wonderful benefits of co-ownership in the summer.
May the one-armed bandits in Carson City?
Gordo, you jeœæ karma.
You can not already jeœæ of fat.
Please, Gordo.
At least try it.
Take a bite of my finger.
He eats.
I think I like yours the blood.
As she passed out, then pull it out
my finger in his mouth.
- So 10 hours of silence?
- How I'll wanted to divide and somehow something,
I'll give you know the.
The trip was not completely of no
lost. At least ...
That was a disaster.
At least a survival mechanism
in my brain started the operation of the AAE.
As early as the beginning zapominaæ,
what's operates about this weekend.
www.tvsubtitles.net