End of unhealthy food.
From now on, our family
You will have the ¿ywiaæ.
Brownie?
(The cake)
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x16 "Malcolm college visits"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Approaches the mine,
first visit to the college.
Stay the night in the dorm,
tour of the campus
and for 18 hours I will be pretending ³
Also my family does not exist.
I Szed of the schools were completely zamyœlony.
I think I should stop,
as I passed the playground ...
but who cares?
My body of this may cause
¿le EAE in the trash basket,
and my mind, and so the bra to the
Shower with hot c the student of the.
/ Come on, are hundreds of reasons,
/ ¿Eby up with me umówiæ.
¯ ³ Eby solution oœciæ father
or wzbudziæ zazdroœc in the cool boyfriend.
May, ¿Eby up znienawidziæ,
or out of sheer curiosity.
I do not know, I can not odwalaæ
the entire job for you!
I was thinking of that the although the I
a chance in the thick.
Name of the EOE her so?
I will not name the j are the grub.
Who is that?
It's Christie's, the new kapuœ.
We have a new snitch?
What happened with the drug addict?
They brought the divorce papers on history.
Come on, is that of none!
Really is a snitch?
Hey, tissue paper of the Company?
Has someone tiss the bunch
You know jakiegoœ dealer?
Why are you asking me?
I do not have many friends.
But sometimes I have an excellent idea of ??y
Where are you going?
Malcolm, it is alive in the world:
"And what the hell".
Part of Young man, I'm ...
AD invalid.
/ You can not zrobiæ me that!
Dad should zawieœæ me and not you!
Malcolm, this is your first
a visit to the university.
We talked with the father and zgodziliœmy up.
This is a big deal
and do not want to zawaliæ.
If I'll go, I'll have Security of,
Also do not say,
nor do czegoœ wrong.
Take off with you a little bit of pressure.
Wait a minute.
You talk about studying with Malcolm,
and not with me?
I'm a year older.
Why not seek college with me?
Well, son ...
I was doing the deal with you balls.
Luzik.
Dewey dinner.
Again, the poison will be cold.
What the hell are you doing here!
Pianos are for customers with money!
Zu are using a key!
Do not buy you a piano.
Never bra of EOE lesson.
We do not need lessons.
I know how to play.
I am a great look.
It's the very cute, Dewey,
but can not afford us.
You know, my company also bear the long bankrupt?
We sell the office furniture
and forcing the to share desks.
Dad, you know me well,
So do not deny
Also I had the horrible childhood.
Now you have a chance sprawiæ,
Also will be a bit better.
He said I was not.
End of discussion.
You will need to znaleŸæ otherwise
¿Eby up rozweseliæ.
/ I do not understand this!
He said I was all goœciom
a romantic ride in ¿d ¿ce
in the fifth reflect the property the night and no one will type the zloty.
Most Guests' no children.
They can not zostawiæ
and pójœæ a ride ¿d tablespoon for couples.
We allow only a couple.
So ...
is a solution of the solution.
We will organize a kindergarten.
Otto, I do not think ...
Will be great.
We'll make them different Debt competitions.
Ê will show them my images
of childhood in post-war Germany.
Bed are delighted.
Otto is œwietny idea was,
but there is one problem.
These people have accepted ¿d ¿aj are here
¿Eby spêdziæ time the whole family are.
We can not pozwoliæ them porzuciæ children.
We can be zostawiæ for the whole night?
Delivery will be on time?
All right.
Customers are impatient.
I did not see the photo.
Are you ready?
I think that you'll be surprised at
Unless I can zjeœæ ice cream.
Look, Reese ...
We were having coffee, watching the Dalio "Pi ³ ê"
jeŸdziliœmy skating.
³ am thinking that the walking
with you will be a little more ...
Entertainment.
There may have a friend or
someone who's heard the decisions actually,
What can help us?
I must to someone zaufaæ,
before I'll go with him entertain.
- Do you trust me, right?
- Not yet.
But there must be some way,
¿Eby this chick like you,
and won the trust of such desperate as I was.
You can also go on the river
and see
and there we can about this myœleæ.
I hope that no slouches themselves the EOE
the interviewers.
Why do not You said to him about his affairs?
How do you know what he says of em?
Pods of uchiwa Did you come to the door?
You should more koncentrowaæ up
on what you do, not me.
Next time, say "bless you",
when someone sneezes.
These people are just excuses search,
¿Eby will not polubiæ.
Okay, room 230
Did you come to take me to a room,
Did you come to choose lunch
Did you come to improve the shirts during the visit.
Is now finally the go?
Why do you want to get rid of me?
Because I should robiæ it all by yourself.
I make sure only
Also do it in a properly.
- Part. You're Malcolm?
- Yes.
I'm Paul.
And that Andrea and Scott.
We will today co-tenants.
- Super. The position of the ê your bags ...
- I'm sorry.
Ch of boys and girls are asleep in the same room?
Yes.
Just like in a real dorm.
Already!
Now all we have so version of the same number,
events in this room.
Exactly the same thing I'd do the, Lois.
Yes, the spa to go with them in the room.
Do not Feel invited timer Did you come by chance?
I can not understand the.
For a week all killed my nose.
K ³ ADE something somewhere, then it does not.
No, it's nothing worth stealing y
Someone deliberately wants me to spread the oœciæ.
I guess you're right.
Love you too.
Part of.
What the ...?
Can I prosiæ lemonade?
What were wonderful,
attentive, a boy were the boy.
Wey trunk of even a sewing kit
moisturizing cream and an extension piece.
Otto, one of the parents
does not appear to take over the ¿d ¿ce.
Their children are here.
That's weird.
No one answers phone
So I came of the rooms.
Everywhere is a "Do Not Disturb".
I'll start with better speech przygotowywaæ
the incentive for the barrows equipment for the morning.
Mom, what are you doing with my underwear are!
EOE was packed the j are in the same corner.
Crumpled clothes are evidence of the
Poorly organized minds u
So Feel invited the am Guide
the Plaza de Espana in Barthelonie.
Do not pronouncing it poorly, so they are saying.
Barthelon.
It is interesting trades.
I wanted to be a more interesting whole.
Thinkers that the use of force of the word "sleight of hand"
It would be pretentious, in an interview with the dean?
What am I saying?
Of course, also be to the Father
But with me g of the b
Chill out. If you will not be
pretentious in college,
this is where you'll be the one He could be?
- Really?
So if I go to college,
then I can speak of each other and Antigone?
Of course.
Okay kids, this is the layout of the ad.
My name is Leland.
And what I'm important in local government will be.
I am the advisor to the inhabitants ¿,
which means that the government's money on the floor.
Then you have œciszyæ music.
You really are so loudly?
S ³ Look, dude.
Can I be your best friend,
or worst nightmare.
Now switched on the radio.
It jakiœ problem?
- Who are you?
- His mother ¹.
Supervises the children in the Mixed room.
I do not believe that the university that allows it.
You know what, not why I'm here.
This radio is at least
5 decibels too loudly.
I'll be they had to skonfiskowaæ,
or go to worse consequences.
You know, Leland?
He was am in college.
I know how are the authorities and the authority you have.
Good night.
Malcolm, your mom is awesome.
I am glad also arrived with her are the EOE.
This is the horn of the car my dad,
and the one with the car we have,
and the one with the light bulb you with ice cream.
Dewey.
What are you doing?
The chute up and spoil, the repair j.
Good boy the boy.
I talked with the lady Hittelman of our street.
And he said that if the want
that you can swim in ¿the piano.
Thanks, Dad, but I have found the
something else that gladdens me.
Well, well.
I saw the EOE my hair in the votes?
I swear that some
things as if they were coming out of the house.
That, or someone up with me teasing.
Dad, it seems to me that
Also know what is going on.
Someone sneaks into the house and steals.
Sure jakiœ punk.
No, not punk, son.
Jakiœ good kid who selected the from of a road.
Anyway, with the catching them.
/ Then judging a book he said:
/ "Is not my boots."
Mom and I will make the AEOI to machine
and wróciæ without holding my hand.
This moment is almost as are the sweet,
as a bar, you do not eat.
Barrier for the goodies.
If I had of 12 years or less,
aka the pop of the'd be.
/ What's going on?
God, do not ...
The machine is out of order.
Forbid my son are the sweets?
Mom, it does not matter.
I go to another floor.
Using the machine is a privilege,
rather than a universal right.
If my son wants a candy bar, you will get it.
/ You can not decydowaæ for him.
I can decydowaæ.
I must be at the same time?
D Ever since I got the key,
that I think that I government money.
Come here, it's not over yet.
Mom, why do not you dress me diapers?
All in good time, Malcolm.
First, you'll get the candy bar.
My parents ... and the water inlet me to madness.
I must zerwaæ with the reality
and run away somewhere.
You know what I mean?
S ³ Look, Christie ...
I must tell something.
The first time you see the I,
This is the smoothed em silly.
But then We have paid close up close ...
and I will like of you.
I can not stand this d for much longer.
What do you mean?
I'm not who you have.
I pretend the fault ever since you've seen the.
It is very difficult is continuously traces zacieraæ
and have the good wymyœlon the story.
I do not want this robiæ already.
I'm tired of force in the amstwie k.
I think I know your secret.
No, I certainly do not know.
But it does not matter
I end of it.
I'm sorry.
S ³ yszeliœcie it?
Yeah, looks as that the is already clean.
So if you want it to Grip the,
then we have poœpieszyæ.
Malcolm wanted to only a candy bar,
but Leland close the the machine.
It can not ujœæ him dry.
From the beginning it does not like the am.
That would never happen at the Barcelona.
Why Americans
are immature?
You can also write a sharp letter,
or smoothed osisz the message
after we receive me are?
Scott, you'll put the frontal and palantom
and tyrants, such as Leland for the entire e force.
The sooner you learn to their pokonaæ, the better.
Nobody's likely to get into
at t the university are not compromised.
And he had to Daae will be the key to us.
How?
I do not know.
But there are many ways
to force people to czegoœ.
It can be found something
load the hose extensions lying in their room.
Dowiedzieæ up dirt jakiœ
from that of EOE girl.
Or you can with full confidence NYM
Insert accused him of something
and czekaæ, until he says something improper.
Wait a minute.
You are still you are using this trick on me.
No honey, it's something completely of no other.
Now we bring Malcolm candy bar.
I guess I'll cool and popular after graduation.
/ Dewey?
Dad!
Here! Come on!
What's going on?
I saw the I, as someone with a bathrobe escapes the mother.
Thanks, son!
/ Everything all right.
/ These are the only children here,
/ That dance and jump the the,
/ Sapling as lambs.
/ PREVIOUS later.
Otto I, Francis.
I have movies, wpuœæ me.
We have a delicate problem.
You know how much I wanted to,
¿Eby everything to the best of children.
I went to the store I bought the cake.
But I see these ¿³ A special,
the strong point lemonade
I bought the three cases.
Forte the lemonade?
This is an alcohol.
Yes, Francis, says the I, also we have a problem.
Who lives in a pineapple in the ocean?
I am.
Not every Insert me in my internal voting.
Why can not we live in
your internal Voice?
That's all I'm talking, man.
But we should AEOI for the meeting.
Oh, my God also?
My parents trusted me,
I otru of them I have the consolation that.
What I'm a monster?
Otto, committing the EOE b than the error,
but everything will be fine.
As soon as the children are here,
that we are safe.
/ I'm the invisible robot!
/ Rules concerning me!
/ Well,
too early for carol singing, right?
Leland poorly zrozumieliœmy up earlier.
Apparently, this job
for you important.
Who knows, perhaps the more so find.
It was to be a great shame if byœ been fired.
Byœ had to return to the home,
to older siblings,
which collects the entire attention,
on which the you deserve.
You really want to ryzykowaæ
for a candy bar for 75 cents?
Overripe Did you come to me.
Just forget about it,
They also lower the rate,
the larger the thrill
thanks of power.
If a candy bar was to be worth one cent,
that I'd be on the accounting ¿moon.
I CYM which control freak.
If the pour me, I'll find another the job,
Where will I kontrolowaæ Such use again.
The search for the Kinko ¿a night watchman
Besides, already wrote I
negative opinions about these kids
to the admissions office.
You only need to press the æ "senden".
She strives intersection of these ¿socket and the wall!
We are like bulls in Bartelonie.
Now, you.
Each was young psychiatrist
see, also your force
not with the deposit of the s just like he wanted Did you come to,
So now you want to
u Insert the force of his son.
I do not know who kibicowaæ.
The fact is that the you are afraid of
wypuœciæ are the only thing in your life ¿,
that has a chance odnieœæ success.
But do not listen to me.
You can also ask other mothers here on their mind?
Right.
There is no other mothers.
Add elektrycznoœæ,
On this floor for benefits.
- Mom?
- I can not zrobiæ.
- What?
- He wanted the am to help you,
¹ æ busy with a few things, but you know what?
I end up with this.
I think that you should robiæ it alone.
What?
This time, ¿ebym back off of a
and give you more of a freedom.
Malcolm, I know you can handle it also.
If I did not miss the sarcasm,
I think it really just thoughts.
I got the permit,
¿Eby radziæ himself.
Well, at least the same zdobyæ candy bar.
But you know what?
I want that bar more than the next breath.
I have a plan.
Malcolm, what are you doing?
My plan!
Pull the foot of the door.
I get stuck of a
By the way,
Our choir will be tomorrow
protest against the concert of jazz.
We should there wpaœæ before departure.
Okay, Jamie,
This will protect us from theft s.
Your dad is a reasonable part of the dnym owiekiem,
but sometimes even he can ¹ æ shoulder.
Not Dr. differs a bear.
Police!
Not ruszaæ up!
We have a warrant to search the house.
We suspect drug possession.
£ nicely!
Drugs?
Please keep calm, uwiniemy in
as quickly as possible.
Did you come to playing Annie Oakley
in the school?
Yeah, but not to the am for good.
My Stuff!
Oh, my God also?
All the time used Did you come to me,
¿Eby with Grip the Parents?
And you for all the time dilowa the EOE
and do not even buy the DVD EOE us?
Zabraæ him out of the d
Hey ... Dr. ...
it must be œwietne feeling
rescue people.
What am I robiæ?
Play in the ball has possession.
The bed to have a little pain g strong words,
but otherwise the whole are quite healthy.
It's a good wieœci.
Thank you for coming, Doctor.
I do not say anything about it, you do not say anything
of the keys that I left a
in your bag the yellow-piece.
Consent.
What do we do with your parents?
Come on, baby.
Time return to the room,
for your wonderful, wonderful dad.
Thank you very much.
Uratowaliœcie we have the ¿eñstwo.
I almost forgot that the women's are.
Let's go, son.
Dad.
Do not talk so loudly?
These are the pros of this situation.
When you pull out the gnêli door off its hinges,
discovered that the Leland had the platen Place For the.
Everyone saw,
and had to U of writ ¹ æ ¹ and retract to the clipboard.
Do not worry, honey.
I'm glad
Also it was to spare and our school.
How to go to jail,
I promise zajmowaæ niejszymi up important matters.
www.tvsubtitles.net