Keys, wallet these ¿I have.
Shopping list.
You know the rules.
Mom did not know about it.
/ Malcolm in the Middle
/ Crazy world Malcolm
/ 05x03 - Goodbye Kitty
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Stevie, the last time I will not be your
partner in wheelchair basketball.
Smells here ... coward.
I'm part-nosprawny.
This is fairly weird.
Besides unfair to those to
which must jeŸdziæ wheelchairs.
Why do not you ask the saliva are lying up
the kid with the tempting the nurse?
Norm ... is never given.
Part, the boys ch.
Mr. Kenarban, there are tools you
It also morally doubtful
for someone who's playing Basketball in a wheelchair,
if in fact it is part-nosprawny?
Even if his best
friend wants wygraæ ...
for his mother?
My son, after two months of absences,
your mom is sufficient that the you see.
I know that long it was to no Stevie,
but it seems to me to defective.
I have always been ..
when I ...
Potrzebowo the EOE.
Do not do this to me, please.
The seventh class ..
first dance ..
fastened fly.
Let the will. But annoy me
Also is continuously remind me.
Keep the continuity ... per game.
Come on, Jamie.
I must AEOI to work.
Eat. Pushing the cockroaches in your mouth,
and it did not even try?
Come on, Dewey.
Well you're doing with it.
Not true. You're just saying.
In the apparatus of me hello.
As a reward you feed the baby.
I must lecieæ.
What are you doing with my diaries from high school?
I'm looking for the book, children's jakiejœ ¹ ¿ki,
which will give the a would be for Jamie.
It turns out that even not zdjêliœmy cellophane
this bought for Dewy'ego.
Malcolm, Reese, move!
What are you doing?
I must æwiczyæ riding in a wheelchair.
This could have a meaning.
You never know.
It can also happen that terrible accident
and will be on the jeŸdzi of the end of life.
It's just basketball.
Yes Hold the.
Reese! What took you so long?
Why do not you admit:
no one in the house but me, does not care about me in the hair!
Come on! Well already.
Come on, Jamie.
Just eat it.
It is not so with the e
See?
She did not wince.
What he said veterinarian of the paint?
All of her are all right.
In the best.
I have a terrible wieœci.
He has inflammation of the hoof œlicznych.
I'm afraid that it will be
j have the uœpiæ.
That is zabiæ?
Poor thing.
Who has to do?
We must, Francis.
You can not be serious there.
We have no choice.
In the end we are real ranchers.
we have to be strong, decisive,
and never uciekaæ against liability company,
regardless of how nasty can be.
Do you want me to I will do it the right?
Otto?
/ My diary.
Come here, Dewey or thrown away your lunch!
Already IDE.
Dinner will give a fantastic insight, Lois.
Thank you very much for the invitation.
Think of am, also when Kitty comes back tomorrow,
Such use byœ the last time spróbowaæ meat.
Do not Believe
what happen to the about me at school.
Jakaœ girl by a mistake tablespoon
in the deposit of s and your diary to my backpack.
You do not know whose it is?
No, but it œwietne.
He writes about his teachers,
classes, friends of s.
It's like the whole world
of which previously I did not know of.
Dig in, Stevie.
It's a real butter on
melts on your plate.
I can not jeœæ.
I'm too excited ...
due to return there.
³ I will do it ... laurkê.
I bake the ... cake.
I wrote ... song.
Stevie, just get
Mroczków before his eyes.
We can suspend Chinese lanterns?
Sure, son.
Whatever you want.
Hal, we can for a while porozmawiaæ?
Sure.
Stevie is certainly the
excited back there tomorrow.
Kitty is not a journey ¿s ³ u ¿s business trip.
The divorce and up with me two months ago the sun.
I have never come home.
What?
Kitty is not a journey ¿s ³ u ¿s business trip.
The divorce and up with me two months ago the sun.
I have never come home.
What?
Kitty is not a journey ¿s ³ u ¿s business trip ...
No, this is not the kind of "what."
Stevie thoughts that the next day she comes back.
I know that I should was to tell him,
but each time,
When I look at his face ...
You know me, Hal.
Always happens to me were hard times ...
you know ... the autopsy.
That was one of my problems with Kitty.
That, and completely mechanical nature
our sex life.
Listen to Stevie must dowiedzieæ,
That his mother did not come back.
You have been completely the right.
You can do it tell him?
Why me?
What is it?
Kitty and the divorce of up to Abe.
Do not come home.
Oh, my God also?
What had happened?
The truth is that the over the last few years,
was to a with me only or the effects on Stevie.
Always been so sick and helpless.
The entire email is the ¿eñstwo was to build
the same care of him.
He had no notion of am.
Two months ago and will announce the,
Stevie also finally œwietnie is doing.
Later, they packed a suitcase and the odesz of a
Listen to Abe, I'm sorry,
but Stevie still has to dowiedzieæ.
Abe, you tell him.
About what?
None of your business.
Come to one of u
How do I tell this biedaczkowi,
That his mother will never come back to us?
I tell him.
Kaza of you hence the odejœæ.
What's going on?
Kitty and Abe divorced.
Now leave us alone.
What?
Abe, you have to post the The five and must be
and póœæ to him now.
What about Malcolm?
Why he can not tell him?
Is there was to be better
if he heard the us of a best friend?
He said I, I I can also of doing this.
Reese, Exit immediately!
Why I had of him to tell me?
Well, there's some of your guilt.
What?
That you always encourages the EOE him to try the new things -
- Dances, mountain expeditions, basketball.
Before you know of,
barely doing the deal with yo-yo.
For what it is supposed to contain because
All components of the & Beverages?
Not now, Dewey.
End of discussion, Abe.
Now Ides!
All right, he said I to him.
What?
You ¿ko bears it.
Someone should be there pójœæ
and with it porozmawiaæ.
It's really weird.
Mine were just three days
ever since the d Stevie found out about the mother,
but it looks as if the SIE to undo the
in the development of 10 years.
So, as you can handle them?
Than we can simply
be afraid of their physical advantage
Come on, Stevie.
I know that you ¿ko you now,
but we play in the tournament.
This should help you
tn deny the thoughts æ ¹ something else.
Just talk to me, Stevie.
I know it is not with you
until that bad.
You have no idea
Going by what and how you feel.
Now, if you let the
I wanted to retain the remnants of the breathing.
I discontinue this to use.
You can not speak of soup ...
You do not need it.
As you wish.
If you do not want
with me to chat I'll go.
This whole thing with a roœniêciem
it is not all right.
When you are born, everything is perfect,
but before you know it all starts with psuæ.
With each time dedicating the day you
less attention,
So you need to robiæ,
and I love you a little less the.
No. So it is only in this family.
Reese!
How many times do I have to speak, ¿ebyœ not leave the
his dirty socks on the kitchen table!
/ "The Eighteenth September.
/ What pissed the day months.
/ "Jakiœ idiot named Hal
/ Interrupts our W-F.
/ "I noticed that the mesh on the pitch,
/ And wynieœli him on a stretcher.
/ "And later, during lunch,
/ This other dude ...
Sorry.
Do not pick it up?
What for?
Because it œmieæ.
Or are you one of those charming people are smokers,
Suggest who are, also is obliged to others?
¯ s the rest of us should be under the AAE for you ¿¹
For the rest of life
and equipment are ba taæ the mess
How are leaving behind?
Let me also ask you about something.
He was born AOE circle something about 45th?
People like you are the reason
amounts to a pair of hose
as soon as I finish college!
Oh, my God also?
This girl government today.
When each also something you lift up,
you have of doing this!
I do not know what to do.
Stevie is devastated.
I'm trying to him to chat
but only calms me.
'll Be all right.
You see, Abe.
Everything will return to normal. Come on.
You do not want spóŸniæ an appointment.
I do not know what's going on with the Yamim.
Already passed out of the food with the word of oiczków,
but are still being wants to be breast-fed.
Not now, honey.
I'm here to do
family matters.
If you do be slightly semi-aczliwy
during the meeting, do as I do -
- Spill coffee on yourself and Exit the room.
You're too good to me.
Hal, what exactly do you do with Abe'm?
I've seen the am as it EoE makes the sweater knit,
and yesterday the lying massage his feet.
I know that you like him very much,
but do not write him replace the Kitty.
This is ridiculous, Lois.
Just behave like a friend.
So, with the otko.
Francis?
Yes?
Do not take care of the EOE even a can of the paint, right?
What's the question?
If it was to,
or hides the'd be in front of you are?
Already well, Francis.
It's not all right for me to
the Weight AAE you with this burden.
We'll do it together.
Think only.
Sends the it to the better place
the vast field of small
and cold mountain streams
where will can flow biegaæ whole day,
and the horses are ridden people.
I think that the by the and of the white horse.
Then spend the whole wiecznoœæ in the lake of fire,
with delicious bales of hay,
were in immediately outside the service area.
Otto, do not kill the've never
anything bigger than a poodle.
And this was to clean the case.
Francis, however difficult that it was to no,
I know that the ladies do the trick.
Nobody he said,
Also force the cowboy is simple.
They met for the fifth, and yoga.
What are you doing, Steve?
I saw the jeŸdzi as the EOE
upwards and downwards on the ramp.
/ You can also look for the other project?
/ Lloyd looks as szczêœliwego.
/ It can also destroy his family?
Stevie, I know also what to do with the
your mom to the awful,
but you have the crap
u ¿Alaa over the Sat.
Rozz continuity up.
I would so do the,
my mom had me opuœci of a
Well, not my mom.
But the thing is, you have also
any right of oœciæ squint up.
/ You're right.
/ Exactly what I want will hear.
/ Thanks a lot.
There you go.
/ This thing is not suitable
/ For sarcasm.
As you wish. B-governments moron.
"Mom and I left a
and I am now helpless the baby. "
Do not let those guys just
siedzieæ and use the Alaa over the Sat.
Orient themselves.
Come on, you're not
until such a wimp.
/ Will not be telling me the
/ How mollusk me.
I know you can swim with ¿k y are
£ ap it!
Look at this
defenseless toddler in the sunset on a trolley.
Look at t the cripple.
Solubility of you crying up?
Solubility of you crying out
cieniasku in a wheelchair?
The child in a wheelchair.
Have you selected the I with the s way
but if they stopped,
It has proven its the right,
can a poorly appearance Daae.
/ I am the little ones!
Skocie his ass.
/ I can not poruszaæ legs.
/ Where's my mom?
Well, the interesting hands.
Now officially qualify
basketball in a wheelchair.
Do not help anyone.
Never to the EOE love, right?
The twelfth of October.
During lunch,
JJ and predicts the future of me.
Again, "girl".
I'm telling you, I'd had of the same girl.
While I'll be laughing at all of the children
This whole e mothering
seems to be a nightmare.
Who's that?
I do not know.
But it comes to second base (the catching for boob)
if I've got something to say.
I just have to znaleŸæ way
that I noticed that the.
I do not think byœ and had to martwiæ about it.
What do you mean?
You know, when he does something,
what you do not like it and ..
is charging you for it.
What!
Do not switch the transport and cargo handling on people.
Honey, I'm sorry,
I'm also telling you this, but ...
the truth is,
Also you all call the "Geba."
Geba?
Yes, but this band
immature small half-grams of pencils.
A director just
I'm trying to fit within.
Abe, not the apiesz flu.
It's just your allergy.
For the EOE ¿s medicine?
Check your jacket pocket.
What I will I do with you?
You can poklepaæ me in the back?
Thanks.
Please, canned paint.
I will give you the greatest of the,
most of the nicer carrots, as the ³ I have found.
Please, Francis, do not overload the gajmy
This d for much longer, than is necessary.
All right, let's do just that.
Do not worry, canned paint.
Coming soon will be over.
As a sign of the cut range for the trigger
and once to the end of her suffering, we aim.
Ready ..
goal ...
pal!
Why not shoot the EOE?
Well, you are not to score ³ ¿EOE.
I was not the ready.
Now already am.
It's good. Here we go.
Ready ...
goal ...
pal!
Come on, Francis, a coward of you.
With me? You're the chicken out of EOE.
Very well.
On three, they both shoot,
regardless of everything.
Once ..
two ..
bang!
No kidding ...
If you do not ...
Can zabiæ me hello yet.
Only after this,
how do you kill the byœ me.
You can not zabiæ horse
but I had no problem with killing byœ Otto.
Canned paint?
What happened it happened?
I think that the throttle of the thighs and up the carrots.
Well, probably no one now than can tell,
Also we are not real ranchers.
I just hope you do not rozbudziliœmy
have too large ¹ between killing.
I was thinking of buying the Stevie
these pendulous of small d ¿insów that always wanted to.
Hal already we talked about it.
All the kids are wearing them.
This does not mean that the accession of the five gang.
Can you're right.
Do you know the best about these things.
Szczêœciarz with him,
Also have you, Hal.
Przynieœæ you something from the kitchen?
Do not be.
Thanks, honey.
Abe?
In precisely tried to kiss me hello the owaæ.
No.
That would be the contraction of the lips
See? Again, I have it.
You know what?
I'm glad it also became about
Because thanks to this something of the uœwiadomi em.
Get out.
What?
I can not replace with Kitty.
I do not wyœwiadczam aperture you try to service the c
But what I ¹ æ start without you?
What I zrobiæ with Stevie?
I do not have the slightest notion.
But you're his father.
So just Wey August in garœæ.
I know that you can handle something wymyœleæ.
Can of doing this.
- Now Ides. - All right.
- Wait a minute.
- There you go.
Mom, I have a proposal for you.
Before you doszukiwaæ August in the gaps,
He wants me byœ send the ear of a
I want to walk perfectly well not only schools were
dostawaæ and clothes for large the boys.
I want to be lords angle and wheel ysany bedtime
and whole food that have ground to a paste.
With gratitude, I will be charming ...
Do you wear diapers?
I want the byœ spotted and my involvement.
/ Oh, my God also?
Stevie!
Stevie, where are you, son? I want ...
Come on.
For the sake litoœæ, son,
What are you doing here?
Przemok the EOE to the skin.
/ At Least You said to me the truth
/ To some case.
Son, I know, also lived for EOE terrible shock,
and father need to deal with this poradziæ.
But that did not happen,
because of your dad's a terrible wimp.
Son, what you do and the mother was to awful.
But what I will not do the I was to better.
Sorry.
/ Go on.
Stevie, I know also that the entire force
EOE had to place any frontal and
przeciwnoœciom huge fortune.
Display the EOE For more dzielnoœci,
than I had the right oczekiwaæ.
And now you okazaæ her even more.
I know it's unfair,
but believe me,
Can of doing this.
Always go out of admiration,
When I see it in you.
And if it will help also, I promise
Also I will always be with you.
¿Terrified wife and full en denial
but I will.
Let's go back ... to the house.
Okay, taken ¿d ¿ck the rim.
When you are doubling,
give to me, and I throw.
I ... throws.
No ... I have.
Already for the third time today
reminding me.
Begin ... przyzwyczajaæ.
Hey, sheep.
Do you think that the that the jajcarskie
be in a wheelchair?
No, no, seriously,
you know that I was on the ...
/ Seventeenth of October.
/ Do not say anything to the am Jason for the entire week for s,
/ And he invited me out of.
/ The old me would never return.
No!
What's wrong?
It is believed that ck, also is all right
change could to?
I flip her back
is everything that you believe
just to zrobiæ impression that
the jakimœ handsome?
Handsome as Burt Reynolds and Sting?
Forget it.
/ So in the the double czyliœmy the exhaust pipe are,
and now dray until paddle.
Applying the momentum of the night than I j are
to two hundred per hour.
She likes with you rozmawiaæ.
Can you listen to.
The Friday we're all going to play hooky.
Father Dave leaving for the town.
After ¿We wish his boat.
Want to Switch the?
Enough of this.
I'm trying to be me, and not of a krytykowaæ,
but I must tell,
It also najohydniejszy, Nastiest
How habit seen in the life of am.
Yes! That's my girl.
Someone about to resist
and stick it to his clothes,
but do you care?
No, because the're just
inward-looking, bezmyœlnym slob.
Sorry.
It's cute how you are
¿ed involved in the arts in general.
Really?
Yes, it œwietne.
/ Barely ³ ³ am breathing apparatus.
/ Am He knew that the kiss of kisses me.
You're a commodity.
With these you ¿.
Reese!
I think I am the sermons you zabraæ ...
What are you doing with my old diaries?
www.tvsubtitles.net