The shoes ... better than me.
Okay, how's you.
What's the big difference the difference.
Just tweak it up.
Can you stop your head on the ceiling fan?
Do not think so.
Look at this.
My ice is two times larger than yours.
But the rout. I'm not ...
Reese.
AD invalid.
/ Crazy world Malcolm 5x10
/ Hot Tub
/ T the interpreter: polishchaser1
Jamie, how can you smakowaæ
is a processed food?
Nothing like the venom want you
B c in the wilderness.
Succeeded in it!
I get the instructor's permission.
I can jeŸdziæ where I want the beauty of the white.
A grown-y does not have to be
visible from outside the car.
I check of that.
Each just leave the test for
Pulling off the attempted gaæ from him.
Mom is really proud of me.
It's fairly me a while to have the e hose y ..
Dewey!
Oh, my God also?
That is, what looks as?
Yes, Mom. This is my friend.
His name is Noah.
I'm of the I meet you, Noah.
I can not imagine myself ¿ck
as is taken ...
Mom ...
If we release There is too excited
we can go wystraszyæ.
So if your concern,
it's just another day.
Come on, Noah.
Dewey?
Well, end of am.
Come here, baby.
I have a surprise for you.
- What is it?
- The hot tub angle ca swimwear.
The EOE lost their mind?
We can not afford to pozwoliæ.
So he said I was, but then the seller
the show me how wrong I was the.
ChodŸcie here, the cool boys!
Hal, I can not uwierzyæ,
Also do the EOE Do not ask me the c.
You know also that such decisions
always take together.
That was a shop promotion.
Dostaliœmy tablespoon discount of 20% percent.
In addition, the card club baths,
and free sealing.
And it should be especially
convince you, Lois - sealing.
Hal ...
Ca hot tub? Bosco.
Yes precisely here. We always get
œwietne things as hot tubs.
The Zwróæ j.
And what about the boy opcami?
They do not have the anything to say?
Yes, Mom. That was to
œwietna entertainment.
No, I do not have the nothing to say,
because the did not stop.
Well, we do not have ...
as if the choice.
¯ s what?
Lois, such opportunities
Incoming not without liabilities.
Nothing on the do not earn.
And if ¹ æ take the inflation into account, it's almost as
as if it is our semi-ACILIA 2800 bucks.
$ 2,800!
I can not uwierzyæ!
Connect the EOE decisions behind my back,
EOE had issued the money, which had no legal EOE spend it all
on the omiast of the Bali!
Do not worry.
It has a very detailed head of the assembly instructions,
where never misplaced, because we take the Malcolm j.
I fit.
G the pencil to the child and under direct sunlight.
- What are you doing, Otto?
- You know the new rules of security.
He was too much
unnecessary accidents.
There is no excuse
for being careless ¿NYM.
Francis!
Do not believe the byœ what happened the o
Almost ...
Otto! Oh, my God also?
Are you all right?
Manfred Schmidt.
And I do not speak of you?
Do not care about the whole world,
when you are in the hot tub.
It's like going back to the amniotic sac.
Jamie will be the spa
for the next hour.
I can of the ¿yczyæ your car,
wyskoczyæ briefly to the Lucky Aide?
I will lead!
Do not be. I can handle it.
- Appearance date on so relaxed, and it's just ...
- None problem.
I have the keys. JedŸmy!
Take a break from the angle of troubles, dear.
No, thanks.
Since the EOE decided, that we are the family,
where Each does what he wants,
I decided the am,
Also I do not want be in the tub.
The fault beams are brilliant.
I do not've heard the saying of what a
And really ... if you are listening,
everything is at your own risk vibration.
Trees and grass ...
Sometimes it seems that
Also the whole world cries.
But you can dostaæ one of these machines are
to us the ear noise and podkrêciæ ...
Stop here.
- And what about the pharmacy?
- I have something to Buy.
But grazing. I can jeŸdziæ.
I have the opportunity Put some are better
to become familiar Polly.
It turns out that the twelve years
no TV
and instead of chemicals,
dry-cleaning facilities in ¿uses.
But it ¿¿d up and it is so cool.
- Gas! Gas!
- What?
She said the gas am!
What do Did you come?
Give me a minute to explained by,
Also does not do anything with the am of the former.
Trust me, do not threaten us
¿No danger.
So pull your foot off the gas.
Okay, what Feel invited Did you come? What is this thing?
This is mine. Belongs to me.
My ex-boy Danny boy the take away of it and never give it back the,
and so consists, also my mom.
- Your what?
- In the middle is my mother. Her ashes.
He wanted the am for her the prettier urns
but precisely Raise my tuition in Wicca School.
So they can not poprosiæ Did you come to it
of these drugs?
That's not the narrowest aœciwszy
method of disposal with Danny.
He's very upset.
What?
Please do not tell my parents.
Let it be between us, okay?
I love Jamie, he to me,
and at the break of me would not be able to go widywaæ.
Literally.
Emotions can œciskaæ
internal organs, Malcolm.
It will help me wybrn can ¹ æ this?
Right.
This is weird.
All of which are now thinking
"But it is fun to lead."
Francis saw the EOE Otto?
What happened on?
I do not like it, allow the eyes.
There are so prone to accidents.
For those over the last few days
demolition of our two cars,
falls of the stairs, and this morning
set fire to the glasses themselves in the hair.
Gretchen, my dear,
that can flow byœ przynieœæ tweezers?
It seems sure that the back of the books I
stuffed cactus.
- Otto just about getting started to Goia.
- I'm sorry.
I do not do this damage resulted from actions.
- Francis, unless the damage resulted from actions they are doing.
- What, mutilation of ourselves?
I do not think that all these
events that were accidental.
As if jakiœ Subconscious energy
and the punishment of my jakieœ unknown ...
Otto, what it means for you
Manfred Schmidt first name?
I was not thinking of it for years.
- I ...
- What?
Manfred Schmidt fiance Gretchen.
This means that the,
as long as he did not sneaked to steal the em.
EOE steals the Gretchen?
He was my best friend,
but it is ¿³ I fall in love at Gretchen.
And on the day when we had to get away,
I he said Manfred,
Gretchen also already leaving for the a and wanted to and up
with him to view the train station in Berlin.
Otto ...
Poor Gretchen became a
for hours in the rain, inconsolable.
Then arrives the I ME
And so all of the deposit of s o ..
And now please - 25 years of perfect continuity me ...
built on the amstwie k.
Otto, I'll tear internally.
Why do not you call him and apologize,
It can really hurt you?
Francis, you do not have enough guts.
Besides, now that I know,
What is behind this, can the problem goes away.
It tacks.
Dad.
Noah bawiæ we had together,
but when I went of his house, there was to it there.
I was waiting for the hour, but he does not show the.
Where fault this pessimism?
You can email him something fixed and drove on the
to the hospital, alba died and his grandmother.
And then my ... a soldier
l the lands on and kills your parachute.
As I'm cold!
See Jamie, flying airplane.
Say "aaaah ...".
I think the voltage in the neck
numbs the taste buds of me.
These burgers are delicious, honey.
Thank you.
And even if you add cheese
cost were less than $ 2,800.
Who has the mustard?
I do not know, can the Reese stole the j.
Just like everything else.
Mustard may like me more.
Mustard can better get with me playing.
I stole the EOE Noah!
You can not suddenly change the subject.
We discussed the mustard.
I said I was about the Noah.
Œwietny kid.
I feel like I had the
m³ younger brother, you know?
He was so proud of me, when for him
Leadership I Jansonowi Craig.
That was the fun.
Malcolm, like those of gone through a
Today's ride?
All right.
EOE just drove to the Lucky Aide
and back, that's all?
Yes.
The Lucky Aide is only 4 km in both directions,
but mysteriously counter pointed to 37 km.
Well, when already I will pick the Polly
I pojeŸdzi the same bit. Sorry.
He was I was so excited, and I wanted to up pochwaliæ,
So jeŸdzi ³ ³ em all around the store.
Thank you for szczeroœæ.
Now give permission.
- What?
- Two months without them ¿d assumptions.
But, Mom ...
Because by the EOE honest with me,
Do not dispose of the garbage.
It's not fair! Dad?
Malcolm, you know that the always
I agree with your mother ¹ ¹.
Regardless of whether the same
Stick to your standards.
That's it!
I can not already znieœæ to scream.
Everybody out!
Hal, take the boys to the movies!
Ruszaæ with the place!
Come on, go!
I did not know of that the tickets are sold out.
I'll take the paper.
And so I did not want to
Daae viewing the film with dogs.
Whatever we go
I must be back in the seventh.
Noah and I attack on Kevin Teevensa.
Again?
You're the gorilla?
It's called a friend.
Very well.
What you want to find similar, ch the boys?
No matter. I'll be the real Radoch had the
with a lift there for me dad.
Come on.
How about this?
This is his review.
It's going to nieŸle.
Let's go.
It bypasses the opportunity
to improve your condition.
- Malcolm, do you agree?
- Who are you?
I'm Danny.
I think I took the EOE of something,
what belongs to me.
Thinking of EOE, also you can not find?
¯ s you get away with it?
Do you think that the I g of stupid?
It is believed that ved that the city is playing!
I do not know which
answer the question.
Sinus pain.
For pain is furious,
increases the pain and anger,
ciemnoœæ then collapses,
and I do not know what to do the EOE.
How can I help you?
I want recover this pot,
Which of the Feel invited and Polly.
- Do you want the ashes of her mother?
- He said, and those also in the middle is her mother?
There is my father.
My father, whom I loved the,
who has devoted himself completely to my education.
That his ashes are there.
- If so ...
- Will you give me t the urn.
I know where you live,
Listen to So.
I'm going zrobiæ patch test.
And immediately after the IDE to your house after the ashes.
Look at those huge the surprise.
Will you tell me now that the it was not of a
a huge waste of money?
Each tub will have a period of
interruption in the operation of your.
Simply adjust itself
the natural chemistry of our body.
- Here is szeœciocentymetrowa layer of algae.
- The logs are all all right.
See? Without objection.
- Ok the break Did you come to me.
- What do you mean?
In precisely meet the em Danny, and he says,
Also in the urn are the ashes of his father.
- That's right, are.
- So sk Did you come to the break.
No, the truth is that the there are
ashes of my mother, his father,
springer spaniel, which collectively We bought
and the cat, which had the am it will know the am Danny.
- What?
- You know how it is when you enter into someone,
mix their plates and a CD ...
Perpetuates the really groŸnie.
Like a real psycho.
Just tell me,
Should I martwiæ?
¿But no, no ...
- Yes.
- Oh Bo ¿e No good.
I must pomyœleæ.
Invent something.
I can not of anything myœleæ.
Wyjechaliœmy of the city,
you can already ignite a light
His plane landed ¹ ³ Moldova hour ago.
He should be here any minute.
Manfred Schmidt.
What if between him and Gretchen is continuously sparks?
Come on, Otto,
Gretchen know how much I love you.
I can.
I'll get Gretchen.
Thank you very much.
Please ... make sure that
Also will cook my kitchen.
Welcome, Mr. Schmidt.
Mia of you a pleasant flight?
Ah, yes. Thank you.
When you fly in the own jet,
zawszy times faster up the swim.
- Arrived and the Mr. Panské it ¿?
- Never married about ¿³ em.
After Gretchen from the break of my heart and,
simply can not ³ em.
Every day thinking about what may cause the appliance wydarzyæ,
and now, thanks to you, what are still being can still e
These are the think that the likes big diamonds?
Next, the five of a change in plans.
Gretchen is not here.
- I am afraid that the like of a fume
- What?
And he said, also was not interested in the EOE,
and then been solved EOE.
- You ¿ka thing.
- I do not believe you.
Not serious. Do you know how
lekkomyœlna is Gretchen.
Not the I flew here from Germany to be
odprawionym by jakiegoœ statue of the ANCA.
I'm not leaving until you
I'll see Gretchen.
Otto, why are you so secretive?
¿Well it's terrible secret?
So ...
Otto pays a flow of for these earrings.
Mom says I can also
zostaæ for dinner.
Cool.
Dewey, you oddaæ Noah
Your chair of o
This is not your friend, Reese.
On the zaprzyjaŸni up with me,
dotrzeæ to you,
and send the supports up you are,
byœ la of whom he wants.
Reese, wyrzuæ it.
No. Listen to.
In some foreign Zesz week got the impression
three boys of the packaging.
There is fairly strong,
oddaæ to them, but you are.
Cape of EOE already Kevin Teevensowi
and Craig Jansen.
It was the only Todd Lemmon
and it switches itself busy ¹ ³ em.
It's a piece of his T-shirt,
his mouthguard
with a piece of pretty tooth
and here the receipt of the suspension me
for four days.
He really dug the EOE.
Thanks, Dewey.
Stuff it, Reese.
Wait a minute. So it already over?
He was em for you
only a couple of the piêœci?
It is a few Guests',
Such use the byœ przylaæ from me.
It prematurely.
You're sure that the Danny
will not come to our house?
He said the am, also will not find
There us or drugs.
I only hope that
Also check the inbox.
Danny is not at home.
It does not work,
when it is in the car.
Puœæ gas!
- What are you doing here?
- I'm here to recover what is mine.
He had no right Did you come to receive my father!
Your father? Please.
As to the sick, the sermons he mieszkaæ EOE
in the wrong car in the garden.
That was LeSabre!
You hear a tone to what I say?
Only the lead.
Dogadaliœmy up.
The ashes were had become next to the coffee machine,
we had and we will be together, forever.
You, me, our ancestors
and animals.
As much as one day come back with wheels you bêbniarskiego,
and you disappear Did you come, not even the c ¿Goodbye!
Danny, you violate the settlement agreement EOE,
You attempted because dominowaæ in the entire ¿my life.
Even striga of the EOE my hair,
and I do not like bangs!
Distraught Did you come?
With your bone are the construction of the ...
AD invalid.
- Do not take my father.
- Will not have my mother.
Give ashes.
No way!
What you plant ...! Malcolm!
No!
Dosyæ us up to the ear of em.
It makes me sick
from the angle of your canvas with drugs,
drugs which do not have the
nothing in common.
- They do not have the?
- These are the I think that, yes.
The problem is your relationship are related,
that remains a problem, if not
begin with each other to chat to people.
I think the reflections of when leave Did you come
without the ¿me farewell.
Sorry about that.
Both we knew
D also the longer it did not make it.
Can not you raniæ the am.
Should I was to retain and otherwise.
- Thank you.
- Not at all.
So if everything's taken care of,
Turn around and go home.
You're a healer of hearts, Malcolm.
Now already it's too late, but surely
the future life of this isolated ¿you rip the Latin.
I must tell that the've seen the
something like this just for the steam-boats.
I must perform some calls
in this case.
Œmia of a, say it.
I know that already you can not doczekaæ up.
Why do I always have to
psuæ whole the fun in that?
What are you talking about?
You know how it be that,
you always have to speak "no"?
I hate this.
Honey, we are grateful for that.
It's you we hold back
before killing himself.
Yes, but it's the only thing I can hear it
"Why can not we?"
and "it never let me."
Is the time though I can not be the
who comes up with the crazy idea?
You know what? As most.
Œmia the Father
What do you have in g half?
I can not do anything wymyœleæ,
so the profession of ION.
All right. It should
powstrzymaæ growth of algae.
Use of this gentleman lives to spaliæ
external layer of the skin,
and the medicine of the Company are gradually kill it,
what about the rest of the Lord's urethra.
That was about the abduction,
and not our fault ...
- Where are Mom and Dad?
- Do not come back yet.
Oh my God,
This ZRZ the device fate.
Zapukaliœmy, and now the universe
corresponds to the "who's there?"
If you ask the to the've stayed here the whole night.
Ch of boys, the mother and the wpad
crazy idea was that you perform.
Probably too crazy.
Lois?
We will jeœæ ice on Chinese tableware.
- And that's just super.
- I said of you.
www.tvsubtitles.net