Finally mom will
had a picture of a beautiful baby
to show the om friends at work.
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 175.0 MB
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x02 "Minding the Child"
Serious does not, as you like, ¿ebym
popilnowa of a child a few hours,
there is no problem.
Lois looks as are exhausted.
No, we can handle.
I'll see you on Monday.
Wait, that today is Monday?
/ It's Friday.
O God, I should be today's the day.
An error occurred am a non-
approaches the ania for my sister.
It is believed that that the reason that the first is the
and the third on the ¿ch of my boyfriend,
This can roœciæ the right to it.
Is that ...
woman from cats?
Yes. And for a while that of the runner and the nag.
But g of mainly working for $ 4 per hour.
- Okay, cool the boys in the kitchen. Will you do supper.
- Why?
Because your mother is not the spa and for 4 days.
/ Ruszaæ up!
And quietly, because caring for a child.
- I do not want break loose.
- Come, come.
I'm telling you, I'm also tired.
Hal please, do not treat me like a child.
Honey, you need to rest the æ.
Together with the boys will take care of opcami
Today a child, and you, you can break loose.
So the crap up with me k the OCIA.
Try nakarmiæ Jamie
I go to the diaper.
How pacifier becomes plugged,
that are clean in the dishwasher.
There will me 10 minutes
and during that time is to be calm.
I believe that we are so
mature, ¿Eby the poradziæ.
He said "nipple".
(Nipple, nipple)
/ Craig Feldspar.
/ How can I help you?
Part of Craig.
When Jennifer Lopez died the tears?
Association of the menace of the means being inconvenienced.
- Buying a Clean Puppies.
- Yes, and I œpieszy.
I do not want krytykowaæ, but I think that
I know why you are buying pure puppies.
By cooling the onnoœæ, right?
People always pay it the attention,
but forget the that the flexibility
legs is most important.
Craig, I'm ...
Ever since I'm from the unofficial, second,
alternative godfather Jamie
I will make it the discernment of a small
I would recommend you snooze CHILDREN.
May the structure of the so that the not
but are extremely cold-consuming, but ...
Craig! For me the continuity's sake,
œpieszy me up!
Biore Clean Puppies, OK?
I do not have time to argue.
Please, you can delete me?
Naturally, ... It has to be $ 7.98.
- Craig, do not do this sensation.
- What do you need, Hal?
I'm sorry for you also naskoczy of em
but you really need those diapers.
After ¿yczysz me the money?
He could of you when I ¿yczyæ,
but it does not help you e
And since also have a tendency to shout
the people who are helping you,
it is not carefully am, also would be the
This m³ dre move.
Lois ignition pays for it tomorrow.
You can not take them æ ¹ is theft!
All right. I'm from the thief.
And what are you gonna do?
Vernon!
Where is the father of diapers?
Dewey, pack diaper bags in three
and make sure that the cover is tight.
And hold your breath, because as
pass out, then nobody will not help e
Oven gloves.
What a fun ... Saturday night.
Nobody does not like it, Stevie.
No need to be sarcastic.
There was to em.
Malcolm, right?
Yeah.
He says the am, also know his name.
We have a proposal for you
and your stupid brother.
O my God e Another one?
And in addition to a wheelchair.
Checkmate!
Kathy?
Want AEOI us out?
Pray ... pray ...
and finally ... happening.
For as the date?
When? Where?
Right now. With us.
The ...
Oh, my God, for the deposit appears that
Also has a toilet. Hammer down!
Wait, Reese. We had
opiekowaæ up is the white brother.
We can not simply
jeŸdziæ amazing car
Three incredibly
sexy girls.
Guys, guys! The I-tape
cover, but I think something overeating ...
container.
/ Ok-looking embarrassed.
Can I at least zadzwoniæ to
family and tell where I am?
Theoretically, you're not
arrested, so do not.
But, as that we are buddies,
This will allow you to odpracowaæ is $ 7.98.
Two hours minimum wage sufficient.
Stop wierciæ,
also know you're not hungry.
I know you want your pacifier-Soother.
Where is he? What should I do?
Can tell you a fairy tale?
Cartoons are cool.
No good.
Once upon a time, was to have each were Jamie
which had the older brother Dewey.
/ Jamie honor of Dewey.
/ Dewey and Jamie always together
/ Hanging out.
/ However, also the nasty older brothers,
/ Is continuously trying to force them uprzykrzaæ.
- Hey Reese, you want to entertain?
- Yes, the game is fun.
Stop it! From Insert the path it!
Stop it!
Shut up, Dewey.
We're better than you.
What are you doing?
- Sorry, Mom!
- I g of stupid.
/ And two grams of older upich
/ Brothers of ignition and pays for his madness.
Warns the am before zadzieraniem
with my favorite child.
Can this time
You'll learn zachowywaæ.
Now you do not already
martwiæ with these two.
And Dewey, remember:
Keep clear to my wardrobe.
Cabinet.
NieŸle.
Ok, here's the deal, freaks.
Our boys the boys left us
in middle school prom
and went on to the œ g of the stupid party.
- Nas.
- As Kevin Such use me to do?
Calls him 12 times a day,
shows up on his training.
Even the change of am whole plan zajêæ s,
¿Ebyœmy have the same.
Now the tide of the avoided.
The large white calipers.
Wait a minute. To the school prom?
Why did not we know?
Now we go on t the events
I will be with you obœciskiwaæ
in the eyes of those bezmyœlnych jerks.
- You, ¿Eby were zazdroœni?
- No, I ¿Eby vomiting.
How to see the that the whole self out such ofermy,
like you, it's never let us ignore the.
The yœcie arrived to our house,
because we are the most disgusting
you know what guys?
/ Earlier jakiœ refused to humped them.
/ He said, also is too proud.
Forget it! There will be paradowaæ,
as is the monkey on the añcuchu.
Already by the time today yœmy disappointed.
Myœleæ stop on the per second!
I do not believe in it.
Thinking, ... The middle also ... I like you.
Dewey and Jamie wanted dowiedzieæ up
What is the secret closet
but the mother keeps a
the key under his pillow the.
So wymyœlili brilliant plan.
Tell me when you'll be mine?
Say, Quando, Quando, Quando.
When I answer "yes"?
/ Craig Feldspar
/ Assistant Menada ¿era
- What kiblujesz?
- Diapers.
Another victim of the apana
the network into a hellish Craig Feldspar.
It's a monster.
He treats all the
night shift as garbage.
In the news power absolute assistant
Menada ¿³ era and mastered it.
We are like slaves.
But we are workers,
that you lead this store.
He owes it to him. You know what we have
wsypywaæ for the coffee machine?
Coffee brand Lucky Aide! There is a
bitter. It's like drinking death.
Do not change the incline ramps
Wheelchair access through the store.
Every day I am waiting,
until someone pushes me.
¯ an iron by hand controls the radio shop.
It forces us to the listening position of songs from musicals,
despite being unanimously
g the osowaliœmy on the golden hits.
What he does not fit with Phil Collins!
What a bastard! You can store not
pozwoliæ so traktowaæ.
Without you, there is nothing.
Must zostaæ defeated.
Vernon.
I do not know.
Craig can not that of the y
Give me a reward the employee of the month
wyczyœci as the am his aquarium.
Reward the employee of the month
is the opium of the masses.
You can store not pozwoliæ,
¿Eby you fear the government today.
S will be forever in the Insert
and cierpieæ in Craig?
/ Note for Lucky Aide.
/ Need, ¿Eby someone warmed by the
/ M 3 slices of the yellow cheese.
Ends with madness now!
He says the am, also will not be the whole of the
night at a party at Lori.
So we will go on
events to Charlotte.
And as they will not be,
Lisa is a party.
A later check events on the pier.
What kind of event? Who are these people?
Come with us to the schools were?
Stop zatapiaæ ... ¹ ³ my ódŸ.
Let's go home, daddy us
punish and be done with it.
What are you talking about? These girls
¹ want us smoothed upiaæ.
Because we are nerds!
Hey, wozimy up limousines are free.
We are on the verge of obœciskiwania up
of girls who does not like the.
I do not know who we are,
but definitely not losers.
EOE thinking of the dock are this is going?
The boy is a boy of Erin Stepanavich.
I saw the EOE this guy?
How to see that the whole regret it
Girl, I'll kill you.
- I know.
- So why ...
Because everything is better
from the current situation.
I have so the partner on the œliczn
chemistry classes of eight weeks.
Her name is Cheryl.
I recently left a her liœcik
with an invitation for a date.
And when he read of a,
and the reverse and he said a:
"Do you know who is Reese?"
And for a while the posi-tion g:
"If someone knows who is Reese?"
And they shrugged their shoulders.
So he said I:
"Jakieœ probably zero."
And you know what?
I had the right.
/ Wow, that's awful, was young.
/ You want my ponosiæ the hat
So today is repaired.
From now on, when I pass the,
Bed the people speak:
"What happened on the face of his?"
/ Someone will say:
"This is Reese. Ca half of himself
the girls are Erina Stepanavicha. "
And with that I can to use.
Ok, you want to kiss the owaæ?
You can also ask what
cockroaches, the more I savor?
You're such a wimp.
See how to do it.
I'm not doing this for trzeŸwo.
Do you drink?
We know the shop where he works one idiot.
Welcome to our country, Ms. Nam-Hong.
I hope that you like it here.
I was recently thinking about the retirement in Cambodia ¿y
S I heard the that the can have up house on the beach Communal
with it ¿s the and is used for the cymi $ 100 per month.
But I must carry the special
the insert orthopedic
which are hardly available in the tropics.
As the brand Pro-Nation
which are not great,
but after the combination with iron-¯ fingers ...
Okay, what was I talking of em?
And so. So Dewey and Jamie
agent waited for the night ...
/ And then have taken their turn.
Do not be afraid to Jamie, not
all in the boulders leading to the dungeon.
/ Wow.
/ And then I realized that the parents
/ Created a secret good home.
To which went ka ¿each night,
the children of spa y
That's why in May the obsession
at the point of time sleeping.
I never get anything good,
and they always look out the bedroom uœmiechniêci.
This 90-inch screen is large for
better than the 75-inch in the bathroom.
Absolutely.
By the way, Dewey again
, asked today about ice cream.
He told the am he, also we can not afford.
I wonder what would do the like
we see the ice chopper.
We have to dolaæ.
The charging of EOE Robo-brother?
Already should be ready.
Drinks, Francis!
We are the worst
parents in the world.
At each time step, questioned Ata
the Security of my home.
/ We are the worst
/ Parents in the world.
/ Even niewiarygodnoœci to what they saw,
/ Are still being were not prepared
/ For The greatest surprise.
/ The most incredible
/ Thing are seen as the:
/ Pants. Its size, never
/ Not worn by the older brother.
/ No holes, no stains, no wonder
/ Smell, no carcass in his pockets.
/ Had to for Insert the these pants.
Sorry.
Not too much of a paste, but you
przykryæ whole continuity. I must zeskrobywaæ ...
We'll get your ...
/ Phil Collins - "Sussudio"
/ (Sussudio is a fictitious first name that
/ Ma ka ¿d symbolizowaæ the girl)
Vernon!
/ When g half I mean a girl
- Vernon!
/ All the time, Sussudio
/ I do not even know my name
Vernon, kittens escaped were the wheels you!
This is not the æwiczenia!
Hamsters were fled with wheels you!
/ How to call me, I'll be there
/ Can I reach the dock from anywhere
/ (Measuring blood pressure)
/ This is what you need,
/ Entire operation ¿my life
/ I feel œwietnie,
/ Just say the word
/ Sussudio
Congratulations guys!
How to sign a confession,
to give him clothes.
What do we do now?
I do not know from where they can be taken ¹ æ beer.
- We can wracaæ home?
- Shut up!
Oh, God also!
Joe and Erin arrived!
Hey, Erin?
You think you're a remove the special?
Look at this.
The kiss kissing each!
You do not have robiæ, Reese.
It j is the disgusting, not me.
- Oh, my God also? Nu-nu Jamie!
- What?
Nu-nu Jamie!
No uœnie no nu-nu!
We have to zawieŸæ home!
Hey!
I'll do whatever you want, just
zawieŸ us home immediately!
/ You know, was young. Nothing
/ You robiæ. You have a heart.
Meet the up ... with us ... later?
In the the the the alarms for, so
Dewey and Jamie were in the public APCE.
O my God e Someone is trying to
ukraœæ Perfect Pants!
Waiting for him for a severe punishment!
Francis Find the thief of the
Ideally Pants and keep it!
Do this, do that.
We're terrible parents.
Through you, I never
trust in another part of the owiekowi!
We're terrible parents.
Jamie! Should
domyœliæ, also it's you.
You have a great being inconvenienced.
You're grounded!
Do you understand me?
I mean declines all television
phone calls and meetings with friends of me.
/ Nothing!
Mora of this one, also I'll be
the cheat you at every step,
like the brothers did that to me.
So here's the situation appearance.
Œpisz.
Do not worry, Dewey!
We have nu-nu Jamie.
What are you doing?
See?
The need it.
Okay, calm down, I have a diaper.
- Dad!
- What?
Wonderful, Jamie precisely the sleep of.
From where they've kind of had the Know-it!
What's going on?
O God, newspaper diapers again?
What wyœcie do?
The child is so rough,
Zaœnie also not the whole night!
We can zabraæ Jamie on
manifestations ¿d tablespoon. It it always falls asleep.
At this hour?
/ He could of me to get used to the æ.
I never am as they drove the Board ¹ ¹ limousines.
Just.
www.tvsubtitles.net