Notable Visitors are, my friends,
members of the press.
When I was told,
Firewall also operates on my hands,
and threaten the natural breeding sites of
fish, I enjoyed the up also I can help you.
Today, the Devil t blow the dam.
Later, I invite you for a light lunch,
provided by the Grotto,
Friend fish and business travelers.
Here we go.
That's weird. Looks as dynamite,
a portable refrigerator.
Myœleæ start, it also
really that of a portable refrigerator.
Crazy world of Malcolm
5x18 "Dewey's Special Class"
T the interpreter: MoszeUsz
Synchro to version PDTV.XviD-LOL:
640x352 23.976fps 174.6 MB
Parents let Dewey'owi select,
where we eat supper today.
I do not know if it was to be a punishment for us
or reward for him.
Probably a little of each.
From where they are Know-hen, also the j
like, how do you say no?
Boys Ch ³, ¿Arcie is.
- Dewey, having fun?
- Really like this.
Wait a minute.
Why do you ask?
He's dying. You wymyœliæ
really good last ¿request.
Reese, he does not die.
If the die is to spring
jadalibyœmy at Red Lobster.
Ms. Walsh, your counselor,
¿wants ebyœ wrote an IQ test.
What?
Do not belittle his brother.
It is completely of no other than you
and will not be automatically
had the same in these to use.
- This is only a test, honey.
- Mom, do not do it.
I will lose all of the friends,
when I went to the class brainiacs.
- We all hate us!
- We had better in this class.
We had computers, microscope
electron seismograph.
That's why they hated us.
Malcolm, something strange is happening
in the brain of the baby boy
and I wanted to I would dowiedzieæ what.
What is ...
- I'm sorry ... Craig!
- Heja Hal.
- What are you doing?
- Protects your record.
Cheaper than the fitness of
and there is no male showers.
- You're œwietny.
- I'm here like the legends.
You stand outside the box, right Feldspar?
Yes sir, you're right.
Hop on, Hal, is funky.
Eat ¿d ¿aj, Davey.
I ...
It's the easy, look at the screen
and do what displays.
/ Try.
It's funny, very funny.
About Bo ¿e Can at least
rzeŸbiæ stop in the ice.
You will be just the two of
For the next month which, baby.
School of thoughts,
Also have been I can be a genius?
But I'm not the moaners,
that at all complaining.
Malcolm is a genius,
Now Dewey is a genius?
The issue of time is
find the genius in me.
I wonder what I'm a genius?
15 x 32 = 3 989
480th
So I'm, like Rain Man,
great for me.
He used invent the machines,
which has such a thing for you.
Ok, the question of the 17 sounded:
"Street is the bees as:
a) pond for fish, b) the den for
a bear, c) for the coral reef. "
That's the anniversary of, right?
From where they have ... Know-it?
EOE write the same test.
4 .. years ago.
How to ... Do you remember?
That's it. That's good, because only in this way
Dewey classes we protect against the brainiacs.
Why ... can not e ..
just uwaliæ?
Tests are written so
Eby ¿³ apywaæ to you.
We Daae such answers,
the mark of the really grams of silly person.
How to ... we do?
Guys, guys! I used to try
wymyœliæ as I am a genius
and I finally understandable,
I should also AEOI to the library!
And you know what? You can instantly watch the porn Daae
the Internet and the librarian can not zabroniæ.
/ I love this country.
/ Ma ...
Head over to us! Trace through this
break for lunch and $ 200 æwiartkach.
There might happen in one of myocardial,
¿Ebyœmy could zagraæ?
For a while.
Showtime!
Yes!
Finally, we are ready.
I did not want to speak anything earlier.
But I save the us
the weekly tournament!
No, it's too soon.
Hal, do not train so you ¿ko,
¿Eby tañcowaæ in your room.
Besides, someone has to oduczyæ
Hayley and Kylie being snobkami,
Suggest as the also are of such great e
You can store not startowaæ in the tournament.
You leave the idiots.
There we will show that,
we'll be large for better.
No, you just walk idiots
because it is a competition for children.
Nowhere is this written.
3 times I read the rules!
And we aim less important than the limit,
You can store zadzwoniæ to the manufacturer.
If you write exactly
such answers,
do not get it
class brainiacs.
May I'd like AEOI class brainiacs.
Apparently they got a parrot-robot
who speaks 20 languages.
Dewey!
You've got to zaufaæ.
I am a good brother,
I just depends on you y
You beat me and wyœmiewasz.
Only if you're nieznoœny.
Dewey, I'm serious ny.
If they tell you that?
The coolest person
in the classroom ... I was to me.
Ok, I'll do it.
You're sure ... It also tripped up
What is certain is that the response Reese
not lead him to the class brainiacs.
I'm emotionally unbalanced wife ¿!
Do not use the term we use.
This is not about pigeonholed.
Blue folder with an asterisk
on your behalf
means that you need a little more
special help than other children.
Part, Phil.
This is the first name Dewey.
/ Dewey, Dewey, Dewey!
Approx. Do not krzyczeæ, kopaæ, bla,
doprowadzaæ to physical contact.
You must semi-AkAA if
We will do it the quiet.
Find the jakieœ the place.
Hey, you can podrapaæ my nose?
What is this?
/ "Do not touch, bite '
You can ignore this sign.
/ "Do not ignorowaæ the"
Umieœcili you in a special class?
Yes, it's very interesting hands. Today
uczyliœmy about the biggest enemies.
"You Zapa the sun"
and "the Lord interfere caj tracting the conversation."
I've seen the like discharged
aircraft simulator for the class brainiacs.
Oh my God, if my mother knows?
Still the ¿¿'re alive, so I do not.
I'm sorry,
I promise also to repair.
Just do not tell my mom
please do not tell my mom!
She likes to b of supplication,
but czegoœ missing.
Better, but that are still being not that.
Dewey, my outflows ata.
The check are $ 93.
I'll be giveth you of all you earn,
until you pull out the GNE of the class.
/ - Part, the boys ch.
- Hey.
Dewey, Mrs. Walsh and give the test results already?
- I have them.
- And it is in the class brainiacs.
Yes Did you come as he would. Counting you're a
happy. Did you come ruined his force!
Come on, Dewey!
I can not jeŸdziæ on a skateboard.
Okay, Chad apologize to the Lester, Max,
Zoe, Phoebe, Garth, Shell and Linda.
We can now once again spróbowaæ
read the Polar Express
in a mundane item such manner.
Hanson.
Obtain a muffler.
Well, open the book tablespoon at
the seventh, and read.
¯ no motorcycles!
Read only what is written.
¯ no motorcycles.
Well, well, just read.
You can also now will stay a while in silence.
- Why do the EOE?
- When you read the book EOE t are the tablespoon?
- 3 years ago.
- ¿It is like everyone else.
Think of the letter as g of upich,
instead of just weird.
This place is killing me slowly.
Time for a pause.
Jeffy, do not stand
at a distance within reach of Kerry.
Why do not we
Child Lock interruptions with other?
We make also are too sad.
- Mrs. Walsh?
- I can help somehow something?
I'm Malcolm, brother Dewey.
I wanted to porozmawiaæ
the test as you write the Dewey.
I can only rozmawiaæ the parents.
In precisely the point. I'll be the laughing
great being inconvenienced, for the same coming of here
but I must tell
why test so he came out of.
Our mother has a problem with the pressure dependence.
Mia ³ a ¿ny Pote recurrence of
morning when I write the test.
O my God e
Therefore, there can Know-that the there was to em.
I do not want tell that the groyne is,
because ... you know, my mom and I love her the.
Wow. It can, that the very
care for a family of his.
- It's very difficult.
- See what I can zrobiæ, right?
You do not have the angle of opotaæ your mom.
Thanks.
I'll be just contact their dad are.
Thanks for the warning.
Wow, 10 messages from advisors
Dewey. I guess I should ...
Æwiczyæ, ¿ebyœmy won.
Right.
5, 6, 7, 8 ..
1, 2, 3 and 4 ..
You the sticks, rear sticks
and œlizg and œlizg.
These shoes for dancing
greatly help in the speed.
I wasted no of the 150 bucks.
- Hal.
- Here comes the Yoko.
It's five in the morning, do not sleep the entire EOE the night.
Honey, I also think this
g the pole and you think that the again fall into trance,
but this situation is
different than the previous one.
I have a gift, Lois.
And b of the EDEM would would not use it.
Right.
So weszliœmy in the second phase.
Will be fine until
We will comply with the rule.
You have to walk perfectly well to work!
You jeœæ!
You can not engage ¿owaæ children.
I cut off my access to the joint account.
He will do the am this week.
Goodnight Fred, Ginger.
I was thinking of that the it was Fred and Barney.
WeŸcie handkerchief and gently
zakrêæcie, ¿Eby zrobiæ flower.
Later Make a bouquet
Carefully angle of the ad tio.
Work slowly, it is not wyœcig.
Why do we use the only tissue?
Because they are soft and non-toxic.
In this way, no one
hurt, and no one will sue the school y
This program can not pozwoliæ
themselves for the next process, Dewey.
Now the wage I can only
for four days a week.
But that g the pole. We learn
of mathematics without the pencils,
And the story we have no
¹ ¿ek book in hardcover.
We'll get although the
equipment for the plastics?
Instruments for plastics,
This among other things, no advances and glue.
These children are up dŸgaj
knives scissors and eat the glue.
Some tried to do zjeœæ s advances.
And he wanted to dŸgaæ glue.
Teachers should pomagaæ students.
May not be the byœ the nieszczêœliwy,
If you were the more you try.
Listen to S, Dewey, do not survive
years of this attitude.
You pozbieraæ all
hopes and dreams and their umrzeæ Daae.
Then I may not have finished
c are staring up at the clock at 4 am,
¿And the mouth of the c that the whole is not half the EOE
So you're the NEB in college.
Thanks, also tried to EOE.
I promise that the you get the
glue it to go zadŸgam.
And then been hacked
and eaten by wolves.
Because that's going on with the children,
that by tugging the for in the hair.
- What are you doing here?
/ - Malcolm, who came of?
Do not worry, he will do the am
master's degree in troubleshooting.
Somehow something I can help you?
My name is Walsh
I am an advisor to the Dewey.
First, let me tell,
how much I admire your courage to the.
Thank you.
- Your son Malcolm came the odwiedziæ me.
- Not true.
Let me take care of this æ ¹. Worries of up
including that the Dewey landed in the planter of the the above class.
Malcolm, as œmia the EOE!
EOE He expressed himself clearly,
but did not have the right EOE
robiæ czegoœ that.
The fact is,
Also browsed through the assessment Dewey am
and the result does not reflect the
results in the classroom.
These are the basis for the repeat test.
Oh no! Absolutely not!
Do not answer that to my son.
The curtain is used the to be in this class!
He needs to be in this class!
No I think that I will not be fighting |.
No future am, ¿Eby zdenerwowaæ you.
No one wants
¿Lose the ebyœ and precise control over each other.
You'll see how they lose control if
not leave Dewey where he belongs!
Believe me, I do not want to
t zadzieraæ of the family are!
You can also talk to a month of the,
how you will feel stronger.
I can reveal a
at your meetings.
It is incredible how this woman says to you hit them!
Really I unsuccessfully tried to
utrzymaæ Dewey away from class brainiacs,
but did not have a right to do so!
Shut up already!
No I think that you do not have the hassle k,
because your an evil plan did not work out of.
/ Hypnotist, the archbishop, the dictator,
/ Conservator knows ¿HUNTERS, bliŸniak,
/ Refractory talk to the months of
/ Animals, seeing the months through walls, negotiator.
That was about œwietne!
Which are your children?
Those two.
Certainly landed the dujecie
on my screen saver.
Do not worry, Hal.
It quickly feel the like
g the stupidly thinking we were on the appearance of the day.
- Let's rock!
- Yeah.
I was thinking of that it will be
have the same costume.
S are almost identical.
I twist the ankle. Once again,
anniversary of em too close to the S of the sun.
- But we tañczyæ.
- I can not, Hal.
But you have to. Too long
and you ¿ko trenowaliœmy, ¿Eby odpuœciæ.
The Ides there and win this coupon
on average two free pizzas!
For both of us.
I know that is not what the zgadzaliœmy
time that this sanctification of em
but no one else
from what I can of doing this.
- What do you think?
- Oh, Hal.
- I take pizza.
- Approx.
Œlepy coming revolution,
I can not patrzeæ.
For each an outsider
This person looks as ridiculous.
We lost him, Lois.
It belongs to everyone.
Mr. Sheridan, why motorcycles
is the way, when he approaches the aj are the in and out?
Hanson, I try to jeœæ lunch.
By the time you are manufac the interpreter,
forget it's still questions.
It seems to me that the my brother Malcolm
explained the manufac of me Zesz of the former year.
"The Doppler Effect, Dewey.
Both the sound and light of
-moving with constant velocity are the,
but the waves are short and long-Longer.
Depending on whether or not to move the
in your direction or not.
Now, of bed pants
you were a freak. "
My imaginary friends
They were right! I am a genius!
He says the c proœciej point is
Also will sound waves from motorcycle
Moving away from him are the same number of
the speed in all directions.
And when the Keep clear to you,
that are more gêœciej of the deposit they
So frequency goes up
and you sound becomes longer.
EOE understandable?
Yeah, I understandable. Oh, my God also?
I taught czegoœ up!
/ Teach the czegoœ em up!
- Teach the czegoœ em up!
- Hanson!
I taught czegoœ up!
Can not you should have nothing to
uczyæ, because it turns you into UCI ¹ ¿happy.
Sit down and b are each quiet!
Everyone who hates the, for me the.
Children, calm down.
Remember, quiet mind were,
This szczêœliwe minds y
/ Let's repeat it together.
/ Quiet minds y, y szczêœliwe minds
/ Quiet mind were, then ...
I am very pleased
Also contest is already behind you are.
Yeah.
Now, if you are already free,
This Potrzebowo in low help with Jamie.
There ¿s narrowed the eye through the whole night.
So, as if you took the first of the
Changing today at night, ...
Nod your head!
Potaknij!
He buys it!
Ok, Dewey. I have a new,
large with a better plan.
In the break I was up to the principal's office
and I created a second, fictional Dewey,
who lives in another district.
I must still up in the hack
to the school server
but you just have to pretend
dead by two days.
- I will be returning to the game!
- Sounds great!
Mom, Malcolm will give the me of the e
response to a test of intelligence.
I'm in class for
¿unbalanced composite of two weeks.
Unless you have a lot to discuss.
Dewey!
Dewey, guess what!
Finally, I know,
as I am a genius.
Here, by the, all the time on display.
Come on, Dewey, please do not fall asleep.
I have so much to show you.
www.tvsubtitles.net