Where the hell are my glasses?!
I've been looking for...
Where are they?!
Are you sure you
haven't seen them?
- No.
- Sorry, Dad.
They gotta be right
there somewhere.
He's been looking for those
glasses for two and a half hours.
He's totally shattered
his old record.
This is ridiculous.
They just disappear.
Maybe they're in the car.
Where the hell are my keys?!
Malcolm in the Middle
6.02 - Buseys Run Away
Synchronisation par Dingo & Tyno,
Script original par Amigo22.
Forom.com & Malcolm-France.com
Give me back the deodorant.
I haven't done the upper half
of my body yet.
No!
This has to last us the whole month,
and you're wasting it!
I am not wasting it.
You used up two inches of it drawing stick
people having sex on the bathroom mirror!
Would you two keep it down?
Your father's talking with that man
he interviewed with yesterday.
Thank God one of
us might finally have a job.
No, no, I understand.
He sounds like an
excellent candidate.
I would have hired
him over me too.
Right, his experience is more...
Okay, he's much smarter...
Right, more charismatic.
Funny.
I said quiet!
And you.
No.
This is the last day
in your Special Needs class.
You have no idea
how many hours I have spent trying to
convince Mrs. Walsh that you are normal,
so don't screw it up.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Do you?
Yes, Mom.
Yes, he does have
a better head of hair...
No, I have no idea what he would like
as a "Welcome to the Firm" gift...
Okay, goodbye.
Don't worry about it.
There's got to be something
I can get a job at.
There's got to be a big
turnover in Test Pilots.
Or advertising.
I can do advertising.
Hal, you have no experience
in advertising.
I am a natural, little jingles
are constantly popping into my head.
A-Wham-Bam!
Thank you, Jam.
Who's gonna love it?
Your family am.
Banana skin,
it's so nice and thin.
There's no better way
to keep your banana in.
Hal...
Newspaper, keeping track
of your neighbourhood raper.
Hal!
Oh, I'm sorry, Lois.
I just feel so useless, sitting around
the house all day doing nothing.
Well, then, how about taking
Jamie to the park?
You never get to do that.
Yeah, you're right.
I should enjoy him before
he's old enough to be ashamed of me.
And I think we should all be very happy for
Dewey to be rejoining the Mainstream class.
It's really quite
an accomplishment,
and I think a positive
example for the rest
of you that you don't have to be
in here for the rest of your lives.
There's always a chance to esca...
get a transfer over.
Okay, well, now it's time
to say our goodbyes.
If everyone would...
We need you, Dewey.
It's going to make
the eyes stop following us.
Things have gotten so much
better since you got here.
Chad hasn't bitten
anything alive in weeks.
I get off my motorcycle for lunch.
You take care of us.
You've got the microscope.
And the beautiful view.
Please, stay with us.
It's not up to me.
It's my Mom.
Hug jail!
Make him stay with a hug jail!
Wow, you guys are huge!
And, shiny.
Thanks, mister.
But we can always be huger.
And shiner.
You're out here all day?
As long as those disability
checks keep coming.
Oh, no, no, no.
What happened?
My keys fell down
the drain again.
And my fingers are too
titanically muscular
to fit through the little metal
stripes and rip ‘em out.
Well, maybe we could punch
the concrete around it into dust,
and loosen the bars.
Guys, you don't have to do that.
Hang on.
This'll work.
Here.
Give me your gum.
Okay, but I've been chewing it all
morning and it hasn't helped.
He did it! Three cheers
for the scrawny guy!
Yeah!
Hooray!
Come on, Dewey,
this is going to be great.
You've seen fireworks before,
and you've seen movies.
You've never seen them together,
at the same time.
Let's get moving,
I want to pay matinee prices.
I don't feel like it.
Go without me.
Come on, we're trying
to do something nice here,
and reach out to you as a brother.
Yeah, you don't have to worry,
we're not setting you up.
Are we?
No.
I just don't want to go, okay?
Leave me alone.
Bye hon, I'm off to the park.
Oh, three days in a row.
Yeah, you know what?
It's great.
It's giving me a new
outlook on things.
I'm sure Jamie's loving it.
Oh, yeah.
Jamie.
We've only got two bottles
of Baby Oil left,
I'll pick up a case
this afternoon.
I think two of
my fingers fused together.
Great. That leaves eight
for me to punish to the bone.
Now, get moving.
You better not be late for school.
You hear me?
And I want you home
at three o'clock.
Your homework better be finished
or I'll set off some fireworks
in a place a lot darker
than a movie theatre.
Have a nice day, honey.
Aren't you going to warn me
not to lose my milk money?
Or that I better be polite to
the crossing guard?
No.
There you go.
Balanced to the penny.
The problem is,
you weren't adding the check amount,
you were adding your address
over and over.
I thought that number had a
lot of words in it. Thanks, Hal.
You see,
it's not that difficult, guys.
And remember for next
time, the stamp
goes on the letter,
not the mailbox.
Is that the thing
firemen use?
No, that's a hydrant.
Remember the "no parking" stump?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I gotta go.
I promised Lois I'd stop by
the market on the way home.
Oh, you had a good day,
didn't you, honey?
Hey, did you like when Carlo
threw you way, way up in the air?
And Daddy was screaming, wasn't he?
Guys, don't worry,
I'll be back tomorrow.
Useless peace of junk!
Good night, honey.
I made you a turkey and cream cheese
sandwich for school tomorrow.
What are you trying to do?
Mom hasn't made you do any
of the crap she's made us do.
Why is she being so nice to you?
Because, for the last 3 days,
I haven't done anything wrong.
You see,
Mom doesn't yell and scream at us because
it's the only way she knows how to talk.
She does it because
we do stuff that's bad.
And if you don't do anything,
she doesn't get mad at you.
You understand?
It's not her. It's us.
Fine, don't tell us.
Well, that's strange.
For some reason,
I'm taking 1/3 less Asprin than usual.
Why are you pacing?
Let me ask you something, Lois.
What would you do if,
hypothetically,
there were a series of
unforeseeable circumstances,
you found yourself commanding
an army of benevolent strong men?
What?
Picture it.
A dozen guys, any one
of ‘em can rip a horse in half,
willing to follow
your every command.
I'd have to do something
really great with that,
something noble and unselfish,
but not too expensive.
And we are not even taking into account that
I could easily be led to the dark side.
Lois, you have to promise me.
If you ever see me holding a cat
and laughing maniacally over a globe,
you need to let me know.
After this,
I'll show you how to play Gin Rummy.
That's always been
mama's favourite game.
Okay.
So, Dewey, do you like being back
in the normal class?
Hello.
Mrs Walsh, what a surprise.
You're here to check up on Dewey,
I can assure you that he's just
as normal and wonderful as...
No, actually, I just came to find out
if Dewey's heard from any
of the children from
the special needs class.
No, why?
Well, uh, seems they've run away.
All of them?
The whole class ran away?
They just disappeared.
Dewey, do you know
anything about this?
Okay, well,
thank you, and if you hear anything,
please let me know.
I'll see ya.
Oh, those kids.
I'm so glad you're
out of that class.
You know what?
I think I'm going to bake
you some cookies.
What are you doing?
We couldn't take it any more.
It's horrible without you.
We're never going back.
This is our new home.
They'll never find us here.
It's perfect.
We took blankets,
and we stole some food from
the dumpster outside some restaurant.
We can't think any more.
What we're doing, Dewey.
You thought I'd steal
food from the trash and
tell 20 kids to run away
and live in the trees forever?
Oh, maybe.
But you can't stay up here.
People are looking for you.
Mrs Walsh came to my house.
We're never going home.
You come live with us.
The sqirrels will have to vote you in,
but I'll put in a good word.
No! This is crazy.
I'm not living up here,
and neither are you.
I'm sorry, but I'm telling.
You're not telling anyone.
Do you realise how much
trouble you'd get in?
What are you talking
about, I didn't...
Zoe.
We didn't want to do it.
It was Dewey's idea.
The whole thing.
He tricked us into it.
Why did you make us
do this, Dewey?
Dewey, come get your cookies,
while the chocolate chips
are still warm and melty!
We've lost Dewey.
It's the only possible explanation.
He's turned on us, and
he's feeding Mom information.
This is bad.
Real bad.
I know. What does
he have on you?
Oh, man.
I have all kinds of things
going on he might know about.
I have my lost dog scam,
the rat baby farm.
The electrified mailbox
I'm noodling with.
We don't have any choice.
We have to neutralize him.
Yeah, but how?
Okay, we let him overhear
something we're planning.
Something way across town.
We make it so juicy
and harmless-sounding,
he won't be able
to resist telling Mom.
So, she waits in the cold
for three or four hours,
and when nothing happens,
he's lost all his credibility.
Nice.
Ready to go to the sewerage treatment
plant and do some unwanted vandalism?
Yes, I've got the shovels and
the flares for the senseless
destruction we've got planned.
I sure hope Mom doesn't
ever find out.
Oh, don't worry about Mom.
She's too stupid.
And besides, she's probably
busy stuffing her fat face.
I sure hope Mom doesn't ever
find out you said that.
By the way, do you think
she's gotten stupider or fatter?
Good question. I'd say...
All right honey,
I'm going to the park.
Oh, I hate ab days.
They keep pulling me in to judge.
All I know, is somebody's tummy is not
going to be as flat as somebody else's,
and somebody's going to end up crying.
Look at this, Hal, they still
haven't found those kids.
You're kidding.
This is terrible.
Where could they be?
All those kids are such messes, they don't
know how to take care of themselves.
Someone has to help them.
Someone will help them, Lois.
As a matter of fact, I think someone's
gonna help the crap out of those kids.
Okay, Dewey, our next pizza delivery
comes with a free collectible cap.
This has to stop!
I haven't slept in four days!
You guys have to come down!
Why, it's going great.
Going great?
You guys are on milk cartons!
This is serious now.
Everyone's looking for you.
The cops, your parents.
Shiny giants in Speedos.
Doesn't matter.
We have a better life up here.
The fairies take care of us.
Mom's right,
I do have crazy eyes.
It's going to be winter soon.
The leaves are going
to fall off the trees.
People will be able to see you!
We've thought of that.
We're gonna head south.
There's a string of
trees along Highway 8.
We may lose a few kids
to predators and stuff,
but they'll know they died free.
Okay, guys, drink a little,
but keep moving.
I guess we should
go back out again.
Dad,
when you've finished watering you men,
can I ask you something?
Well, go ahead, son.
What is it?
I've got this decision to make.
There's a lot of people depending on me,
and I'm not sure what to do.
That's the part of leadership
no-one talks about, son.
You think it's gonna be all parades,
and strong men carrying you around
in one of those fancy Sultan do-dads.
But what they don't tell you about,
is the crushing responsibility.
Men who expect nothing
in return, but
an able general,
who could lead them to victory.
And instead,
you break their hearts.
Men,
I've been wasting your time.
You deserve better than me.
I've let you down.
You haven't let us down.
We've let you down.
You're the smartest man in the world,
and we let you down.
It's all our fault.
We're weak.
Weak.
Weak little girls.
Does this mean I'm a daddy?
Hero?
I wouldn't say hero.
But you can, if you want.
I just don't understand, I mean,
what on earth could have possibly
possessed you children to do this?
What do you expect?
We're creepy.
Yeah, we are.
Well, I think the first thing
we have to do is eliminate
the things that get
you over-excited.
I think maybe your recess time might
be what put you over the edge.
Wait, they didn't mean
to get everyone so upset.
They just wanted...
Thank you, Dewey, it's really
not your concern any more.
It was nice while it lasted.
What do you mean,
not my concern?
How come nobody even cares
about any of my concerns?
Dewey, what are you doing?
I've got so much feelings
running through my head,
and I can't get any
of them straight,
and they're pounding,
and they're pounding!
And they're after my ***!
The kid's gotta do some
work out on his labs.
Dewey, knock it off!
Stop it this instant!
I hate it! And the people!
And the people, and the hands!
He's normally not like this!
I think it might be
best for everyone if
Dewey goes back into
the special needs class.
Just for a while.
See you later, honey.
I'm going to the park.
Hal, it's that job
you interviewed for last week.
They saw you on TV,
I think they want to hire you.
Hello?
Thank you.
Well, sure I can.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, thank God, I can't believe it.
I know, me too.
I was starting to worry that neither
of us was going to find a job.
I thought you were going to spend
the rest of your life in the park.
Okay, men, quiet down, I have some
important news I have to tell you.
I... got a job.
That means I'll be going
to work during the day.
Which means I won't be coming
to the park any more.
Oh, no.
Not coming to the park?
We need you, Hal.
What are we going
to do without you?
I'm gonna miss you, too.
This past week has been one
of the best of my life.
And you'll be fine, I promise.
Well, Eddie, look at you.
Using that ATM like old pro!
I swear, you've been
doing it all your life.
And you, Marcus.
Who's taping Guiding Light
and watching it with dinner?
I know who!
And the rest of you guys.
You're amazing.
Every one of you.
Ah, you greasy goots.
We'll never forget you, Hal.
You did so much for us,
I wish we could pay you back somehow.
Yeah.
Oh, hi. Today's my first day,
I'm not sure where to go.
Oh, it's okay.
They're with me.
www.tvsubtitles.net