Who wants some ice cream?
Who's been a good boy all day and
deserves some delicious ice cream?
That's right,
Jamie gets ice cr...
That's it, Jamie.
He sure loves his ice
cream, doesn't he?
Malcolm in the Middle - 6.04 - Pearl Harbor
Synchronisation par Dingo & Tyno,
Forom.com & Malcolm-France.com
This place holds a surprising
number of living species...
This blows.
Get up and change
the channel.
I didn't lose the remote.
You get up and
change the channel.
I didn't lose it either!
So the stupid cops let my dad
off with another warning.
We've lived in this
neighborhood for three weeks
and they still haven't
carted him off yet.
No!
Jessica, you don't get to keep barging
in here every day like you own the place!
Go back outside
and knock.
And then go away!
Seriously, what do you
have to do to get
popped for drunk and
disorderly around here?
He was out on the curb in his underpants,
rolling burning trash cans into the street.
The sad thing is, we're still
the worst family on this block.
Coming up next, The Strongest
Man in the World Competition.
Yes, finally!
What are you doing?
Watching House of Style.
You don't get to
change our TV!
Malcolm,
back me up here!
Reese, give her a break.
Why? We live in just as big
a stink-hole as she does.
Where do we get
to escape to?
Reese, you're right.
This is your house.
If you don't want to watch it,
you can get up and change it.
Nice try.
Dad, I need some help
with my homework.
I don't think so, Dewey.
I put in all this time and effort,
then you just have
Malcolm correct everything
after I go to bed.
I can't do this with Malcolm.
I'm supposed to do a 300-word report
on how you're my personal hero.
Me?
You think I'm your... hero?
Dad, don't freak out.
We had to pick one
of our parents.
Can I just watch
you for a while?
Sure. As a matter of fact,
you can help me with my project.
What are you doing?
Well, you know that jerk across the
street who's always got it in for me?
Parking jerk
or lawn mower jerk?
Huh? No, Christmas
jerk! Bill Rendall.
Every year that guy waits to see
what decorations I put out
and then finds
a way to top me.
I string lights,
he strings better lights.
I put out Frosty, he
puts out an elf village.
I put out Dracula, he does nothing
and I look like a jackass!
I mean, what kind of sick mind uses
a religious holiday as a weapon?
Wait. Which one is
call-the-cops jerk?
That's like four of them.
Anyway, I decided to
let Rendall have
his precious little Christmas victory
if it's so damned important to him.
Okay.
I'm doing Pearl
Harbor Day instead.
What?
Pearl Harbor Day.
December 7, 1941.
The opening shot of
the Second World War.
I am going to build a spectacular
tribute to those courageous soldiers.
It's going to be beautiful
and dignified and uplifting...
and it's gonna
be all mine.
Want to help?
Yeah. It sounds fun.
Are you really gonna put up
a formation of flying zombies?
Nah. I just drew them'
cause it looked cool.
Jessica, your pasta
recipe is terrific.
Look at us, eating
healthy for once.
Reese, you want
some more?
No.
She took over the TV, now
she's taking over dinner?
This isn't even food.
Reese, it's just low-fat.
And if you knew anything
at all about food,
you'd know that fats and oils are
the vehicles by which flavor travels.
Fat is what makes
things taste good.
That's why a wise and loving God
created fat in the first place.
She is a guest in our home,
and I think it's delicious.
She can make me take it,
but she can't make me eat it.
Do you think we should
cut up some of these guys
so there's more body
parts floating in the water?
Nah, that's a little gruesome.
Just melt them
with a lighter.
Okay, I have a little
announcement to make.
You know how last year,
with the conspiracy trial
and your father and me losing our
jobs, we ended up $20, 000 in debt.
Yeah?
Well, after six months of scrimping and
saving and going up to $28, 000 in debt,
we are now down
$26, 000 in debt!
Look out world,
we're back!
I know how much you boys have
sacrificed, kicking in your paychecks
and working extra shifts, and, well, we
thought you guys deserved a reward.
Really?
This is great.
I thought she was going to
start charging us for water.
So, your dad and I are
taking the whole family,
and Jessica, to see...
a musical!
A what?
A musical.
From Broadway.
It's called Mamma Mia.
They take all those
old ABBA songs
like "Dancing Queen," and "Fernando,"
and stick some story in between.
Oh, my God,
you're serious.
Six partially obstructed seats.
At first I thought of treating
you boys to a rock concert
or Motocross or
something like that,
but then Jessica told me about this
and I thought this sounded perfect.
Wow! I mean, I just mentioned
it'cause it was interesting.
I didn't think you
were gonna take me.
What a nice surprise.
I need your Calculus notes.
I couldn't listen to a word Mr. Jacobson
was saying in that stupid golf shirt.
How can a man have
nipples that big?
What?
You can hang out here if you
need to get away from your dad,
but don't act like
we're friends, okay?
Why are you mad at me?
Because I stick up
for you all the time.
You turn around and manipulate my mom
into doing something only you want to do.
Wait. You're talking
about the show?
Let me explain
something to you, Jessica.
My family doesn't
have fun.
We aren't nice.
And the one time Mom actually does do
something nice, you hijack it for your own...
I didn't do it for me,
I did it for Reese.
What does Reese
have to do with it?
You know what he
has to do with it.
No, I don't.
Please tell me
you're kidding.
About what?
Oh, my God.
You honestly don't know.
You are actually so self-involved and
narcissistic that you can't even see it.
See what?
You know what, Malcolm?
Why don't you try to go
for maybe two seconds
without thinking about yourself
and see what you notice?
Stop insulting me.
What the hell are
you talking about?
And it never even occurred to you to
wonder why Reese is so angry all the time?
Why he acts like
such a jerk?
Because he's a jerk.
That's right. Just because
he's your brother
doesn't mean you should
put any thought into it.
He couldn't possibly be dealing
with anything weird and confusing.
He couldn't possibly be afraid
to admit that he wanted
to go see a musical because
you'd make fun of him.
Of course I'd
make fun of him.
What kind of guy wants
to see a Broadway musical?
Yes, Malcolm.
What kind of a guy does want
to go see a Broadway musical?
Come on.
Maybe you're not
being selfish.
Maybe you're just too scared
where it leads if you think
about how much he fusses over his hair
and his body and his gourmet cooking.
Some people just don't want to see
what's right in front of their faces.
Nuh-uh.
Look, maybe I'm butting in where
I don't belong, but you're his brother,
and he should at least be able
to count on you for support.
Thanks a lot for sticking
us with that stupid show.
I didn't do it for me,
I did it for your brother.
Malcolm's gay?
I knew it!
Wow! Look at it go, huh?
They may have been responsible
for one of the most devastating
attacks in American history,
but by God, they make good toy.
Is that what I think it is?
Dad, it's not really...
I'm just gonna
take a little peek.
"My Dad, My Hero."
I might have
jazzed it up a little.
Dewey, everything in this
report is just made up.
Every word of it.
I... I never did any of this stuff.
Are you sure? I could've
sworn Mom said something
about you giving your parachute
to an orphan in midair.
You are not going to turn
in a paper full of lies.
But, Dad, it's due on Tuesday!
You're just gonna have
to find another way.
Let me explain something
about heroism, son.
There are all kinds of
bravery in the world.
All kinds.
You don't have to be
a Special Forces Ranger
or fight crime in
a cape to be a hero.
There's the unsung bravery
of the common man.
Normal people who prove
their courage every day,
by standing up for
their families or...
being decent to
other people and...
Is it bleeding?
Hey.
Hey!
You want half?
I'll fix my own.
Peanut butter's good, too.
Nothing wrong with
having peanut butter.
What?
Just because I'm having ham doesn't
mean you have to have ham.
Just because we're
brothers doesn't mean
we have to enjoy
the same thing, right?
Exactly.
Everybody's different.
It'd be stupid if I tried to force
you to like something I liked.
Right. Plus, it wouldn't
work anyway.
People can't help
what they like.
That's just the
way they're born.
I know. Like me,
I've never liked... ham.
Really? 'Cause maybe
if you tried it...
No. But that's me.
I'm not putting it
down or anything.
I hear you.
There's no...
right sandwich.
So, um...
the ABBA thing...
Should be great.
Yeah, absolutely.
Just great.
Hey.
Have a good snack.
You, too.
Hal, you have to get ready.
The show starts in an hour, and we still
have to drop Jamie off on the way.
Almost done. Hey, have
you seen Dewey around?
I promised him he could
fire-bomb the Utah.
He's doing schoolwork.
It was so sweet.
He told me this afternoon he's writing a
300-word report about how I'm his hero.
What a wonderful night!
How could they say the theater is
dead when a spectacle like that
is being bused all
over the country?
Yeah, who knew you could use
the same three chords
over and over and people would
sit through it for two hours?
You can be Mr. Fancy Pants music snob
if you like, but everyone else loved it.
Thank you for including me.
I had so much fun.
Yeah, me, too.
I especially liked the
part where the father
was stabbed in the
back by his son.
That wasn't in the show, Hal.
Well, I saw it somewhere.
I'm glad you boys
liked it so much.
I've never seen
you like this.
You didn't stop smiling
at each other all night.
How could you not
love a show like that?
Yeah, nothing creepy
about it at all.
You guys want to
listen to the CD again?
Again?
Oh, yeah. Love ABBA.
I could listen to it forever.
...and then I said, "You keep
your sexist, adolescent humor
to yourself, Your Honor."
Let's just say two days of picking up
trash on the freeway never felt so good.
Wow, all these great stories:
the judge, those bikers...
I don't know any other way to say this,
Mom, but you're kind of a... bad-ass.
You know I don't appreciate
that kind of language.
If anyone cares, I'll be in the garage
alone, commemorating our heroic
stand against a heartless,
back-stabbing, traitorous attack.
Okay, hon.
Then there was this time at the store
with this huge shoplifter and he...
Beautiful Bianca is
ready to make
the Fashionistas swoon
in her flowing crepe jumpsuit...
This is nice.
What'd you think
of the Versace?
Well, it has a nice drape,
and it seems like a...
kicky look for fall.
Yeah, I think it's...
yummy.
Okay, you know what?
This is stupid.
We have to talk about this.
Right.
I mean, just because it's weird
doesn't mean we can't handle it.
We're brothers.
Right. We've been through
everything together.
We shouldn't be pussy
footing around about it.
I got you something.
Hey, I got you something.
Really? See, this is
what I'm talking about.
We're being open and supportive
and honest with each other.
Here.
What's this?
It's called
"If You're Gay, It's Okay."
It's full of great resources.
What's this?
Naughty Pool Boys III.
I watched ten
or 12 of these,
and this one seems to have
the most stuff you guys like.
Wait.
I'm not gay. You're gay.
No, I'm not. You are.
I'm not gay.
Malcolm, check out what
they're doing in that movie,
and then tell me
you're not gay.
No, this is...
She said...
Oh, my God!
You plan, you hope, but you never
think it's going turn out this good!
Stop laughing.
I don't think I can!
When you guys were dancing,
and you did that little...
Oh, my God,
it was so sweet!
There's nothing more
I can ask for, honestly.
You guys make
me so happy!
Oh, God, it hurts!
Well, I better go drag
my dad off the lawn.
He likes to fall asleep
right next to the toilet.
See you guys at dinner.
Vendetta.
How could she be so...?
Vendetta!
Yes, vendetta.
Reese, I promise,
we'll get back at her.
But we have to be careful.
She's got Mom
totally on her side.
Oh, yeah.
It's tricky.
Somehow, we've got to figure
out a way to turn Mom against her.
Okay, got it.
What?
It's a little risky, but
I'll tell you one thing.
No one calls me gay
and gets away with it!
Wow.
Dad, it's beautiful.
Well, I did what
I could on my own.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Then he accused me of
loving Mom more than him
just because I wouldn't
slash her boyfriend's tires.
I'm so sorry, honey.
Parents shouldn't put
their kids in the middle.
Or hit on their friends.
Boys, come get
the groceries.
I hope this means
we can eat soon.
Hold it.
What's that?
What?
That.
A turtleneck.
What do you care?
You don't wear
turtlenecks.
Can I just get the
groceries so we can eat?
I've got a ton
of homework...
Aha!
Mom, don't!
Who gave you that?
None of your business!
What is your
problem, anyway?
Can't you go five seconds
without butting into my life?
What?
It wasn't her, Mom!
I swear!
You always think you know
everything, but you're wrong!
You're dead wrong this time!
I think you and I need
to have a little talk.
But I...
Come on.
When your mom
comes out,
she's gonna want to know
what I said to you about this.
Make up something good.
He did it to me again.
I suppose you have a
good explanation for this.
Not really.
Lois, I'm sorry.
I'm not going to lie to you.
I gave him the hickey to keep him
from doing something really stupid.
Excuse me?
I'm not saying I was
smart either, but...
There's this girl that Malcolm's been
chasing, and she's really bad news.
She's sexually active and I'm
pretty sure she's into drugs,
and the only reason why
he's interested in her
is because he's so
insecure about himself.
We got into this fight
and I was saying that
he could do so much better and he
said that nobody liked him anyway,
and I was telling him that
a lot of girls liked him
because he's sweet and
cute and funny, and then
he kinda grabbed me
and we started kissing
and I couldn't stop because
then he would think
I was making the
whole thing up and...
I'm sorry.
I didn't know
what else to do.
Wow, that's a pretty convincing
lie for just winging it.
I mean, you went a little overboard with
the crying, but the basic story was good.
Drug girl was
a nice touch.
Creepy, a little sad.
But how did you...?
Sweetie, I'm a mother.
It's my business to know.
You've got talent, but
I turned pro 20 years ago.
Which isn't to say
you haven't been useful.
I never would've been able
to enjoy that play in peace
if the boys weren't occupied.
And the gay thing
was very entertaining.
But more important,
those two idiots actually
treated each other
decently for a few days.
Thank you for that.
So, here's the deal.
As of today, you are
banned from this house.
You violated my trust.
I don't want you
around my boys.
Knowing that, they will automatically
forgive you and sneak you back in.
You will be here every day after school until
6:00, except Thursdays when I work until 9:30.
You will have complete
run of the house, but
I want Reese to do his half
hour of assigned reading
and Malcolm to complete all his college
applications, not just the Ivy Leagues.
And no junk food.
Understood?
For how long?
We'll see.
"Ice Capades" are coming
in a few months.
Sure would be nice
to go as a family.
Do you think
we have enough?
Let's hope so.
I cleaned out every
bait shop in town.
What the hell did
you do that for?
Your stuff was
in my spot.
I would've moved it.
Try asking, butt-munch.
Right, like you hear anything
but the sound of your own voice.
Get bent.
Bite me.
I liked you better
when we were gay.
Me, too.
www.tvsubtitles.net