I said Washes!
Malcolm in the Middle
6x05 "Kitty's Back"
Translation: naruto94
It was good Abe!
Yes I know
Reese stops or you'll chopper leprosy
Thank you very much for
invited to the anniversary of Dewey
Are you having fun while my child?
I was not expecting anything and
I'm still disappointed
It's funny
I hope you like your gift cherished
You know birthdays will be
more complicated until our
financial situation improves
I love my pieces of each state
You see, we started by
that of California and the Maine
Oops, they both come from Maine
You no longer need that the
Where is Francis?
It was supposed to be for my birthday party
He called. There was a program on TV that
do not want to miss it will be once
you're asleep you
Well I do not want to overshadow
our star of the day Dewey
Feel free to me
I can not keep the news to me
Stevie has been selected to receive
a "prize courtesy"!
This is fantastic
I do not see who else you could have
What is it like price?
The International Association of courtesy to
decided to give it a "Gallet"
It is a reward that gives young
man who respects the laws of courtesy:
impeccable, discreet, polite, gentle and obedient
Congratulations, Stevie.
Thank you.
See? it never stops.
We are all very proud of you Stevie.
In your place, I will keep it to myself.
There are limits to the protection
Disability
The awards ceremony will take place on 12
We would like you're there.
You were so nice to us
when things were difficult,
you're part of the family
By the way how is the divorce, Abe?
You finally found Kitty?
Address but not seeking
on the internet, I found very pictures
interesting
It seems she has overcome her fear
make new friends
But the page is turned to me.
Just yesterday, the charming
new teller of
my bank has flirted with me
Really?
Listen to this she told me that I had forgotten
to honor my check. Honor, Hal.
Wow.
Excited by this award?
It will take ...
you to help me ...
with my ...
speech.
There is ...
so ..
so many people ...
to thank.
And if you said just
"Thank you all"?
I ...
a plane.
Oh my god.
This is so cool.
Say, you know that under the skin, there are still the skin?
Why have I always been so careful?
Thank you for this wonderful evening.
You want me to tell you: I am seriously considering
I go to my bank tomorrow to see if the
new teller needs company
Kind of heartbreaker.
Leashes for your little buddies.
-Goodbye.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Kitty?
Kitty Kenarban!
It's how long you're out?
Not long. All evening.
It seemed like a great evening.
Hello, Hal.
Hello, Kitty.
I think ...
What are you doing there?
I sort of followed my family so far
Without the courage to speak to them
I want to go.
You want to go?
I know what I did was horrible.
I do not know what went through my head.
I think I spent so much
time stuck, completely rigid
something broke in me
and I had to be mean.
The last two years of my life
are a mist
binge drinking in orgiastic
of hotel rooms
There were so many parties,
both parties so strange.
The game of musical chairs
will never be the same for me
Just as "The Four Corners"
"The game factor" or "Blind Man's Bluff."
You know what's really great?
Now that I have literally done everything.
It's over.
I stop.
You did everything?
And now I'm done.
Once and for all.
"Blind Man's Bluff" yes, but "Four Corners"?
I'm really, really sorry for everything
I did
I dream of me at the feet of Abe
and beg him to forgive me, but
it seems impossible today
Would you be kind enough to intervene
him for me?
Kitty ...
It is absolutely out of the question
I'm doing this for you
But ..
You left your family.
You realize the suffering,
the humiliation that you made to undergo a
lovely man
and a poor boy
innocent?
I know we have been friends in the past,
but what you have done is so
unclean
it is not enough to say "I'm sorry"
so that it gets better
It does not help.
Hey, so this party where it is?
Hello, Kitty.
Ok you tell me about it later
Ok, Dewey.
Now that you're old enough,
You'll follow iniatiaques rythes
Family brotherhood
Wow, seriously?
Yes, Reese knew it,
Malcolm knew that now it's your turn.
Great, it starts when?
Immediately.
Get out of that bed and lie down on the bed of brotherhood.
and give me the pillow of the brotherhood.
Hi, Abe.
We need to talk.
What's going on?
Give me 5 seconds ...
I'm a little stressed.
- What happens?
- Kitty came to see me last night.
Oh, Abe.
Do you want tea or coffee?
Thank you but what I want,
is to see more clearly
What?
Have you actually told the woman I love
you found it disgusting and evil?
- Wait a minute. You want me to me?
- What happened, Abe?
We talked all night with Kitty
and she told me absolutely everything
In detail as horrific as it is
And in the morning, we decided to
be given a second chance
Stevie is on cloud nine, he needs a mom.
And God knows how much I need a woman
So, I'd like that in the future, Lois,
you to do be a little more understanding
and respect my wife
You're mad at me?
You'll do as if he had
nothing happened in the last 2 years?
Not because you are not concerned,
nobody asks you to give your opinion
Should you see it.
Tell you that I'll never get anything in my life
Prepare to be amazed
I will fully peel me toes hair
to have a single skin
The most unheard of thing all the time
Reese, that horror removed immediately
my chair and releases.
We're talking about very important things
Ok, you do not have a penny on the Rights
Film
How dare you blame me for me?
I've always been there for you day after day,
month after month
I invited you to dinner, listening to crying on the phone
It was me who went to PTA meetings / students
for your son. Finally, Abe.
I'm your friend
So I expect you to be like you're conduises
And now if you'll excuse me.
I have a whole photo album of wedding
to go pick up.
Get the flow of water seals
our bonds of brotherhood
Although separated by a diabolical maternity
these links are eternal.
Ok I think that's it I felt something
Well, Dewey.
Bon appetite.
You'll need energy if you want
take the next 3 days
You took three days off to do it
Stop saving me time and sucks it
By ... on ... everything ...
I love ...
thank ...
my father.
I have.
Ladies and gentlemen, dear friends,
Dear families, colleagues estimated the
courtesy.
It is a great honor and I take
the opportunity
which is given to me tonight
share with you
Hoist the banner of all the cordiality
and
Reese ...
We're trying to work on speech Stevie.
The timing is critical guys.
I found a button and I do not know
if I go around and I pull all
The skin is pretty darn fine.
You're grotesque, Reese.
You do not you realize the
crucial step that I have undertaken, Malcolm.
I am trying to create a new Reese.
I get rid of my old life, it is
why snakes are eternal
You're an idiot.
I have brought chips and lemonade,
anyone?
No thank you ...
my mom ... ignoble
gave me the juice.
This is not fair, Hal.
I do not see why this is mine
they want
Kitty demolished their lives.
She was persecuted for
2 years and I'm the bad?
I did not give my name to me an STD.
It is not I who carried God only
knows what across the Turkish border.
Hal?
You're absolutely right dear
- I have said exactly the same thing.
- Hal, do you think it helps me that kind of comment.
Excuse me but you're Lois put you in trouble alone.
Since the time, you should know that you should not say anything
wrong on a girl to a guy who just broke up with her
They always end up getting back together
We loins of high school romances
And I do not understand how it
could forgive him
He loves it all and despite everything
happened it is still in love with her, I
understand
If it happened to us, I also
forgive you
What are you talking about? I know very
while not
Without you life has no meaning
Do not be silly. Go goodnight.
You're not too old for this?
Get ready to enjoy the beverage product of enfort
fraternal
It stinks it's horrible. Wait, is the tray
the fridge
Do not ask questions.
I never drink this tray,
it's disgusting.
That's right, it's dirty but must perform the ritual
Good to go.
Great, Dewey.
You did it!
I finished?
You overcame the tests with flying colors.
You are now a member of the brotherhood.
I will now give you ...
the cookie fraternity.
- That's it?
- How so?
I did all these stupid things for a common cookie?
This is not just any cookie.
It is a symbol of something very
special little ungrateful.
It is the symbol that I'm a big stupid.
You did not understand the brotherhood and content
its ritual.
Give me back my cookie.
I am now faced with a major obstacle.
I had forgotten that the sun does not cross the clothes.
You got leggings danceuses?
As well as do something that is niquel.
And I backup.
I think it will work.
Why ...
it need your mom ...
be so mean?
When it's really good in one area,
it clings.
I'm glad ...
you understand ...
about my mother.
What makes you think that?
What?
Stevie, I can imagine that my mother
cows has said things and unjustified.
But your mother abandoned you both.
Have you ever forgotten the horrors that you
was subjected?
It is too easy to clear all
saying I'm sorry.
This ...
Conversation ...
is ..
complete.
hand ...
piece.
I need some help, I
hard behind the
Rise turns me this horror
What are you wasting your time to help Steve
prepare for its price to two bullets
and you're not even able to help your own
brother to become immortal?
Out!
Stevie ...
Wait!
Ok, Ok
I know what it is.
You do not want to reach my dream
I'm sorry you missed the award ceremony
Courtesy
But we must monitor the status of Dewey
What the doctor said?
A very strange thing. It would have caught
one thing intestines qu'attrapent
the inhabitants of the third world
by drinking stagnant water.
Bizarre ...
You know, you're not obliged to go.
Hal, Stevie is a lovely boy
and I want to support it deserves ..
- He does not want you to come.
- Too bad.
I will promote it like it
or not.
They think I have a problem, they are mistaken
all Hal.
And I will not let them
away with it.
I'm just saying it might be really bad at home
That I guarantee you we will be
And if you do anything to relax
the atmosphere I do not forgive you
Thank you very much to "Jam Master".
Who said rap was rude?
I would like to thank all those who have
allowed this event to take place
Unfortunately not enough time ...
Just kidding, we all the time.
Erin Errison Barnett Errison,
Barnett Junior Errison ...
When I think you're coming with
this stuff
This thing has a name Malcolm
While mashed potatoes is not
supposed to accompany the duck
I like that against all odds, like it
Duck or not
- Ok and for you?
- A fillet of beef.
Even though I know that carrots are the background
the problem, I would much rather give up broccoli
This may be an excellent metaphor Mrs.
but you will ruin your meal
I'll have another Margarita
And speed, it is a matter of life or death
You still want the paper, Dewey?
Shut up!
If-you-please, I'm sorry.
I got carried away.
You know, you really missed
The humiliation and torture is the only way
to express our love
The only person you comfort by saying
this is yourself
Ok, ok.
I want to give you something, Dewey.
Something special.
I've never talked to Malcolm and Reese
This is the ultimate defense against Mom and Dad,
warranty bulletproof
I'm listening.
In the room on the night table,
side Mom, there's a candle with vanilla,
you know where she is?
Yes ...
Mom and Dad the light when they go ...
when they make their adult stuff.
Sex you mean?
We taira details.
Whenever this candle is lit,
they only think of one thing,
return to their room.
And it works all the time
Wow.
Thank you.
We are now brothers candle
Francis, you must stop raving.
Another Margarita if you please.
I learned a lot tonight.
I did not know there were so many
ways to say thank you
I would like there to be more to say
it was not a pleasure
Excuse me.
You know what's missing?
A Margarita.
Lois, please.
This tension is unbearable.
Kitty sorry but I'm not amnesic
You are the only one to have a problem with that
You are a very well-bred old lady
Can I have a hug?
Excuse me.
Come here grandma, make me a hug.
Alcohol is over for him.
This is Kitty Kenarban there at your table?
Yes.
You have both the same occupations so
You know, sniff sniff, rrrr?
I beg your pardon?
No nothing
Could you give it to me?
It was part of the choir, it is
possible that she wants to join us
work her singing
With great pleasure.
Ladies and gentlemen, I ask you
host presenter PBS
Frank Walston.
Before receiving our guest of honor
I'd like to tell you all a few words about
courtesy
I am aware that from time to time good
ways seem to be a bunch of cans rules
invented by our parents lectured us to better
That you said!
But the way it's so much
Only human beings have a code
reminding them to behave them
That allows us to live in harmony
They allow us to live graciously
with each other
but the most important is that, thanks to them
we can forgive ourselves.
Good manners allow us to hear the echo
of what there is best in us
And what delights me ...
Kitty, if-you-please forgive me.
Well, the best is yet to come
Welcome so warmly and courteously
our "Gallent" this year, Stevie Kenarban.
Ladies and gentlemen, dear friends,
Dear families, colleagues estimated the
courtesy ..
It is a great honor and I take this opportunity to me
sucks, sucks, sucks, sucks
This means so much to me
and so little for you
lick my ass
In conclusion, this event does not
be complete without that I found you
I'm actually a girl
Thank you, fuck you
He speaks
He is cured
Reese, I noted that your punishment
will be lifted when the carlage
bathroom does rayon
so much so that you could eat off it
that thou wilt also for 2 weeks
And rid yourself of this is disgusting
Disgusting?
If Malcolm had his clone
I'm sure you'd be trying to compliment
No!
He sucked
It could have been me
I need to be alone with the vacuum cleaner
You must sign this paper
You have disrupted the class?
Insulted the teacher?
Dewey I warn you that it will ...
heat.
We will have found a punishment
up to ...
- Punishment.
- Yes it will be really really ...
It's very nice dear.
You, you're ...
Dewey, let's talk
later.
Absolutely.
Laws, there is something I want
show you in our room.
Translation: dp
www.tvsubtitles.net