So, if Rex Huntington is the
finest doctor in Spring Valley,
why is he defending
Jessica in the murder trial.
Because, before he got pushed off
that mountain and got amnesia,
he was the finest
lawyer in Spring Valley.
What I can't believe is Jessica is
having an affair with the judge.
I mean, he's totally using her to get
his hands on the Farnsworth fortune.
You can't ground me!
That fire could have
been started by anybody!
Why don't you ever take my side?!
You never listen anything I say!
You know, Reese, some very manly men
watch soap operas with their mothers.
Malcolm in the Middle
6.21 - Buseys Takes A Hostage
Synchronisation par Ravez & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
If you are diligent in your efforts,
you will find that our spring project
will develop your fine motor skills
and powers of concentration.
Also, it will teach you a vocation
that may, one day, lead you
a life of semi-independence.
Hello, class.
Hello, Principal Jeffers.
You've come at
a very exciting time.
We're about to open
a new box of key clips.
And how are we all today, students?
I know no one gives a crap
about the kids in this class,
but could you get us some books
so we could actually learn something?
The only thing we've done here for
the last ten weeks is make lanyards!
You know what subject I hated
most when I was a kid? Math.
Dewey, I need you to
re-sort my pills again.
I just finished sorting them.
It took me a half hour.
I know. But then I unsorted them so
I could see if I could sort them by myself.
I can't.
All right. Just don't
touch them anymore.
I'll do it with you after school.
Dewey, I need your help after school.
I'm already helping Hanson.
But I need you!
The sidewalks told me they wouldn't
let me walk home anymore.
Can you...?
Okay, just wait till I'm done,
then I'll walk you home.
But, seriously, you guys have to start
trying to do a little more for yourselves.
Oh, that reminds me.
My uncle died,
and my parents were wondering
if you'd explain death to me.
Are you studying?
Yeah. My stupid teachers wait
until the end of my senior year
to tell me I have final exams.
In every single class!
I've got to get serious now.
If the finals are anything like this
practice test, it's gonna be brutal.
It's just a bunch of
true/false questions.
So it's a 50-50 chance.
Do you know what the odds are
of getting one of those right?
$23 for the neighborhood association.
The annual meeting
is tomorrow night.
It's been a year already?
Those people are relentless.
You think, if we showed up once,
they'd stop inviting us?
-That's always been the pattern.
-Hal, don't worry. You have a good excuse.
Tomorrow you're cleaning the
dead possum out of the chimney.
The smell has gotten so bad, I can't tell
when Jamie needs changing anymore.
You know, if we just wait a few more
weeks, it'll disintegrate on its own.
Tomorrow, Hal.
I'm sick of all those crows on roof.
Hey, Dad.
What? Wait.
You think patriotism is a joke?!
Representative government is an
outdated sham? I can't believe my ears!
What are you talking about?
What did he say?
I can't even repeat it. I'm sorry, Lois,
but the chimney will just have to wait.
I'm taking Malcolm to the
neighborhood association meeting.
Let's hope seeing democracy in action
will give our little cynic a wake-up call.
Chad, I have to finish correcting
everyone's homework.
It's been in your mouth a half an
hour. Either spit it out or swallow it.
Dewey?
Oh, hey, Francis.
You want to talk to Mom?
No. I called to talk to you.
Me? Really?
Yeah. Listen. I'm up for a job as
activities director at a summer camp,
but I have to show them what kind
of program I can put together.
I need you to help me.
-You want my help?
-Yeah.
I have all these great ideas for games,
so I'm gonna come home tomorrow
so I can play them with you.
You know, to make sure
they're fun enough.
So how does that sound?
Like a setup for a cruel practical joke,
but I'm willing to take the risk.
Excuse me.
We're here for the
homeowners meeting.
Oh, my God! Really?
Oh, that's fantastic!
Jim Phipps.
I'm the association's attorney.
So... where is everyone?
Well, I kind of am everyone.
No one's ever shown up for
a homeowners meeting in 20 years.
You're kidding. Not one person?
Not one... not one...
I send out 150 flyers every
year, exactly as mandated by the
developer, but nobody ever comes.
I've tried different fonts,
I've upgraded the doughnuts,
but people just don't
seem to be interested.
So, every year, you rent a room,
and hold a meeting for nobody?
Absolutely.
My contract with the
developer is very clear.
In exchange for a $2,000 annual retainer,
I'm to conduct annual meetings,
take the minutes, and manage
the association's financial interests.
Financial interest?
Well, actually, there aren't any. I didn't
mean to come off so self-important.
Only the homeowners can decide
where the money goes, so I've just been
putting the dues in a savings account.
The bank gave me a toaster in 1987.
I never even opened the box.
So, 150 homes paying 23 bucks over 20 years,
passbook interest, minus the retainer...
Oh, my God! If my math is right,
he's sitting on at least $83,000!
Who am I kidding?
Of course my math is right.
You know, it sure would be nice to have
someone finally take charge of this thing.
Would you ever consider being president
of the neighborhood association?
I don't think so.
It sounds like... work.
Dad, what are you talking about?
Of course you want to be president!
This is your chance to really do
something for the community.
-I don't think...
-You can't turn this down.
You've always told me that
a real citizen is willing to make
sacrifices for the greater good.
-This doesn't sound like...
-And I took those words to heart!
They inspired me.
And now I have a chance to see my own
dad show me what democracy is all about.
You can't deny me that.
-Well...
-It's not just for me.
It's for our family, our block,
the whole neighborhood!
Think of all the people you could help.
The world is waiting for you
to make it a better place!
Well... Okay. I'll do it.
Finally!
This is exactly the reason
I went into zoning law.
I don't see how this helps.
Where's Dewey?
When I was his age,
I was out of school hours ago.
Doing independent study...
at the library...
not smoking.
So, it's exciting about the job.
Yeah. It's been a long hunt,
but it finally paid off.
Don't you have to have some kind of degree
or something to work with children?
You never think anything
I ever do is good enough!
I happened to do very
well at that interview.
All I have to do now is just show
them that I can put together a
good program for the summer.
So you don't have the job.
I have the job! What don't
you understand about that?!
I don't know. It just sounds like
the real estate thing all over again.
Why can't you just have
faith in me for once?!
Gin. Want to play again?
Sure.
-You know who's hiring?
-I have a job!
I am appalled.
This completion stitch is kinked.
Young lady, if you neglect your education,
you deny yourself the keys to success.
Dewey, wait!
I can't. I have to get
home to see my brother.
But I need you to help me with
the algebra problems you gave me.
I went over those problems 20 times!
But my head passhrough a magnet,
and I think I forgot everything.
I'm sorry! I can't!
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Dewey. We understand.
Yeah.
Go have fun with your
brother. We'll be fine.
Everyone turn in their assignments.
I have to take this one home with me.
It doesn't believe that I have a cat.
It's 3:00. It is now time
to clear your area!
I don't think you want to do
anything physical with Chad.
Don't test me, young man.
I am an educator who is not
afraid to use discipline.
All right.
Now it's a matter for the police.
Dewey! What do we do?
He's not here.
Somebody do something!
Excuse me, Mr. Flerch?
Well I think of the
three ideas we had,
this was the best.
I win!
Good job.
Okay, Dewey, of all the things we did today,
what seemed like it could be more fun?
The rainbow acle course or the tickle maze
or the shower of lollipops?
I have to tell it was all fantastic.
It was by far the best day of my life.
I can make you happier.
"President, comma, Newcastle
Adjacent Neighborhood Association."
Hal, that is so fancy.
Feel the little duck. That's embossed.
So. How's my little bureaucrat?
Fantastic.
I'm just finishing up the details
in all the neighborhood initiatives
you've been talking about.
I was?
Yeah. Remember you said,
"I hope I do a good job"?
Obviously that mean
structural improvements:
like installing lights at the basketball
court and building a skate park...
and Friday night dance
parties with a killer DJ.
Isn't that kind expensive?
You have to think
of it as an investment.
It's actually expensive not to do it.
There's $87,000 in the account?
Well, a lot of it gets eaten up
servicing the infrastructure.
Like, there's no point in having
a DJ if you're not going to have
a really rock sound system.
Why are we just give the
homeowners a refund check?
We could.
But we wouldn't have the money
for what you said was the most
important thing... security.
Security is big.
I've been racking my brain, trying find
a way to give every area equal protection.
I wish there was some magic kind of
mobile security system that could
weave through the neighborhood.
Like a security car?
Dad that's brilliant!
And then citizens from the
neighborhood could drive a car
out to make sure there's no trouble.
I don't know.
Purchasing a car isn't the only expense.
You got to think about storage fees...
Wait, we could park it at our house.
You have a real talent for this.
Hey, it's almost lunchtime.
Where's Flerch?
I don't know.
You'd think he'd be here by
now, but he definitely isn't.
I know. I'm so fed up, I don't even
think it's worse complaining about.
Listen, guys, I'm sorry
I blew up be here yesterday.
I guess I just kind needed a break.
Forget it Dewey.
We need start doing
things on our own.
And you know what?
I think we're already doing things
we didn't think we were capable of.
3,081.
Did you pull all night?
Yeah. Math. I kept getting confused,
so I'm making a list of all the numbers
3,082.
Where do they stop?
The state-of-the-art rehearsal
studio is essentially free,
because once the garage band makes
it big, the community gets ten
percent of the record sales.
So it's basically the same business
model as the extreme sport camp.
So, did you get a chance to
go through my proposal for
a girls' volleyball tournament?
Well...
-Jim, what are you doing here?
-I had to share this with you.
What is it?
I was so inspired by
what your son said,
that I went beyond the requirements of
my retainer and wrote a new constitution
for the Neighborhood Association.
Pro bono of course.
It's designed, so that everyone in a comunity
will have an equal voice in all decisions.
I think it'll really get people participating.
That sounds great, Jim. Thanks.
No, thank you for showing up at that
meeting and making me belive again.
What a jerk.
What? Why?
Coming in here with his agenda like you
are not doing fantastic job when you are.
I think he just want the voice
of the people to be heard.
You are the voice of the people.
You are the one with the vision.
You are the one with the amazing ideas
topping out of you every second.
- Maybe not every second.
- Yes.
Your brain is a factory of ideas.
Please do not close the factory.
You know, sometimes
it's feels like a factory.
Of course it does. You are
the leader of this community.
Everybody recognizes
it and they love for it.
Well don't worry son,
I won't let the people down.
Okay, Dewey, I've got a pretty
good handle on these games, I
just want ask you some questions.
Okay.
When I was cheering encouragement at you,
did it ever make you feel scared or angry?
What? No.
Good.
And when you lost the candy
tag, did it make you feel bad
and want to hurt yourself?
What do you talking about Francis?
This questions are weird.
I'm just try understand better, Dewey.
I mean, I don't know all the right
questions ask kids like you.
What you mean "kids like me"?
Well, you're in that class.
And this is a special camp
for children with your...
needs.
I'm not emotionally disturbed,
what the hell is wrong with you?
There's nothing wrong with either of us.
I'm not in that class because I'm disturbed!
I'm in that class so I can help...
You're a jerk!
Okay, my games obviously
have too much sugar.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
This is my favorite time of day.
The sun's about to come up and
my mean voice is still asleep.
I hate walking to school in the dark.
I have to run past people's houses
so I don't catch their nightmares.
We have to tell Dewey about this.
No. This is exactly the kind of thing
he doesn't want to be bothered with.
We can't handle taking care of Flerch!
If he dies, we're gonna
have to tell everybody!
Are you saying I'm not doing
a good job feeding him?
I chewed his steak for 20
minutes before I gave it to him!
Oh, help me! It's my heart, weakened
as it was by a childhood ailment!
He's dying! I totally called this!
Give him CPR!
- I-I'm not strong enough!
- We have to keep his heart pumping.
Use your legs!
Chad, help him breathe.
One, two, three, breathe!
Wait.
I saw this thing on TV once
where they helped a guy breathe
by cutting a hole in his throat
and jamming a pen in it!
I've got a pen!
Somebody get scissors!
Eddie, for God sake, help me!
They're gonna kill me!
I'm sorry I assumed you could break-dance!
I'm actually one-sixteenth Cherokee myself!
Dad, you okay?
Malcolm, I couldn't sleep.
My mind has been on fire with the possibilities
of what this neighborhood could become.
At first it seemed crazy
and kind of stupid,
but then I remembered what
you said about the factory!
In the middle of the
night I had a vision.
You had a vision without me?
- "Mulberry Village"?
- Mulberry Village.
A new utopia!
What the hell is all this stuff?
Just a few compulsory guidelines
to help people make the transition.
"Failure to smile 'Hello,' $50 fine?
Not knowing your neighbor's name: $25?
Failure to remove your fence: $100?"
People can be resistant to change.
- What's the "Hug your child" initiative?
- Everyone has to publicly hug
their child at least once a day.
A hotline will be set up so that children
can inform on non-hugging parents.
You're going to make kids
inform on their parents?
Parents, neighbors, teachers, everybody!
If they've got nothing to hide,
they've got nothing to worry about.
Tell me about the "reeducation center."
Oh! That's where the best, most
neighborly children will be plucked from
the corrupting influence of their families,
and immersed in round-the-clock
friendliness training.
I call them the Mulberry Youth.
Dad...
give me the fliers.
Thank you, son, but they've already
been distributed throughout
the whole neighborhood.
Like a modern-day Martin Luther,
I nailed them to the front doors.
Maybe we should go out the back door and
spend the rest of the day at the library.
Not now, Malcolm.
The villagers are coming.
Look, I told you, leave me alone.
I'm just going to ask your
teacher if I can have ten minutes
with your buddies at recess.
What the hell happened?!
Isn't it obvious?
I know we're not supposed
to ask for help, Dewey, but...
this one kind of got away from us.
We gotta get out of here.
Let's go call the police.
You're just gonna bail?
You don't understand these kids.
If I fix this problem, there's
going to be a hundred more.
It never stops with them!
Dewey...
you don't get to choose the
people who need your help.
Look, I don't know much,
but I do know two things.
These kids need your
help, you gotta do it.
And even though I've never
met him, that guy is a total dink.
I thought when I decided to help,
something would come to me,
but I'm completely blank.
You're all going to jail.
If you untie me in the next five
seconds, you and you alone
will see some slight leniency.
Lanyards belong in the lanyard box.
What?
That's my lanyard. I made it.
Mr. Flerch is going to flip out if you
don't put it back in the lanyard box.
You couldn't have made this.
I bought it at a truck stop
200 miles from here.
Can I see that, Francis?
Can you think of any connection
between the thousands of lanyards
that were made by the emotionally
disturbed children at your school,
and this one my brother found
for sale at a retail outlet?
Mr. Jeffers, I would be horrified
to think that a public school principal
would use innocent
children as slave labor.
I don't know what you're
talking about, young man.
It was all his idea!
I'm just his obedient stooge!
He dangled Assistant Vice
Principal in front of me!
It came with parking!
I wonder who would
get the worst penalty.
A bunch of emotionally disturbed kids
who tied people up for a little while...
or the trusted public servant
who forced them into slavery?
We could ask a judge, or everyone
could just keep quiet about everything.
Sound okay to you guys?
That depends.
Can we get five minutes alone with
these guys before you untie them?
-What's up with Mom?
-She just saw my report card.
I flunked out of every single class.
What?
Every single one of my finals,
I got every question wrong.
Oh, my God.
I know. Now I get to
repeat my senior year!
Isn't this great?
I worked so hard for this.
I had to make sure I flunked every
class so completely, I couldn't
make it up in summer school.
Now I don't have to move
out or go to college or get
a job for a whole 'nother year!
This is the greatest
achievement of my entire life!
Yeah, I know, Mom.
www.tvsubtitles.net