Two kids down, three to go.
Malcolm in the Middle - 6.20 - Stilts
Synchronisation par Ravez & Tyno,
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk & Malcolm-France.com
So, there I was innocently
paying the bills,
when I was suddenly slapped
in the face by a charge for $45.
It took me almost an hour to
sniff out your little rathole
behind the refrigerator.
Would you care
to explain these?
Hal, I'm sorry.
Lois, we are poor!
I thought we had
an understanding.
I know. You're right, Hal.
I just saw them in the store. And
they're not real Christian Louboutins.
They're just a cheap knockoff.
I just wanted to try them
on, just for a second.
Then I saw them in the
mirror, and they looked
so elegant and glamorous,
and I guess I just wanted for
once in my life to see what
it would feel like to be...
pretty.
Oh, please, I invented that act!
Everyone says they'll economize, but
I'm the only one rinsing out baggies.
I'm the only one splitting two-ply
toilet paper. I'm the only one
snacking out of birdfeeders!
Look at this!
$18 for a three-minute...
What the...?!
Welcome to the
Hot Fantasy Sex Line.
-What's your name, baby?
-This is...
Are you aware kids
call these numbers?!
Put some clothes on!
Yeah, baby,
would you like that?
Oh, you just love not
responding, don't you?
You're such a bad boy.
Well, big spender, I can keep
going as long as you can.
And that slapshot you took
totally turned the game around!
Well, I wasn't aiming right for his
mouth, but sometimes you get lucky.
You guys are not gonna
believe what happened!
I was at the college, checking out
the trees over by the sorority houses,
and then this guy comes up to
me and asks if I wanted a job!
Experimental drug testing?
He must've thought I was in college
because of my binoculars and everything.
Can you believe it?
They pay people
just to take pills!
Why is anyone doing
anything else?
Reese, this is the kind of job
they give to guys on death row.
Yeah, and I'm totally
skipping that part.
Jamie, get out of
here. I have to...
Francis, I am not going
to ask you again!
You tell me where you
hid my pearl necklace!
Somewhere you'll never find it!
I have a hiding place so perfect,
you could look for a hundred
years and it won't matter!
Your earrings, your
necklace, your bracelet,
all your meaningless
material possessions you
hold so dear, gone forever!
Now I can go to military school
knowing you're as miserable as I am,
'cause you'll never
find it! Ever!
The stash.
Jamie, where did you...?
The stash?!
What about the stash?
I didn't say anything
about the stash.
I think I heard you very
clearly say "the stash."
We don't talk about the stash
unless we found the stash.
I didn't find the stash!
Okay, but I suggest you
remember our deal.
If any of us does find it,
we split Mom's reward three ways.
Because we're brothers
and we love each other.
Malcolm, come on!
We're going to be late!
All right, all
right, I'm coming.
Why aren't you
wearing your smock?
Because the longer
I don't put it on,
the longer I can pretend
I don't work in that soul
killing fluorescent tomb.
As shocking as it
may sound to you,
I don't actually like stocking wart
cream and telling 80-year-olds
which diapers leak the least.
"Thank you, Mother, for getting
me a job so I don't have
to be a bum on the street."
"You're welcome."
"Can I open the door for you, after
everything you've sacrificed for me?"
"Why, that's very
thoughtful of you."
You really got to stop
being such a snob. There's
pride in doing anything well.
I'd rather you were the best
toilet scrubber in the world than
a slapdash Supreme Court justice.
And how about showing me
a little bit gratitude?
There's nothing embarrassing
about working at Lucky Aide.
Listen to your mother.
She's a beautiful, foxy lady.
Okay, everything looks great.
You're young. You're in excellent health.
You're a perfect candidate for this study.
Now, one last question:
are you taking any other medications?
Of course not.
Billing. Can I help you?
Yes! I've just spent the last half
hour trying to explain to you people!
You cannot charge me $800 for
a phone call I never agreed to!
This is wrong and unethical!
You're absolutely right, sir.
We're bad.
What?
We've been very bad.
We need to be punished.
What would you
like to do to us?
I don't want to
do anything to you!
Whatever you want, big boy.
You're the one paying for this call.
Malcolm!
Did you hear the news?
They fired Sam the stilt guy!
Word is he puked into the
sunroof of the boss's El Dorado.
This is bad, Malcolm, really bad.
Bad? He's been coming to
work drunk for 20 years.
I meant bad for me.
This means they're
paying attention!
Sam was my canary.
Now my work has to
speak for itself!
Don't say I never
listen to you, Malcolm.
I had to lobby hard for you, but...
you're replacing Sam.
It's 30 cents an hour more;
you get to work outside and
wave to all your friends.
This is so sweet.
I'm gonna make 2,500 bucks,
and all I gotta do is
swallow 300 pills a day
and sneak Jamie's urine into
a cup once in a while.
Calonil, Frageset. Suppository.
These taste the worst.
Okay, Jamie, can you help your
favorite brother find the stash?
Remember this, the necklace?
You know what I'm talking
about, don't you?
Do you know what
I'm talking about?
Oh, my God!
Where did you...?!
Can you show Dewey
where you found this?
Sure, you can.
You show me where you found this,
and we can write our ticket with Mom.
We cut Malcolm and Reese out.
It's just you and me.
Is it in the bathroom?
Mom's underwear drawer?
Of course!
She'd never think of
looking for it there.
There's probably a false
bottom or something.
What are you doing?!
God, look at the dump
this guy lives in.
It's not bad enough
I have to take his job.
Now I have to take his
stilts from him, too?
Those stilts are company property, and
it's our responsibility to get them back.
It's nothing personal.
Cough up the stilts, alkie!
No, no! Please don't do this to me.
I love my job!
Malcolm, you gotta help me!
Sam, I'm sorry. I feel
really terrible about this.
Don't drag this out, Malcolm.
You got to crush him like a bug.
It's kinder that way.
You're a ghost, old man.
No one can hear you.
Malcolm, please!
Just tell them you won't do it.
Then they'll have no choice.
They'll have to take me back!
Please, I'm begging you.
I'm Uncle Sam!
Please! I have nothing else!
No family, no friends!
This is my life!
Please!
You want me to kiss your
ass and call it ice cream?
I'll do it! I'll do it!
It's ice cream!
That's delicious ice cream!
You know who has delicious ice cream?
That gas station down on Cedar.
Smells a little funky, but mm-mm-mm.
Malcolm, please!
Please!
Sam, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, no! No, no! Please!
Okay, grab the suit and
we'll get out of Sam's hair.
Please!
Sorry, Sam.
Sorry.
No, Malcolm!
Sam, I'm sorry.
Please!
-I'm really, really, really sorry.
-Please! Please!
Please!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Please!
Give me liberty or give me death...
to cockroaches, fleas and ticks.
Lucky Aide Bug Bombs only $2.49.
Two years ago, I was thrown out of
the locker room completely naked.
Compared to now, that was a
moment of pride and quiet dignity.
Fourscore and seven
stool softeners for the price of six.
How you doing, honey?
The manager says he hasn't
heard you announce the Lucky
Leader specials all morning.
No one cares about the special, Mom.
All right, if you want me to get up on
a ladder and do it with you...
It's a grand old sale
It's a high-flying sale
On an exciting personal
hygiene product that's new.
See? It's fun when
you get into it.
If your jock has a rash
And you want to save cash
There's a star-spangled
ointment for you.
Crap. I'd kill myself, except they'd
run that picture in the paper.
Sorry I'm late, big guy!
Hey! Where's the stopper
for your pee hose?
Hey, man, you don't look so good.
You want to try some of
these experimental drugs?
What's all this stuff?
I'm supposed to chart my
progress in these journals.
You know, blackouts,
hallucinations, routine stuff.
You're lactating?
Not all the time.
Usually, it just comes out
in little sticky bubbles.
Hey, would you fill out
a few of these for me?
My hand isn't writing down
what I tell it to anymore.
I have to go shave my feet again.
Jamie, where did you go?
You were supposed to let me follow you!
I just turned my back for a second.
How did you do that?!
Jamie, come on!
Do you have any idea how
much this means to me?
Okay, what do you want?
Okay, I'll get you the pony.
But, first, you have to
show me the stash.
Fine. Pony first.
Oh, Dewey.
I need your help.
You're always skulking around,
listening in on everyone's conversations.
Do you have any dirt on your mom?
I need something really big and awful.
I did something bad,
so I have to find something
that she did bad,
then I can confess what I did, and
it won't seem like such a big deal.
Sorry, Dad, but I don't
just stash away information...
Stash? You found the stash?
You and me partners.
We cut everyone else out.
No! No! I didn't find the stash!
Okay, okay. Are you sure
she's not having an affair?
Because that would be perfect.
Sorry, Dad. I think she loves you.
Damn!
If I can't do the "You
did bad, I did bad" thing,
then I gotta do the "I did bad, you'll
get a big, expensive present" thing.
Never get married, Dewey. If you want
kids, get your eggs from the state.
Mom, what are you doing?
I was in the middle of a game!
Do you want to explain why
I found circled want ads
sticking out of your backpack?!
-Yes, I do.
-I'm not interested!
You are not finding another job!
Huh?
No! I...
You are not getting a job away from
my constant supervision, and that's it.
I'm not going to risk your future by
giving you even a second of freedom!
This family has too much invested in you.
Oh, cheer up.
Once I find a proper wife for you,
you'll have your precious space.
Hi. Yes. Do you have a pair
of Christian Louboutins red
open-toed sling-backs, size 8½?
Not the knockoffs, the real thing.
You do?!
Good!
Now, I'm in a situation where money
is no object, but how much...?
Would you put a pair
aside for me, please?
Right. Yes. They will
make a nice surprise.
Hello?
Reese?
Francis, you gotta help me.
I don't want to take drugs anymore.
Oh, geez.
Okay, Reese, I want you to
tell me very specifically what
kind of drugs did you take?
All of them.
Dude, didn't you learn anything
from when my friends baby-sat you?
Remember Richie trying to dry
you off in the oven?
I don't know how it happened,
but I think I did something bad.
I don't know what to do.
Reese, I want you to
listen very carefully.
You're going to be okay.
I'm gonna talk you through this.
Now, the first and
most important thing
you have to do is...
Okay, Jamie, I need you to focus.
You got your toy.
Now take me to the stash.
Here?
Do we have to dig for it?
Jamie, come back!
You can't just go into
someone else's house!
Get back here!
Come on, Jamie! Hurry!
Before someone sees you!
I'm not kidding.
You're going to get caught!
See? That's the ringleader!
They've been stealing stuff
from my house all week!
Every two years, they have
another baby just so they
can fit through the window!
Hal? What are you doing here?
Is everything all right?
Not yet, but it will be...
as soon as you put these on.
Are you crazy?
If loving your wife is crazy,
then I'm a drooling lunatic.
You deserve the moon
and the sky, Lois.
Maybe someday I'll be able
to buy them for you, but for now,
these will have to do.
Oh, Hal.
Thank you.
I accidentally spent
$800 on phone sex.
I was doing my makeup in the rear view
mirror, and I ran over your golf clubs.
I burned a hole in
your favorite dress.
You didn't get that promotion
because I called your boss
a fat-ass at the Christmas party.
I lost my wedding ring three years ago.
This is part of a lawnmower.
Your Aunt Lucy isn't angry with you.
She's dead. I just forgot to tell you.
I've read that the Chinese invented stils
so they could survive among Panda bears.
Of course, that was before
they built the Great Wall.
After that, only the Emperor
was allowed to walk on them.
Well, I had to do it
behind Mom's back,
but I was going through the
want ads, and I finally found...
That explains the 15-foot high
cloud of bourbon I was smelling.
You stole my life!
Sam, great! I-I was
just about to call...
Oh, my God! Don't worry, Malcolm.
I'll help you!
Sam, you've got to listen to me!
Hang on!
Damn it!
What aisle are the screwdrivers in?
Wich batteries are the double A?
The little ones,
or the really little ones?
Sam, please listen...
I'm never gonna shake this guy.
He's way too good.
I can't outstilt him.
I can't outstilt him,
but I can outskate him.
Okay, your brother got the funeral
he wanted. Now let's get our $15 back.
Once again, brains triumph over...
This hurts so much
worse than it looks.
You're a Yankee Doodle dead man.
The weird thing is, I always
knew I'll died this way.
Okay, God, you've had your fun.
Please, I'll settle for the
lamest, most pathetic miracle
you've got lying around.
Just...
Well, I purposely dropped that
bowling ball on your foot
so you couldn't go to
your high school reunion!
I'm two years older
than you think I am!
Damn it, Hal, we're to point
here I don't think either
one of us wants to get to!
What are we supposed to do?!
I've just got so
much rage built up...
Are these your boys?
You little monsters!
How dare you get into trouble again?!
After all your mother does for you!
Your father slaves away to
put a roof over your head,
and this is how you repay him?!
Okay, everybody,
let's just calm down...
Why don't you mind
your own business?
We don't need you coming
in here and telling us how
to handle our children.
We know what we're doing.
Thank you very much.
Mom, Dad, the drugs
are weared off.
Sundance, baby, is that you?
Will you listen to me?!
I found you a job!
What?
I've been trying to tell you.
It's perfect for you!
It's at the circus!
The circus?
In what world do you depreciate
an elephant over two years?!
I want this all redone tonight!
What are you looking at?
Get back to work!
That is fantastic son!
Reese's roommate in
detox is a lawyer.
He thinks he can blackmail him
into defending his felony case!
That's great.
Hey, the feeling is back.
Apparently, the medical term
for what happened to me is
"Holy crap, come look at this".
because that's all
the ER guys kept saying.
But if I ever have to give
birth, it'll be really easy.
And Mom seems to be
in a good mood lately.
The toilet's backed up again!
I'll get it.
www.tvsubtitles.net