Monkey!
Squid!
Kangaroo!
I have no idea if a monkey could beat
a squid or a kangaroo in a knife fight,
but if I admitted that, we'd have
nothing to do for the rest of the day.
Monkey!
Malcolm in the Middle
6.19 - Motivational Speaker
Synchronisation par Dingo & Tyno,
Script original par Raceman.
Forom.com, Life-is-Unfair.tk
& Malcolm-France.com
A motivation seminar.
For the whole weekend!
Can you believe this?
Like I need motivation.
And they just told
you about it today?
They claim it was in some "memo"
they sent me three months ago.
So now, suddenly my job includes
weekend seminars and memo-reading.
Can they really
force you to go?
Lois, they can make
you do anything.
Once you sign up for a job
in this country, you give away
the whole kit and kaboodle.
Our weekends, our house, our kids...
we don't own any of it.
Okay, everybody, dinner.
This is all just an exercise to
remind the little man who's boss.
They're just trying to motivate
me to keep me in my place...
to kill any dreams I might have
of ever digging my way out...
Oh, my God, it starts at 9:00?
Sorry. I forgot
how late it was.
Why are your fingernails clean?
Did you clean your fingernails?
I thought I'd try it,
and it turns out I like it.
It makes me feel
good about myself.
Well, that's enough of that.
It's time for dinner.
Damn. Pack of dogs is
in the garbage again.
Go away. Scat.
You know why they like our
trash is Jamie's dirty diapers.
If he digested his food a little
better, there wouldn't be so
much for them to eat in there.
Filthy, disgusting animals.
You know, Mom, if you
double-bagged the trash, the dogs
might not be able to smell it.
Uh-oh. Reese just made the classic
mistake of expressing an interest
in something that Mom said.
All right, Reese, since you're so full of
good ideas, why don't you be in charge
of cleaning up the garbage from now on.
If he just shuts up now,
it might not get any worse.
I don't see why it matters if some dogs
dump a little garbage on our lawn.
The backyard's a mess already.
Oh, this is hard to watch.
Hey, get lost. Get out of here.
You come back to laugh at me?
You think you're so smart?
I am a human being.
I am probably smarter than the
smartest dog that's ever lived.
Now shoo. Shoo.
I've got a gun!
You make one step,
and you're all getting it.
Go away!
Hey, that's mine! Give it back!
Reese, where have
you been all night?
I started chasing these dogs,
and it turned out they were really cool.
So we went to the park,
and then we found a tennis ball.
And I took it from Toffe, and then Toffe
took it from me and gave it to Rusty.
And then we drank some water.
And then we turned
over some trash cans.
Then Lucky did this hilarious thing
where he rubs his butt on the ground.
I can't do it.
So then we chased this cat
that was all like, "Aw!"
Stupid cat.
Then we stopped at the 7-Eleven, and
I went inside and had a Coke while they
had some burritos out of the Dumpster.
Spike ate his twice.
Wait a minute. You spent
the night in a dog pack?
Yeah. So then there were these
squirrels who were like, "We're
up in a tree, you'll never get us."
You're talking about them
like they're friends.
They're just animals.
Well, I'm sorry that we're not like
your friends, sitting around all
intellectual, discussing multiplication.
You can't get into bed
like that. You stink.
Hey, I got checked out pretty
thoroughly in that department,
and I didn't hear any complaints.
Every one of you is here
because you're successful.
Successful at letting
yourself down.
Nobody's better at settling,
making excuses,
shortchanging yourself and
those who count on you.
Congratulations.
You all got here
the exact same way:
one step at a time.
Postpone that dream.
Reduce that goal.
It's just another year.
It's just another cookie...
Now you tell yourself
it's good enough.
It's not good enough!
You think you can't
help it, but you can.
I'm going to tear
away the nonsense,
the dime store philosophies,
the catchphrases
and bring out your inner Viking.
Scott Porter.
It says here you'd rather not
talk about your recent divorce.
Sorry I missed lunch.
I was at the library,
and I forgot to look at the clock...
Do you think I'm a idiot?
Huh?
Do you think I don't
know where you've been?
What do you mean?
Did you think I wouldn't
recognize the signs?
The clean fingernails,
good posture,
the cookie crumbs
in your pockets.
You're never hungry
at dinnertime.
You're seeing another mom.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't lie to me!
It's not what you think.
Who is she?
-Why does that matter?
-Who is she?!
Mrs. Finnegan.
It doesn't mean anything.
A couple of weeks ago I stopped by
her house, and she had her iron out.
She was just so nice,
and there was cake.
Well, it'll be a long time before
you get any cake around here.
I wasn't expecting any.
After everything I've sacrificed
for you, all I've done...
you come waltzing in here day after day,
reeking of her fabric softener.
Yes. I like fabric softener.
Mrs. Finnegan doesn't mind taking a
little time to stop the rinse cycle.
And maybe it's nice to have someone
who's got more to say to me than just,
"Clean your room," "Comb your hair"...
Do you love her?
Of course not.
It's just snacks.
Oh, you like her snacks?
You like filling
up on her cookies?
You know they're store-bought.
That's beneath you, Mom.
Doesn't feel good, does it?
Well, you're not
here to feel good.
You're here to face the
lies you tell yourself.
You can stop.
I think I'm at bottom now.
You're not at bottom.
I'll tell you when
you're at bottom.
You think you're fooling anybody
with those vertical stripes?
What are you,
30 pounds overweight?
You might as well be a
thousand pounds overweight.
Is anyone in this room
attracted to her?
Do you want to know what
you have to do, Angela?
Hello.
Aw, geez, really?
I got to go.
Hey, shouldn't somebody...?
Angela?
What do I do?!
Hey... come on...
you know...
Yes.
You're right.
I do know.
Of course I know.
Thank you!
Can you do me?
Oh, who am I kidding?
Guys, I need a night off. I've been
out with you I very night this week.
They really want me to come.
Reese, this is crazy.
What could you possibly
be getting out of this?
You don't know
how good it feels.
You know where you
stand with these guys.
I've got Toffe and
Jonesy under me,
but I'm under Duke,
Chewy and Spike.
Scout tried to cross the highway
yesterday, so I moved up.
And Lucky's totally the boss.
There's no phonies. You know what a
growl means, you know what a lick means.
You're kidding yourself.
You're not one of them.
You're just jealous
'cause I'm popular.
Morning.
Hi, honey. How was the seminar?
Unbe-freaking-lievable.
I haven't slept in 48 hours.
The Viking guy had to leave
suddenly, so I stepped in, and I started
talking to people about their lives.
And honey, I got to tell
you, I have wisdom.
Nobody was more
surprised than me,
but I did so well they have me
leading motivational seminars
for the next eight weekends.
Wow.
This is the beginning
of something, Lois.
The bosses are seeing me
in a whole new light.
Did they cross you off
the probation list?
In ink.
Morning, son.
Hi, Dad.
Thanks, Mom.
I called Mrs. Finnegan.
You what?
She knows I know.
You're never seeing her again.
I can't believe you told
her we had an understanding.
Morning.
Reese, I need you to put your
dirty clothes in the hamper
before you leave this morning.
I already did it, Mom.
You did? Why?
I feel bad I haven't always
pulled my weight around here.
I mean, you're the leader.
It's my place to respect you.
Well... thank you, Reese.
Hey.
Good morning, Malcolm.
There's money on the
counter for your yearbook.
I don't want to buy a yearbook.
I don't want anything that will remind
me I ever went to that stupid school.
how can you say that?
Being part of a
group is important.
Don't you care about loyalty?
I think loyalty is the most
important thing there is.
Well, I'm glad at least one of my
sons knows something about that.
Hey! What are you doing here?!
This isn't your house!
You don't live here!
We live here!
This is our house!
What do you want?! Huh?!
What?! What?! What?!
What?! What?!
What?!
You'll have to climb the ladder of
achievement one rung at a time.
You'll never reach the top
if you don't start climbing.
And when you reach the top,
you realize that the
journey never ends.
Excuse me.
If you're at the top,
how come the journey doesn't end?
Because at the
top of the ladder,
there's a car.
The question is,
will you be driving?
Or just a passenger?
Whenever you let somebody else
drive, he might have errands to do.
Where do you think
he might stop?
The dry cleaners?
Very good.
Where else?
Drugstore?
Yes!
Where else? Tim?
There's a place you can go to
have your shoes treated so they
won't develop a smell over time.
Excellent!
Okay, now... what
does all this... mean?
It means nothing.
It means nothing!
This is what happens when you
let somebody else drive the car.
You've all got to be the
drivers of your own car.
And what do you do if the gas
gauge says your tank is empty?
Stop at a gas station?
No! You keep driving!
You don't let anything stop you.
Let me hear some "Vroom."
You know!
Excuse me, Hal.
I need to have bathroom break.
Need... or want?
I'd say need, Hal.
I really have to go to the bathroom.
-I need to go.
-Me, too.
So this is something none
of us feel we can overcome?
This has us beat.
Well, then, we can put our work here
aside and all go to the bathroom.
Only there's no
bathroom in the car!
Hey, Mom.
Here's your lunch.
Mm. Meatloaf Sandwich.
Oh, morning, dear.
Oh, honey, it feels so good
to be helping people take
control of their lives.
Milton in Accounting called me
from the Motel 6 this morning.
He had to leave his wife and kids, but as
soon as the Ice Capades reads his script,
he's moving the whole family to New York.
What are you doing?
Oh, I keep trying and trying
to get Jamie to use the potty,
but he keeps refusing.
Those stupid parenting books say
to put stickers all over it, make it
a happy place, so I figured why not?
I obviously don't know
anything about raising children.
Damn it!
What's wrong with these boys?
Honey, let me handle this.
You are a superstar!
You're not afraid of this potty!
This potty is afraid of you!
You have to visualize
your success!
Now, let's look at the five lies
you tell yourself that prevent you
from being all that you can be!
Oh, Hal!
Reese, where have you been?
Why weren't you in school today?
A pack from another neighborhood
was sniffing around, trying to move
into our territory.
Me and the boys had
a score to settle.
You were out
fighting with dogs?
What is wrong with you?
Is that a bite mark on your leg?
This little crazy guy
went after Toffee,
Oh, man! And then Chewy
and Angel went down!
So we brought down a couple
of theirs! Tit for tat, baby!
Oh, we're gonna settle this
thing no matter what it costs!
It's gonna go on and on
until the bitter end!
They need me.
$120, $140, $160, $180.
That'll have to do.
I'm giving you a
good deal, kid.
I didn't get in this business so
I could rip off little children.
Hey, you need a gun?
Let's hear from some
more who aren't afraid!
I'm gonna be a vice
president in two years!
Hey, come on, he knows!
I'm gonna get out of debt!
Hey, she knows!
I'm gonna have sex with
a member of every race!
All right! All right!
Now let's see who's next up.
Gerry? Is there a Gerry
Morrison in the house?
Oh, Gerry, it says here that you
turned down a promotion four times.
Lady Luck smiles, but you give her the
old stink eye. Gerry, what's going on?
I guess I'm just frightened.
I mean, I'm good at what
I do now, and if I start trying
to move up the ladder,
I'll probably let everyone else down.
Gerry, did you know that Michael
Jordan didn't even see a basketball
until he was 30 years old?
No, no. I didn't know that.
Who tied your tie
this morning, Gerry?
I did.
Somebody just came in, pulled
up your pants, shaved your face,
combed back that
lovely head of hair?
No. I did it all myself.
You did it all by yourself.
You were in charge
this morning, Gerry.
But somehow when you walked out
that door, you let the world take over.
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
Well, I do know, Gerry.
It's because you denied the
giant that's inside you.
You two. Get down on
your hands and knees.
I actually have a bad back.
Is that your back talking,
or your mind?
-Actually, it's my doctor.
-Or your doctor's mind?
You tell your back it
takes orders from you now.
Climb on top, Gerry.
What?
Climb on top like
the giant you are.
Okay.
I think my back is...
A bridge of steel!
How does it feel, Giant Gerry?
Tall.
Damn tall!
All your life you've been letting
people call the shots for you.
Well, no more!
Today is the day.
You're a giant, Giant Gerry!
The world looks
better from up here.
You bet it does!
And that's where you live now.
So what are you going
to do, Giant Gerry?
I'm gonna take that promotion!
And I'm gonna become head
of Systems Management!
I-I'm in Systems Management.
Damn right you are!
And I'm gonna take you off
these seminars and I'm gonna
put you on my team full time.
I'm gonna work that department,
and I'm gonna work it until it's the
strongest one in the whole company!
And I'm gonna push my
workers until they've given me
everything that they've got.
And then they can all say
good-bye to their families
'cause I'm driving
straight to the top!
Man, that was amazing!
They won't be leaving any more
messages on our side of the park!
Where we going now, Lucky, huh?
Lucky, where you leading us?
Really?
You guys mean it?
All right,
I won't let you guys down.
Let's roll!
You found him in
a chicken coop?!
It's hard to know exactly
what happened, ma'am.
He and his friends appeared to have
had themselves quite a little party.
They just don't train ya to
handle a scene like that.
The law's a little murky in
this area, but when we figure
out how to charge him...
I'll be back.
I never thought about
how it would end.
It just felt so cool to belong.
The important thing
is you're out.
But my boys...
They rounded us all up
and then these vets came in,
and one by one...
They killed them?
No.
But they're not
my boys anymore.
Mom...
Dewey.
I want to talk.
I really don't feel
up to that right now.
I know I hurt you
and I'm very sorry.
Thank you, Dewey.
But words are cheap.
I wanted to do something that would show
you I'm committed to this relationship.
I want you to know how
much you mean to me.
I want you to know that no
one can take your place.
LOIS IS MY MOTHER
I'm going back Tuesday.
I passed out before they
colored in the drop-shadow.
It's not that I
don't appreciate...
We are going down to the
hospital and you're gonna
have that lasered off right this...
Okay, I know you're trying to...
But what is wrong with...?
I never imagined
you'd be willing to...
But that is so stupid!
Oh, look, they made a heart!
www.tvsubtitles.net