Dewey you mind getting me a pair of socks at the bottom of my drawer?
Agree
No mine is the top one
No this is the first! the top one just before you!
this is your drawer! one next door
Across
Not behind idiot!
It is not complicated to open the drawer
You idiot Dewey
After two months of unemployment, Mom resigned herself to go begging
his former bosses to take
they finally return to the store to test
Remember the lesson Malcolm, when you want to wear a gown you need to know to take upon himself
I forgot how good it was going to me ...
Honey ...
I have a surprise ...
It is already late I have to be careful as I am testing ...
It's worth it!
It is a playground for cats ...
you always say that we have no reason
to have a chat ...
Now ... we have one!
There's a ball at the end of a wire, two bridges,
an activity center, and a platform for monitoring
other cats ...
I called the world of cats!
Whenever I have an idea
it considers the poor
Is it going to snow?
I do not think it has not snowed
very long
Sometimes things change, we could have
I want it to snow
I can not take it out but your
mother requires ...
It is a little too big
You sure that the garbage will
take?
I know they will ...
Why ... I bought them a pack of beer ...
This is the best thing I managed to do ...
Dewey we go ...
You've worked here two months ago?
Yes I have worked here for twelve
years ...
This ... is poised to be a record ...
The chief said that all employees during
test are required to put this badge ...
Yeah .. big
I have known several testing periods as Lois ...
All humiliations ... should not they get to you
try to break your spirit with their badge and
draconian health tests ...
In fact ... they changed the code toilets for women
it is 4569260305
ah and men is 459929
And shit ...
zero body 2 ...
I'm sure you're good
in a lot of areas!
What is this?
New ad campaign
of alcohol-free beer
This is very shocking as panel ...
Nope
It is a black sweeper with a broom and
a pack of beer in his hand ...
Well, I do not know if my scanner
it may have spilled something ...
It is called Dopey?
Surely a tribute to the old cartoon
I'll throw it in the trash ... yeah
If you get caught I'm not aware of anything
And I would have loved to be called cheesy at my age!
Garbage collectors have left
No
Where are the beers?
He picked ...
He drank one and poured the other in his thermos ...
He left it here to make fun of me ...
Maybe we should be cut into pieces ...
No Dewey is not going to make him what I am well pleased
my soul and my heart to build this thing for all that
a garbage man refuses to take
There are principles that must ... Oh! scram!
The company entered a spin ..
What are you doing?
This is to replace one that was stolen is
Greg who has to take it to believe it
had a friend
Nobody stole it is I who put in
the trunk
Mom, I remind you that you are in a period
Test
This ad is racist and insulting limit
it has nothing to do in this store
But the boss asked me to give
Well I'm telling you to remove
I can not you're not my boss
It is not he who brought you into this world
I know
So are you gonna take that thing
yes or no?
No
It is not going to follow me?
Excuse me, excuse me
Yes
You remember I
deposited it in front of me there is already
one week
I left because it was too big
But you took the beers that were above
it was thanks
Actually I thought it was to apologize
How does an apology?
Why should you apologize?
Because you are real pigs
half of what you throw not even served
and nine months after your wife has forgotten three
pills that you put the plate with
your panties layer
you have a strange sense of priorities at home,
you buy low quality layers but
every Friday you offer chocolates
So tell what's in our garbage does not concern you!
Forget that we erase everything and start again,
we behave like civilized people
you do very hard work
I respect that
Hey Oscar, good appetite
He farts a lot for a dustman
Case two
What is this?
I thought them all torn
I still negative, it is a reminder of
the former Malcolm who can distinguish
between good and evil
This is not because I did not obey you you
have the right to humiliate me
Humiliate you but how?
By posting a photo store
particularly ridiculous to you?
My son also loves to wear costumes
such
Call the
I removed it immediately!
if you think I'll do what you ask me
you when you refuse to listen to me
will perhaps have to consult your boss because
you do you care that his opinion
"No employee is expected to have effects
in his personal workspace "
Do not worry mom, it does not significantly increase your
test period than a day
I'm sorry Lord,
the regulation that compels me
Now I do not know at all who I am
That's for you
I must admit that I had
not seen it coming the
Health services of the city ensure we
our garbage has an irrefutable alibi compared
the last night
and if I want to get rid of me there alone
$ 1200 takes to the dumpster and
license to drive
I am absolutely certain of not having
Honey, I want you to know that you do not have to
worry
I'll get rid of it though
costs me
Hey! what right you throw your garbage here?
I'm not gonna lie and say
the context is not ideal but if ever
we refuse to live in a battle on a
dumping ground
and not just any worse, that of
mind
I'm sorry for our neighbors and
lawn thoroughly clean
but be careful especially not higher air
And yet there would be so many things to say
such that nothing would have happened if you
we had left to have a chat
It's amazing what people can throw
You have closed the door and put the spray?
Just dive in and then you get used to
odor
How do you know if the milk is drinkable
Everything in this house stinks
The principles do not feel all the pink
we are in this situation
because we fight for these principles
I expect that you stay stoic
Do not worry I will remain stoic
As the mountain of garbage starts
not to decompose
and that caffards and maggots do not compete
the rat droppings,
no complaints out of my mouth
I feel that there is a leak, Reese
checks the window
I think I will not take
On the table
Hello Greg, go on road
You go with Greg?
Yes
We could go both
Not you think? you gave yourself so much trouble
to deny our family relationship
No it is not at all what I've done
I'm not a little boy I distinguish
between what happens to us
and what happens at work
Ah I see so you can deny all these principles
as it is done for money
That's mom, for the damn money. I gave up
all morality and decided to go to hell for $ 6 / hour
You know very well that this pub is absolutely
ignoble
No it is not that much
This is a picture of a guy with a broom and
pack of beer
types that sweep often drink beer
and guys who drink beer are often sweepers
Dopey?
It has tripled sales of non-alcoholic beers,
that's incredible
When I think I raised a son who became
insensitive to what are currently the most important
If I became insensitive to force it to
model you
Stop both,
appointment the unbreathable atmosphere
Come on Greg
I think it's nice to take pains
to organize our poker night, it impresses
these tons of garbage in front of you,
draw back before you do anything
Even these chips have an amazing flavor
Who distributed this rotten game? I want to be thrown out
I do not know what to do if I give up now,
What image of me will I give to my son?
It is true that the stakes are high, a father
sabotte deliberately authority no longer
no chance
to remain the leader of the mountain
bins
If you please the guy that makes it worth
you should be compassionate
this is not good I have one! you know the
new group in fashion? gulls in the area
the street!
Oh no it is not true
If someone looks at my cards I warn you
I know
But what are you doing?
I thought I'd show it to our friends
That way you can explain why you are
want to store as
I do not like it especially it's my head that I
asked to install
You said yourself that it was not so disgusting it
Perhaps you can explain to everyone here how
this thing is not racist
First they pick their cotton and now we
must be used to support their moral dilemmas.
This is probably the most distressing aspect of the enormous
impact that racism had on white
How son and white mothers will have yet
tear before we have finally understood
Already that we have to dance together at weddings
and they are looking to shake their big soft buttocks
Enough now I need your support, you must admit that
it is a cliché representation of African-American man!
You want to know what you really not stand?
It's not what you think I'm biased,
is having to accept that I do not work
you obey the finger and the eye
and as I grow gradually you lose all your
authority over me
you can not stand the idea that one day I am free
I have a dream
Sing my brother sings
You want to talk about what disturbs you deeply?
Is that in the background you know that it is I who am right
you also have a moral sense that you simply try to deny
How dare you talk about morality
While you use this trick to me
ridicule in front of friends Dad?
Is what I told him that you think he realized
he ridiculed
and he would drop this showdown
stupid with the garbage? I told him?
And well no!
because even if I want it to death I will always treat
with a modicum of respect
I will realize that I am ridiculed?
Hal it has nothing to do!
If you stay in it, enough stop. Why do you continue to
fighting? This is a very pleasant evening.
We came to play
cards so if you please play cards.
Why? what do you got?
Nothing
Papa
Dewey?
Yes
Dewey, where are you?
I do not know
I'm surrounded by garbage
You breathe well?
It will but it still stinks
Keep digging until you see
light
Well I got your message.
I need a shot
hand I am completely overwhelmed
You did well to call me
You swear that your mother will not know
You have my word
There is a way to solve the troubles you but
I must be sure that you're not going back, he must
Do you really veuilles
Appeal to you shows you that I'm really ready
any
Well, it will, we have passed the point of no return.
We will implement my plan tonight
It is imperative that you're here to 18h
But it is in 20 minutes ... we go now?
Ok
It's not stealing, it's just a loan.
It begins with the garbage of our lawns,
is complete with a container of the hospital and
we will make a visit to a garbage
Dogs and they will come out?
They wake up in half an hour ...
with a slight headache
If only you déployais much determination
and perseverance in your studies, you can
become ... oh no you've missed the boat
More than six hours and small farewell this badge
the last 6 hours are a kind of area
all hazards
eyes were so fixed on the finish line
we do not even realize we are
trying to fill the pockets of biscuits
Tell me Greg, you Differencies right from wrong?
I do not understand what you mean
Say that there is a thing to you to do and
you hoping someone else would
but eventually you realize that you would do yourself
even in defiance of all the rules
Oh there it is I thought I was dreaming, this thing we have
do ... What?
We'll do this we will finally
from both, it's amazing
I beg
Oh you we
get rid of this thing
Oh yes Shirley is too early, I
most can bear
I understand you completely,
since the installation of this panel
I find that there is much more black
before the store
Pardon?
They are not part of the customer and we
does not have enough staff to
follow all
Thank you Lois
What are you doing?
I put it back in its place
Really?
I am always ready to
recognize my wrongs
There are things that had me completely
escaped
probably because I was obsessed with the fact
you to obey me
what matters is that I want him to stay here,
must stay here!
Talk about something, now I'm
to remove
It's true look at that
We live in what time it is called
Dopey is the great delusion
But if I remove it believe that it is through
pure spirit of contradiction
I am a spirit of contradiction?
No, I find it completely shocking thing
I really do and I did not know before
because I was damn upset, unless it
or otherwise ...
I know, I'll think about how to get rid of in
leaving in its place and acting as if
nothing was
Ok you can go
Reese what are you waiting for go!
Dad, I followed a possum who showed me
the way
Dewey Not now, Dad handles
bins
You're sure it's a good idea?
This is really not the kind of questions
ask now.
What are you playing Reese?
What's the point of running? We live here!
Whatever!
If I leave, Mom what she wanted,
if I take it off, Mom has made me obey and
she has got what she wanted
I decided though is ...
a minute ... I am not required
deciding
I can rely on luck, face
I take it off, I let battery in its place
I do not obey my mother ever
From now on, I will not obey
to me alone
I'm glad you like it
This dish goes well with wine
you will be able to take three containers
today?
Two course, both!
Translation by dp
www.tvsubtitles.net