Dewey? (SIGHS)
Come on out, honey!
How does he know
he's going to the doctor?
I certainly didn't say anything!
Dewey?
Son?
Dewey, come on out!
We love you, son. Dewey,
come on, we're gonna be late!
Oh, poor little thing.
Go start the car.
# "Boss Of Me" -
They Might Be Giants
Awesome dinner, Mom!
Those are the best
fish sticks I've ever had!
Seriously, I don't know
how you do it.
The microwave. But for
the perfect amount of time.
I'd better clear my plate
and start my homework.
I thought he was sick,
but tomorrow he's old enough to get
his learner's permit.
He's on his best behaviour
until he passes the test.
Can I get anyone a nice cup of
peppermint tea? Helps digestion.
Mom and Dad have been looking for
any excuse to ground him,
but he hasn't screwed
up once in three weeks!
It's actually
getting kinda boring.
Aah!
Didn't think so.
Remember, Dad, you're picking me up
from school to take me to the DNV.
I wouldn't miss it, son.
(Dear God, what
are we gonna do?)
(What can we do?
He hasn't done anything.)
(It's Reese! We
haven't looked hard enough.)
We're gonna have to face it,
that kid is gonna be mobile.
Reese surrounded by
6,000lbs of steel
and 20 gallons
of explosive fuel?!
It's like giving a shark
a sub-machine gun!
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello?
Hey, Dad. Francis!
Hi, how are you? We
haven't heard from you in so long!
Yeah. You know how I've always been
impulsive and independent-minded,
but basically
just unlucky? What?
Well, there's been
a certain incident here
and without going into
the blame game, let's just say
there's been some damages.
That's why you're calling?
No, you can't do that any more.
You're on your own, you've
emancipated yourself, remember?
You can't run to your parents for
money at the first sign of trouble!
I'm not running to my parents,
I'm calling as one adult to another
for an adult... loan.
No! You've made whatever mess
you've made and you take care of it!
I have been taking care of it!
I got Big Red to cut me the lumber
in exchange for fur-lined boots.
I got Pete to make the boots,
but only because I promised him
a new set of teeth.
As you probably know, teeth don't
come cheap!
And that's where you...
(SIGHS)
Hey, Dave! You know that digital
camera Bernie got that you like?
Yeah? Well, what would you pay
if I could get it for you?
You can get Bernie
to give up his camera?
Absolutely!
I've been waiting for this
my whole life!
Once I'm driving,
everything changes.
I've got to stay out of trouble for
the next 16 hours and I'm home free!
How's that? A little
tighter on this side.
OK, you're all set. Now, remember,
do not untie me until the morning,
no matter what I say
or how much I beg. Got it.
Uh-oh, I gotta go to
the bathroom. Too bad.
Just testing.
Thanks, buddy.
It's weird. Reese suddenly doesn't
seem as irritating as he used to.
It's amazing what a driver's licence
can do for a relationship!
Hi. Dewey, I am warning you,
if you even touch me,
you can forget about me driving you
anywhere for the rest of your life!
I have nowhere to go.
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello? Hi, Lois, it's Craig.
I can't talk right now, er, I'm on
the other line. Only take a second.
I have something to say to you
that I only feel comfortable saying
because we're like family.
Your son Malcolm
is a filthy vandal.
What?! He threw eggs all over
the front of my new apartment.
Him and his wheelchair friend.
They wanted some free candy,
I said no, next thing I know,
it's like D Day here.
Malcolm, get in here! You'd think
I'd be the last person he'd target
after I forgave your family
for burning my old place down,
which I'd like to remind you,
I hardly ever mention.
Craig, I am so sorry!
Well, boys will be boys.
All I want is for him to
come over and clean it up.
If he could get me a non-fat latte
along the way, that would be great.
Don't worry, he's on his way.
What is the matter with you,
throwing eggs at Craig's door?!
What are you talking about?
I did it, I did it!
You passed the test? I aced it!
You got five wrong! Yeah, but I got
11 right, and that's good enough.
If the DNV was running my school,
I'd be, like, a C student!
Well, congratulations.
Send the cheque
to the driving school?
Yes, Reese. You sure you
signed it? It's not gonna bounce?
Everything is fine. Just go there
straight after school tomorrow.
You guys are the best!
I promise when you're old and crazy,
I'll drive to the home and visit you
Maybe go for a drive round
the park. Would you like that?
I can't wait(!)
Why are you still here? Get
over to Craig's, start cleaning!
I didn't throw
anything at his door, I swear!
Why would a grown man lie about
something like that?!
I lied because I
needed your help.
I finally got
my insurance settlement.
This receiver works
at both SRS 5.1 and DTS.
Subwoofer for
surround sound,
progressive-scan DVD player.
Plays both AIFF and MP34
on either CDs or CDRs.
I figured you'd be
comfortable with this.
I mean, the guys at the store
couldn't find the graphic equalisers
with two hands and a flashlight.
You got me here to hook up your
stereo? Can't you get one of your
friends to help you?
And tick off the
other friends I didn't ask?
Malcolm, this goes
far beyond just a stereo.
This is going to be the greatest
entertainment centre ever.
Have you ever wanted to
be the best at something?
Not just good, I
don't mean great,
I mean the absolute best?
I don't know.
Well, I have.
Ever since I was a kid
watching Land of the Lost
on my tiny black
and white six inch.
I knew there'd be a day, a day when
I could create my high-def universe.
A magical realm where fantasy
and technology intersect
on my every whim
because I'm the King.
So your lifelong dream was to become
the world's best TV watcher?
Yeah. I'm in!
I still can't believe it! For
the first time ever, I'm gonna be...
..behind the wheel!
(He keeps doing that.)
I have to go to
Craig's after school.
You still have more to clean up?
Yeah. I made a hell of a mess.
Hey, Dewey, I want you to know
there's no hard feelings
about the last couple of weeks.
(Because you're gonna suffer
every day for the next ten years.)
Yeah, they're brand new.
The college boy got 'em for me.
This is awesome!
Willy's grandson will love this!
Remember, you gotta get that sled
team out to Camp Three before dark.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
You've driven dogs before, right?
What do I look
like? Stop worrying!
Neil, you know how to drive
a dog team? Yeah.
Do you still have a
crush on Joe's sister?
Yeah, but Joe won't let me
date her just cos I'm Irish...
..and I got a
bounty on my head.
Lemme see what I can do.
Sorry!
Ooo, sorry! I'm sorry!
Ooo, sorry! Damn it!
I thought I paid
this gas bill already!
You're doin' great. Turn right,
you're ready for street drivin'.
What?! Jackie's been driving for
half an hour! Her turn is over!
It's only been 10 minutes, Reese!
I've been timing you!
You've been driving
exactly 27 minutes.
You're gonna use up my turn!
When did you learn to tell time?
It's digital. I can't believe
I have to be in the same car
as a low life like you!
Oh, I'm a low life?
You spend everyday at lunch
sucking on a straw
that's been under my armpit!
You pig! That's
it, I've had it!
I don't even know
what text messaging is,
how can they charge me
15 bucks a month for it?
Malcolm?
Don't connect those cables,
their impedance values aren't equal!
You'll get a reflected transmission.
That's what the scan modulation
is for!
Trust me, 480P is more
than enough to take care of it.
Then I can't use the analogue
pre-amp to play my SACDs.
You're tired,
you're not thinking right!
I'm using single-ended interconnects
for the front left-right speakers!
Are you mad? You can't
do that! Just watch me.
I know it sounds weird, but this is
the most fulfilling conversation
I've had in weeks.
Shouldn't there be a signal to tell
these cars to get out of the way?
Does anyone see a
thingy of stamps by their feet?
It's been 45 minutes! I'm not gonna
get my turn! OK, pull over.
Finally! I just need
to go to the post office.
Oh, God, look
at that line.
What are you doing? It's my turn!
Oh, sorry, doesn't look like
we'll have enough time.
But you got very valuable...
watching experience.
We'll get to you next week.
Slide over. No way!
(BELCHES) Ugh!
I at least get to drive
back to the stupid school.
I'm not going home without at least
touching the steering wheel.
(SMASH!) What was that?!
You crashed! No, I didn't.
The car's not even in drive!
Yeah, well, you're behind the wheel,
what are you gonna
do now, hotshot? Ah!
I'm so sorry, I...
Aaarrrggghhh!
You're two
clicks away
from the new shape
of lip colour.
Infallible colour
lasts up to 16 hours,
even after
eating.
The conditioning balm
helps lock in moisture.
Brilliant!
In ten radiant shades.
Colour that's made
to stay on your lips...
And only on your lips.
Infallible?
It's my lip colour.
The lip duo
compact
that lasts
up to 16 hours.
Because you're worth it.
Get great results
all around your home
when you try
new Cillit Bang Multi Power.
It was so quick and easy.
Look how it cleans this toothpaste
and my make-up
stains. What a shine!
And a new fresh smell.
For taps clogged
with limescale...
Look, it's amazing.
Clean as a whistle.
It also works
in the kitchen
and gets rid of cooking spills
with so little effort.
For great results
all around your home.
Try it now!
Cillit Bang Grime & Lime
Multi Power.
And no more tedious scrubbing
with Cillit Bang Grease & Floor.
The new
all-purpose cleaner
that gives great results
on large surfaces
and even
when used neat.
Cillit Bang
Grease & Floor.
There comes a time when
a dog's joints get a bit...
you know, not
what they were.
But with new
Pedigree Joint Care +,
you could see a
real difference.
One treat a day
for just six weeks,
and you'll soon see why
you can't keep a good dog down.
So, let's see,
you've got grand theft auto,
malicious crashing and what else?
Oh, yeah, kidnapping me!
I knew you'd go to prison,
I just figured it'd be after prom.
Shut up and let
me think about this!
Do you realise you are
driving 20mph on a freeway?
I am not getting a speeding ticket
on top of everything else!
Will you just leave me alone
and let me figure this out?
(SIRENS WAIL)
Ha!
OK, don't panic, it's
just a cop, that's nothing.
You can handle
one stupid cop.
Oh, man!
What are you doing?
Aren't you pulling over?
I don't know.
I think I'm still going.
If you're being chased by the cops
and they say pull over, you have to.
That's the law!
Yeah, well, even
so... You can't!
You know, that's a
really good plan, Reese.
There's just one
little problem with it.
This is a driver's ed car!
Oh! Those cheap sons of...!
(UPROAR) Don't start screaming at me
about Francis! I haven't seen him!
I spent hours digging post holes
cos he promised me a satellite dish!
He promised me
a satellite dish!
Where the hell's
my George Foreman grill?
I'm just as mad
as the rest of you.
I'm pretty sure these
teeth came off a dead guy.
Tastes like a Canadian.
Well, he's through
taking advantage of me!
Pierre, your identical American
cousin is in a heap of trouble.
Oui.
Another half turn. Easy!
Easy, don't strip it.
Got it! Beautiful!
Now all we have
to do is adjust it.
Congratulations! It was pretty hairy,
especially with the hub connectors.
Stripping quarter inch
off the leads was inspiring.
I hardly remember it.
I was running on adrenaline!
You know, Craig, I gotta tell you,
this was a lot of fun.
I actually enjoyed
spending time with you.
You didn't have to lie
to get me over here. Yes, I did.
Yeah, OK, but
you wouldn't now.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is,
you know,... I'm sorry for
all the times we made you miserable.
It's OK. You're a good guy.
I like you.
Run down and check
the signal, will ya?
OK.
And try not to
screw it up,... buddy.
We're getting 42 percent!
Try moving the dish
a little to the right.
A little more!
57! Up a little more!
61!
"A low-speed chase involving
a teenager, a driver's ed car
and what appears
to be a hostage."
"It all happened so fast.
They just took off."
"With my chequebook and all
my financial papers in the car."
"That's not an excuse,
I just hope that B of A
understands the situation."
"The hostage is unharmed,
but it's a matter of time
before police end it -
one way or the other."
Oh, no! Now they're
never gonna let me drive!
How's it looking?
Malcolm?
Malcolm! I can't hear you!
You're not watching
without me, are you?
Whaa!
Malcolm! Malcolm!
(INDISTINCT TELEVISION BROADCAST)
Just let me talk to him
and I can end this in five minutes!
I'm sorry, I don't
think that's a good idea.
We have psychologists to
handle kids in these situations.
We know how they think.
Think?! My son doesn't think!
He's driving in circles. He's made
three laps around the city already!
There's our dry-cleaner again.
Here's another picture of
my brother you can show on TV.
Just get him on the phone
and let me handle this.
I'm the only one who knows how.
Trust me, we have it under control.
Don't think I don't know
what's gonna happen!
You're gonna do your standard police
thing and my son is gonna get shot!
Ma'am, that almost never happens.
Just get him on the phone!
Tell him if he wants to see daylight
again, he'll pull over this instant!
"Your mother wants you to know
that she loves you and..."
He has 10 seconds to pull over
that car or I will...!
"Give you lots of
hugs and kisses."
You heard your mom, you're not
in trouble. Can you pull over now?
That's not my mom.
Please, dear God, I know I haven't
been a saint, but I swear, if you...
Ah! Aaaarrrggghhh!
No, Daddy, this is not my fault,
I'm just a passenger.
How is this making you look like
a chump? I'm the one...
Hold on.
Hello? No! No,
I'm on the other line.
If you wanna talk to him,
use the bullhorn thingy!
Hi, I'm back.
No, I was not
talking to Mom, it was the...
Daddy, I don't
care who she's...
No, I will not tell her!
You have to stop
putting me in...
Go ahead. Go ahead, cancel
the card, cancel all my cards!
I'm gonna be in this car
for the rest of my life, anyway.
OK, I've got an idea.
What? There's a railroad
crossing about a mile ahead.
If we jump out a second before
the train squashes the car,
we can start new lives
as circus people.
Reese, come on,
this is getting scary.
What are you gonna do?
"This is your
last warning."
"Pull over or you will
be forced from the road."
Jackie, I have to
tell you something.
Just because I hate you
doesn't mean I'm not sorry.
What? I didn't mean
to get you into this!
It's just that I'm not...
You know, I'm not very smart.
So when I get in trouble, I panic,
then I do things that make it worse.
I'm really sorry.
And your dad is a tool.
Hey, I was just kidding about
the kidnapping thing.
You have enough to worry about
without me being a jerk about it.
Wait a second!
Jackie, gimme your phone!
I have a brother who's a total
genius, he'll know what to do.
How many police cars are behind you?
I don't know, eight, maybe nine.
What are we gonna do?
There's no way out!
Sometimes things look their darkest
right before the sun breaks through.
And sometimes
you just have to realise
that the game is over
and that you've lost. The...
The only left thing to do
is to stop running,
stand up and face the
consequences like a man. And...
And even if the outcome is more
horrible than you could've imagined,
you can hold your head
up high, show some class
and end it with dignity.
Class? "For the
love of God, stop! Argh!"
Where is he going? He's turning.
# "In Too Deep" - Sum 41
Wow! Nice! ..It was!
OK, that's impressive.
Look, he's pulling over!
I think he's gonna
parallel park! No way!
The spot is way too small! He hasn't
given himself enough space!
He did it! Now just get out of
the damn car, please!
Reese, that was amazing!
Listen, when the kids at school
ask you about this,...
..tell them I
got under your bra.
I'll call the lawyer
and have him meet us there.
Give 'em a reason,
give 'em a reason!
"The suspect appears to be
resisting."
"Oh, looks like they're taking out
the pepper spray." "Argh! Argh!"
Why do we have to have to dress
like this? It's his hearing!
I want the judge to see that Reese
comes from a respectable family
that loves him very much!
Why aren't they trying him
as an adult? Come on, we gotta go!
I have to go to Craig's.
He's getting his cast off
and wants me to videotape it.
Craig's talking already?
Good for him!
I was really creeped out by that
one blink yes, two blinks no stuff.
No, you got it the other
way around. One blink means no.
So the soup was too hot!
# "Boss Of Me" -
They Might Be Giants
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
www.tvsubtitles.net