'Previously,...'
It's a company picnic! Attended
by my new boss whom I haven't met!
I like her. Don't screw this up!
Laurie, hi! It's
so good to see you!
Keep moving.
Is your new boss here?
They're all here! There's
Landon, head of the company.
I woke up with the dog...
licking my face.
I thought it was my husband!
I better see what my boys are doing.
It is a real pleasure to meet you,
Mr Landon! Er, same here!
You're playing girls?! The men won't
play us until we beat the ladies.
You're responsible for these.
The coach wants to make a wager.
What's up with my skates? The blades
are dull! Somebody unscrewed mine!
If you liked someone, would you
tell them? I like you, too.
Oh, my God! What? I was
talking about Gary Spindler!
You're going to be tied together
for three hours. Let's get hopping.
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
Wow, these are nice woods!
Come on, Malcolm,
we're still friends!
We can still have fun, right? Why
don't you help me with this clue?
"North of the fork
and up a small hill,
under a joke without J
is a yellow bill."
This doesn't make any sense!
You'd think they'd
make sense! Gary Spindler?!
Malcolm! What do you see in him?
He high-fives people when they decide
what they want on their pizza!
He still says, "It's the bomb!"
"Hi, I'm Gary.
I have a laser pointer!"
He's nice. Can we concentrate
on the scavenger hunt
or we'll fall behind!
It's a yellow duck
under that oak tree there.
Joke without J, oke. Oak tree.
The fork was back there.
(SQUEAKS)
Wow, you were right!
That's great, Malcolm!
You're good at this! Yes, I am.
I have a lot of other good qualities.
There's lots of things to like about
me if I was given half a chance!
Can we just do this?
Fine.
OK, clue number two.
"Look for this gem
on an overgrown hem."
"Stay to your right
or it might take all night."
For God's sakes! Gary Spindler?!
What's going on out there?
We've gone back two goals!
I can't get speed with
these skates! Get them sharpened!
I already had Francis
sharpen them twice! (COUGHS)
Besides, number 32 is amazing!
She's a monster!
She's crippled our front line!
(CHUCKLES)
Sorry to take you away
from your family, Mr Landon.
About this Mr Lan- I know, Bert.
Bert, I need your help! The cubicle
dwellers are getting restless. Ah.
Apparently they know about my
reputation for downsizing. I thought
you could shoot them a little BS
to calm them down. Actually, I...
Great! Hey, everybody! I
know there are some concerns here
so I've brought Mr Landon over
to put your minds at ease.
Now, he's taking time away from his
family so not too many questions.
This is beautiful! Phil, Mr Landon
would like to put our minds at ease!
Isn't that right, Bert?
Hal?!
Ah, Bert. Albert.
Halbert. Hal! You know?
I'm sensing a lot of confusion here
but the keyword to keep in mind
is loyalty.
When you're worried about
your job it's very tempting
to make a fellow
co-worker look bad
but who really cares if
someone's wife's an alcoholic...
..or that someone has an unnatural
attraction to women in suits?
The important thing
is we're in this together!
And remember,
nobody likes a snitch!
So, let's have a
great picnic, huh?
Hah-hah!
"Go north of the fork
and up a small hill."
"Under a joke without J
is a yellow bill."
I don't see a fork. I saw a broken
spoon! Shut up! I'm trying to think
of a joke without a lot of
Js in it! Ohh, I found a cup.
You're supposed to look for a fork!
You know, a fork? The little thing
with... things! Geez!
You go. I'll stay here.
We're tied to
each other, you idiot!
Oomph!
Ooh! (GRUNTS)
Aaah!
Got it! Five more and we win!
Five more and we win.
You're a genius! Thanks.
You're, er,... big.
(MUFFLED)
Help!
Yeah! Lavernia, looks like we're
gonna make it nine years in a row!
Maybe we should put our pregnant
girls in, make it more of a game!
Wh-Who is that helping? All that's
gonna do is make her feel bad
plus now all our pregnant girls
are gonna wanna get in the game!
Number 32 is killing us!
Looks like it's time
for a little strategy!
# "Bad To The Bone"
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Oomph! Argh!
(REVVING CHAIN SAW
ACCOMPANIES MUSIC)
Eric!
Yeah!
(ALL CHEER)
Now let's play some hockey!
(WHISTLE)
(REGGAE MUSIC)
You were amazing! I would never
have found those kids without you!
You know something? Together we make
the perfect three-legged person!
I wish we could stay
like this forever! Yeah.
Wait! Why can't we?
There's people that do surgeries!
You're the smartest guy
I've ever met! Thanks, buddy.
We've got to find that fork.
Hey,... I... want... candy!
What did I tell you? Sit in that
chair until the picnic is over!
Excuse me? Are you Lois?
Yes. Where do you get off talking
to my wife about my mother?!
I wet my bed every night
until I was 16.
My mother changed those sheets
for years and never said a word! I
don't care if they don't get along.
My mother's important to me. I never
said anything about your mother!
By the way, I don't
have a porn problem!
She introduced
it into our home!
I don't have any interest - It was
her idea and now I'm the pervert!
I don't know what it is about porn.
Maybe it's the safety
of emotional distance! That's it!
If you're gonna make me do this
we're gonna do this. Now sit down!
Your problem is you both
see yourselves as victims.
You've got to talk to each other.
There's a thing called give and take
to make it work. Do you
understand? Yes. I'm not finished!
If you're gonna make this work you
have to make sure that you are home
every night at 6:30, not 6:35.
Create an atmosphere of trust.
(HOOTER)
I think we might win! Damn right!
I've got 600 bucks riding on it!
What are you doing?
You're a man short. Where's Amis?
He ran out yelling about government
helicopters and murderous clones.
(THUMPING)
'Hello? Is anybody there?'
Don't worry. I'll cover for him.
Alright. You're a good man, Francis.
I'm doing what
anybody would do.
Sorry.
.
I've always loved Elnett.
You know why?
Elnett from
L'Oreal Paris.
It's so fine.
It:
My hair feels like satin.
It holds perfectly.
For me, it's the best
hairspray in the world.
And now:
Because you're worth it.
It's important to
protect your teeth
from the build-up
of invisible plaque.
But how do you fight
something that's invisible?
Simple.
Orbit Complete with xylitol
helps protect teeth from plaque.
WHOOSH!
WOMAN EXHALES
RATTLING
WHOOSH!
(giggles)
New Dove
go fresh deodorant
in cool
cucumber & green tea.
Stay dry, go fresh.
Hey, look at this! We're doing
great! You're so good at this.
Stop! What are
you doing?! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Just tell me,
what's your big problem with me?
Malcolm!
Seriously, I want to know!
Am I too short? Am I too smart?
Malcolm, can we please drop this?
I'm smart. Is that a crime? I'm sorry
I'm not a moron like Gary Spindler!
Malcolm, stop it!
What are you doing?
Tell me why you don't like me.
Why are you doing this?
I want an answer!
I can't believe I liked you!
You liked me?! I knew it!
I wasn't crazy! You did like me!
So what the hell has changed?
Tell me! I defy you to tell me!
Nothing! That's the problem!
You're still the obsessive whining
know-it-all who doesn't listen!
But you did like me!
Malcolm, I DON'T like you!
Can you get that through your head?
Before I just didn't have a crush
on you. And now I can't stand you!
You want me to tell you why I don't
like you? You want me to tell you
why I like nice, funny Gary Spindler
and absolutely despise bitter
annoying Malcolm? Do you?
Look,... Well, I'm gonna tell you!
There is something wrong with you!
I don't know how you do it!
You're cute, smart, funny
and somehow you managed
to mess that up!
Like today. It was an awkward
situation, but it would've passed.
But you just kept picking at it
and picking at it until it turned
into this big horrible thing!
There is something wrong inside you!
There's something rotten at
the core of your personality!
You're just off! That's
not even the worst thing!
I... want... candy! I
opened my purse to get a Tic Tac
and he dropped out of a tree
on my back! I am so sorry!
Now you go and you sit down in that
chair and you put your head down!
OK. Did you straighten things out
with Pratt?
Almost. Oh, for God's sake, Hal!
Where is he? I'll talk to him.
No! It's too late now. It would be
awkward. Hal, you work with the man.
He'll find out! It'll be two seconds
of embarrassment and then it's over.
Now go!
Pratt, do you have a moment?
For you, Bert? Of course!
You're fired!
What?
I don't think
it's working out.
I haven't started yet!
What could you be basing this on?
My gut. I didn't get this far
without trusting my instincts.
I'm sorry, son. I think it's best
if you just leave the picnic now.
They have foil
if you wanna wrap that up.
(SOBS) I'm so sorry, Malcolm! I just
started talking and I couldn't stop.
And I said all those mean things.
I didn't even mean half of them!
Who am I to say that
your kids would be screwed up?
You might not even
have kids! Are you OK?
(SOBS) I think I
can stop crying now.
Can you get me more
leaves? Oh, Malcolm!
No, really, I'm fine.
No, Malcolm,
that's poison oak!
Of course it is!
Take the shot!
(CRASHING / WHISTLE)
Ahh, geez, guys! Am I bad?!
How could I have done that?!
Ahh, don't beat yourself
up, buddy. We all make mistakes.
Shake it off.
You're doing your best.
Eric, I'm doing terrible!
Why's everybody being so nice to me?
You're doing your best! You're part
of the team. We're in this together.
You boys have all the items
on the list. Plus a wallet,
a girl's bracelet and a fork.
Give us the 100 bucks. There you go.
Thanks. How about
we separate you two?
I'll miss you!
Nice(!)
Mom, you don't have to
hold on to me. I'll be good!
OK! Lois! You
don't have to thank me.
Let me enjoy the
rest of the picnic.
You told my husband I'm
insane and should be committed!
I didn't say that! Then how does
letting him video-tape us in bed
help our marriage?
What?! I didn't tell...
You've gotta stop this! I don't have
time for my own family's problems
without listening to you two
nutcases! So why don't you just...
(ALL) Oh!
I don't think
you understood me.
(ALL) Ohhh!
# I don't give a damn
what the people say
# I'm gonna do it my way,
gonna do it my way
# I'm gonna let it all out
Just doing my thing
# A boom-lah-boom
and a bang, bang, bang
# Boom, bang,
boom, bang-bang
boom, bang-bang # Ahhh!
(ALL) Ohhh!
(ALL) Ohh!
(ALL CHEER)
Come on! We can
do it! Get in there!
Er, I don't think I... Eric,
there's something I've gotta tell...
Dammit! Get up!
Do something!
Ooomph! (GRUNTS)
No-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
(WHISTLE)
Eric, are you OK? Someone
took the cup out of my jock!
(GROANS) I'll be fine.
Just win this thing!
(WHISTLE)
Ohhh!
Now, just to be clear, I'm not
looking for anything long term here.
(WHISTLE)
# Go, go, go!
# Go, go, go! #
(HOOTER)
Yes! Yeah!
You did it, man!
Alright! Way to go!
Let me collect my money so we can
treat Francis the way he deserves!
You know, there's a
funny story about that money.
(ALL) Yeah!
You boys did alright!
Yeah, it was fun.
Francis, how you doing?
Well, cold!
It won't be much longer. There's a
kid's skating party in a half hour!
(ALL LAUGH)
Dewey!
(GROWLING) >
Dewey, is that...?
Oh, my God! (GROWLS)
(GROWLS) Dewey,
get away from there!
(GROWLS) Oh!
(CONTINUES TO GROWL)
Alright, alright.
Everything's gonna be alright.
Come on, baby. Come... to... Mamma!
Everything's gonna be OK.
Everything's gonna be...
Who's that idiot that just pulled
out and flipped everyone off?
That's Pratt, sir.
He starts this week. No. No.
The only thing he starts this week
is a long lifetime of misery.
You have our friends at
the IRS give him a call.
So, maybe we can hang out sometime
or something. When you're better.
Oh, come on, Malcolm! It's
not that bad. Give me a smile!
Are you smiling?
I can't tell.
I'm smiling.
(GROWLS)
That went better than I
expected. (CONTINUES TO GROWL)
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
www.tvsubtitles.net