.
My turn.
(FARTING NOISE)
Wait, wait.
I had no idea homework
could be so funny.
It's suicide.
I don't care.
I'm going in.
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question
# You're not the boss of me now
You're not the boss of me now
and you're not so big
You're not the
boss of me now
and you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
Guess what? I just
got back from the doctor.
My spine is curved!
How bad?
No gym for two years.
Brilliant!
Maybe my third nipple
can get me out of wrestling.
Here comes... Her
Royal... Bitchiness.
Cynthia just got back
from a semester in Europe
and she's totally changed.
She's bitter and sarcastic.
I could pull it off,
but on her it's
really unpleasant.
Malcolm, can you move the herd
to move an inch to the left
so I could get past?
I'm sorry, did you say inch?
Don't you mean 2.54 centimetres
or 0.254 decimetres,
or 25.4 million nanometres?
Guys, stop teasing her. You stink
at it. Don't defend her, Malcolm.
If I wanted abuse
I'd talk to my oboe teacher.
She's... dead...
to us.
Hey. Are you OK?
What do you mean?
You've been acting kinda strange.
Malcolm, look around and reconsider
your definition of strange.
Fair enough.
Dad, look how
high my kite is!
That's great,
son. That's terrific.
You wanna try?
Er, no.
Why not?
I don't like kites.
Why not? I don't like kites and they
don't like me. We don't get along.
You'd like it
if you tried it.
Come on, just try it.
Hold the string.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
Agh!
Hey, Lois.
Karen, what are
you doing out there?
Come on in.
Sorry. I didn't mean to lurk. I was
working up the nerve to talk to you.
Are you OK?
You look different.
I'm sober.
Oh. Yeah. After I drove over that
miniature golfcourse they made me
get into a 12-step programme.
Good for you! Thanks. I'm up to
the part where I'm supposed to make
amends to people I've hurt.
What did you ever do to me? Remember
New Year's at Deb and Rich's where
everyone was kissing at midnight?
Yeah. When I kissed your husband
I stuck my tongue in his mouth.
I felt terrible, then I put my
cigarette out on Richard's toupee...
You were French-kissing my husband?
He pushed me away after, like,
five or six seconds.
Well, no more than ten.
I'm sure he was only moving his
tongue because he was trying to say
something. That's enough, Karen.
Sorry.
Now I have to tell Stephanie she can
take down those lost-dog posters.
Francis, it's Friday night. Can
we please go out and get hammered?
Is getting drunk
all you think about?
We work like dogs all day, drink,
then work like hungover dogs.
Is this how you
pictured your life?
Ever since I was little. What did
you picture? I don't know.
There's more to life than falling
down drunk and acting like a jackass.
Look what we found!
(LAUGHTER)
You stole a totem pole?
No, he asked to come with us.
He hasn't shut up for an hour.
You can't leave it here. People
worship these. It's a sacred object.
Do I have something in my teeth?
Be honest. What's wrong with you?
You see a symbol of a world beyond
scraping grease and you think,
let's profane
it in our cabin?
Don't you have
respect for anything?
Look, a penny! It's mine!
I saw it first!
(SCUFFLING)
Is my coffee ready yet?
I can't believe
you only have instant. Sorry
it's not up to your standards.
You'd seem more sophisticated if you
weren't wearing a kiddies' sweater.
I'd take style tips from someone
who keeps track of wrestling feuds?
Ever since you've been back
you've been mean. You think you're
better than us. Even if it's true,
you don't have the right to be nasty.
You won't have any friends soon.
You think you know
what everybody's problem is?
You think you're so smart and
together, and no-one notices what
an unhappy little person you are.
Well, sorry. I won't stroke your
fragile ego by confiding in you.
Oh, yeah? Well,
you're on fire!
Aaaagh!
Mommy!
How could you
do that to me?
You were on fire. I wanted to help.
By yelling, "Oh, my God, where did
those come from?" I'm sorry!
It's just, you scared me.
THEY scared me.
I mean, they startled me...
I hate this! Everyone looks at me
like I'm some kind of freak.
I was surprised, that's all.
I mean, I would react the same way
if you had a new haircut.
(A giant haircut!)
No-one can know about this.
You can't tell anyone.
What?
Promise me!
But... Promise!
Alright, I promise!
Come on, you're fine.
It's just a change on the outside.
Inside you're the same. If you give
people a chance they'll see that.
Stop staring at them!
Am I staring?
Dad, I've been thinking
about your kite problem.
I don't have a kite
problem! It's OK, Dad.
We could start with you
explaining why you hate kites.
Let me try it! I want
to try it! Fine. Here.
Jerk!
Help!
I just do! There
doesn't need to be a reason!
Doesn't Dewey get homework? He seems
to have a lot of time on his hands.
Something wrong? I had the most
interesting conversation with Karen.
She's in this programme where you
have to apologise to your loved ones
and I wondered, do I have
anything to apologise for?
By you, you mean ME, and since it's
a question, you know the answer.
Karen said you French-kissed her
on New Year's Eve. I did not!
I can't believe it!
You're actually accusing me of this?
Why would Karen lie?
Why would I lie?
For the past 20 years yours
has been the only tongue
that's been in my mouth.
I don't lie!
So can we fly kites tomorrow?
Sorry, son I have to testify
at a murder trial.
But, darn it, I'll go to the park
with you! Thanks, Dad.
(Kids don't count.) It wouldn't be
so bad if you'd just admit it. Lois,
why would I kiss Karen?
You're a MAN!
What's that supposed to mean? You've
been with the same woman for 20
years. It's natural to be curious.
About what?
In 20 years of marriage you've never
even thought about another woman?
What are you talking about?
If you're just
gonna be ridiculous,
there's no point in carrying on this
conversation. But you are on notice!
Wait! I wanna talk to you!
(DEEP VOICE) You are unhappy!
Yes, I am.
Why?
I may have ruined my life. I left my
family and friends to come up here.
I wanted to find myself,
but all I feel is empty.
I have the answer to your suffering,
Francis. The answer is...
Francis! Who was that spiky-haired
kid who was friends with Little Lou?
What...?
Don't worry. Maybe it'll
come to you if you sleep on it.
.
The diamond standard of dishwashing
won't come from a dirty dishwasher.
Finish Dishwasher Cleaner is far
better at removing hidden grease
and limescale.
And a cleaner dishwasher
means cleaner dishes.
It's only dishwashing,
but you deserve perfect
results every time.
# ORGAN
TINKLING/WHOOSH!
# DRUMBEAT
(giggles)
Feel
fresh:
..with new Dove
go fresh deodorant
in energising
grapefruit & lemongrass.
Stay dry, go fresh.
Because kids never stay still,
Garnier
has created:
Upwards or
downwards,
the continuous
spray
can cover every inch
of the body rapido,
to provide advanced UV protection.
Garnier suncare research
is recognised
by:
And always remember
to wrap on a T-shirt,
splat on sun cream
and wear a hat.
No one makes the sun safer.
You know when your cat
doesn't want to know.
You'll know when he doesn't
want to be disturbed.
And you'll know when he
wants something he really likes.
Like new tastier
Whiskas pouches.
Gently steam-cooked
for total satisfaction.
Not a morning person?
Wake up with...
..enriched with caffeine.
The cooling moisturiser
instantly hydrates
and refreshes
tired-looking eyes.
The roll-on massages the eye area
for a
bright-eyed look.
One sold every
30 seconds.
Got yours?
Everything's ready. The kite tail is
set. It's a windy day. Now SAY it!
I am not cursed!
Good. Now run. And don't stop
until it's in the air.
I am not cursed!
Get off the field!
Excuse me!
Sorry!
It's flying! It's flying!
(CROAKY LAUGH) You guys threw fridge
magnets at Dabney's back brace?
He was walking around all day with
"Florida is for Lovers" on his back.
(SQUEAKY LAUGH)
That laugh is so not cute.
I'm sorry my laugh isn't as
melodious as your cracking voice.
(CRACKING) I'm Malcolm. I have all
the answers but no-one listens to me
Funny! (STUPID LAUGH)
This was fun.
Hi, Reese.
What a pig!
What?
She was never that great, but now
it's like she's TRYING to be ugly.
Shut up! She's not in Europe any
more. In America, we take showers.
She doesn't smell.
She dresses like a bag lady.
I know, her butt is gigantic
and she's trying to
hide it. This is great!
I have a wide-load sticker,
and I can make the truck noise
when she backs up
- beep, beep, beep!
Reese, when is
she gonna back up?
OK. When's her lunch period? I can
sneak in and throw bacon at her.
THEN she'll back up. Beep, beep...
She's not hiding her butt,
she's hiding her big boobs!
So if you tease her
you're just gonna look like a....
You are a good, good brother.
No...
I lied! Her butt IS huge!
I think it helped Cynthia to talk.
She's in a better mood.
She even stuck her homework
on Dabney's back.
Agh! What're you doing?!
Algebra.
What did he say to you?
Malcolm, calm down! I'm just
helping him with his homework.
Reese doesn't care
about school. So I thought,
but when he asked me for help
he sounded so pathetic,
I couldn't say no.
How are you doing on number five?
Awful. I'm not gonna get this.
I'm such an idiot. No, you're not.
Everyone says I'm
an idiot all the time.
Well, he IS!
Malcolm.
It's not his fault. Someone at some
point decided I was dumb, and that's
all anyone ever sees in me.
Why do they always focus on one
detail, never the whole person?
I don't know.
You missed another shift! I'm not
walking away from this totem pole
when I'm this close to figuring out
what it's trying to tell me.
Have you eaten anything?
Fasting helps my meditation.
There's some kind of energy here.
It gave me that dream.
It's trying to help me.
We're getting rid of it
and putting you back on corn dogs
and porn for your own safety.
Back away from the pole!
So...
you guys wanna go...
shoot some eagles?
Nothin' else to do.
What're you gonna do to her? I don't
know what you're talking about.
OK. I've been dying to tell someone.
Malcolm, I'm gonna see them.
What?! I'll make her my girlfriend
and get her to take her top off.
You're crazy! That's what I thought,
but I've got it all figured out.
Tomorrow I reveal an embarrassing
secret that makes her feel trusted.
Friday, sneak a kiss, then
apologise. Monday, I ask her out.
She catches me crying. Make out.
She finds love letter in my pocket.
Heavier make-out session.
All culminating in March 8, DD-Day.
You're pure evil!
Who's more evil,
me or the person who told me?
You! Yeah, but YOU'D be in trouble.
She'd never forgive you. Excuse me.
I have to go make a mix tape.
OK, we had a little setback,
but don't give up.
Forget it!
I'm sick of this!
I hate kites! I
have always hated kites!
Dad, don't freak out
in front of the other kids.
I'm never gonna get this
and I don't want to!
You can't give up.
I can give up, and I give up!
I'm tired of your attitude.
I'm going home.
Dewey! Dewey, come back here.
It's too far for you to walk.
Dewey!
Dewey, stop!
Don't you ever run
away like that again.
There's something
on the back of your pants.
I'm flying a kite!
Lois, I did it! I did
it! I actually flew a kite!
How could I think these
were evil? I love this kite.
Why don't you kiss it?
For God's sake! Are you still
obsessing about that?
I want a straight answer. Lois,
from the moment I laid eyes on you
YOU were the only woman for me.
Unlike all other men,
you don't even have a glancing
interest in other women?
You alone stand outside the dictates
of millions of years of evolution!
Why is that so hard
for you to believe?
Because I look at other men!
Not seriously. I would
never do anything about it,
but, God, hell, I notice!
And if you don't, it means that...
..it means that you love me
more than I love you.
Well, honey, that's always been
true. Of course I love you more.
You're OK with that?
Oh, yeah.
If you loved me as much as I love
you, we'd never leave the bedroom!
Nothing would get done.
We'd die of starvation.
I love you!
Not as much as I love you.
I have fasted,
I have meditated,
I got frostbite from a
night in the wilderness!
I just want to know what to do.
What am I missing? There's a wolf.
What's that? Loyalty.
Eagle.
OK, insight... insight...
The frog is...
bug-eating!
What does that have to do
with anything?
Please just give me a sign
or a signal, or something!
Oh, my God!
Are you the dirtbag
that took my pole?
Huh? It's my pole. I
want it back. Oh, of course!
I'm so sorry. I
didn't take it.
I'm going crazy. Can
you tell me what it means?
Well, if I hit it, it means I'm five
inches away from the back of my
carport. You use it as a wheel-stop?
This beautiful, sacred thing?
Sacred? It's a decoration.
Like a coat of
arms or a storybook.
It's a pretty chunk of wood
my kids helped me carve.
But you can't tell me
you can't feel the energy!
You white boys all think
cos I've got dark skin,
I dance with the bears and listen
to the spirit of the wind.
I got news for you -
I work for a living.
I'm a Baptist,
and I'm proud of it.
But... you sure?
And by the way, I have
only one word for snow -
snow!
(GIGGLING) >
No! Stop! Malcolm!
He's not who you think he is.
Reese is only interested in you
cos I told him you have big breasts.
What?! It just
happened. I'm sorry.
He only wants you for
your boobs! Stop saying that!
He planned all
this. I can prove it.
He wrote it all down. This isn't it.
Where's your REAL calendar?
That IS my calendar. All proceeds
went to animal shelters.
He's using you
and you fell for it!
Leave me alone!
You heard her.
But...
What's her name?
What?
I know what her name is.
And I'm not gonna
dignify that with a response.
I know what her name is,
and her name is...
Ohhh!
How could you
be so creepy?
Don't you have any sense of decency
towards a fellow human being?
(THUDDING) I have feelings!
I will be treated with respect!
I will not be objectified!
I will not be humiliated!
Now kiss my shoe!
Kiss... my... shoe!
The private says, "But, General,
I didn't touch your toast!"
(SQUEAKY LAUGH)
Something's different about you.
Did you get a haircut?
Very stylish.
(DOORBELL RINGS) Cynthia,
did you like Europe? I did.
I forget sometimes that there's
a whole world out there that's not
full of prurient adolescent boys.
There are people who treat me nicely
and keep their mouths shut.
I get it!
Yes?
Is Lois here?
Honey?
Oh, God,
are you Lois' husband?
So who's married to the bald guy
with the earring? Donna.
I thought that was one house
I didn't have to go to.
Excuse me.
Oh, I lived in your house while
you were on vacation last month.
We didn't go on
vacation. Darn it!
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
You're looking at the
standard we set ourselves.
It's the one standard
that measures the shine,
the clarity
and the brilliance you get
with Finish Quantum.
It's only dishwashing,
but we believe you deserve
flawless results every time.
Finish Quantum.
www.tvsubtitles.net