Make your
skin feel:
Skin Contact.
BELL
ELECTRONIC FANFARE
New Sure Men Absolute.
Agh!
Future-ready protection.
You would not!
I would, too!
No clothes, go across the street
and ring Mrs Conlan's door bell.
Yeah, I would do it but you
don't have ten bucks. Dewey.
Ah-ah!
No underwear,
no clothes at all.
Of course.
What are you doing? You said no
clothes. I'll be right back, losers.
Never thought he'd do it.
I guess he outsmarted us.
You opened her
gate, right? Of course.
(DOG BARKS)
(CRASHING)
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
So, the universe... can be...
finite. And unmounted.
But if...
Are you... listening?
Oh, my God! Sara
Coleman is so beautiful!
The way she runs her
hand through her hair.
And that smile. You look at her
and you can't even see anyone else.
Every day,
you do this.
Ask her... out.
Come on, Stevie! Sara
would never go out with me!
She's smart, cool, good-looking. If
we went out it would make me happy.
It won't happen. I am destined to be
the most miserable person on Earth.
Boo...
..hoo.
Shut up!
Look, it's complicated, OK?
You don't just walk up to a girl
and say, "Hey, I like you!"
You'd look like an idiot. Sara
wants to know if you like her.
What? He likes
her! She likes him, too.
Remember yesterday when we were
sitting and we got a drink of water?
Then we sat around again.
We should totally do that again. OK.
Look at me, it's official.
I have a girlfriend!
I'm officially
someone's boyfriend. Watch this.
I can do that
any time I want!
I hate this. This is where we have to
split up so my family won't see us.
I'll miss you.
You're a really
good kisser. Thanks. Bye.
Thanks. What does that mean?
What's wrong with the way I kiss?
Are my lips too wet? Maybe they're
too dry. I don't see why she couldn't
just return the compliment!
My God! I'm the
worst boyfriend ever!
OK, just calm down.
I'm a good boyfriend.
She wouldn't be my
girlfriend if I wasn't.
I have a girlfriend!
You don't understand. All I did
was take a doughnut out of a
dumpster. How is that stealing?
I had to fight a cat to get it!
The restaurant owner
wants to press charges.
Look, I know the guy. He's a bit of
a hothead, but I promise you he'll
lose interest in four or five days.
Four or five days? I have to start
a logging job and I'm late as it is!
It won't be bad. Three meals a day
courtesy of my wife. You look like
you could use some home cooking.
What would you like for dinner,
chicken or a nice porterhouse steak?
Porterhouse, I guess. Oh,
you're gonna love her cooking!
Well, thank you!
At first I had no
idea what was going on.
Then I realised I was looking at
a 4-25 requisition form.
Shelby had filled it out
thinking it was a 4-28.
This isn't interesting, is it?
No, it is! You just need to know
what a 4-25 form is!
You see - Dewey,
how was your day?
I got a new friend,
his name's Ronnie.
He just moved here.
He's got a Nintendo, a Playstation,
and a nanny. He's really rich.
Well, nice to
meet you, Ronnie.
No, he's real! I can
make real friends, too!
Of course. Don't be frustrated if
it takes you longer than other boys.
Ronnie is real!
(LAUGHS)
Reese! What are you doing?!
Malcolm's got a
girlfriend! What?
Son, is this true? Damn! I was
saving that for report card day!
She's not... We're just friends.
Malcolm, look at me!
Oh, my God, it's true! Malcolm, no!
You do not do this yet!
I saw them behind the 7-11 French
kissing. That's with tongue.
Don't you wanna go to college?
Don't you care about your future?
You are not old enough to prioritise
between homework and some tramp!
Your mother's right.
I waited until I was eleven
before I kissed my...
How old are you? Never
mind. What I'm saying is,
it was a different time
back then. There was a war on.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
I'll get it.
Maybe it's Malcolm's girlfriend come
for some kissing.. Who is this girl?
Mom, don't make such
a big deal outta this!
I knew this is exactly how you'd
react! This is none of your business!
It's nobody's business!
It's not a big deal, OK?
Well, it's not. I would appreciate it
if we could just drop it.
This is Ronnie Demarco.
As you can see, he's real.
Ow!
Hm! Interesting!
We'll be in my room.
I can't believe how much stuff
you have. You wanna play cowboys?
No, I hate cowboys.
You can have 'em.
Really? Thanks! No take-backs.
Ronnie! Ronnie, would you please
empty the dishwasher for Mommy?
OK.
So, Dewey, come here. Ronnie's
birthday's coming up and I want
to throw him a surprise party.
But he doesn't know
that many people here.
I thought cos you're his first friend
here, you could help me. OK.
I want to invite
your entire class.
All 30 kids? Yeah. Isn't that what
you do for your birthday parties?
Huh? (LAUGHS)
What are we celebrating?
(BOTH) One, two,
three, four, five.
Damn it! You get
back in here now! I won't!
Sorta. I was thinking Ronnie would
like a Starwars theme for his party.
No, do cowboys!
What?
Cowboys. He likes cowboys
better than Starwars.
OK, that'll be
fun. Thank you, Dewey.
Oh, Brock! What is it?
You're trembling, what's wrong?
Chad's getting suspicious.
You know he's been asking questions
at the orphanage. We need to get out
of here! Say goodbye to the money?
We just need to bide our time.
How can I trust you, Brock, when you
haven't told Cassandra about us yet?
Have a heart, Vanessa!
The woman's still in a coma! Coma?
Hey, honey!
I just got back
from the Mayor's office.
He thinks he's gonna kill
our little real estate deal.
What about the pictures of him and
the Hastings girl? They're on their
way to the newspapers right now.
Perfect! Now all we have
to worry about is old man Landers.
Maybe we should send Largo
to pay him a little visit.
(BOTH LAUGH)
What a mess!
Mr Hirkaby just called. He said you
got Cs in your last tests and you
didn't turn in your history paper.
I warned you! This has
nothing to do with Sara!
I just forgot.
I'm doing it now, OK?
So, what kind of
socks are you wearing?
Yeah, I like those.
Which shoes are you wearing?
Not the sneakers?
How about your boots?
Your sandals! God, I
totally love all your shoes!
Yeah, I guess I
have homework to do, too.
You hang up first.
No, you hang...
(DIALLING TONE) Hello?
Thousands of you
have voted:
..Hair Colour
Product
of the Year.
Why?
Excellence gives you
sensational colour
and really cares for your hair.
With the new comb,
it's so much easier.
Combs in rich,
radiant colour.
Combs in advanced protection.
Combs out every last grey.
My hair feels so soft
and the colour
looks truly natural.
New, improved:
It's the
hair colour
that makes me
feel younger.
We're worth it.
Get great results
all around your home
when you try
new Cillit Bang Multi Power.
It was so quick and easy.
Look how it cleans this toothpaste
and my make-up
stains. What a shine!
And a new fresh smell.
For taps clogged
with limescale...
Look, it's amazing.
Clean as a whistle.
It also works
in the kitchen
and gets rid of cooking spills
with so little effort.
For great results
all around your home.
Try it now!
Cillit Bang Grime & Lime
Multi Power.
And no more tedious scrubbing
with Cillit Bang Grease & Floor.
The new
all-purpose cleaner
that gives great results
on large surfaces
and even
when used neat.
Cillit Bang
Grease & Floor.
This is all your fault.
You bought him that acne medicine.
I thought we were safe.
He's still goofy-looking.
His head is five times
too big for his body.
We shouldn't have to worry about
this with Malcolm. He's gifted.
Girls shouldn't be interested
until he's 28 and a billionaire!
Certain things are beyond
the boy's control. It's his
genetics. Girls, they just swoon.
Sorry, what am I telling your for?
You battle with it every day.
There's nothing we can do.
Oh, yes, there is!
I can ground him, and I can ground
him till he graduates from Harvard.
He's gonna pull away, then we'll
have another Francis on our hands.
Are you blaming Francis on
me? No! That's what you said!
No, I meant that... Lois, let's not
have this veer off into us
somehow not having sex tonight.
Oh, God!
Why do they do this to us?
Why can't they learn
from their mistakes?
Even if they're just
being stupid on purpose.
Seems like the
only logical conclusion.
When they're grown we don't
have to let them visit, do we?
Absolutely not.
It's just gonna be you and me,
old and shrivelled
in a big empty house.
The only sound a gentle
sucking of the respirator.
And all our money will be sitting
in the bank, helping no-one.
Mmmmm!
You guys seen Sara?
No.
That's weird.
She's two minutes late.
Were you supposed to meet her here?
No, not exactly. But it was implied.
Implied?
We meet at the water fountain at
eight. We're always within 30 seconds
of each other in the lunch line.
When I get home I wait four minutes
before I call. That's how it's been.
That's our thing. Wow! I didn't know
having a girlfriend was so creepy!
It's not creepy! This is totally
normal! This is dating!
You spend time with each other,
get to know each other's habits.
When you're in a relationship
you'll understand.
I'll just hang out
outside the bathrooms.
Hi, Mrs Demarco.
Sorry to bother you,
but the nanny put too
much banana in my smoothie.
Oh, we'll fix that.
I just booked the cowboy!
He's gonna be passing out cowboy hats
and making balloon animals.
Does he do trick shooting? I'm
sure we can find someone who does.
I bet Ronnie would
like a moonbounce, too.
This relationship is
finally starting to make sense.
For a while all we did is fight and
make out, then fight, then make out.
But that's all behind us. We were
screaming at each other five minutes
ago. Now it just feels so right.
Wait, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
Home. We've been kissing
for two hours, my face is sore.
Yeah, she's right.
We can't make out all day.
We've both got our own
things to do. She's so smart.
If you're seeing someone else
just tell me! What?!
I-I'm sorry. I don't
know where that came from.
Look, I've gotta go home.
I'll call you tonight.
That was pathetic!
You were watching us?
Believe me, it's the last time!
Just because you have a girl doesn't
mean you should act like one.
I don't know what's wrong with her!
She's driving me crazy!
I freak out 20 times a day!
Dude, you think about everything
too much. Calm down.
Turn off your brain.
It's not that easy.
Sure it is. I do it
all the time. Watch.
You can't just
turn off your... Reese!
Reese!
Whoa! How long was I out?
And as I pulled her
from the wreckage,
she was so...
(TEARFULLY)
..disfigured that I didn't even know
it was my own sister.
Don't worry. Dimitri is the finest
reconstructive surgeon in the state.
Who's Dimitri?
They had a municipal hospital. He
and Vanessa had an affair last year -
Shut up in there!
Oh, man, who's got their assignment
on Cambodia? I need to borrow it.
Where were you... last night?
What?
The Space 1999 marathon
on the Sci Fi channel.
I made you a tunic
and a hologram badge.
I-I'm - Forget it! I
gave it to my mom's boyfriend!
Thanks for nothing!
Guys, look, I'm sorry.
I've just been... Sara
and I were on the phone...
Never mind. I'm just sorry.
I promise this
won't happen again.
I think I turned a corner
on this thing.
Sara and I were talking
and it just came to me.
I think we worked things out.
Can you guys excuse me?
I'll be right back.
He does seem... sorry.
I say we cancel
our vote of censure.
I second that. He was there for us
after the arboretum broke down.
And how can you look in those eyes
and say no to anything he asks?
(BOTH SIGH)
I think... he's
learned... his lesson.
OK, only two invitations left.
Ronnie's gonna have a moonbounce
and a make-your-own-sundae car.
I'll go. Maybe you will. What
kind of present would you bring?
Skateboard?
Excellent choice!
Ronnie has a brand new skate board.
Why don't you let ME
worry about Ronnie?
Sit!
Look at yourself!
They've put you on
probation. Probation!
If you do just one more thing wrong
they're gonna kick you outta school!
Do you have any idea how serious
this is? Is this who you wanna be?
You wanna be a lap dog
who ruins his life for some girl?
For God's sake, Malcolm, you beat up
a foreign exchange student!
He left his country to get
away from this kind of abuse!
Are you listening to me?
Yes, I'm listening!
But I've got bigger problems!
You may not have noticed,
but I've been screwing up a lot.
All because of some stupid girl!
I'm on probation! I beat up a kid
who doesn't even speak English!
I'm going through a lot
and you don't even care!
We can still pull this off!
You'll never pass the DNE test,
and even your lies won't be enough.
But Brock, if you didn't buy
the mining rights, then who did?
Don't you see? The person who bought
the mining rights is the same person
who stole Mrs Bronson's brooch.
And the person who ran Nathaniel's
car off the road that night.
That person's name is -
OK, you're free to go.
Ssh!
Come on, move it!
Just five more
minutes! Wait! No!
It was the Mayor, right?
Or the widow Farthington?
What about the creepy janitor?
No, his amnesiac brother! Argh!
(BELL RINGS)
I didn't understand one word
that was said in the last six hours.
I'm exhausted. I
couldn't sleep all night.
I finally figured out
what I gotta do. Sara! Wait up!
Look, I've done a lot of
thinking and we need to talk.
Sara, this just isn't working.
Since I've known you I've been
nothing but obsessive and neurotic.
A jealous creep
who's way too clingy.
I don't like what this is turning me
into, so I got you this pager.
What? It's perfect. Now we know
where the other one is every second.
No more worry or doubt.
We'll be able to trust each other.
We have to break up, Malcolm.
I don't think
you heard me.
I'm proposing
the exact opposite.
That's what the pager's for.
I'm sorry. Bye.
No!
No! No!
Sara!
You can't break up with me!
Because I am filled with nothing
but love and good feelings!
And no anger and no jealousy! And
none of those things that will lead
you to not wanting to be with me!
OK, fine! Get outta here!
I don't need you! I hate your guts!
I never needed
you! No, no, no, no!
I love you! I
always have, I always will!
We were meant
to be together!
I gave you my soul, Sara!
I gave it to you, my soul!
My soul!
Sara!
There you go, sweetheart.
I always thought
you hated cookie dough.
So, are you having a
good time? Yeah, Mom. Thanks.
You really should help Dewey.
He was a big help in planning this.
You ruined by
birthday! I hate you!
I've had two sundaes
and four snow cones.
Malcolm, look.
Come on. Come on.
I can't feel my fingers.
I'll go get us some punch,
how's that sound?
You know, son, this is
all part of growing up.
You're just gonna
have to get used to it.
No, I don't.
I can go back.
I can go back!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna play.
You can't! You're
too big! No, I'm not.
I'm going back. No, you're too big!
You're going to ruin my party!
# Party day
# Sleeping our cares away
# On our way
# to where the air
is sweet # (LOUD BANG)
OK! Don't panic! OK!
OK! Hah!
Yeeeargh! You're
OK! Don't be scared!
Oh! Don't be afraid, son.
It was just a loud explosion.
Everything is going to be OK.
Don't be afraid.
(HIGH PITCHED WHISTLE)
Just once I'd like to learn
without something exploding.
# That's how the West was won #
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
www.tvsubtitles.net