Lois, are you about done? No! You
gotta get outta there - I'm late.
NO! You should
get up in time!
I WOULD if someone
didn't turn off my snooze alarm!
It went off every SIX minutes
for an HOUR! What are you doing?
Getting in, Lois! You are NOT!
Not until I am finished!
(HUSKY VOICE) I don't think
I'll be able to come in today!
I've got a pretty severe
fever, scratchy throat...
Cough.
("COUGHS")
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
You're not the boss of me now
And you're not so big
You're not the
boss of me now
And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
No.
No. No.
Wait.
Gimme that! No.
No.
Wait.
Hi, boys. Got a second?
You have a pretty good life!
Uh-oh.
Spend your days flying kites,
playing video games.
It's time you enriched your lives.
When did we have kites?!
I won't have you grow up to be
selfish little pigs.
So I volunteered you
to do some charity work.
You can choose between helping
old people, or helping poor people.
Or I can make you do BOTH!
OK! Old people.
(What can be hard
about old people?)
Poor people!
We want poor people!
Hi. I'm Francis. Mr
Price said I should see you.
Oh! I can't believe
how cold it is up here!
Course it is Alaska, but you'd think
they could dome the place, or...
put tunnels between the buildings.
You must know my buddy Eric Hanson.
He got the logging job for me.
Do you give out the axes?
Cos I'm a lefty if
that makes any difference?
What's that?
A broom, genius(!)
Grab an apron, sweep out my pantry.
And quit starin' at my bosom!
You don't understand...
I came here to work as a logger.
Lemme tell ya
about loggers -
they're filthy, drunken,
low-life swine,
..and YOU are their slave.
You will feed them, do their laundry
and clean out their privys.
Don't steal, don't back talk, and
don't socialise with the Eskimos.
OK... WHAT'D I
SAY ABOUT BACK-TALK?!
Eric? Francis?! What's
goin' on? I thought you -
(SOBS LOUDLY)
I don't hear sweepin'!
You boys should be
so proud of yourselves!
People will really appreciate this.
I'm gonna say a
special prayer for you.
Yeah. That should make us even(!)
Why are we organising trash?!
It's not trash! It's
stuff donated to the poor.
Look, Reese, it's just like yours.
Except nicer. It doesn't have holes.
Well, this jacket
is better than yours!
You're right.
Everything IN here
is better than our stuff!
Haha! You're poor!
No wonder I never
got a rocket sled.
What are you doing? Trading! But-
Look, I'm making a donation.
Instead of ONE poor person getting
a new shirt, TWO poor people do.
What's wrong with that?
I can't move...!
Ten hours scouring deep-fat friers
with a 20 minute break
to de-tick sled dogs...
What's wrong with that woman?!
Her name's Lavernia. She controls
every facet of your life.
She finds out your weaknesses
then gets inside your head...
and makes you
hate yourself...!
Women...!
They're just like the woods.
Mysterious. Full of wolves.
(SOBBING)
Whoah...! Pull together man!
It could be worse.
At least we're making good money.
No, we're not! See her ledger book?
She charges us for EVERYTHING
and deducts it from our pay!
Food, rent, aprons,...
Hair gel.
My first cheque was for $6!
(ELECTRICAL SHORTING)
Great(!) Generator's out again.
So, what, we just
sit around in the dark?!
Oh, this isn't dark. Ever spent
the night in a caribou's gut?
Who is this old coot?
He's my best friend here!
(SOBBING RESUMES)
So nice of your boys
to help us out like this!
We've always LOVED this old church.
If you cut through the parking lot
you miss the traffic light on Sixth.
Keep up the good work, boys!
Alright, I'll be
back in two hours.
During which time I suggest you
think about the horrible...
thoughtless...
whatever it is you did to deserve
this punishment. That's just it!
We didn't DO anything. Mom said
we needed to build character.
YOUR character, right?
Well,... see that you do!
What are you doing? Trading again.
A backpack for a backpack.
Dewey, wait! A yo-yo
isn't equal to a GameBoy.
What if I throw in my Mightyman.
OK, two toys for one seems fair.
Yeah. I mean, as long as what
we trade is equal, it seems...
Whoa... Check these out!
Is this fair?
Think of it this way...
When you add the value of the work
we're doing, we're still way ahead.
Where do I dump this?
Ya don't dump it! You take the
bucket, heat it to 190 degrees,
run it through the hair trap
and make gravy for dinner.
Re-use old filthy fat?!
DO YOU LIKE HAVIN' A JOB?!
Hey, Lavernia. I need some licorice,
some paper towels and a 6-pack
of beer. Sure, hon.
Oh, no. It took me six months
to get you paid off last time.
I'm outta your book for good.
Hard cash! Got it exactly!
Good enough.
Like a freshly
baked muffin. Only $8.
You gotta be kiddin'! Eight bucks
for a lil... Are those raisins?
Last ones till spring.
Quit starin' at my
caboose - back to work!
Hey, you don't have
to snarl at us everyti-
High school's brutal! Don't get this
much homework in other classes.
They just keep heaping it on!
Is Monday OK? Make it Friday.
I don't wanna ruin your weekend.
Oh. I lost the crystal off my watch.
Your parents gave you that.
There's one like this at the church.
Could you get it for me?
If you donate something of equal
or greater value.
How about aftershave? Mom got it
for me for parties and dances.
Poor deluded woman! Sold. You
wouldn't believe the stuff they got.
Clothes, toys, comics...
Yesterday a guy donated an old
Nintendo - the Double Dragon 4 game.
DD4?! The... Sacred... Stone?
Yeah, why?
I give you... $20 for it.
Money?
I guess we could put it
in the collection box.
This is great! The church
is only charging $5 for it.
This way Stevie gets his game
and the church gets an extra $10.
No, the church gets an extra $15.
I think we deserve something
for our trouble.
Think of it this way... The church
gets three times what it asked for.
Yeah. We're makin'
this work for everyone.
Any porcelain tea sets? NOT for me,
of course. For my sister.
Isn't she at Vassar? Look,
do you want the cash or not?!
"..and my job in Alaska is great -
making tons of money and friends."
"So your dire predictions of misery
and exploitation were, as always,
dead wrong."
Oh, he's a good boy.
They're all good kids.
Mrs Potts at the church
says they're a godsend.
Whoah, whoah...!
Where are you off to?
We told Mrs Potts we'd be back after
lunch. Charity's fun. Thanks, Mom!
Well, whaddaya know! Are we finally
getting something right with them?
..
..with your
children.
# HEROIC FILM SCORE
And experience
the just-washed freshness
of new
Persil.
..
This is ridiculous! The wolves
had me tree-ed for half an hour.
I've just about- OW!
YOU CAN'T TREAT US LIKE THIS!
This is inhuman! We are
citizens! This is America!
Isn't it?
I'm sorry, Francis.
It's all my fault.
Stop crying.
It's OK, man.
No, it isn't!
God, you must hate me.
Come on...! You're my friend.
I can't hate YOU!
(HARMONICA PLAYS
"STRANGERS IN THE NIGHT")
Er, sorry.
Thought I's pickin' up the vibe.
Look, Lavernia may be evil,
and she may be tough,
but we can beat her.
How?
Our lives our controlled
by that ledger book.
Everything we do increases our debt.
This is what military school was for
To wage war against all authority
no matter what the odds.
She may be a manipulative monster,
but Mom can't win every round.
Who? Lavernia!
We gotta get her where she lives.
We gotta get that book!
I HATE that book.
Know what book I hate?
Valley of the Dolls.
What kind of ending was that?
OK, Stevie wants Pam Grier
memorabilia. IF he can keep it here.
If he's got the money,
the church doesn't care.
And the liquor store guy
will take the breadmaker.
Hey, we're up to $159! What
shall we buy?
I say we buy a saddle.
Then they can't say no to
the horse. I don't WANT a horse!
I say we vote. Dewey?
Can God see everything we do?
What? Mrs Potts said
God sees everything we do.
Yeah, Dewey. God can magically
see through roofs.
What are you worried about?
We're not doing anything wrong.
Then how come we have money?
Well,... sometimes when you do good
things, good things happen for you.
Satisfied?
I mean, think of
it this way, Dewey,
people are still
getting what they need.
OK, we DO have some money, but
the church does, too, so no-one's
getting hurt an- (NOISE OUTSIDE DOOR)
This is bad. Once we get
the saddle, we should just quit.
We're not getting the saddle!
This was ALL a mistake!
I should've KNOWN something was wrong
when YOU started making sense.
This is YOUR fault!
You're supposed to keep us
OUT of trouble!
So YOU'RE going to hell!
We're ALL going to hell!
You guys seen
the remote for...
What's going on? Dad,
we've done something terrible.
It might be the worst thing
we've ever done. Just calm down.
Let's talk this through.
It can't be that bad.
You've been stealing money
from the CHURCH!
And maybe some... merchandise.
You boys, you've been taking
stereos,... toys...
Is that cheese?
Oh... god...
ARGH!
My god...!
Dewey, get a washcloth!
Here you go, Dad.
Nice and even.
You stole... AIR?!
WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU BOYS?
Do you EVER stop and think of the
consequences of ANYTHING you do?!
Do you realise the SHAME
you'll bring on the family? DO YOU?!
Forget THAT,
what's MOM gonna say?!
Right, we sneak this back into the
church, and no-one will ever know.
The church left us alone with
all that stuff. It was entrapment!
Reese, no more excuses!
(ENGINE MAKES ODD NOISE) Oh, damn!
IT'S GOD, HE FOUND US!
It's not God, Dewey.
It's just my crappy car.
Although he COULD have
helped out in my career a bit,
thrown a promotion MY WAY
once in a while. Maybe it IS God!
This is the street mum drives down,
and she finishes work in TEN MINUTES!
You, sir, a shirt? Three shirts.
Some pants? You'd be a 34 waist?
Look, I don't want these!
Why not, they're free!
What's wrong with them? Nothing!
Oh, look, just gimme five bucks!
Alright.
What's going on? This guy's selling
me all this for five bucks.
I'll give you
five for that.
OK, gather round. I've
got a good-as-new stereo.
Who's next?
I am. This your stuff?
I know how this must look, but
I didn't steal any of these things.
My boys took 'em from a church.
Neither one of you nimrods leave
until that grill is spotless.
And after that, get that jar
of poison and bait the rat traps.
That doesn't make sense.
Why poison them if we have traps?
Because I'll fire your ass!
Perfect. Nice job
with the tape! Thanks.
Most people put the tape on too
tight so you lose that nice clang.
Everyone hates her so much,
they'll never pin it on us!
God, look at this next to my name -
emotionally dependent on pornography,
loves nut clusters.
How does she know
I love nut clusters?!
Took the tape
off the door.
You dragged me to Alaska.
Nnnrrrrrrgg...! Aarrrnnnnng...!
(BOTH SOB)
Listen, if you do hear
from them, please call me.
(PHONE RINGS)
Yes! Hal...!
You had me worried sick!
The police said they released
you three hours ago!
By now you'll know everything.
The boys and I are gonna disappear.
Hal, where are you?
I am not at liberty to reveal that.
"BUS NO.23 FOR OMAHA NOW BOARDING."
Hal, you're a middle-aged man,
you CAN'T run away from home!
I have a credit card that begs to
differ! Hang up! She's tracin' it!
DON'T YOU HANG UP THAT PHONE!
Hal,... you're not gonna do this.
You and the boys are
gonna come home right now.
Why would I do that? Because
you love me too much
to run away.
That may... may be true, Lois.
But maybe we'll just have a long
distance relationship for a while.
Some of those can work.
Hal, have you even thought what
you'd be like without me? Well, no..
Do you have any idea how much
you'd miss me? Do you?
Yes...
Yes. I... I have some idea.
Dad, you're folding!
He's folding! I knew we should've
paid that wino to make the call.
Er, honey?
We're back.
Hey, guys. Why don't
you wash up, dinner's ready.
It's your favourite -
meat loaf and mashed potatoes.
OK. Great.
Why isn't she mad?
What happened? Our stuff is gone!
I gave it all to charity.
You've two changes of clothes -
one for school, one for home.
Something wrong? No
problem. No, fine. No, no.
More wine?
Please.
So, how long is it gonna take us
to work off all this stuff?
Well, this... should put
us into the 23rd century.
Sesame cracker?
Don't mind if I do.
I've been lying
here thinking about God.
I don't know much, just that he's
this all powerful, all knowing being.
Kinda like Mom, only invisible.
So I feel better on his good side.
And we probably all focus
too much on material things.
What are you doing? Praying.
No you're NOT! He's got chocolate!
GET HIM!
(SCREAMS)
Come on, give it!
IMS Subtitles
New Savlon Advanced Healing Gel...
..creates optimal conditions
to help speed up the healing...
..of cuts and grazes from the
moment it touches the skin.
Which could be a problem
if your child likes...
..showing off their wounds
to impress their friends.
www.tvsubtitles.net