Oh, with the boys asleep
this house is so quiet!
Mm-hm. Such a nice
idea to build a fire.
Yeah.
Hey, I didn't build a fire.
I thought you built a fire.
Well, looks like Reese got
a D... in English.
And Dewey seems to be
fighting again. Biting.
Malcolm, tell your teacher I'd love
to chaperone the class overnight!
We can share a tent!
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
I can't believe you're allowed to do
a video project instead of a paper!
You... could have asked! My parents
aren't rich enough to buy a camera.
(WHEEZES) Rich... and compensating.
I don't know what to write about.
What's your movie gonna be about?
The creative... process.
You writing...
..your paper.
Is that on?! Turn it off!
You'll make me
look like an idiot.
I'm serious!
This is...
..great! Now knock... me over!
(PHONE RINGS)
Hal.
Hey, it's Abe! Hi! I
know it's short notice,
but someone dropped out of our poker
game. Can you make it tonight?
I've been waiting
for this for months!
See you at eight.
Thanks!
Wah! Yah!
Honey, guess what, guess what! I'm
gonna play poker at Abe's tonight!
Tonight's our first
dance class! That's tonight?
Yes! It was your
birthday present to me.
Oh...!
Fine, go play poker.
I LOVE YOU! Mwah! (CACKLES)
Great(!) Who am I gonna go with?
Did Reese finish his homework yet?
Of course! Good! Come
to dance class with me.
What? I was lying.
I didn't finish my homework.
I don't know what my
homework is! Go get your shoes.
(WIND HOWLS) If the weather report's
right this storm will last a week.
Now, you ration these
supplies. Make no mistake,
you're the last ones we'll dig out.
We're supposed to live for a week
on meat paste and caribou jerky?!
That's a week I don't get any work
out of you!
No-one's cryin' for me!
It's just a friendly game.
We sit around talking
and eventually get around to cards.
Good. I want to meet your friends.
Everybody, this is Hal.
Hal. Hi, Hal.
Hal, this is Brian,
Trey, Steve and Malik.
(CLEARS THROAT)
It's great to meet you.
So, what's the buy-in?
$50.
There. So, what's with Wanda?
Ain't no thang! (ALL) Whoa!
(ALL LAUGH UPROARIOUSLY)
Put a dollar in
the pot. (ALL LAUGH)
Oh, we got a regular D-dog here!
(ALL LAUGH)
Right, left, cha-cha cha! God made
artificial hips for a reason!
Use them! And
back. Cha-cha, finish.
Very good. Everyone, let's pair up.
May I?
Oh,... OK.
No way!
You be a gentleman!
It's just like touching a corpse...
How many lessons
have you had? What? None!
Really? I'm impressed!
You have very good instincts.
I do?
Mm-hm. You're built for it.
You have a dancer's ankles.
I do not!
You're a lovely young man. You don't
shake like all the other men here!
Mind if I cut in?
You wait your turn!
I'll give you five bucks
to dance with me. OK!
And still... he has...
..nothing!
Alright! That's it!
I'm writing about
you doing a movie.
But my movie's... about your paper.
Yeah. I'm doing my paper
about your movie
about me doing my paper!
Fine(!)
My movie's...
..about you doing...
..your paper...
..about me doing...
..my...
Alright, I get it!
..movie...
..about you...
Hey, guys!
You should do your movie about
old people. They've saved money
for years, and outlived everyone
they wanted to share it with.
Talk about sad!
Raise you five. I'll see
your five and raise you...
..two.
(ALL CHUCKLE)
Call. Full house!
Kings over eights.
Straight flush to the jack.
I knew you had it!
But he had nothing on top! He never
stays in unless he's got something.
Well, perhaps we
should call it a night.
We're definitely
bringin' you back! (ALL LAUGH)
When was the last time you won?
He can't remember that far back!
Now you got something to sneak
INTO your wife's purse! (ALL LAUGH)
I had the most
wonderful time at dance class!
Every time the instructor
showed us something,
he used me as his partner. I always
thought I was such a clodhopper!
I cannot believe what I have missed
all these years. How was your game?
Hm? Oh, it was great!
Why wouldn't it be?
I love Abe! I love poker! A whole
night playing poker with Abe...
..and his friends.
I have a dancer's ankles!
What do you think, huh?
Wanna dance with the star pupil?
Huh?
You know,... dance.
No, I'm not in the mood.
You're always in the mood!
Not every single night!
Yes, you are!
I'm not some kind of machine!
You can't just snap your fingers -
Yes, I can. I always have.
Oh, alright!
Pumpkin oil, pectin,
manganese sulphate and...
..zinc oxide? Yes!
That's meat paste, baby!
This sucks! We knew we were
gonna be stuck here for a week
and no-one brought a deck of cards?
I could do my foot-puppets again.
Please, no! How long
have we been stuck here for?
I have lost all sense of time.
I'd guess about five days.
We just gotta keep ourselves busy.
Let's put our heads together
and recreate episodes
of Gilligan's Island!
We already did that.
That was this storm?!
If we don't come up with something
to do, I will go insane!
Come on, Reese! We're gonna be late!
We're doing the mambo tonight.
I'll be home about 10:30.
Eeargh! Arrgh!
What are you doing? Is it too much
to ask for pickles that are edible?!
Hal, what's wrong?
Nothing. Just go to your class.
Look, you have been snapping
at everybody all week.
My class can wait one minute.
Now, you tell me what's going on.
(SIGHS) OK. This thing happened.
I didn't wanna talk about it
because I'm not sure it happened
and if it didn't I'd be a jerk
for saying it did when it didn't.
I'd be creating this BIG issue,
but it did happen. Ohhh, it did!
I've recently come into a little
money so I went to the mall to buy
myself a CD player,
then I saw a kid
who looked like you
and I thought of
something better.
Here.
Wow!
The look on your face!
It was totally worth it!
You're the worst
brother ever! I know! I know!
Oh, we like to think the differences
people have aren't differences,
but then I'm taken advantage of
because I'm different!
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
We can talk later. Bye!
(RINGING TONE)
"Hello?"
Abe, it's Hal. "Please leave
a message after the beep."
Abe, it's Hal. I don't know if this
is recording, but we need to talk.
I could be mistaken, and if I am,
it's gonna make me sound like -
"(BEEP)"
I'm an idiot.
(ENGAGED TONE) Dad!
Stevie's being really annoying!
He's filming everything I do!
Malcolm's...
Dammit, Stevie,
I don't wanna hear it! You behave!
You are a guest in this house!
He was a guest in your house! People
should never yell at children!
Especially children
that aren't their own!
I apologised two minutes later!
And Stevie accepted the apology! You
know, he's not that fragile. Relax!
Really. What? At least I'm man enough
to apologise when I've been a jerk!
What is that supposed to mean?!
You know what I'm talking about.
The way you and your
friends treated me! What?!
Oh, please! Obviously I'm different!
I stuck out like a sore thumb.
I thought it didn't matter but...
If you're implying
what I think you're implying.
You want me to just say it?
I think you better.
Fine! You and your poker
buddies all ganged up on me
because I'm not
a professional!
Excuse me?! You and your doctor
and lawyer and dentist friend!
You decided it was OK to skin a guy
just because he's a working stiff!
And I bet you had
a big laugh about it!
We didn't gang up on you!
You just stink at poker!
That was a cheap shot.
The... truth... hurts.
If we played a straight game,
I'd mop the floor with you.
We did play in a straight game. And
you went home crying to your momma!
Let's play right now and we'll see
who will do the crying and who will
do the mopping. I will own you!
I-I mean... I
didn't mean...
I meant - Oh, shut
up and get the cards.
.
My home is full of
messy little rascals.
Thank goodness
my Air Wick Fresh Matic
keeps the place
fresh automatically.
It releases bursts of fragrance
every 9, 18
or 36 minutes,
so it always
smells great.
(sniffs) Ahh!
Whatever my lot
get up to.
(sniffs)
Ahh!
Now there's a new discreet
Fresh Matic Mini.
It goes anywhere in the house
and automatically
keeps it smelling lovely.
.
Gonna see me?
(He doesn't have the flush.)
(What?)
(He has a tell. He licks
his lips when he's bluffing.)
I'll see your five,
and raise you five.
Fold.
Hah-ha!
Bet's ten.
I call. Straight.
Flush.
(DING!) Time's up.
My turn with the string.
I gave it to Pete.
I gave it to Francis.
And then I gave
it back to Eric.
What?! You did not! Yes, I did!
What are you trying to pull?
I'm just sayin',
I don't have the string.
You're the last person I saw it with.
What are we gonna do without it?!
It's just a stupid string!
(ALL GASP)
So, what would be a
reason for saying that, Eric?
You seem to have a motive
against the string.
No, I love the string! It's - Maybe
you loved it a little too much.
And I quote, "If I can't have
the string, no-one will."
I didn't say that!
Someone said it! You! Just now!
Don't try to twist this around. He's
not the one on trial. What trial?!
Guilty!
Guilty! Guilty!
He raises four.
Your four,... five more.
Maybe you should -
You wanna play? Fine.
I almost feel sorry
for them. Almost. (LAUGHS)
We're gonna end this
right here. Winner take all.
Fine.
Turn 'em up.
Three fives!
Three fives with a jack.
Yeah!
That makes six fives. What the hell
kind of deck has six fives?!
I got them from the boys' room.
You don't even have a decent deck!
I'm sorry I don't have solid gold
cards like you're accustomed to!
This poor-guy act
is getting tiring.
Your superior act is old! If I'm
such a jerk, why'd you come over?!
Pardon me for wanting to
play poker with my best friend!
I mean, I-I was really excited
to come over and play poker and...
..meet your other friends.
Truth be told, I was...
excited for you to come over, too.
I bought a new shirt.
That Hawaiian one?
I like that one.
Why are we fighting like this?
Because we're idiots!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Boys, what do you say
we go out for ice cream?
Sounds good to me. Dewey, come on,
we're going for ice cream!
Where's your brother?
See this, ladies?
Mrs Angelo gets her dance.
As for the rest of you -
I am not running a charity.
You have to come up with the dough.
I do not dance on credit.
No offence, but some of you might
not even be around next week.
(WALTZ PLAYS)
(ALL APPLAUD / CHEER)
Oh, I didn't want that to end!
That does it - I am signing up
for your Monday, Wednesday class.
Maybe Saturday, too!
Lois, Lois, please.
Come with me.
Um,...
..we have to stop this.
Why?
Honey, you've outgrown me.
I give beginning dance lessons,
usually to people
who can barely move.
This is another instructor.
He's across town.
He is the best. He's the only one
who can take you to the next level.
But I really love it here.
Lois,... you have a gift.
You mustn't waste it.
It's time for you
to - to spread your wings.
Fly.
Fly away, little bird.
Oh, my God! Francis!
You're going to do it?!
I'm your best friend. I'm not gonna
let these jerks brand you.
Everyone's gonna know
you're a string thief! Aaaaaargh!
We're shovelled out.
Vacation's over.
He took the... string.
Every damn storm!
So, Dewey, how come
you're not playing with your toy?
What are you smiling about?
"(BALLROOM DANCING MUSIC)"
Where did you get this?!
"# ..cheek to cheek #"
"# Is heaven... #"
Have a seat. In a minute you and
Mrs Johnson do the forbidden dance.
You think that's the only copy?
What do you take me for?
Enjoy your assembly tomorrow.
I'm going to the ball game with Abe.
He had one ticket. Invited me.
That's great, dear.
I'm glad... What's this?
"(WALTZ PLAYS)"
He was trying
to get rid of me!
Hal, turn this off.
Hal!
Oh, my God, I can't believe
how beautiful you dance!
Hal, you are such a fool.
(WALTZ PLAYS)
'(CRASH!)'
'(SMASH)'
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
Apply again, again, again...
Applying Athlete's Foot treatments
day after day can feel never ending.
Try revolutionary Lamisil Once.
A single application and the lasting
film keeps on working in the skin...
..to eliminate
Athlete's Foot.
Once and you're done. So
you can feel in touch again.
Lamisil Once.
www.tvsubtitles.net