Leaving so soon, cadet? Sir, by
statute 614 of the Alabama Legal
Code I am officially emancipated
and considered an adult.
An adult who no longer chooses
to attend Marlin Academy.
I have copies of the documents
if you want to see them again.
Oh, no need!
I'm sure everything was
done on the up and up.
But let me tell
you something, cadet.
In all my years
at this academy
I have never had a student
who was more bull headed,
more committed to avoid
learning at all costs.
A cadet who's constant byword
was insubordination.
Thank you, cadet.
What?
Before you came to this academy
I was bored, uninspired,...
..and this close to retiring.
But your insolence and stupidity
have been the irritating grain
of sand around which has formed
the pearl of my renaissance.
I like me again. Cadet!
As a thanks I
want you to have...
..this.
Normally these are reserved for
cadets who have distinguished
themselves or whose parents
have donated a building but you've
left your mark here in your own way.
So, what the heck!
Wow! Sir,... this is great.
Farewell, cadet.
Thank you so much.
Careful that's razor...
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
Normally I dread the first day of
school. Mum's been on such a rampage
about Francis it's a relief be here.
Thank God...
..summer's... over.
Hello, babies.
How's baby school, babies? Didn't
high school start a half hour ago?
If I'm on time they'll
expect it every day.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Hi, Reese. This is Gus. He's in the
lead to replace you as school bully.
He gives a wedgie that'll knock your
socks off. I'm not just saying that
cos he's got me in a head lock.
Grab your wrist and stave your
fingers. You'll get better leverage.
You listen to him. He's the man.
I've completed the research on our
new teacher if anyone's interested.
Lionel Herkabe.
Born July 8th, 1963. Parents,
John and Ida. Notice anything?
He was a Krelboyne. We
won't have to talk down to him.
Finally, someone
who knows our pain.
Bentley. Gifted High. Princeton.
Harvard Business. Why's he teaching?
Well, there was some unpleasantness.
He quit a government think tank
to start a... dot.com.
(ALL GROAN) One time
net worth 200 million.
Now 137 dollars.
(GASPS) Here he comes!
Here he comes!
Who's Dabney?
Me, sir. I took the liberty of
ordering you a decaf soy latte.
Let me guess.
Emotionally needy. Closet bed-wetter.
You get no affection at home
so you'll be seeking it from me.
Look elsewhere, son.
Who's the anal-retentive outsider...
..with repressed
matricidal tendencies?
Yo, sir! Me, sir! Please, stop.
As you may or may not know I was
once one of you, a Krelboyne.
And I'm sure I would have made
the same lame attempt to ingratiate
myself to the new soft-headed
thick-wit teaching my class.
I've been there. I've been coddled
and preened. "Oh, you're a genius."
"You can do anything you set your
mind to. It must be easy being you."
Well, bull!
(ALL GASP)
All that gets you is an ex-wife
and 14 million dollars in debt.
I won't let you fall into the trap
society has set for you.
Playtime is over, children!
You've had a free ride so far.
It's time somebody challenged you,
tested your mental limits!
I don't have a teaching certificate
from a two-year community college
like most of the people I said hello
to this morning in the teachers
lounge but I'll muddle through with
my double doctorate from Harvard.
This is a test!
Correct. You have 20 minutes.
There are six essay questions.
I'm sorry, I thought this was
the gifted class. Begin!
Thanks for the ride. Are you sure
about this Alaska thing? Absolutely.
I heard Alaska's a hole. Are
you kidding?
Cruise ships go there!
For six weeks in the summer.
Isn't it dark the rest of the year?
I don't have to justify myself
to you or anyone.
That's why I got emancipated, OK?
OK. Good luck
with your parents.
Well, they had a week to think about
it. Let's see how they take it.
(DOOR SLAMS)
You...! You...!
You ungrateful son of a...
This wasn't meant to hurt you!
All I'm saying is you can get your
diploma first then do what you want.
It's all about maximising your
options. Take in the long view.
(WINCES) Sorry about the closer.
Nonsense. I wouldn't have taught you
if I didn't want you to use it.
What do I always say?
The nards are fair game.
The nards are fair game!
Sometimes you're presented with
an opportunity you can't pass up.
Understand?
I'm not the one to worry about.
I know. I wanna get this straight
with mom. That's why I came here.
OK, then. Honey!
Your son has something
to say to you.
Huh! I didn't know the
Henderson's painted their house.
(BELL RINGS)
I have your test results.
You all got A's.
But, since this is the gifted
class, I also factored in...
..cogency of argument,
economy of language and penmanship,
which enabled me to do this.
What is that? A ranking board.
I thought you said we all got A's.
Oh, you did. But some of you
got better A's than others.
But we all still
have A's? Of course.
So, er, what does being
number one get you? Nothing!
Just the knowledge that
you are number one.
Or that you are
not number one.
Yes, number five?
It's Dabney, sir.
I know. What is it
number five? I forgot.
What... a jerk. Is that what
we're gonna turn out like?
If I ever start acting like that
you have to promise to kill me.
No! No more death pacts.
Don't worry about it.
The only way that stupid board can
have an effect on us is if we let it.
Those numbers mean nothing.
What are... you doing?
Nothing!
You were studying?
No, I wasn't. My book
just fell open at this page.
You know... I'm
really not hungry.
I think I left my recess
stuff in my locker.
My God! High school is awesome! They
have an entire room for detention.
They put you in with juniors and
seniors. Some of them have records.
It's really inspiring.
What are you looking at?
Francis.
He's still out there? Yeah, he's
eating out of the bird-feeder.
Who's shoes are these? Who left
their shoes in the living-room?
They're mine. Sorry. You're right,
you're sorry! Leaving your shoes
around like you don't care!
I hope you like walking to school
in your socks! I said sorry.
I've heard sorry before!
I don't think so.
OK. I tell you
what we're gonna do.
From now on when you wanna wear
shoes you check them out.
Sign them in. Sign them out.
Just like a library.
Clean up those toys!
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(PANTS) Oh! Oh, thanks.
It's freezing. It's good
to see you. I've missed you.
Ow! What's that for?!
Emancipation? What, you're
divorcing the family now?
How could you do this to mom?
She left me no choice.
Ow! We've done a lot of bad things
to mom but we've never abandoned her.
I'm not abandoning her!
I'm just going to Alaska!
That's 5,000 miles away!
It is not... 5,000 miles? Are you
serious? Oh, my God! It's gonna take
me forever to get up there!
Then, don't go. Guys, I'm not doing
this to hurt anybody, I just...
I really think this is my best
chance to make something of myself.
Tell it to mom. I can't. She won't
talk to me. She's being so immature.
In the meantime I'm stuck
outside in the freezing cold.
Hey, would it be alright
if I slept in here tonight?
You do like your
whites, don't you?
Of course.
But look!
It's grey.
And look at this.
This stain's been washed in.
If you want really white whites,
try Vanish Oxi
Action Crystal White.
One scoop and you see
the difference in just one wash.
Look what it's doing
in your machine.
Drop your stain
over this.
Look at it go!
This is good!
And it's perfect
for all your
washable whites.
She was right.
Vanish Oxi Action Crystal White.
Certainly the whale represents
the search for God.
But that could be limiting.
We could say it was
the search for the self.
Melville could be considered
a pre-existentialist.
You can't deny the whale could be
the search for truth which has been
a theme throughout his whole oeuvre.
You can't overlook the fact that it
is a whale which was the biggest
industry in the 19th century.
The oil was used in lamps,
soaps and even cosmetics.
Today whaling is outlawed but many
Aleutian islanders are legally
allowed to harvest whales for...
..ritual purposes.
But I digress! (SOBS)
Wow! Nine places.
That's gotta be a record.
OK, on to new business. This
Friday Principal Littledove will
be dropping by for an evaluation.
I think he'll be very impressed with
what he sees. I don't think he'll
understand it
but his tiny brain will have the dim
perception of the progress you can
make
when students are properly
motivated. (SOBS)
Now, who would like to sink their
teeth into some Bernoulli equations?
Come on, guys. If we don't let the
rankings get to us they mean nothing!
Easy for you to
say, number one.
I have a name!
We all have names!
Oh, my God! I can't
remember mine! This is ridiculous!
School used to be the one place
where you were happy and Herkabe
has taken that away from you.
That stupid board is ruining our
lives! We can't let him do that!
What choice... do we have?
We have the choice that
people have had for centuries.
We can choose to fail.
Like the French?
You mean... we take...
..today's test?
No, we don't take it...
..we nuke it!
Every answer wrong! No complete
sentences! No punctuation!
And we use number
three pencils. (ALL GASP)
You can't rank zeroes.
Brilliant!
He'll have no choice but to throw
out his system. We'll be free!
(ALL CHEER)
I'm very disappointed in you.
Everyone else, nice job.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I tried. My hand
wouldn't let me.
I regret... nothing!
Interesting gambit but the lemmings
didn't follow you off the cliff.
When you spend some time in the real
world you realise you can't fight
the system. And now,...
..I'm the system.
(SIGHS)
Don't worry, I just let the air out.
We can talk while I put on your
spare.
I'm sorry I had to resort to this
but you have to give me five minutes
so we can talk.
(LOUD MUSIC) We can
talk over the music.
You can't drive on a flat!
You're gonna ruin your rims!
That was a red light!
You might want to notice my entire
opening paragraph is a palindrome.
You might want to
notice... my formatting.
What's this? Irrigation techniques
of pre Roman society and how they
helped advance western civilisation.
I thought we were just studying
Mesopotamian farming. We were.
I used that as a start on how their
influences spread through the
Egyptians, the Carthaginians,
through the whole ancient world.
I think you'll be happy with this.
Very nice,... number 12.
It's nice to see a little
effort put forth
while some are content to do
the absolute minimum.
So,... he wants...
..to play. Ho-ho,
we'll play, alright.
What is it we're playing?
# "Pump It Up"
- Elvis Costello
# I've been on tenterhooks
# Ending in dirty looks
# Listening to the muzak
# Thinking about this and that
# She'll say that's that
# I don't want
to chitter-chat
# Turn it down a little bit
# Or turn it down flat
Pump it up
# When you don't really need it
# Pump it up
Until you can feel it
# Hey!
# Pump it up
# Until you can feel it
# Pump it up When
you don't really need it
# Don't really need it
# Don't really need it #
OK. I think we're ready to show
Principal Littledove what motivation
can accomplish.
Well done, class.
You know, maybe we should just put
our heads down and take a rest for
a moment, shall we?
Yes? Did you know I can count
to a million by prime numbers?
I can, too!
So can I! It's easy!
That's not necessary.
Two, three... Five, seven...
11,...
13, 17, 19...
23, 29, 31...
Now by hundreds.
101, 211, 307...
401.
503, 601...
Seven! No!
That is enough!
5,000, 1,009, 2,003...
2,023.
No!
Where are you going, number three?
It's hot! It's hot and I'm stupid!
I'm stupid, too!
Everybody please remain seated!
(SCREAMS HYSTERICALLY)
I'm nothing!
I'm invisible!
(WHISTLES) Boy, that's quite
a show for your first week here.
You were right.
You can't beat the system.
But you sure can break it.
I love you guys. I'll write
you when I get there, OK?
Someday when you come back and
you're unemployed
and have no place to live,...
..you can come
stay at my castle.
Thanks, bud.
He's leaving. He just wants to
talk to you. Just hear him out.
Lois! This has got to stop!
He's going very far away and you're
not gonna see him for a long time.
Honey, there are moments in life
that you just don't get back...
..and I know you. If you do not deal
with this now it will haunt you for
ever.
Fine.
I've lost a son
but gained a baby.
I tried.
I know.
Are you sure this
is what you want?
Well, it better be.
< Francis.
I'm listening.
This is what you get
for the way you treated me!
I'm going to Alaska and
you'll be left without a son!
And the way you treated me is
now a matter of public record!
I treated you?!
I've sacrificed for you and you've
caused us nothing but pain!
You want pain? I've got your scars,
baby! Three years in that school -
We went without for that school!
Oh! Maybe I should thank you?
Thank you for making my life hell!
Living hell? You've been a problem
since you were born! I'm outta here!
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
p
www.tvsubtitles.net