BELL
CROWD NOISE/CHEERING
Make your
skin feel:
Skin Contact.
BELL
.
There it is. Kill it. A spider has
as much right to live as you or I.
Besides, it's unlucky
to kill it in the house.
OK. Hello, little fella.
Come on, sweetheart.
Oh! (SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMS)
Go, go, go!
Door! Open the door!
The back? Side? Side.
No, back. No, side! Run!
Oh, my God, did we just...?
Go. She can only ground me.
Get your keys
and go. But...! Go!
(LOIS SCREAMS)
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
and you're not so big
# Life is unfair
My dad's company picnic is
tomorrow. Laurie will be there.
I've had a crush on her
since third grade. (GRUNTS)
I haven't seen her since
she moved last year.
I've grown four inches,
but I can't count on that.
If I do 10,000 of these, I should
have something to show by tomorrow.
No candy tomorrow,
understand? I'll be fine!
You won't. What happened
at the last company picnic?
I got into a fight
with that red-headed boy.
Why did you do that?
Because I ate candy.
Because you ate candy.
You do not metabolise sugar well.
You get mean, crazy, get
into fights and end up crying.
Do you want that to happen again
this year? No. Get ready for bed.
OK. What do you think?
This or this?
What are you doing?!
This is an important function.
It's a company picnic.
Attended by my new boss
whom I haven't met yet.
Gotta start off on the right foot.
You're making too much of this.
No, I am not! You have to make
a good first impression.
It sets the tone
for the relationship.
Al, this is your new
supervisor, Miss Plum.
I look forward to
working with you.
Same here.
Oh, and what do we have here?
My... big, fat sto-mach.
I'd like you to meet your staff,
but I'm not sure where they are.
(LAUGHTER)
It is great to meet you,
Mr Jacobson.
I want you to know I'm
gonna do a terrific job for you.
Great. Have you met my
daughter and son-in-law?
No, I haven't. Kelly? Steve?
I want you to meet somebody.
Hi. I'm Hal.
Hi. So nice to...
Oh, my God! There's
a toothpick in my eye!
She's gushing blood!
Put a tourniquet on her neck!
I'm outside of my body.
I can see a light.
Grandma? Is that you?
I'll chew off your face,
spit it out and dance on it!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm gonna drag your carcass
through the street.
She's got a toothpick in her eye!
It's like a chess game.
Every subtle move is vital.
(STRAINS) Eight.
God, what did you
do? You're huge! Shut up.
Be careful. You might frighten
Laurie with your savage manliness.
Who says I'm doing it for Laurie?
So Laurie's fair game?
I wonder if she likes older men.
Don't. I really like this girl.
Please! It's my first chance
to see her since she moved away.
I'm asking you as a brother. Please
don't be a jerk and screw this up.
Wow, this desperate grovelling
is new for you. Keep it up.
Call yourselves a hockey team?
To beat McCallister Oil you'll
have to play better than that.
You're making stupid mistakes,
missing opportunities.
Keep your mind on the game!
Are our pay cheques here yet?
Aren't you done with that sink yet?
There's more than when I started.
You don't leave until it's finished.
It'd be faster if Eric helped.
I'm not letting my star player
near that toxic filth.
I slave away by myself
just because he plays hockey?
He doesn't just play hockey.
He skates like the wind.
He's got a 70mph slapshot.
Well, indoors, fresh ice.
We'll teach those thugs
a lesson they won't forget.
Those chicks won't know
what hit 'em. You're playing girls?
The men won't play us
till we beat the ladies' team.
Those girls play dirty, make
fun of us, and steal our women.
Wow! People who are more humiliated
than me. I'd love to see that.
Wish granted. You're our
equipment manager. What?!
Rinaldo came down with
jock lung. Here's your cheque.
Eric, there's a little extra
for you. Thanks.
There's no money in this cheque.
It says I owe you $14.
I didn't buy anything last week.
Cost-of-living increases.
Your room, board, pillow rental
and the rubber gloves, princess(!)
This is insane!
I won't work 60 hours a week
and still owe you money. I quit!
Fine. Give me the $604
you racked up and you can go.
What? How can I have possibly $604
when you keep taking my money?
Shut up! And get back to work.
Don't let your equipment-manager
duties get in the way of your real
work.
Man, that sucks.
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello? It's Francis.
I'm in a real bind.
I don't have any money.
"Hear me out."
Tell Mom they're sending
the smart kids to Washington, DC,
get $600 and spend a weekend
at Stevie's. Reese, phone.
Hello? Reese. You know the hardware
store? The entry way is slippery...
Dewey, phone.
Francis? Yeah.
Money? Yeah.
I don't know why I go
to these things. I am so nervous.
My stomach sounds like
a bunch of dogs fighting.
Get your ear down there.
Hal, you'll be fine.
What are you doing?
Just keep moving.
Is your new boss even here?
They're all here.
There's Landon. He's the head
of the whole company.
Of course the new guy's here.
Don't talk nonsense!
You've never met him. Do you know
who you're hiding from?
That's a good point.
Is the new boss here yet?
Yeah. He's right over there.
Let me know when
you'll introduce yourself.
We figure you'll set him on fire.
Don't give him ideas. Bet's off.
I'm nervous enough as it is.
We're just teasing you.
You'll do fine. You and
I both know that's a lie.
Yeah, well, I tried.
Hi, Mom. Splendid
day for a picnic.
You want to do this the
easy way or the hard way?
The hard way.
Spread 'em.
I won't always be around to do this.
You have to control yourself.
I know.
Undies.
Malcolm? Laurie, hi.
It is so good to see you.
Yeah. Good to see you too.
I can't believe how tall you are.
Yeah, well, you know...
I've missed you guys so much.
I've missed you too.
I mean, we've all missed you.
Everyone. Not just me.
Are you doing the
three-legged hunt? What?
They tie your leg to another
person's and send you to find stuff.
You can win $100.
I just need a partner.
Do you want to do it?
Really? Yeah, it sounds great.
Cool. Is that
your brother?
Hi, Reese.
Sorry. I'm gay. OK.
(You owe me!)
.
The diamond standard of dishwashing
won't come from a dirty dishwasher.
Finish Dishwasher Cleaner is far
better at removing hidden grease
and limescale.
And a cleaner dishwasher
means cleaner dishes.
It's only dishwashing,
but you deserve perfect
results every time.
.
Do you work for the company or are
you a drag-along? A drag-along.
Me too. My husband drags me along
then runs off
and talks to his friends.
I hide. Hide?
From my kids.
It's great to have somebody to talk
to. I'm bad at social situations.
My psychiatrist says
I'm emotionally detached
and that I have paranoid fantasies
about what people think about me.
(GIGGLES)
Uh-huh?
It can get really ugly.
False accusations, crying attacks.
I don't know why my husband married
me. I know why I married him.
I'm addicted to
disapproval. Ah. Really?
Yeah. Of course,
I only have myself to blame.
He's exactly like my father was.
Oh, my God! He was so judgemental.
Every time I spoke,
I felt I was torturing him.
Wow, they're good.
They got nothing on my boy.
How's the diarrhoea?
You feeling alright? Tiptop.
There's Lavernia. I hear she might
actually have a team this year.
Think we ought to adjust
the front line? Clarence?
Clarence! What?
Hey, Lavernia! I was afraid
you'd show your face.
Not that I was afraid you'd play me,
just that you'd show your face.
Hello, Clarence. I thought
you only gave pep talks in your van.
You'll get a boyfriend one day.
You'll have a
moment of bliss,
then you'll bite his head off and lay
your eggs in his decapitated body.
Was that comment necessary?
That's why people don't like you.
People like me.
Who doesn't like me?
I got a good feeling about today.
These girls aren't so tough.
Wait till I get out there.
I'm gonna... (SCREAMS)
How's my breath? It seems fine.
Not too minty?
That can be just as bad.
Please give me
back my compact.
OK, get in, get out,
just say hello and go.
No. (GASPS)
Mr Landon. Hello. I told you about
the first time I met this guy?
The urinal-cake guy?
(LAUGHS) Unbelievable.
But I didn't fire him. He's one
of our finest systems managers.
It goes to show that even
a gibbering idiot can surprise you.
That would make a great chapter
heading for your new book.
I thought he dropped his pill case.
Excuse me for being considerate!
Hi! John Pratt. It is
a pleasure to meet you.
Hi. You are a hard man to find.
I had to have someone point you out.
Well, it's not like
I'm avoiding you.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I heard you had
a great sense of humour.
I know it's gonna be great
working with you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I should get back
to my family now.
Right. Sorry to hold you up.
It is a real pleasure to
meet you, Mr Landon. Same here.
Boys, you got ten minutes. Leave
your wallets and valuables in here.
You gotta get out
on the ice and warm up.
I don't think I can play. My glute
cramped up on the ride over.
You have to play.
Go lay down on that table.
You! Get over there.
Give him a good, strong massage.
Work that knot out of
his glute. Out of his what?
No way! He's our
goalie. We need him.
No! Look, you owe me $604.
You do this, I'll take off $1.50.
$1.50?! And if you don't, I'll
charge you $50 for the ride home.
The rest of you, get out there.
Show 'em what you got.
Here. You're responsible for these
valuables till after the game.
Don't be afraid
to dig in deep.
If it helps, I'll
unhitch the trap door.
Get up, you idiot! Are you stupid?
Ow!
I said, hustle for
the breaks! Hustle!
I was in the locker room
and the other coach approached me.
What's that reptilian sack
of dog logs trying to pull now?
He wants to make a wager with you
on the outcome of the game.
$642, to be exact. I don't bet.
I earn my money and hold on to it.
He said you'd be
afraid. Oh, he did?
He also said John Grisham
was a hack with no sense of plot
and a tin ear for dialogue.
He said that about Mr Grisham?
Alright, he wants to bet? We'll bet.
Tell him to make it 700.
He was pretty adamant
about the $642. Fine.
Hey, Chuck! I need you
to hold on to some bet money.
That idiot Clarence has no idea
what we got in store for him.
Easiest 700 I
ever made. (WHISTLE) >
What's with my skates?
The blades are so dull.
Somebody unscrewed mine.
I got Vaseline on my grip tape.
(KLAXON)
Go, go, go, go!
He is never home.
We last had dinner together
six months ago... with his boss!
Did I tell you about
our anniversary?
I bought $30's
worth of candles.
I wore a negligee
the size of a postage stamp.
He walks in an hour late and spends
six hours in a computer chat room.
I drank an entire bottle
of champagne then I passed out.
I woke up with the dog
licking my face.
And I actually thought
it was my husband!
I'm gonna find my boys.
As if he would show me
any kind of affection.
To him, I'm the fat lady that
answers his psychiatrist's phone.
In my mind, I do see myself
as a 200-pounder.
But I have seen the way
other men look at me.
Wanda! So good to see you again.
Wanda, Meg. Wanda, Meg.
Why don't you get to know
each other? I'll be right back.
So, how do you know Lois?
Que?
I like you. You're fun.
I like you too.
Want some of my candy?
(YELLS)
Fill up on that bread. It's better
you get sick on that than on candy.
I got enough to worry about
without you going crazy on me.
Stay here!
Hi, Lois. Are you hiding back here?
No, just enjoying the shade.
Did you meet your new boss? Yep.
How did it go? Fine. We hit it off.
What happened? What do you mean?
It went well. He likes me.
Is it so hard to imagine I made a
good first impression? Mr Landon?
You should give me a
little credit. Hey, boss!
Is he calling you...?
Of course he isn't!
Whatever you were
going to say, he isn't.
I'm not going
anywhere until... Lois!
Mr Landon!
Did I tell you that his mother
is coming to visit me this week?
She despises me, but
at least she talks to me.
My husband hasn't said two words
besides, "Where's the remote?"
and "How far are
those gonna sag?"
This isn't a good time.
Every year, he has to go
to this stupid get-together
for his friends from college.
We're about to go to this party
and he tells me
not to say anything stupid.
I embarrass him one time!
I didn't know
who Ernest Hemingway was.
Alright, girls? OK,
Pete and Cathy, you're next.
It is so great to see you again.
Great to see you too.
For those of you without partners,
we've done a random pairing.
Mike and Christina.
Reese and George.
I'm Reese. I'm George.
You can call me George.
I can eat eight hot dogs.
That's good, George(!)
You've got to
be kidding me!
It's weird being away from
the friends I grew up with. I bet.
Malcolm, can I ask
you something? Sure.
If you liked somebody, and you had
no idea if they liked you back,
would you say something?
I've always thought honesty
was a good thing. Me too.
But what if they lived too far away
and it'd be really hard?
I like you too, Laurie.
I really like you.
Honestly, you
have no idea.
I've liked you for years.
I think about you all the time.
Oh, no! What?
Oh, my God! I am so sorry!
I was talking
about Gary Spindler!
Oh, no! Erm, it's OK.
No! This is so humiliating!
It's all my fault.
Malcolm, I am so sorry!
Really, it's not that...
"Malcolm and Laurie."
Remember, you're only going to be
tied together for three hours.
Let's get hopping.
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
Get great results
all around your home
when you try
new Cillit Bang Multi Power.
It was so quick and easy.
Look how it cleans this toothpaste
www.tvsubtitles.net