.
(WHIMPERS)
Argh!
Fine! I'll go to
parent-teacher night.
# "Boss of Me" -
They Might Be Giants
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello? Hey, Stevie.
The usual. We're on punishment.
We had the eggs, we had
the golf clubs, what d'you expect?
Whoa! Really?
I want that thing spotless! I want
to be able to lick the bricks.
When you gonna lick the bricks?
I want you to lick the bricks.
I'll lick the bricks right now.
This is your last day of punishment.
You want one day more?
Alright, alright!
Oh!
Stevie's dad got three extra tickets
to the Demolition Derby!
Cool! That's not the best part!
We get the handicapped seats
in the front!
Mom, can we go to the
Demolition Derby tomorrow?
Demolition Derby?
What? You wanna go tomorrow?
Yeah. Why not? Our
punishment's over tonight.
Think we may have something planned
for tomorrow? The Demolition Derby.
Or could it be that tomorrow is
your father's birthday?!
Oh. We talked about this!
Maybe Dad can come with us. Yeah, we
could get him a ticket as a present.
You're not going anywhere!
You're staying at home
and we're gonna throw your father
a party like we talked about!
I have something very special
planned. Like what?
It's none of your business. It's
a surprise. I can't believe you!
You have to be forced into
celebrating your father's birthday?!
You should be
ashamed of yourselves!
You don't have to yell, we can hear
you just fine if you talk
in a normal tone of voice.
I'm OK with the
present system.
Get back to work.
I'm not OK with the present system!
How does she make me say things
like that?
Oh, my God! What is it?
Francis is coming home.
Really? You're kidding!
No, this is his itinerary.
He gets in tomorrow.
I hope this doesn't ruin Mom's plan.
This is Mom's plan!
Why didn't she tell us?
Because it's a surprise for Dad!
And if we blow her secret,
Mom is gonna kill us!
So we just need to keep our mouths
shut and finish our work. Right.
Come on, Dewey,
you call this clean?
(TELEVISION BLARES)
# Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
# Happy birthday, dear Dad
Happy birthday to you #
(TURNS TELEVISION ON)
"You've never seen
anything like this before."
"The Demolition Derby comes to
the fairground tonight at 8:00."
"Doctor Bob Edwards
and his '76 station wagon."
"Aw, damn, destruction,
mayhem, big cash prizes."
"Winner takes home $150!"
"..prohibited on the
third ring." "Come if you dare!"
This is so unfair!
Dad has tonnes of birthdays,
but there's only one
Demolition Derby.
We never get to
do anything good!
Well, at least
Francis will be here.
"..and his '76
station wagon. Oh, damn!"
Ah!
Not bad.
Still have a little snap in my skin.
For the love of God,
what did you do to me?
What do you mean?
All those situps I did,
all those miles I
ran every morning
and this is how you repay me,
by looking like hell?!
You think I look bad? Please!
The crow's feet, the turkey neck?
OK, a few years have gone by,
there's been a little wear and tear.
Wear and tear?!
You look like a puppet of yourself
made out of cottage cheese!
What are you talking about?
Check out the pant melons!
They still do the trick.
Sure, it's magnificent.
But you won't be able to
coast on that forever.
I postdate cheques to the power
company all the time, why is that
suddenly such a big deal?
(I'm a little short because
I spend a lot of money to surprise
my husband for his birthday.)
But next month...
No, it was a special circumstance.
Look, can I speak with
your supervisor?
No, don't put me on ho...!
Damn! Oops, lemme get those.
Oh, there's one.
Yes, I'm still holding.
Do you have to stay on the phone?
Give me a minute, they're
threatening to cut off the power.
It's a 24-hour number, you can call
them back. No, I can't! (You can!)
There was a time when I didn't have
to ask for your attention!
What? Yes, I'm still...
I wanted the supervisor!
A man likes to be noticed
when he walks in a room, Lois!
Boys, would you leave the room
so your father and I can talk? No!
Excuse me? I'm not leaving!
You guys just chase us out whenever
you want without even asking us!
I'm tired of it! Watching TV is
the only thing to do in this house
that's actually fun!
So you're left
with two choices!
You can either fight somewhere else
or get us a TV for our room!
There's no reasoning with
that woman.
I thought you
made some good points.
It doesn't matter, she doesn't
listen. It's like talking to a wall.
(LAUGHS) Hey,
that's what we're doing.
Just relax, it's only
for a couple of hours.
When Francis gets home,
they'll forget all about it.
We can get through this.
We've been waiting for 20 minutes,
Lois, when can we eat?
Hal, we have to wait for
the ice cream to loosen up.
You know you like
it soft. No, I don't.
Yes, you do. In
fact, so do we. We all do.
Since when? Since yesterday.
What happened yesterday? Dad, just
be patient. This isn't a witch hunt.
Just calm down, and
whatever happens is gonna happen.
What are you talking about?
What I'm trying to say is we're
gonna get through this together.
As a family.
And as individuals.
In this great
country where we live.
(DOORBELL) Thank God!
Come on, Hal! What...?
What are you doing?
Giving you your present!
Ta-da! Happy birthday, Dad!
Francis! Oh, my
God, it's Francis!
(LAUGHS) Oh, look
at you! Come here!
I can't believe it!
How long are you staying?
A few days. You surprised?
Surprised? I'm, I'm, I'm in shock!
You should be! I've been
planning this for months!
Thank you! Happy
birthday, honey.
Well, hold on, I got
another surprise for you.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Everybody, this is Piama.
She's my wife.
We're married. Hi.
I was gonna tell you over
the phone and then I thought,
why not bring her down here
and surprise you!
You're married?
Piama and I are husband and wife.
We got married last week.
Last week?
Francis, who is this woman?
She's my wife.
Her name is Piama.
Hello.
Well, come on, isn't
anyone gonna congratulate us?
What? For getting married.
That's what families do.
I think I'm gonna be sick. Come on,
Mom, at least try and be happy!
This is a hell of a thing to dump
in my lap on your father's birthday!
Yeah, it's all
about you, Mom.
Excuse me for thinking my family
would be excited to meet my wife!
I can't believe you guys!
Come on, Francis, it's not
their fault. What d'you expect?
You could've called ahead of time.
Boys, go to your room!
What? We're on your side!
I said go!
How long have you known each other?
You never mentioned her.
I only met her a month
ago. Today. Happy anniversary.
Plus we had the
whole bus ride down.
A month? (LAUGHS) I misjudged you!
That's the longest you've ever stuck
with anything in your life!
Congratulations, you
outlasted his paper route!
Lady, you don't want to
stick your hand in my face.
Hey, everybody calm down. We are
calm! It's Mom's who's flipping out!
Oh, Francis, I haven't
even started to flip out!
Why can't you be happy?!
We're supposed to be happy?
You behave like this,
after all we've done for you?!
I'm confused! Are we talking about
the years of psychological abuse
or sending me to
military school?!
This family sucks. They don't care
about us, they don't listen to us!
Let's get outta here.
To the Demolition Derby?
No, let's really get outta here
and get away from these people.
Where are we gonna go?
Wherever this takes us.
I snagged it out of Dad's wallet
this morning. You knew we'd need it?
Er,... yeah.
I'm in. Yeah, but... ..into a pulp
and throw me in the trash!
Why do I even try? You've been
nothing but a problem since...
Let's go. He's
trying to explain it to you,
if you'd listen
to him for once!
Why are you talking?
Why are you talking?!
Can we just stop this?!
Let's get in the car
and go for a drive to cool off.
We can still have a nice party.
Oh, we are long past
having a nice party!
As usual, Francis has taken
something that should've been sweet
and ruined it!
Don't pin this on me, I'm completely
willing to have a party right now!
Oh, you want to have a party?
Happy damn birthday!
Hey, why don't we
all have some cake?
We don't want to be a part of this
family any more, we're leaving!
Oh, great, here we
go with the dramatics!
Who else wants cake?!
Thank you. You're welcome.
Who wants some
delicious damn cake?
Can Piama have a rose? Why not?
There's plenty to go around!
I'm the one who broke
the ice maker last year!
Why do you have
to ruin everything?!
Well, I learned
from the best, Mom!
.
You're two
clicks away
from the new shape
of lip colour.
Infallible colour
lasts up to 16 hours,
even after
eating.
The conditioning balm
helps lock in moisture.
Brilliant!
In ten radiant shades.
Colour that's made
to stay on your lips...
And only on your lips.
Infallible?
It's my lip colour.
The lip duo
compact
that lasts
up to 16 hours.
Because you're worth it.
.
Wow! I've never been in
a hotel this fancy before.
This isn't a hotel, Dewey,
it's our new home.
OK, lemme do all the talking.
May I help you? My dad
called in a reservation.
OK.
There you are. As soon as your dad
signs this, you're all set.
Oh! He's out at the car,
but we can take care of it.
If you wanna have a seat,
we'll just wait for your dad.
Could we speed this along? My little
brother isn't feeling very well.
Yeah. My dad's gonna be a while.
He's cleaning up Dewey's sick.
I'm sorry, but an adult
needs to sign for the room.
Look, he's really sick.
He could blow any second.
He doesn't look
that sick to me.
(RETCHES)
Dewey, that was amazing!
I'm hungry. I bet you are.
How do you guys
want your steaks?
Shall we look in the park?
Nobody goes there
since they put the lights in.
Oh!
Why didn't you tell us you were
getting married?
It happened kinda fast.
How can you know anyone in a month?
Dad, I knew in a minute.
Trust me, Piama is the one.
She's a little fiery, but she's also
kind and funny and completely real.
You just haven't gotten to know her.
And who's fault is that?
I know, but that's why I brought
her, so you'd all get to know her!
It wasn't supposed to
turn into the Apocalypse!
And what about you and Mom?
You got married pretty quick.
Yes, but I was a few years older,
I'd already been with a lot of...
I had lived a full life.
So you were older.
I just ran into the right person for
me a little earlier than you did.
Once you meet
that person, why wait?
Huh? Why not do
it if I'm sure?
Should I not do it
cos my family's not sure?
It wouldn't matter if the wedding
was next week or 10 years from now,
you and Mom would've
had a problem with it.
All my life - I
would've come, Francis. What?
If you had invited me,
I would've come.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Didn't I tell you
flowers were a great idea?
OK, we're all set.
You have the Plaza burger,
the main lobster,
the porterhouse,
large French fries
and the complete dessert cart.
Your parents have an interesting
taste in food. Yeah, they do.
Actually, I'm gonna need
one of your parents to sign that.
I left the tip blank, why don't you
put in what you think is fair?
Bon appetit.
Dewey, your dinner's here!
There you go, Reese.
Thank you, Malcolm.
So this is what a
$24 hamburger looks like.
I thought it'd be
as big as my head.
Ah! Why don't we have
a jacuzzi tub at home?
Because that would make us happy.
Forget about that place.
Tonight, this is our home.
You got a lobster? Yes.
I think I deserve a lobster.
We all deserve
something nice for once.
Whoa! This dinner was expensive.
I wonder what
Dad's credit limit is?
Let's find out.
They should be
home with the boys soon.
How's your tea?
Fine, thank you.
Sugar? No, thanks.
That's a pretty
bracelet. Thank you.
What kinda stone is that?
Turquoise. Francis got it for me.
Oh.
How was your flight?
We took the bus.
I guess that's what Francis did with
the money I sent for his plane fare.
Plus the bracelet. (CHUCKLES)
Let's talk about something else.
Francis isn't the screw-up
you think he is.
Really? Did you know he works
16 hours a day at his job
and he still built a
wheelchair ramp for my uncle?
In fact - I don't think
we should talk about Francis.
Why not? He's my
husband and your son.
He and I have a very long
and complicated history together
that I don't feel
like explaining to you.
Admit it, you
don't like me.
I don't even know you.
Well, what would you like to know?
I'm 19, my mom ran
off when I was three
and my dad kicked me out when I was
14 because I threw out his liquor.
I've been married once before,
no kids, thank God,
and last year I spent three weeks
in jail, but it wasn't my fault.
Will you stop this? You can't stand
for someone in your fancy family
to marry beneath him.
What? Just because I'm not
all classy like you.
Classy? You think I'm classy?
Don't laugh at me. I'm sorry,
it's just this is a first.
I hate to break it to you,
but I am not classy. Oh, yeah.
I guess what you call
class, I call manners.
I came down here
hoping to get along with you.
But you're not
gonna let that happen.
You might be surprised at
what I'd let happen.
So,...
..what's gonna happen?
I don't know.
What is gonna happen?
(DOOR OPENS) Good news!
The boys stole
my credit card!
We just have to call
the credit card company and...
Why don't...? Let me
show you my tree house.
About time! We called for chocolate
syrup, like, 30 minutes ago!
(GASPS) Argh!
Hello, Malcolm.
(GROANS) Hi, Mom, hi, Dad.
Beat it, Vicky. We'll
finish the cuffs later.
OK, boys, get your things,
we're going home.
No! We're not
going back there!
You can't stay
here for ever.
What you gonna do,
live under a bridge
and steal food out of dumpsters?
We're not going home!
We've had it with the way
you treat us and all the yelling!
You are a terrible influence on us!
All you ever do is scream!
And order us around!
Something's wrong
with this family!
Families should have some way of
communicating besides yelling!
OK, everybody, calm down.
I understand what you're saying,
I am not gonna yell,
I am not gonna scream.
We are capable of talking about this
without raising our voices.
Now, boys, I want you to understand
I'm sorry about what happened.
But you have to understand
I get a little emotional
when I learn that my oldest son
was acting like an idiot
and throwing his life away.
Now, that doesn't mean...
Stop talking about him
like that! Francis is my heart!
OK, we're even! Everyone's fine
and there's no need for escalation!
Isn't it beautiful
when things work out?
It's gone pretty well, considering
we got off to a rocky start.
We couldn't have asked for
a better ending.
Get your wife
out of my sight!
(She called you my wife,
that's progress.)
So Dad's birthday
wasn't that bad after all.
He got a new back shaver,
we got to eat cake cut by a knife
and Mom has promised
not to yell at us any more.
Bye, Francis. Bye, Malcolm.
Happy birthday, Dad.
Thanks, son.
Piama. Lois.
Any time you want to finish
our little talk...
I'd like that. Maybe
I'll come for a visit.
Maybe I'll come
back down here.
Any time, any place.
Er,... yeah. OK. Bye.
(DEWEY SCREAMS) Get
back, you little weasel!
Reese!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
it's all my fault!
I'll clean my room
and do all my homework!
We may wanna go back to
the old system.
"Boss of Me" -
They Might Be Giants
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
.
(THEME TUNE)
www.tvsubtitles.net