What - ?! (GRUNTS
FRUSTRATEDLY) Those kids!
Not my Frampton
Comes Alive...! (MOANS)
(LAUGHS ANGRILY) "Honest, Dad, we
didn't even know you had a watch!"
Thank God they paved
the drive last year!
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
'Jury duty? They
want me to do jury duty?!'
I can't believe this!
You can't do it.
Spring break is coming up.
The boys are gonna be out of school.
I can't handle them by myself!
You're gonna have to tell them no!
That's not one of the options, Hal.
What are they thinking? Jury duty?!
This is America!
I don't have a choice!
Oh, yes, you do.
You wanna get
out of jury duty?
You just let me handle this.
(ALL) We, the jury,
promise to faithfully uphold...
This'll be great! I've
never been ice-fishing before.
It combines my two favourite
things,... ice and holes!
A bunch of guys roughing it! A true
test of courage and determination!
Man against the elements!
No crust on mine, thank you.
I hope you packed
enough toilet paper for four!
(ALL CHEER) You're kidding!
How'd you get Piama's permission?
I don't need my wife's permission!
I picked a fight. She kicked me out.
(ALL CHEER / LAUGH)
Oh, my God, Dewey, you are not
gonna believe what just happened!
We were supposed to go
exploring in the sewer!
I waited two hours for you! You're
not listening. This is incredible!
You promised that when spring break
started, you would take me!
I did all your chores,
all your homework,
I took your antibiotics -
Dewey, just shut up!
We're trying to tell you
something important.
We just saw Stevie's mom... naked!
And she's a total babe.
We were at Stevie's
getting stuff for the sewer
when we hear something
behind us. We turn around
and there she was,
in the hallway,... naked!
Buck naked, except
for her shower cap.
First she was screaming,
then Stevie was, then I was...
Yeah. Why'd I do that? Then she tore
the curtains down to cover up!
But you could see through them.
I'm so glad they just remodelled.
That is not a good reason! Mom walks
around here naked all the time!
She was naked
this morning. She -
If you've just combined those two
things in my head, I will kill you!
No, we're good. So, she was -
I got to get going.
Where are the boys?
At the library. I know. But if they
were doing something really bad,
they'd have come up with
a better lie.
So,... deliberations
start today. Nervous?
Nice try. You know I
can't talk about it. OK!
Is the counselman as tall
as he looks on TV? Hal!
Yes! Your eyebrow
went up! It did not.
It's the Panty
Bandit, isn't it?
This isn't right! We're married.
We tell each other everything.
We've never kept secrets from each
other in our entire relationship.
I keep secrets from you
all the time.
Oh, fine(!) Go! I
won't keep you from your...
..big, secret trial!
Thank you very
much! (CHORTLES)
For what? Oh,
nothing. Nothing at all.
You didn't say a word.
(CACKLES)
This sucks! We been here 15 hours.
We haven't caught a single fish.
How much longer will
this take? You never know.
I been ice-fishing my entire life,
never even seen a fish.
I'm with Francis. I got
bored on the drive here!
Can we at least talk?
About what?
We could use this opportunity
to get to know each other better.
You know, one time I walked in on
my two dads making love!
Guilty.
Not guilty.
And... guilty. That's
seven guilty and five not guilty.
The contention, for those of you who
don't think Marty stole the bike -
If it'll get us out of here earlier,
I'll change my vote. What?!
I don't feel that strongly
either way. Yeah, me, too!
Which side was winning again?
This is not a question of winning,
or of voting to
get out of here early!
We have to have some basis
for deciding. There was a trial!
And evidence, and laws...
Yeah-yeah-yeah.
Let's vote one more time
before we get into all that detail.
We might just get lucky.
Who wants to change their votes?
Whatever! There
you go! It's unanimous.
Hey, wait! What do
you think you're doing?!
You can't send
a 17-year-old kid to jail
just cos you wanna go home early.
For God's sake, we took an oath!
Did you vote guilty?
Yes, because -
Then, there's no problem.
We're all just agreeing.
Fine(!)
Then, I vote not guilty.
This is cool! There's no alligators
down here, right? That's made up?
But if there were, they'd
probably be blind, or albino,
or transparent!...
But that's not real.
This is so cool!
He hasn't shut
up all morning.
I was just as excited the first time
Francis took us. It's kinda cute.
Did you get the snake?
Right here.
They'll hear him
screaming in Russia.
Dude, finish the story!
She was standing there, buck naked!
I went like this. (GASPS)
Malcolm was like this. (GASPS)
It was incredible! The sun
was behind her. She was glowing.
A naked,... glowing... angel!
Stevie, back me up on this.
That's what she looked like, right?
Can we go now?
I get to lead! No, rear.
No, wait. Front!
I'll scout ahead!
What? You are
talking about his mom.
Change the subject. Show
some class. OK, I get it.
Whoo, Stevie! Is
that you or the sewer?!
It turns out it
wasn't a boil they removed
but the vestiges
of my unborn twin!
OK, let's just go.
(ALL) Yeah! Good idea!
Best idea I've
heard all day!
OK, here's something interesting.
There's a gigantic bear out there!
Don't worry. It's
part of living in Alaska.
How far away is it?
(GROWLING / CRASHING)
Well, answer the question!
(DOORBELL)
It's open!
I thought we were
having lunch today.
Huh? Oh, I'm sorry.
What's all this?
My research on the trial
Lois got assigned to.
Oh, my God! Reyes?! Did she talk
about the four-fingered magician?
Was he any good?
She won't tell me anything.
I dug this up on my own. Information
is being suppressed from the jury.
Lois will have to find Moynihan
guilty. Why not? He did it.
You're a fool! Everyone
knows the wife killed him.
What? She loved him.
Didn't you read the letter?
How come she didn't admit
being married before?
She was underage
and it was annulled.
It means nothing. The
judge ruled it inadmissible.
The same judge that won't allow
the cab driver to testify! Well,
if the wife did it, why did
four witnesses say they saw a man
leave the crime scene?
Oh! A man...
..like this?!
You just drew hair on!
If I could do
it, she could!
She worked for two years
at the Windmill Theatre.
Let me see that!
OK, here's our mark.
When we came here with Francis,
this is the farthest
we've ever gone. This is it?!
This is as far as you went?!
Who would brag about this?
Mr Alligator?
So, Stevie,
did your mom go
to college? What?!
Did she get a degree?
Was she in a sorority?
Wait a minute. Unless we thought
some girl called Molly Hatchet ruled,
this isn't our mark.
This has to be it!
We went right, right, straight,
left, right, left, and right again.
No! We went right, left, left,
then straight, left, right, straight!
No. We went...
..right,...
..left,...
..straight...
Oh, man, we're lost!
What? No! Oh, man!
What are we gonna do?!
Nice! We got him crying!
No, we really are lost!
What? What do we do?! I knew you'd
find some way to ruin this for me!
Even when you're trying to
be nice, you make me miserable!
And now... I get
to die in the sewer!
A perfect end to a
crappy life! Shut up, Dewey!
Alright. Let's focus
on finding a way out.
Stevie's mom must
be worried by now.
Shut up... about... my mom!
What? I simply made a
comment. You're... a perv!
I have a healthy interest
in the opposite sex.
Well,... they
don't... return... the favour!
What does that mean?
Girls... hate you.
That's not true!
Yes, it is.
Come on, Reese. You're a joke.
Yeah. Even I know it.
.
Marty claims he was at work,
but his boss says
he didn't show up until 6:00.
The gas-station attendant puts
Marty there between 4:00 and 4:30,
and as we remember from
testimony - Can we vote again?!
We've been through this
five times! We vote guilty,
she votes not guilty. We vote
not guilty, she votes guilty.
Yeah. So you go first
this time! Alright! I abstain.
(ALL GROAN) What is
it that you want, lady?
I want you to do your job!
Weigh the facts of this case
and make a reasoned decision!
You have the sworn testimony
of the arresting officer,
in which he states -
Yeah, if you believe
what he says. OK! Fair enough.
It is a question of credibility.
You have a high-school dropout
with a history of reckless behaviour
against a police-force veteran.
You can't trust cops. They're always
comin' up with ways to get you!
That's right! My neighbour's a cop
and he's got a 30-foot boat.
How can he afford that
on a police salary?
They all get away with it!
(ALL TALK AT ONCE)
Stop!
This is not about
how you feel about cops!
This is not about who
you like and who you hate!
This is about what you believe
happened, based on the facts.
Did Marty or did Marty not
steal the motorcycle?!
Wait,... I thought
Marty was the cop!
Fine(!)
Let's go through this again.
Yes? Is it OK to
hate you? Absolutely.
But the money was really being
funnelled to Mr Reyes's mistress
and their love child.
Once Moynihan found out,
it was "Good night, Mr Reyes".
You've... got... nothing!
He was seen arguing with the victim.
He can't account for his whereabouts
when the murder occurred, and they
found the murder weapon in his car!
Means, motive
and opportunity!
It's all a little too neat!
Because he's guilty!
My gut says he didn't do it!
Saying so doesn't make it so!
Talk to this guy!
YOU'RE AN IDIOT!
(CRASHING) Oh, my God,
that thing's a monster!
I've been around bears 40 years.
There's nothing to worry about.
Really? Yep! We just
got to stay real quiet.
Pretty soon he'll get bored
and fly away,...
..that is, unless
he's protecting his eggs.
This is crazy!
We can't stay here!
Somebody's got to
make a run for the truck.
That's a suicide mission!
Well, what are we supposed to do?
Stay here and starve to death?
He's right. I say we try it.
I vote for Eric. What?!
Go to hell! I'm not going! You go!
I have a wife at home!
And my life doesn't mean anything?
Artie's the camp outcast. Pete's an
old coot! It's a miracle he's alive!
I should've slit your throat
when I had the chance.
(ALL YELL)
This all looks... the same!
Yes, this is the same.
It's all been exactly the same
ever since the day I was born.
I start to trust them,
they make me regret it. I get
my hopes up and they destroy them.
I -
Shut up! We get it!
Every girlfriend you ever had left
you crying like a baby! What?!
Oh, who's Mr Big Shot now?
I'm a joke with the girls, huh?
What's worse, being
a joke or a crybaby?
I wasn't crying that hard!
You wet... your pants. Oh, like
you've ever even been with a girl!
I have... a note... from my doctor!
I could get a doctor if I wanted to.
THAT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE SENSE!
That's right!
Turn on each other.
Well, you know what?
No girls like any of you.
And I don't blame them.
You're all pathetic.
You know who's a
joke? Girls! Yeah!
They make our lives miserable. You
can never understand what they want.
They always say, "Stop staring."
They don't laugh at farts!
They only wanna talk about clothes.
They cry... all... the time.
Man, this is helping us get out(!)
(FRANTIC PANTING)
Whoo! Time? Time?!
11 minutes.
(SHRIEKS TRIUMPHANTLY)
In yer face! See?
The wife did have time
to run down here from home!
That leaves her...
two minutes to stab him,
remove the head, and still make it to
the party in time. It makes sense!
And the blood magically
jumped to his clothes(!)
Do you really
need this spelled out?
After killing her husband,
she took off the bloody suit
and rubbed it all
over Moynihan! Impossible!
You just don't wanna be
proven wrong! I am not wrong!
The knife entered at a downward
angle. She was 5'2". He was 6'4".
She'd have had to ask him to pick
her up so she could stab him!
She could've stood on something!
Oh, she brought
a stepladder(!)
Look! A milk crate! She could've
hidden behind the dumpster,
stood on the crate, pulled out the
knife and stabbed him several times
with a downward
motion, like this! (SCREAMING)
Agh!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
I may be fat, stupid,
colour-blind and dyslexic,
but I don't have three nipples!
Shut up! That's a mole.
You! Your family changed their name
so you couldn't track them down.
No-one will miss you.
I'm sure it started with an O.
All three of you
are pea-brained idiots!
And I do suffer more than
everybody else. (GROANS)
Let's just vote on it!
Who votes for Francis?
Who votes for Eric?
Artie?
Pete?
Four votes! No,
you tricked me! Argh!
He'll reject me!
I... I've tried me!
I taste awful! Arrgh!
Alright,... that's the worst thing
any of us has ever done.
I'm not proud, but we had no choice.
Like I care about your opinion!
Wait a minute.
Why don't we hear eating?
(ENGINE ROARS) He got to the truck!
Pete!
Pete! Pete!
See you in hell!
(SOUND OF ENGINE RECEDES)
The witness saw Marty gassing up the
motorcycle an hour after the theft.
That gas station closes at 5:00. Not
on Fridays. That's in the transcript.
Er, I think we're ready for
another vote! Lois?
Go ahead. By show of hands,
who thinks the defendant is guilty?
Great! Let's go
tell the judge. Wait!
I don't think
Marty is guilty. What?!
I went through all these papers.
The kid sings in a church choir.
He wouldn't do something like this.
That is not fact. That's bias.
You're basing a decision on feelings
that have nothing to do with facts!
Facts are things, like witnesses
seeing Marty steal the bike,
like Marty being apprehended
while he was driving it!
Like Marty pulling tons of stupid
stunts just like this one.
Those are the facts. I just don't
wanna send that poor boy to jail!
Believe me, jail will do more good
than three years of military school.
Military school? I
didn't read anything about that.
Oh, yeah! I know I
saw that somewhere.
He dropped out of
vocational school.
After the school where he got caught
messing with the teacher's aid.
No, I know for a fact
that Francis went -
Who?
Oh, my God!
I think I have to excuse myself
from this jury. All in favour?
I'm trying to be
the best me I can be,
but I don't know what to say to
girls, so I say something mean.
I'm afraid of
getting hurt. My problem is,
I get so frustrated
over things I can't control.
I forget people have
their own will. I play...
..mind games.
It's all... I have.
Why isn't there ever a
flash flood when you need one?
I really want a girlfriend.
I want somebody to hang out with!
Yeah. Someone
you can talk to.
Someone... to hug.
Someone to show my poetry to.
You write... poetry?
I dabble. What do you
think of Brenda Pollock?
She's nice. She'd be good for you.
You'd make... a cute couple.
I thought so, too.
Hey, I know this sounds weird,
but can I read you one
of my poems? We'd love it.
ARGH! AGH!
(ALL SCREAM)
(ALL) Aaaargh!
(ALL CONTINUE TO SCREAM)
(GIGGLING)
Hey! What happened?
Did you read them your poetry?
(GIRLS CONTINUE TO GIGGLE)
You guys can't
even do this right!
I wanna serve on another jury!
I messed up this time,
but next time I won't.
I don't schedule that.
I'm sure you have
connections. Please!
There was a mistrial. Everything's
backed up. You'll have to wait.
I'll do the best I can, if you'll
stop bothering me right now.
Deal! I gotta go. My husband's
probably going crazy without me!
IMS Subtitles
www.tvsubtitles.net