.
Reese has had the remote
for four hours.
That's four hours of mindless crap
in five second increments.
You go to the bathroom,
you lose the remote! Fine.
I can wait.
I dunno. You drank a lot of soda.
It must really be pressing
on your bladder. Not gonna work.
THEN I had four glasses
of Dad's iced tea.
He just kept POURING and POURING.
Not gonna work.
The equivalent of 3 semi-trailers
of water pour over the falls every
second.
Not gonna work.
(LOUD SLURPING)
Not...
gonna...
..work!
Turns out this is way better
than anything on TV.
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
Alright, turn it, turn
it, turn it, turn it...
NO! Too far. Go back! Back,
back, back, back, back, back.
THERE THERE THERE there! Just
three more inches clockwise and...
Wh-wh-wh-whoa, whoa! easy...
Back a coupla degrees, steady..
YES! Perfect! Haha!
Oh.
These needles are going against
the grain. That'll be ALL I'll see!
Don't move!
Spend a couple of days with Grandma.
You can leave right after Christmas!
I am NOT visiting that woman!
She's EVIL and she HATES me!
Francis, it's Grandma's first
Christmas since Grandpa died
and you're closest.
How can you be so selfish?
Did you invite her there?
She's knows she's always welcome.
Maybe we'll come and surprise you.
Don't you threaten ME!
I am ending this discussion!
You are going to White Horse.
You are going to buy her a gift.
You will both have
a proper Christmas!
(LAUGHTER / SMASH!)
I hate you!
Get this off of me,
you stupid son of a-
BOYS!
Dewey asked us to do it!
What is wrong with you?!
The tree is barely in the door
and already you're starting...
I can't leave you alone
for a second without you
trying to kill each other!
This is supposed to be
a HAPPY TIME!
I dunno what it is, but
Mom freaks out every Christmas.
(CHEERY CHRISTMAS SONGS ON HI-FI)
Ho ho ho!
Who did this?!
Drop and roll, honey! Who did this?!
For God's sakes, drop and roll!
Maybe it's the lack of sunlight.
That can mess with people's brains.
Hi, Grandma.
Oh, sh...
God sake's, it's colder in here.
Don't you turn the heat on?
I'm not paying those
pirates. Of course not.
Well, in the spirit of the season,
let's begin this pathetic charade.
I never know what you're talking
about. You talk like a jackass.
(CRUNCH!)
(# CARD PLAYS JINGLE BELLS)
You do this to torture me, hurt me?!
You don't like Christmas music?
It sounds like a song they sang
when they rode through villages
throwing babies on the fire!
They sang Jingle Bells?
They sang something.
Well, look at that - 8pm already.
Way past bedtime. Where do I sleep?
You're sittin' on it.
Does it turn into a bed?
Yes, it becomes a bed.
It's a special magic sofa(!)
It opens up for
magic lazy boy(!)
The angels come and feed you grapes
and sing to you while you sleep.
It flies around the room granting
wishes for boys what are STUPID!
Alright, it doesn't fold out(!)
Can I look yet?
Just... a minute.
Hey, this is from BOTH of us!
I picked it out. I stepped in it!
HEY!
Hey...
(LAUGHING / CRASHING)
Gotcha!
Mom. How nice
to see you home.
I HAVE HAD IT!
What are you doing?
I am taking everything!
Every present, decoration and treat
and locking it in the garage.
Every single Christmas,
you burn or break or destroy,
AND I AM PUTTING A STOP TO IT!
She's stealing Christmas!
You can't do this!
It's the last year Dewey
will believe in Santa. What?!
If you boys behave until
Christmas morning, there will BE
a Christmas morning.
Otherwise, these go back
to the store
and Christmas
will be cancelled!
You wouldn't cancel
Christmas. You're bluffing.
(LOUD SOBBING)
You cancelled Christmas?!
No, I'm holding it hostage.
It seems harsh but
nothing else has ever worked.
Every year we yell and
threaten, bargain and beg...
Maybe this time they'll behave.
We're in this together.
I'm playing the unity card.
Bu- Unity card, Hal!
But... I love
Christmas...!
I know you do, dear.
Is there anything
that trumps the unity card?
Hal?
(CLICK)
I really think we
can win this 'Nam thing.
That's not for you.
That's for the carollers.
(HACKING COUGH)
You ruin smoking for me.
You sound like you're dying.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?!
You can't wait to get my things.
Yeah(!) I got big plans
for these doilies(!)
And that 30-year-old can of
peaches. Don't touch my peaches!
Like I'm gonna...
(CAROL SINGERS APPROACH)
(COUGHS)
Stop that racket!
People are trying to sleep!
Your stupid music!
No figgy pudding for you!
Please pass the syrup, please.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
More coffee? Please.
I'll get it, Mom! It's OK.
I hope you'll let us wash
the dishes. Love to. Absolutely.
Now, THAT I'll
take you up on.
We can do this. It's Christmas Eve
and we've behaved for 10 hours.
OK, eight were asleep,
but we can do another 24, right?
Who wants the last waffle?
I do! I do! I do!
Oh, no...!
You know, I would
really like that waffle.
Yes, but I am a growing boy. Perhaps
it would be best if I had the waffle
Thanks for offering it to me, boys.
They're such good boys.
.
Introducing new Dove Supreme
Cream Oil
Shower Velvet.
I tried it.
It was a really
lovely sensation.
It made me feel like velvet
was covering my skin.
Like a "me" moment.
Our richest cream
with lush softening oil
in new Dove Supreme Cream
Oil Shower Luscious Velvet.
Go on, get your
own little luxury.
.
(ACCORDION MUSIC ON TV)
(# JINGLE BELLS)
(# JINGLE BE-)
(# JINGLE BEL-)
AARGHH! God, what the hell's
wrong with you?!
You like pushing me? That's what
happens when you push, tough guy!
Can't you do the entire
family a favour and DIE!
All you've ever done
is treat us like dirt.
You shouldn't be ALLOWED to be
a Grandma! Are you finished? YES!
Yes, I... AAARRGGGGHHHHH, GOD...!
Oh, I am SO sorry...!
I should've kissed your boo-boos
and made dem better.
I was supposed to tell
the bad little boy stories
and bake you giant sugar cookies
and knit you fluffy sweaters,
carried you and held you, and told
you how much I loved your diapers.
Why don't you just unhinge your jaw
and finish me off? After Magnum PI.
Lois! I'm home!
Honey, look, I saw something
and I just HAD to get it for you.
It's a little more than we agreed
to spend on each other
but - hey, it's Christmas! -
we got a whole year to follow rules!
It's beautiful..!
I mean, isn't that what
the season is all about?
Relaxing, enjoying things,
making people happy.
Hal, that's so
sweet and thoughtful.
I hope I get to open it.
Rats!
You're doin' it all wrong.
You've seven ornaments, I'm putting
them on your tree - what's wrong?
Go get the angel off
the - hic! - mantel.
Who's this?
That is your grandfather
when he was - hic! - young man.
Euch! Tell me that eyebrow
isn't genetic(!)
You and him. Both the same.
Always had to
have your own way.
Nothing ever good enough.
Always had to fight everything.
Victor always had to be
SO independent.
Left home when he was 11,
lived on his own,
go to work on farm,
ploughin' the fields.
Like a man. Worked 18 hours a day.
Had to sleep with the pigs.
But he never complained.
He was strong.
He made something of himself.
Nobody like that anymore.
Everybody's too soft.
Hey, Grandma, why don't
you let me help you with that?
Your grandfather was tough!
He didn't take anything
from anybody.
He was... proud.
A man of... honour.
He was a wonderful,...
..wonderful man.
(MUMBLES IN RUSSIAN)
Grandma?
Grandma? Oh!
Oh, God!
Just one more night.
We can get through one night!
We should be proud. Everything's
put away.
And not a single fight.
We did it! We're
going to get presents?
We're gonna get presents.
What do we do now?
We could take a nap?
Or play quietly.
VERY quietly.
(SQUEAKS)
(GASPS)
SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
Oh, God... I will be so glad
when Christmas is over!
Then we'll be safe for another year.
Mom's doing this NEXT Christmas?!
Why not? It worked, didn't it?
And maybe not just Christmas!
What? She could do it for Halloween
or Fourth of July or birthdays?!
She can't do this! I can't
take any more!
We have to stop her!
Something drastic.
I'm in.
Mom needs to know she
can't take occasions hostage.
That we DON'T negotiate!
She turned a BEAUTIFUL
family holiday into a nightmare.
We'll show her the
TRUE spirit of Christmas.
First, you mustn't think
of this as Christmas cider.
It's a non-denominational
winter cider.
The boys are doing
so well... (GROANS)
Lois?
I'm a terrible mother!
I shouldn't be
allowed to have children.
Sweetie...
I've ruined Christmas!
Whaddaya mean? The boys are behaving
like I never knew they could!
I thought that's what you
wanted. But not like this!
I wanted to take it back five
minutes after I took the presents
but I didn't know how!
I'M A MONSTER! No,
you're not a monster...!
I am. I really am.
No, you're not a monster.
WHY WON'T YOU ADMIT I'M A MONSTER?!
Alright, in this particular case,
you're a monster. I know...!
(WAILS)
(PHONE RINGS)
Let the machine get it.
Come on...! You know
when you cry it makes me cry.
You are a WONDERFUL mother.
And you're a wonderful person.
(BEEP)
"Hey, Mom. Francis. I am DISGUSTED
with how you treat Grandma!"
"Abandoning a helpless old woman at
Christmas? I hope you're ASHAMED!"
I am... I am.
Hal, the boys
don't deserve this.
They're a little high-spirited,
but they're GOOD, GOOD boys!
God, this feels so right!
This is WAY better
than real Christmas!
Remember, mess 'em up just enough
so Mom can't return them.
Wait a minute... Mom got me
the exact video game I asked for.
These are better
than what I asked for.
You know what?
Mom got me everything I wanted.
Me, too.
She listened to us. OK,
so she got lucky a few times.
I never asked
for a stupid globe!
That's mine.
The cleats are yours. Oh.
Mom really tried this year.
All she wanted was a nice Christmas.
And we ruined it.
In all fairness,
we ruin everything.
Remember, how happy we were
a minute ago. Can we go back?
I dunno.
Do we have any
paint left? No.
Oh, well...
What are you doing?
Doin' you a favour, so
why not shut up and enjoy it.
What is this? Oh, you don't wanna
look in there, it's too sad.
Grandma, what are
all these things?
There must be a
thousand dollars
worth of stuff
in here. $2,735.
$4500 Canadian.
Why are they in your
closet? They're gifts.
For the family, for
relatives, for friends...
But you never give... Oh, my God!
Donatello with pizza-throwing
action?!
I wanted one of these when I was
six! I know. I bought it for you.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
And then, right before Christmas,
your mommy put you on the phone
you call me "Poopy" and hung up.
Is that the breadmaker
Mom wanted last year?
If she wants bread so much
she should write back when
her mother writes to her.
This was for cousin Nicola.
I spent a day
shopping for it.
Then she marries a Protestant.
That camera? For your father.
Then he refused to drive me
to the liquor store.
All the nice things I do for people.
Oh, my god, you're crazy!
I just thought you were evil,
but you are nuts!
What are you talking about?
Grandma, gifts aren't conditional.
You give them to people
because you love them!
They're not something you can take
away because of some petty slight!
You're not teaching people anything
They don't KNOW they've upset you!
You've just constructed
a monument to your insanity!
WHAT SORT OF PERSON DOES THAT?
A lonely,...
..bitter,... old woman.
What?
Look what I've done.
What use is all
this to me now?
They could have brought someone some
happiness. Instead they rot here.
Oh... Grandma?
My hea... heart.
I think it's... melting.
Yes...
It's melting. Oh...
You showed me the way,
Francis, by yelling at me.
Go get my magic sled and me and my
reindeers will go and give Christmas
to all the mean, stupid,
rude people!
We'll all join
hands and sing songs
and we'll sprinkle the
ingrates with fairy dust!
Are you sure you
wanna do this? Yes!
I mean, taking
presents away from children?!
What sort of sick
person does that?!
Let's get everything out of
the garage and set it up inside
and have a nice Christmas!
You know what?
Let's wake up the boys
and have Christmas tonight!
Imagine their
little faces...!
Well, Hal,... that was...
..smart of you...
to wake up the boys...
..so they could help us
carry in the presents.
Yes, yes...
C-come on... hurry up, boys.
Yeah... Sure...
OK...
(# JINGLE BELLS)
I'll cut off his hands and stick
them in his kakushnik!
(# JINGLE BELLS CONTINUES)
(# JINGLE BEL...)
(JINGLE BELLS
HEARD OUTSIDE)
You're a klebleck!
(CHEERY CHRISTMAS MUSIC)
Oh, roller skates!
I hope you like 'em, sweetie!
I think we have another present here
for Reese! I wonder what it is?!
This really is the best
Christmas we've ever had!
I dunno why we didn't try this whole
denial thing a long time ago.
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
BELL
CROWD NOISE/CHEERING
Make your
skin feel:
Skin Contact.
BELL
www.tvsubtitles.net