'I agree, Mrs Wiggins.
These pastries are delightful.'
Son, whatcha doing? I'm having a tea
party with Mrs Bear and the ladies.
Oh, that's... good.
Care to join us?
Yeah, I have...
actually,... a...
Why don't we go buy that stealth
bomber model you've been asking for?
OK.
Sometimes it's
just too easy.
# Yes, no, maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
Want to camp in front of PC World?
The Norton anti-virus is out.
Your mom let you?
She's there now!
Are you serious? What's the big deal?
We have a life outside this place.
How are we doing, gentlemen?
Everyone sticking to the experiment?
Absolutely. Right on track, sir.
I know how tempting it is...
..to stray from a
rigidly defined protocol.
It's the siren's song
of pure research
but you must resist
her seductive powers because...
(ALL) Unstable compounds
require stable minds.
Jackass. It's like
he's talking to children.
It was a legitimate variation.
There was less than
a 48% chance this would happen.
Well, your cavalier disregard
for the laws of the classroom,
not to mention the laws of nature,
have led to the inevitable.
It will now take weeks
to decontaminate that classroom.
During that time, you'll be placed
back into the general population.
(ALL GASP) We can't do that.
The whole school hates us.
They'll destroy us!
Rage is a projection
of their own insecurities.
And as for me... I've been
offered a temporary position
in the phys ed department
where I'll get to wear a whistle...
..and dress in shorts!
I'm sure none of this will
be reflected in your grades(!)
Don't play connect the dots
with your chickenpox.
You'll get an
infection. I'm bored!
I know. It's no fun being sick.
I'm bored! I'm itchy! I'm bored!
Honey, remember we were gonna use
our not-horrible voice? I'm bored!
Then find something to do! Here.
Play with these.
I don't wanna.
You will be contagious for six days.
Want to spend them here,
like a good boy, or in the hospital?
You don't go to the hospital
for chick... OK.
Damn it! Maybe we
could tack up a blanket.
I'll tear the porch down
and build another one.
Good luck getting permission
from the council. What?
Part of the house is on tribal land,
from the window to the wolf picture.
What? The whole house
used to be on the reservation,
but my idiot grandfather
built it on a glacier.
It moves two inches a year. In
100 years, we'll have a lake view.
Wow. So, part of this house
is on an Indian reservation?
Dealer has 20.
Look at them. All they're
thinking about is how many places
they'll dispose of my body.
Hey, Ian, Eddie!
How are you doing?
What are you doing?
There's no more seats.
There's a seat over there.
Scoot over. Go sit down.
You're gonna get in trouble.
Hey! Hey!
Wassup? Wassup?
God, it's so great
to have a normal conversation.
Abandon all hope,
ye who enter here.
Is that from the new
Ministry album? What?
Abandon all hope. Is that
from the new Ministry album?
Actually, it's
from Dante's Inferno.
It's the inscription over
the gates of hell. That is way dark.
Kick that guy's butt!
Remember when I did?
No, he kicked your butt!
You want me to kick your butt?!
Argh! Damn! A splinter!
You are dead! You are dead! Argh!
Don't pick! It
will get infected. What?
You're making it worse. Let me
get it. You carry a first-aid kit?
Just a crisis pouch.
I leave the kit in my locker.
There. Wow! That
didn't hurt at all!
Thanks.
Hey, Dewey. Wow! Look at that!
Is this helping take your mind
off the itching? It was.
Oh, you've got a split
and you've got a crossover.
All those dominoes.
All set up.
Just ready to...
Hey! Check out Alesha.
En fuego.
Totally.
Yeah, she's cute.
Check out Pam.
Muy en fuego.
Totally!
Yeah, she's cute, too.
Excuse me.
(RAP MUSIC)
Hey, Stevie. It looks like
everyone found a place.
Parasites adapting
to a new host body.
Except Herkabe, I guess.
We heard the cleanup crew's gonna
put their dumpster where we skate.
Where are we supposed to go?
Why do they pick on us?
Damn Krelboynes.
I'll think of something.
Hey, Malcolm. Can you
settle this? You know Stacy?
Yeah. Is she en
fuego or muy en fuego?
Hard to say.
My God! Dewey!
Look what you've built here!
You have stairs and a ramp!
You've spelled your name.
Oh, so many,...
..many dominoes.
Where did they
all come from?
From the Lippers. They got a crate
the year Mr Lipper was paralysed.
They even buried him
with one of his dominoes.
So this isn't really a complete set.
Oh, no, Dewey, don't scratch.
It's itchy! I know, but sometimes
you just have to restrain yourself.
Even if you feel like ripping
your eyes out of their sockets
rather than go one more second
without... scratching.
Will you watch this for me? I have
to go to the bathroom. OK, son.
Reese! Don't even think
about it! What's going on?
He was about to knock down
Dewey's dominoes. What?
I didn't do anything.
You're not going to.
They're keeping Dewey from driving
my crazy! If they get knocked over,
I'll blame you. If a door slams and
knocks them over, I'll blame you.
If a condor dies in flight,
crashes through our roof and knocks
them over, I'll blame you!
But that's not fair.
I will blame you!
Don't. What?
I saw that look.
What look? My look!
Now I know where I got it from.
I have no idea what you're talking
about. I'm gonna get a drink.
Let's go.
I can get it myself.
It's alright.
HIP-HOP MUSIC
HIP-HOP COMBINES
WITH LATIN MUSIC
Mixed up flavours.
Extra fusion, extra fun.
Fact - most cleaners remove
dirt but could leave bacteria.
One bacteria could become
two million overnight.
So some things
that look clean...
aren't.
Dettol next
generation
All in 1 is unbeatable at
cutting through tough grease,
and powers through soap scum.
But, unlike ordinary cleaners,
it kills 99.9%
of bacteria,
leaving surfaces
clean and safe.
Dettol All in 1.
You're two
clicks away
from the new shape
of lip colour.
Infallible colour
lasts up to 16 hours,
even after
eating.
The conditioning balm
helps lock in moisture.
Brilliant!
In ten radiant shades.
Colour that's made
to stay on your lips...
And only on your lips.
Infallible?
It's my lip colour.
The lip duo
compact
that lasts
up to 16 hours.
Because you're worth it.
It's important to help protect
my skin from the sun.
And I want to keep it
feeling firmer too.
L'Oreal Solar Expertise
Collagen Sun Protection.
Our first anti-ageing,
firming sun cream
that helps protect
against premature skin ageing.
It helps my skin look
younger and feel firmer.
Yes to summer,
no to premature
skin ageing.
Because you're worth it.
Man, I can't believe the school gave
the skaters our basketball court!
Skaters safety program.
Sounds suspicious. So what do we do?
We kick their butts! Guys!
Guys! There's an easier way.
We'll take over the east court.
No, that's where the Goths hang out.
Why don't you let me
worry about the Goths?
They can't take our court!
That's where I second-hand smoke!
Some old lady complained
we were scaring her.
No, you weren't. Look at this
handwriting, the girlish swirls.
This is no old
lady. It's Dabney.
Well, where are we supposed to go
now? What about the posers' corner?
You're trippin' if
you think you'll stop us!
This is our turf now! We're in the
middle of a student council meeting.
That ain't no thang. Thang is 200
years of oppression in this country.
What are you talking about? It's off
the hook. Justice in the hole, too.
You haven't heard
the last of this!
Sucker!
Um, Kevin,... you're supposed
to wear underwear with those.
(ALL ARGUE)
Don't make me blow this!
Do not make me blow this!
Who removed my whistle pea?!
That is a detentionable offence!
It's awfully tempting, isn't, Hal?
Go ahead. I'll
blame it on Reese.
You'll get off scot-free.
Alright! Pencils down!
Turn in your geometry tests.
But I didn't study!
Turn around, old man.
There's nothing for you here.
I can't take this any more.
If I hear one more en fuego...
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
..and six on top for the dealer.
Whoops! Free deal.
Hey! I had blackjack!
You're cheating me out of
my winnings! Come on. Relax.
I don't want trouble.
It's all in the tribe, right?
Let's just calm down.
I don't wanna hear it.
It's what your
old man used to pull.
He was nothing but a lying jackass!
Tell me something I don't know.
This was just a misunderstanding.
There. You got your chips back.
See? We take care
of our own, here.
Francis, maybe you should - I'll
turn the fan on once Ivan leaves.
Dewey? I spoke with the doctor. He
says you can go to school tomorrow.
OK. Tomorrow?
So the dominoes...
Go back in the
crate tonight!
Let me make this easy. I'm not
leaving until I know you're at work
and I can wait all day.
All I've got is school.
Hey, Malcolm! I'm sorry. I can't
listen to you talk about who's hot.
This stuff used to sound fine to me,
but now it's stupid! You are stupid!
I don't mean that in an insulting
way. I mean that in a factual way.
You wanna say hot in a different
language? There are 700 languages!
Vary it a little! We came to tell you
a fight's going down at the school.
Between who?
Everybody. Oh, man!
Hey, come on,
dealer. Let's go!
And that's seven for the dealer.
Piama, where have
you been? Shopping.
You were supposed to relieve me. Do
you know what time it is? Now I do.
Where did you get the money?
I took $200 from the stash!
But that's all our money! We can't
afford that! It's all in the tribe.
Ha!
Huh?
Wha...? Wha...?!
What happened?
I cleaned them up.
You knocked them
over?! Without me?!
Why would I knock them over?
I spent four days setting them up.
What's going on? Why did you
spend all of that money?! Hey!
You talked about
easing our people's suffering.
I suffered a little less today.
You don't spend money
and not say anything.
What's the problem?
It's all in the tribe, right?
That's what this is about?
Am I overstepping my bounds
because I'm white? No, but it's...
It feels weird.
Look, we're married.
That means I'm part of your family
just like you're a part of mine.
If I had anything in my
heritage besides mini vans
and non-stop screaming,
I'd share it. It's not the same!
Because I'm not your people,
I don't deserve that money?!
Why are you so obsessed
about the money?! Because!
I wanna pay Lavernia so we can go!
What do you mean?
We live here! What?!
You want to spend your life
in this godforsaken place?
This godforsaken place
is where I grew up! It's our home!
You should have
said something!
I have been
complaining about this place!
I thought you were a complainer!
You complain about everything.
Yeah, but this is real.
I hate this place!
I can't even imagine raising
our kids here! Kids?! I hate kids!
These seem like some
pretty big issues. Yeah.
You know, we got
married so fast...
So what are we gonna do?
We both like wrestling movies.
Yeah, and we both like pizza.
I love pizza! Sausage and
mushroom? Yeah,... on half.
We wait till the jocks take out
the Goths and then we swoop in.
I made an alliance
with the drama club.
When the skaters see me
drop my cape, they'll come in.
No-one'll expect us to be working
together. Is this a good idea?
It's too late for second thoughts.
The tribes have Balkanised.
(SIGHS) They don't
like each other. Oh, right.
We don't stop until
we have total control.
Deploy special shield.
(CHANT) We're just right,
we're OK,
we're smarter
now than yesterday!
School is fun,
cos learning is for everyone.
They've got Derek.
He bites. No! Stop!
This has gone too far. Look what
you've been reduced to! I'm helping!
We all used to hate this school
equally! We hated the teachers!
We hated the administration!
We hated the building!
But now you've taken that hate
and turned it against each other!
And why? Because people dress
differently or talk differently?!
You're just making school even worse!
Dabney was a Krelboyne two weeks ago.
Now he's a jock! That proves that
these differences are meaningless.
We need to focus on what makes us the
same, because if we hate each other,
who's gonna hate school?
You were a Krelboyne?
Ha! You've got a Krelboyne!
You guys got one right behind you!
He's the one who wanted
to fight in the first place!
Hey, we got one, too!
I found one!
He's our leader!
(WHIMPERING)
If it's any consolation, we get
our new classroom in five weeks.
(ALL SOB)
Thanks for the heads-up
on the underwear. No problem.
What is with the self-pity?! Albert
Einstein had to carry spare pants
until he was 24 and
did he cry about it? No.
He drew on that experience and
helped build the first nuclear bomb.
Now buck up and
get in the van.
Oh, video camera!
IMS Subtitles
www.tvsubtitles.net