(CLUNK)
Whoa! Hmmmmm!
(DRAWER SQUEAKS)
(RATTLES)
(SIGHS)
(CAR CHUGS)
Hal, did you replace that bulb?
What does it look like I'm doing?!
# Yes no maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question?
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
Here we are, Bernard.
This is my cage.
Are you serious?
(WHISPERS) Mom? Dad?
This is Bernard,
the hamster from my class.
It's my weekend to take care
of him. This isn't a good time.
I want you to see how good
I am at taking care of him,
and how good I'd be
at taking care of a dog.
Did I mention that all
the other kids have dogs?
Honey, your father
and I need to talk.
I saw a nice one at the pet store
and I could name him Jeff and -
Go play in your room!
OK.
I'll put your cage
right here, Bernard.
Sorry I said I wanted
a dog in front of you.
Is your brain big enough
to get your feelings hurt?
Me neither. I'll
take good care of you.
Bernard?
(SQUEAK! SQUEAK!)
I thought you were getting a routine
check-up. That's when they find it.
Can't they do anything?
Not until they get the biopsy back.
There you are.
(SQUEAK! SQUEAK!)
You can't call that a short cut!
It has to be shorter! Says who?!
Says the word! It's just when
you don't use regular streets.
If it took 150 years
to cross the street,
as long as you went through some
bushes, that'd be a short cut?!
You hate being wrong.
Hi, Mom. Hi, Dad.
What is wrong with you?
Look at that floor! Oh, sorry.
How many times have I said
don't track mud into this house?
We'll clean it up. Not good enough!
You're grounded for a week!
What? You can't do that!
Want it to be two weeks? Dad!
You heard your mother. This is
ridiculous! You're being unfair!
Just because Malcolm got mud on his
shoes and tracked it in the house
doesn't mean he should be
grounded. Go to your room now!
What's her problem? They're so boring
they invent stuff to be upset about.
Are you the biggest idiot
to ever walk this Earth?
Good morning. What did
I tell you to do, jackass?
Paint the kitchen, which I'm doing.
What kind of a moron
paints it white?
Wanna see all the dirt?
What'd they teach you in college?
I'm a high school dropout and I
used the paint that you left for me.
I moved that paint so you
could get to the green, idiot.
Do it over, even if
you're here all night! What?
That paint you wasted is
coming out of your pay.
I should paint it
the colour of your dye job.
What?
He didn't say anything.
I said maybe I should paint it
the same colour as your dye job,
you sagging, leathery,
hatchet-faced, dried-up old hag.
Alright, college boy, you want it?
You got it! I'm gonna kick your ass!
Excuse me? I'm kickin' your ass.
Don't ever disrespect me like that.
You can't challenge her to a fight.
I didn't challenge anybody.
Hey, Lavernie's
fightin' college boy!
(CHEERS) We've got an opening
Sunday at two before Mass.
Sunday. Two o'clock.
Your ass, my foot.
There's no way
I'm fighting a woman!
If I don't mind, why
should you? Oooooo! (ALL LAUGH)
See what she did? She called him
a woman. It's gonna be a blood bath!
You're right, Dewey. When was
the last time we played ball?
I don't know.
Sometimes life gets away from you
and you forget the things
that are really important.
AAARGH!! Egh!
This is crazy. I have enough on my
mind without worrying about you!
But, Mom - Don't leave this room.
I don't want to see or hear you.
I don't want to sense your presence.
For crying out loud, Reese,
there's a mirror right there!
Believe me, I am going
to watch that door like a hawk.
What's her problem?
This can't be about mud.
Something's going on.
What've you done lately?
The Richardsons' fire, the
windshield, the Sampsons' fire,
the Jacksons' fire. Nothing
she knows about. This sucks!
Well, if you can't do the time,
don't do the crime. See ya Monday.
Hey, moron, do you know what tomorrow
night is? Christine Matson's party!
That's this weekend? Yeah, and
her sister's bringing her friends.
They tongue kiss
whether they like you or not!
It's shaking hands to them. It's
a cultural thing. We have to go!
Reese, if I show
you a way we can go,
do you promise never to let anyone
find out even though you're an idiot?
I swear.
OK.
I was saving this for a
life or death emergency...
..or a really good party.
Tell me!
No way. We're not hitting Mom
with that! Reese, tomorrow night,
we take out the floorboard and sneak
outside through the crawl space.
Wow. Tunnelling out of our own room.
She can't lock us in any more.
Mom's powerless. Yeah. Now she's
just a crazy old lady we live with.
Thanks, Dewey!
It's Dewey. Let's
hurt him, fellow idiot.
Yes. I hate him
for his handsomeness.
Aaaarrgh!
Hi, Dewey.
Hi, Lance.
Well, what do ya know?
It's Bernard. Let me see him.
You can't have him.
That's alright. I can wait.
Next week is my
turn to have him.
We're gonna have a lot of fun.
You can't keep the hamster.
He belongs to the class.
He won't be safe.
You take good care of him,
but you have to share him.
Lance isn't my friend.
He tore Billy's shirt off after
school and - (PHONE RINGS)
Hello? Yes! This is he.
He killed a frog
and brought it to school.
Dewey, I said no! Do you want to be
grounded like your brothers? No.
I've never seen her this worked up
for a fight. She's done this before?
Since I've been here,
she's fought five guys.
You're lucky you
got some warning.
Know Big Don?
The guy with one ear?
Yeah. He was going to the privvy
and she dropped on him like a spider.
What's wrong with her?
We were having a stupid argument.
How did it turn into a fight?
It's how we settle things.
There are three other
fights tomorrow. Four.
Ned cut in front of Daryl.
Well, I hate to disappoint you
but I'm not fighting Lavernia.
Really?
Are you sure?
No, he'll fight her.
No, I won't.
Thank you!
Fellas! It looks like we're having
a coward's cotillion. '(ALL CHEER)'
I'll get the dogs ready.
I'll sharpen the pig-sticker.
What are you talking about?
Fighting's the only entertainment
here. You've seen our TV reception.
If someone cheats the boys out of a
fight, there's a coward's cotillion.
What the hell is a coward's
cotillion? It's always different.
You never know what animal
the blood will attract.
My choices are to fight a woman
or the stupid cotillion thing?
Well,... there's always the...
..Howdy Stranger.
.
How can they make us wait
another 24 hours?
They're short-handed at the lab.
Don't they realise it's your life?
Don't worry. This is for
the best. I'm setting you free.
You won't have to worry
about anyone being mean any more.
Come on, Bernard.
Run. Run like the wind.
You have to do this, Bernard.
It's for your own good.
I'll be OK.
Go on! I don't
want you any more.
I don't like you. I never did!
Go on! Go on,
you dumb old hamster.
Bye, Bernard.
Booby trapped? A broom handle tied
to a string of tin cans. A classic.
If Mom trusted us, I think
she'd be pleasantly surprised.
Yeah. We're basically good kids.
She's so unreasonable.
Are you almost ready?
Just a sec. Will you come on?
If anyone asks,
I'm in junior college.
< (SCUFFLING)
Hi, boys.
You don't know how lucky
you are. Everything is new.
Everything is open to you. Please,
don't ever take that for granted.
Make every moment
the best you possibly can.
God, I am so proud of all of you.
You kids are the best thing
I've ever done.
You'll never know
how much I love you.
Maybe you're not
supposed to. (SNIFFS)
Sleep well, my
little angels.
(BOOM!)
Aaaaargh! Aaaaaarrrgghhh!
Aaaaaaarrgh!!
Aaaaaarrgh!!
'(BOTH SCREAM)'
Amazing! I made out with a sophomore.
I'm so far ahead of schedule.
Did you see the TV fly off
the roof into the pool? That was me.
I hope we get
grounded next weekend.
'(BOTH SCREAM)'
How dare you?! How
dare you defy us like that?!
We wouldn't have if you weren't so
hard over a little mud on the floor!
You two are the most ungrateful,
badly behaved, inconsiderate boys
ever born! How could you be
so heartless? What's heartless
about going to a party with
a bunch of slutty girls? Be cool.
You were at a party?! While we were
here worrying?! Can I have a napkin?
I cannot believe you two!
Alright. That's it!
You're grounded for the rest of
the school year! You can't do that!
You're crazy! You do not talk
to your mother that way ever!
You'll show her the love and respect
she deserves whether I'm here or
not!
This family sucks! You are ruining
our lives! I wish you were dead!
What was that all about? She usually
just says, "I'm taking you with me."
I want to tell you something.
We'll talk at two.
I'm gonna tell
you this right now.
I hate your guts. You're the most
horrible person I've ever met.
You are mean, sadistic, twisted and
spiteful. And I owe you an apology.
What I said was a cheap shot
about your looks
and you don't deserve that.
No-one deserves that.
You're right. Thank you.
What the hell are we doing this for
anyway? This won't solve anything.
We're just putting
on a show for idiots.
If you think you
have to prove something
because you're a woman,
you don't. You came and built
a successful business in this awful
place. You have accomplished plenty.
Oh, my God! You're
coming on to me! What?
Peddle your sugar to somebody else,
cos this bee ain't buyin'. What?!
The last thing I need is some young
punk frolicking in my nethers.
You don't listen t...
I try to talk to you... Ew!
Do you hear anything?
Mom's still crying.
Did she ever go to sleep? At 3 she
went from sobbing to a quiet whimper.
She's just trying to psych us out!
I don't think so. When was the last
time you heard Dad yell and Mom cry?
You're right.
Something weird is going on.
They've been whispering a
lot, too. I just figured it out.
Oh, no. Oh, no!
(CHEERING)
I've never seen her like this.
What do you expect?
The boy tried
to jump in bed with her!
Dude, she's killing you!
Do something.
I will not hit a woman.
Then, here. Take this.
What is it? A
screwdriver. Jab and twist.
I'm not using the
screwd... Aaargh!
Fight. Ugh!
Back. Ugh!
Ease up on him. His
only crime was loving you.
Ugh! You disgust me.
You better run home to Mama,
so she can kiss your tears away and
make you cocoa and tell you - Ugh!
Yeah! Yeah! (CHEERING)
My mother's a tormented
control freak.
It would never occur to her
to make me cocoa!
(SPITS / PING!)
(CHEERING)
You're going down, college boy.
Bring it on, you toad.
(CHEERING)
Yeah! Yeah!
(WHISTLING / CHEERING)
Ned. Daryl. You're up.
Somebody help me clear this floor.
Alright. I'll
get the camera.
If anyone at school asks,
your name's Bernard.
You like carrots and
having your tummy scratched.
'No. We've been waiting for hours.
Now please give us the information.'
Negative?! Negative! That's
a good one, right? Yes, thank you.
If Mom does a load of blankets
I'll bring you a friend.
Oh! Mom. Dad. We
have something to say.
We know why you've been crying.
You don't have to protect us.
We think getting a divorce
is a great idea. What?
You don't have to stay together.
We've known for years it was a sham.
Your relationship isn't working.
Mom needs a man who'll control her
and Dad needs someone younger.
You both deserve some happiness.
I think we all do. Amen to that.
We should go to
a motel with Dad.
Our bags are packed. Mom,
you're still part of our lives.
We'll see you every other
weekend. Call us any time.
We've already
discussed it.
I get full custody.
IMS Subtitles
sky.subtitles@bskyb.com
www.tvsubtitles.net