What are you doing? We've started
showering in gym class.
# Yes, no
# Maybe
# I don't know
# Can you repeat the question
# You're not the boss of me now
# And you're not so big
# Life is unfair #
(BELCHES) Could you pass
the peas, please? (ALL LAUGH)
(BELCHES) Thank you.
(ALL LAUGH)
(BELCHES) You're welcome.
(ALL LAUGH) Hal?
(BELCHES) Alright, boys.
That's enough. (ALL LAUGH)
(FARTS)
(ALL LAUGH)
For once could we have
a civilised conversation
during dinner free of sound effects?
It's not asking too much for us to
have some nice dinner conversation.
Malcolm, how was school?
History class was cool.
Tell us about it. Jimmy Perkins
kicked the crap out of Fred Nason.
He beat up Fred Nason? He's huge!
Fred knocked Jimmy's hat off
and Jimmy punched him in the face
five times in a row in a second!
Fred fell and he started
hitting him. It was way cool!
Jimmy Perkins is crazy. I told you,
crazy beats big every time.
(FARTS)
(ALL LAUGH HYSTERICALLY)
So, how was your day, dear?
Hey, how's Alaska? Where are you?
You were meant to be here already!
No-one will pick me up, I ran out
of money and had to work for a week.
There's a serial killer loose
in Idaho who looks just like me.
I don't know how much longer they'll
hold the job. "I'm almost there!"
Do I take the
provincial highway 99
or the 27 to provincial highway 12?
What?! I'm near to British Columbia.
I'm in Bellingham, Washington.
Francis, you're 2,000 miles away!
What?! No way! I've just exchanged
all my money for Alaskan dollars!
There's no such thing
as Alaskan dollars! Sir!
Are you almost finished with that?
What have you got in mind?
Will you watch the boys next Tuesday
night? I've joined a book club.
You don't wanna do that. I joined
a record club. They hounded me for
years. It's not that sort of club.
This is women from school.
Adults discussing books.
Oh. I live in a house filled
with boys. I listen to boy talk
and boy noises. I need
to spend some time with females.
Mmm-hmm. When I see them they invite
me to do things and I never go.
Yeah? I need to do
this for my sanity.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES) Yes! Yes.
Are you even listening to me?
Of course I am.
Here's what I think.
It's a great idea. It's about time
you did something like this.
You have a brilliant and beautiful
mind that needs challenging.
I hope those women
can keep up with you.
Make a wish.
I left the phone number on the
counter. The dishes are in the sink.
The batteries from the remote are in
the smoke alarm. Just for tonight!
Will you relax, honey? You're off
the clock! This is your night out!
Just enjoy yourself, huh? Yeah, Mom.
Stop worrying. Have fun.
Take the garbage cans
to the kerb tonight.
Stop worrying! Go have some fun!
Now? No, let's let Mom
get a few blocks away.
Right. This could be a trick.
What are you talking about?
We've got fireworks buried outside.
We'll dig them up while Mom's gone.
Tracy Hines is having a party.
We're not invited.
Our justice will be swift but fair.
We'll be fine! 'I
don't want to screw this up.'
'Lois needs time to herself.
She deserves a night out.'
'She'll have fun
and will come home happy.'
'I just have to keep the boys under
control. What am I talking about?'
'They're good kids. What am
I talking about? They're monsters!'
'They'll destroy everything and then
ruin Lois's night! Then she'll feel
like we can't be trusted on our own!
She'll never want a night out again
and it will all be my fault!'
We're going out back.
You're not going anywhere!
Stay in your room all night
with the door shut! Now go! Go!
Hmmm! This cheddar is
wonderful! It is good.
So, I really liked the book!
Really?
Oh, Karen, let's
have some more wine!
The voice of the narrator was
shifted from character to character.
Oh, I'll just have to take your word
on that. I didn't read the book.
Oh, was anyone else confused
by those flashbacks?
Am I the only one
who read the book?
Actually, Lois, we don't make it
mandatory to read the book.
What? I mean,
we're all busy.
That shouldn't prevent us
from enjoying a relaxing evening
once in a while.
Lois, don't you feel you deserve
one night away from the bickering,
the yelling and the TV blaring? Away
from all the stupid little problems
that can't seem to
be solved without you?
A little more.
Thank you! Thank you for stopping!
I'm glad to. The name's Roy.
Francis. It's freezing! I've been
standing there for six hours!
People were flipping me off as they
drove by. Why would they do that?
How far are you going?
Mamu.
I'm going to Green River. I can take
you almost the whole way. Really?
It's taken me the last 3 days
to get 20 miles! Thank you.
You OK? Yeah, it's just...
people aren't very nice!
You want some coffee?
(SOBS) Yes!
My Mom and I were screaming
at each other. She's finding time
to tell the cab driver which route
to take! She's a control freak!
She sounds like she's afraid. What
would my mom have to be afraid of?
If she doesn't control every aspect
of her life or the lives of the ones
she cares about that horrible things
will happen. What horrible things?
Her oldest son moving
5,000 miles away from her.
Alright, you got me there.
You're pretty smart.
I'm on the road 18 hours a day.
Gives me a lot of time to think
about things, people,
why they do the things they do.
I'm a wannabe psychiatrist.
I'm glad to be out.
I've got a line that I won't cross.
If anybody tries to push me
across it, I'm gone.
Everybody's got a line.
But what's interesting is everyone's
line is different. It moves.
Look at your situation here. It is
freezing cold, there's no other cars
on the road... Hypothetically,
if I said put on a curly red wig
or I'll throw you out, are you
gonna go back out into the cold?
That's ridiculous! You
can't use a silly example...
You're kidding?
OK!
You haven't made a sound in half
an hour! What's going on in here?
Nothing. I expect
perfect behaviour tonight.
If you try anything,
ANYTHING AT ALL, I will be on you
like a rainbow on an oil slick!
'Good. You sent them a message.
Fired the shot across their bow.'
'Now they know
who's in charge!'
Maybe I was too harsh. If the boys
push back they might do something
ten times worse and spoil everything
for Lois! 'Don't go soft!'
'All these boys understand
is the iron fist!'
No, I need to
get them on my side!
Dewey, be lookout while we dig up the
fireworks. What's going on with Dad?
Maybe he's dealing with
something at work.
I hope he'll be OK. At his age
carrying around that tension
can't be good for you. Oh!
Dad's here! Who wants ice cream?
I come home after work after
a ten-hour shift and I see my boys
and they're covered with grass
and paint and all they can say is,
"Where's dinner?"
(ALL MURMUR IN AGREEMENT)
Too much is expected of us.
Our society is just so screwed up.
30 years ago you could just at least
pick something and go with it.
A housewife, a career woman, sex
slave. But now you're supposed to
do everything and it's impossible!
Unless you're
Lillian Miller. (ALL) Yeah!
If it weren't for me my family would
be living in trees, eating berries.
Do they appreciate what I do
for them? Nooooo!
Lillian's family surprised her
with a trip to Spain! No kidding!
I discovered a two-inch-long hair
growing out of my shoulder. How long
has it been there? I don't have time
to put myself right in the morning.
Lillian Miller brought 20 home-made
cakes to the school-bake sale.
I had those!
They were delicious!
The woman just cooks like a god
but she never puts on a pound!
You can't be 45
and still be a size 2!
Those are sizes for
children! And Lillian!
Ladies, I just realised something.
Society isn't making us miserable.
Hell, we're society!
(ALL CHEER IN AGREEMENT)
No, no! Every single one
of our problems can be traced back
to that tight-assed overachieving
marathon-running master chef...
..Lillian Miller!
# Mademoiselle from
Armentieres, Parlez-vous
# She got the palm
and the croix de guerre
# For washing
soldiers' underwear
# Inky dinky,
parlez-vous... #
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! What?
It's hinky dinky parlez-vous.
That's what I said. You said inky
dinky. You've got to start over.
I'm not starting over. It's
freezing! I can barely feel my lips!
# Mademoiselle from
Armentieres, Parlez-vous
Parlez-... #
Thanks for the ice-cream, Dad.
You're welcome, Dewey. Don't worry
about this mess. I'll take care
of it. Just sit there and relax.
Alright, what the
hell is going on?
I think he's feeling guilty about
something. Maybe we can exploit it!
How? Send Dewey in there crying
about the train Mom put in the attic.
Mom didn't put a
train in the attic. Exactly!
When he's up there,
we can dig up the fireworks.
Dewey, we need you to cry. It's
gotta be the right kind of crying.
Not sobbing, more of a penetrating
whining sound. Give me a moment.
OK, that was a good idea.
They're happy.
I've got them motivated to behave
themselves and Lois is gonna see
that I can handle them without her.
'Are you kidding? You've gone soft!'
'You've totally lost their respect.
Lois isn't gonna like this!'
Come on! They're under control.
'What if they aren't? What if
they're pretending to behave
so they can set you up?' (CRASHING)
Occupy them. Keep them busy so they
don't have time to get in trouble.
How am I gonna keep them busy?
You better find a way. (CRYING) >
Dad, Dewey really wants you - Boys!
Let's spend a little time together.
We can... I know!
We can do some callisthenics!
What?! You boys love to exercise!
But I just ate a ton of ice cream.
You are starting
to get a little flabby.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm too full.
When you start moving you'll feel
better! Let's go! One. Two.
One. Two. One.
Two. One. Two.
Stupid! Stupid!
It was a terrible idea!
It was a great idea!
A great idea poorly executed.
Terrible idea.
Terrible execution.
Why don't you just lock them in
the bathroom until Lois gets home?
Look at that house. It's perfect!
No, no, no! We didn't come here
for a mindless vandalism.
We came to screw up her car!
See how she feels when she's late
for car pool like a real person!
She probably won't even be able
to get out of bed on a morning!
This time next year she's
gonna be living in a trailer
with little ceramic donkey in the
front yard. (ALL GIGGLE DRUNKENLY)
Shhh! Shhh!
Whoopsy! Whoops!
Will you shhh?!
She's wearing pearls
to make cookies?! (Doilies!)
(What kind of a monster
is this woman?)
Oh, God! Those cookies smell good!
Let's kill her and eat them!
(Karen,... why
don't you go stand guard?)
(Come on!) Quick!
(ALL GIGGLE DRUNKENLY)
(STIFLED DRUNKEN GIGGLING)
Oh, one of us should probably
know something about cars.
It doesn't matter! Just pull some
of the wires! Let's get out of here!
(WILD CACKLING)
Karen! Karen! You've gotta stop!
Karen! You've gotta settle down!
Whoa! Whoa!
Karen, why don't you see if you
can say the alphabet backward?
Z, y, x, w, v,
u, t, s, r, q,
p, o, m, n, l, k, j, i,
h, g, f, e, d, c, b, a!
(GIGGLES) I've been
pulled over a few times.
Hey! Lillian's gone!
What do you mean, gone?
RUN!
(ALL SCREAM)
(ALL CONTINUE TO SCREAM)
It's a pointless exercise!
You haven't proven a thing.
You haven't determined what my
limits are. This hasn't bothered me
and if you think it has,
the joke is on you! Clench.
"(INDISTINCT) ..10-31 and 6-42,
2 men... (INDISTINCT)"
That's the third time he drove down
that alley! He knows we're in here!
This is gross! I can't believe
I'm wearing open-toed shoes.
(SOBS) I can't believe I'm hiding
from the cops in a dumpster!
I just wanted to
talk about books.
Oh, and it was
such a good book, too!
The first shadowing was effective
without being heavy-handed.
The characters were flawed
but compelling and the entire story
was brimming with insight
into the character's condition!
But how did you find time to read
it? Your family sounds so horrible!
I was lying!
I made all that stuff up
so that I would fit in!
They're wonderful!
I mean, they're idiots!
But at least they try. I wanted
it to be the happiest night!
Look what I did with it!
What are you doing? You'll see.
Go home to your family and hug them
for me. They sound wonderful!
Hey, piggy! Over here!
Here, piggy, piggy, piggy!
< Come on, show
me what you got!
< I'm supposed to be afraid
of an electric shaver?!
< (BUZZING)
Aaaaarh! (THUMP!)
"..lighter than most minerals."
Why is he making us watch this
about salt?
Would you rather be locked in the
bathroom? Or chased by the monster?
Do something! I'm trying! Every time
we make a move he's ahead of us.
He's impossible to predict! With Mom
you get a little consistency.
Dad's operating on a
whole other plane. (SIGHS)
Hey, you put salt on French fries!
Ground them! Cut
off their food supply!
They just need love!
Give them the belt!
(ALL JEER)
Make them fear you!
These are precious years!
Get in the car and go.
(ALL SHOUT AT ONCE)
SHUT UP!
OK, that's it.
I am going to take a bath.
I'm asking you boys
one last time to behave.
Not for me but
for your mother.
After all she does for you
one night of peace
shouldn't be too
much to ask for.
So if you love her,
you will do this for her.
Wow, I've never had anyone empty
the box before! I'm outta props!
I was bored with your experiment at
first but I admit, I learned a lot
about myself. Who am I to judge
people for the choices they make?
From now on I'm gonna be a bit more
understanding and a lot more humble.
Wanna stop for some dinner?
What, like this?
Sure! Why not like this?
Have you thought about writing
a book? I'm sure - Hey, Merna!
What time's the pageant?
Fluffy's collar?
Mom said he ran away!
Get out of there, Dewey! (CHUCKLES)
Tracy should have invited us!
This is what you
get for being rude.
We'll hide these in the closet,
then we'll cover up the hole
and by the time Mom's home,
we'll be sleeping. Boys! FIREWORKS?!
FIREWORKS?! Omph!
How did she...? I don't know!
You boys are in so much trouble! I
can't leave you alone for a second!
Next time I'll chain you to the
floor! We tell you to behave -
you don't even pretend to listen!
You might as well cut off your ears
and throw them in trash!
You are grounded for the next month!
"Get down on the ground
with your hands behind your head."
While you're being punished
I hope your friends are
doing all sorts of fun stuff
because you won't
be doing any of it!
You are gonna suffer!
I should get out there.
Nah, you'll just screw it up.
Good call. '(CONTINUES
TO SHOUT INDISTINCTLY)'
IMS Subtitles
www.tvsubtitles.net